Subtitles By: BakaSan
http://www.llamakillers.com/
Hey! Open Up!
What is it at this time?
Idiot! I told you repeatedly to
not take your eyes off from him.
No way... Gaara...
Where did he go?
I hope nothing happens...
A Evil Hand Sneaks Up! A Hospital Room Targeted.
Konoha Hospital
He sleeps a lot... it's like he's dead.
Yamanaka Flowershop
Sasuke-kun hasn't been back yet.
I get Sasuke-kun's information before you get it.
You failed to go see him alone, Dekorin-chan.
Not that. This is for Lee-san.
It's about time for the last one to die.
I see...
Lee-kun! Stop it!
191!
Please don't touch me!
I'm not finished yet!
Here you go.
Thank you.
I hope Lee-san's better.
Yup.
Huh?
What's up with that?
It's useless. It's totally clogged... so troublesome.
Hey. You finally woke up, eh?
Where is this?
The Hospital. I heard you were sleeping
all day and all night for three days.
Three days...
Three days and nights?!
What... what is it?
Shikamaru! When does the real final start?
T...tomorrow.
Whaaaaaat?!?!
Why didn't you wake me up earlier?!
I don't have the luxury to keep sleeping at a place like this!
Where's Ero Sennin? Where is he?
I need him to train me soon.
Huh? What're you talking about? I have no idea...
I can't find my clothes.
Where? where where where?
Man... when I thought he's been sleeping a
long time, he starts moving around like crazy.
Calm down a little bit!
Listen. Nothing will change even
you try to do something one day before.
Taking a rest is also part of training...
Hey, Naruto... What's wrong with you?
I'm hungry.
Hey... Don't make me surprised for everything you do.
Oh, yeah.
It was so tiresome, but I bought a Fruit-set for Choji.
But the doctor said no. So, let's eat this together.
Choji? Did he get that much damage?
Don't get it wrong. He ate too much Yakiniku...
and broke his stomach. That's how he got serious damage.
That's just like Choji.
Well, you two are not the type of guys
whom girls pay a visit at hospital.
Here you go.
Looks delicious.
What?
Let's eat in front of Choji,
since we're gonna eat these anyway.
You're tiresome. (You make me tired.)
Nobody is here.
OUT FOR LUNCH
It's during lunch time?
Oh well...
Good.
Lee-san... I'll leave the flower here for you.
This isn't enough for me.
Are you trying to annoy me, Shikamaru?
Oh, that's right.
Why did you save him?
This boy is my beloved precious subordinate.
My body... doesn't move.
You...!
What are you trying to do at place like this, huh?!
Hey, Naruto.
My body moves the same during the
Kagemane-no-jutsu (Shadow copying)
Oops. Sorry, Shikamaru.
What're you trying to do?
Choji! Feeling better?
Ah, Ino!
The time of Chubbies arrives!
What did you try to do to Gejimayu (Thick eyebrows)!
I was trying to kill him.
What?
How can he stay so calm...
even though his body can't move because of my Kagemane.
Why do you need to do such a thing?
You won the match. Do you have any personal grudge against him?
I don't have such a thing.
I'll kill him just because I want to do so.
What a selfish thing you're talking about!
I believe you didn't grow up in
normal way. You're extremely selfish.
Besides, he's a little strange... It's chilling me...
If he starts to do something, it's
too much for me and Naruto to handle.
Man... what should I do?
If you stand in my way, I'll kill you two, too.
What? Do it if you can!
Hey! Stop it, Naruto!
I guess I'll bluff a little to see how he reacts.
I know you're strong from watching the match with him.
But both me and him believe we can do good, too.
We still haven't shown you our "special moves" in the prelims.
Plus it's one against two. You got the disadvantage here.
If you listen to us, I won't mind
letting you leave without a scratch.
I'll tell you one more time. If you stand in my way...
I'll kill you.
This guy...
A guy like you can't kill me!
I'm telling you to stop that.
He's as strong as a monster. You know that, right?!
I have a real monster inside of
me. I won't lose to a guy like this.
Huh?
I came here because I heard Naruto is here... but...
It's so messy here.
I guess he's alright judging from this.
What are you doing rubbing him a wrong way, idiot!
A monster, huh?
The same here too.
As you said, I've not grown up in a normal way.
I was born by taking away the life
of whom I would've called my mother.
To be the strongest Shinobi, my father's
Ninjutsu made my body possessed by the Sand incarnation.
I'm a born monster.
The Sand incarnation?
It's called Shukaku... a wraith of Hidden Sand's
old priest, which was sealed in a teakettle.
It's one of the Hyoui-no-Jutsu, to
have one possessed by spirits before birth.
To do that extent, it's crazy.
There's something inside of him, too?
Is that something a real parent would
do? It's a messed up way to show love.
Love?
Don't measure me with your stick.
Family... I'll tell you what that connection was for me.
It's just flesh that's connected with
hate and the intention to kill.
I was created as the village's best
creation with my mother's life as food,
As a son of Kazekage.
I grew up being taught the secrets of
shinobi, one after another, from father...
overprotectively indulged and left alone.
I believed that was love...
...until that incident happened.
That incident?
What was that, anyway?
What happened?!
For the last six years, since I was six years old...
my real father has been trying to assassinate me.
But you said you were indulged by your father.
What did that mean?
An existance that is too strong turns
into the existance that is to be feared.
My mind is unstable because I was born by a Jutsu.
The fools in the village finally realized
that there's a problem in me emotionally.
For my father, as Kagekage, I was the ace for the village...
but at the same time, I was dangerous object.
It seems that I was categorized as a
dangerous character around the time I turned six.
I was just treated carefully as the village's dangerous tool.
For them, I am a relic in the past that they want to erase.
Then, for what reason do I still exist and stay alive for...
When I thought that, I couldn't find the answer.
But a reason is needed while being alive.
Otherwise it is the same as being dead.
What is he talking about?
I can understand...
He is... the same as me.
And I concluded that...
I exist to kill everybody other than me.
I was finally relieved of the fear of
death that I could be assasinated anytime.
I was able to recognize the reason to
be alive was by killing assassins.
To fight only for myself and to live loving myself...
If I think all others exist to make me feel that...
then there's no other great world than this one.
As long as theres others who I should kill, and who
make me feel the joy of living in this world, exist...
my existance won't be erased.
What is this guy? He's seriously dangerous.
I was all alone, too.
I didn't know why I'm alive and it was painful...
but because Iruka-sensei recognized my existance,
I was able to feel that I was alive the first time.
On the other hand, this guy...
this guy is still all alone.
and he feels that he's alive by killing others?!
There's such a guy in this world?
The world he's living in is too different from mine!
There's no way I can win agaisnt such a guy!
What's wrong, Naruto?
What?  Kagemane-no-jutsu is
supposed to be sealing his moves.
Naruto! Hey! Be strong!
Man, you're troublesome.
Now, Let me feel it.
I guess it's over.
That's enough.
The real match is tomorrow. There's no need to hurry.
Or, do you want to stay here from today?
Please don't leave me alone.
No blood comes out, but I feel so much pain here...
What am I?
I will definitely kill you guys.
Wait for that moment.
Hey Konohamaru! What were you saying about your secret hand?!
I was late from the beginning! It's not even a
short cut and it's making me farther away from the arena!
The real match is going to start soon....
Anyways, hurry! hurry! hurry!
run, if i run, when i run, i'm gonna run
Next episode:
Fierce Moo-Chase Moo-Dash
Final exams begin!
I can't trust in your final hand at all.