Subbed by Gandelr
Chekked by Kyubi
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
It is not the answer that I expected,
Tsunade.
As you can try to kill to me!
In any case Kabuto thanks,
For your loyalty and your ability to discover the attack of Tsunade…
S ì,
there are all two trains you to the same medical techniques,
I have been able to perceive the flow of Chakra that used.
Tsunade,
I was serious when I spoke about their resurrezione.
All the also my promise not to destroy Konoha.
Orochimaru,
I have understood that mentivi for Konoha…
I knew…
I wanted…
See again them…
Just a last time.
A last time only, I wanted see again them…
Just a last time…
I wanted to touch…
Their aces.
But,
I have realized, in the moment in which I have tried this feeling on my skin that see again Nawaki and Dan…
I have comprised…
That they have been stupid!
All and two…
The simple one to remember itself of their aces overwhelmed to me already.
Sorellina!
Tsunade.
I loved them…
So a lot.
Here why…
I wanted to see them and to embrace them of new!
But,
I have not been able.
I will not lose  this bet!
Thanks to this child…
They are remembered to me of their dreams…
Those dreams that I wanted to forget.
Konoha is the treasure of the Grandfather!
And  the proteggerò!
Because they are the grandson of Primo Hokage!
I love so much this village and its inhabitants.
And for that I want proteggerli.
I  will become  like my grandfather;
And  I will receive  the title it of Hokage!
They are not like you!
I will strain myself  in order to receive the title it of Hokage!
The dead women of my sister…
It is  the single reason for which I go ahead.
Here why I want to become Hokage!
In order protect all.
Because to become Hokage it is my dream!!!
All and two have sacrificed their life in order to realize their dream…
And the possibility to see a day this dream to come true itself is vanished under my eyes.
"All  that  that takes shape extinguishes a day."
You said a day.
But…
This memory is one what that…
It will not be never extinguished!
I suppose that the agreement…
It is not more valid…
It would seem that we must force to you to cure to me.
Episode #93
The end of negotiates!!
Hey!
Orochimaru!!!
If us task, memory to me is not never struck against of she.
Damned!
As you say, they are the solo to being able to fight against she.
You! Insignificant refuse!
I will kill  to you  here and now!
If it hits to us with its incredible force…
with a single blow it would be the end for we.
Thanks but I had understood it.
One would say that to strike itself around to the castle…
It is complicated.
Tasks that would have to go elsewhere?
S ì  task that is better.
There is also an other person…
with the girl who accompanies Tsunade-sama.
Chissa when it is made alive.
You die!
About who it speaks?
It is  a Sannin like you and Tsunade-sama.
Jiraiya.
Lascerò  not to scappare  to you!
Che cos' is happened!
Watched this casino…
Sure it is work of Tsunade.
That  wants to say that…
Tsunade-sama has refused?
Where has gone that Old one of Tsunade?
This is… of Tsunade-sama…
Ton-Ton, from that it leave?
Much good!
One would say that Tsunade is losing breath.
Slowly.
They are not much Bravo in the Taijutsu.
"Hyourougan "?
[ Pill of the Soldier ]
Those seal are…
This boy uses "Irou the Ninjutsu "?
[ Technical Doctor ]
My muscles!
I have hit your abdominal biceps and muscles.
Hour you cannot more use your incredible force.
It uses the chakra?
Why you have not hit directly my arteries?
This is true, could divide your body, could have cut all muscles and it is gone sanguinei.
But during a combat, I do not have the time to go so much in depth.
But in any case, if touch your neck, would be the end for you!
Merda!
My lungs!
I cannot more breathe!
This boy…
It is not a normal school ninja.
It is  better than me as far as the techniques and the movements!
Unfortunately I cannot kill to you now.
I have not attacked the neck, you cannot yourselves be moved.
It is  extraordinary!
It would have to suffocate and to try to resume the air…
However…
It would seem that it must carry it…
In life end!
I do not succeed to move my arm…
and my leg…
One does not move!
Impossible!
In this situation, is all the force that I succeed to use?
But sure…
This was not a simple fist…
But a nervous attack!
It seems to have comprised…
This is, a nervous attack!.
I have converted chakra in current the electrical worker, that I have made to flow in its nervous system!
The brain and the body communicate through mark them electrical workers.
Tsunade has disturbed this flow of marks them, sending of the current in the 360 points of its nervous system.
After much time without to strike itself, is this the power of a legendario Sannin?
The cures consume a lot chakra…
But I do not have other choice…
When I try to move my right hand…
My left leg that moves.
When I try to move my left leg…
My left shoulder moves.
E' like if 80% of my body did not answer more correctly.
This technique… I can move!
Not lowered the guard!!!
How?
As  it can  move in this state!
You have fear of the blood?
Ve I will show  it  endured!
Jiraiya?
Last E' much time, Jiraiya.
Orochimaru, always this matto look from.
Ka.... Kabuto-saint!
Naruto-kun.
I see, that already you know yourselves
We have supported with the examination of Chuunin.
Why six, here Kabuto-saint one?
It moves to you!
I  of he will take care.
Even if you can move…
Your body is not to the maximum!
Therefore you cannot move as you would want!
I will not allow  you  to scappare!
Too much late!
It seems that my movements are return to you normal.
Blood…
To have to face two Sannin is too much dangerous.
I must stop of… one now!
Tsunade-Sama!
Hey, Hey! What is happening?
Why Kabuto-saint and the Old Tsunade…
Six too much weak person, Naruto-kun.
Here why you will not be able to defeat Sasuke-kun.
Its watches well coprifronte.
It is a servitore of Orochimaru.
S ì.
I was a spy of the village of the sound.
About what it is speaking?
This must be one lie… Kabuto-saint.
During the examination of Chuunin, you have taught many things to us, and you have to us also saves to you.
It was only in order to collect information on you.
Naruto-kun, from your data, is rendered me account.
You do not have the stoffa for being a ninja.
Six different from Sasuke-kun.
This is before the time that I see Tsunade-Sama in this state.
Ve I pray some found again the calm.
I will take  cure of you.
Tsunade the Old one…
Not to watch to me with that frightening face…
Not six small and graceful other that a genin.
Six single fort thanks to the monster that is in you…
But of forehead to a Leggendario Sannin…
Not six nothing.
Six like a small bug…
and if you interfere…
I will kill  to you!!!
Detention, Naruto!!!
My body is still…
It cannot  use its right hand.
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
If we attack it all in the same moment,  I will break off  its defense, and I will crush  it!
Why you!
Che cos' is?
Merda!
"Fukumimari "!
[ Needles ]
I have still not recovered the use of all my senses!
I cannot move!!!
Lacked!
That great movement in one such situation…
Thanks.
This is…
A pill that coagulates the blood.
A pill that coagulates the blood?
It is  in order to recover from the blood that it has lost?
This boy…
He is  like me, ninja a doctor.
He would say himself that he bleeds very, Kabuto.
Orochimaru-sama…
You want to remove the handwraps from your left arm.
Therefore Orochimaru is he…
It seems that it is the hour sfoggiare some of our abilities…
Shizune.
S ì!
Occupied of the quattrocchi.
And I occ uperò  of Orochimaru.
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
Not to say fesserie!!!
I will not escape!
I will not abandon!
It watches well!!!
This is like conceives the life of the ninja!!!
Next episode:
You take this!
The fury of the Rasengan!