I knew.
I am various from you.
Our roads s' do not intercross.
We have gone ahead in four, and effectivelyÉ
É I have tried more times to convince to me that this was
the just road for me.
É but to the end my heart has chosen the vendetta.
E' only for that scope that I have continued living.
I cannot become like you or Naruto.
You have decided to go of new towards the solitudine ?
That time you have taught to how much the solitudine to me is painful!
And hour I succeed to understand it end too much well!
I have one family and of the friendsÉ
ButÉ
if you lost to youÉ
É for meÉ
he would be like remaining single.
From this moment everyone of we
new road will begin to covers one.
I....
I am in love of you!
I LOVE TO YOU TO DIE!
If you will decide to be with me.>.
I swear to you that you of it you will not repent!
We will be always allegros
And I you  will render  happy sure!
I will make  whichever thing for you
This whyÉ
Portami with youÉ
Just sixÉ
É insopportabile!
The 5 Ninja di Konoha + one!
The perfect formation!
Not to forget your obbiettivo.
Not to go!
Thanks.
Sasuke-kunÉ
They are already the four of the mattino.
The 5 hokage a P˜ takes advantage of  too much  the persons.
It could go same to take documents
that she has forgotten herselfÉ
What takes to you ?
Hei!Svegliati!
You will become ill yourself if you remain to sleep of the sort in a place.
Thanks.
Sasuke-kun!
Optimal job.
You were sleeping!
You have sent we to take documents and
you have put yourselves to sleep!
Rather Quinta HokageÉ
What is one that we would want to communicate to you.
What ?
You say indeed?
S “.
From what Sakura says,
it seems that it is just cos “.
I would not have thoughtÉ
É that one would have moved cos “  soon.
I will be  frank with you
The next time  I will destroy  completely
the village of the leaf.
It wants the abilities of the Uchiha.
That pervertito bastard.
Izumo, Kotetsu.
There is a person that I want that you go to call.
Sbrigati to eat, Shikamaru!
From papˆ today also mission will begin one!
Therefore you do not have much time for the training early riser.
.
It is answered with a solo "s “ "!
Uffa..Si begins already with the rogne to this hour.
Who will be never cos “  soon ?
Papˆ Hei.É
What is ?
Why you have decided to marry mother that it is cos “  strict ?
WellÉ
Also it to times sorride in kind way.
Dev' to be for that one.
And enough ?
Shikamaru!
They have come for you of the persons sended from fifth hokage.
Yesterday in full night Sasuke Uchiha if n' it has gone.
E' a lot probably
one is oing towards the village of the sound.
If n' it has gone!
E' why ?
Why Orochimaru has irretito it!
...... a moment.
Why Sasuke would have to be invited gives
a tizio like he !
The motivation interests not there.
Our problem is that we do not have much time.
Therefore Shikamaru
I will entrust  you  your first mission.
I must only recover Sasuke !
If not there are opposing, too much difficult what will not be one.
.>.
But.>.
beyond demanding an immediate execution,
this mission has good possibility to complicate itself.
Probable E' that of the subordinates of Orochimaru
they are in company of Sasuke.
Therefore the situation is delicateÉ
But he.>.
Between all my contemporarys were what I held of eye
why I considered it skillful in all.
Then I would want that the four members of this mission.>.
É they were all Chunin and Jonin.
This is not possible.
E' why ?
You know very well.
It is not a case that Asuma, Kakashi and also your father
they have already of the assignments.
E' be decided to leave in the village the indispensable minimum
of the Jonin. All the others are outside engage to you in mission.
Parts within half hourÉ
After to have re-united the highest number than genin that it considers skillful!
Of it I do not have nobody wants,
but inasmuch as draft of that I know,
I cannot ignore it.
Be',  I will make  of my best.
There is someone in particular
that I would want to advise you for this mission.
Cosa?!Stai joking true!
Geez, six truly noisy this morning.
Why just he ?
DeficientÉ
It waits for a moment!
Me endured change!
Beyond to me, you have already thought next to qualcun' other of valid ?
Alarm clock!
Six sure one that make the case ours ?
Not there is much choice.
Patatine?
Taste barbecue.
It helps me eats these.
It is arriving.
You  lascer˜  not to eat the last patatina.
We have passed much time together.
It is that one with which I can operate there better.
You had spoken about someone of valido!Dovresti to call
people like Chino!
You urli too much.
Too much simple!
Chino is via with its father for one special mission.
HeyÉ not to say to meÉ
It has been decided.
It thought  that it will be interesting.
It is worth always the pain waking up themselves soon and going
to make one walk.
Hey Shikamaru, and the others ?
I would want to try of others but we do not have time.
We are to the end of the village if we will not find nobody
we will remain in this formation.
It seems that your operation has gone well.
You succeed to move to you well ?
It has said that  I will be able  to return to train to me serenely
between some time.
I see.
Hour I have understood.
It could be annoying, we will be better with
one person in more
In this moment, I am.>.
LeeÉ you make  that  that you must make.
From tomorrow  I will try  to go up these alone scalini.
Lee!
I will be  well.
Gone also.
Past due time.
Cos “  we are in 5.
It goes well cos “!
Boys seguitemi!
Naruto ListensÉ
Even if I do not have any wantsÉ
I would be the squad leader.
We will indeed succeed to carry out a mission entrusting us to you?
It is not that it has too much confidence.
And creeds that the things would go better if you began to
they give airs to you from great Naruto head !
However it is is not that it convinces me of allÉ
to take orders from one svogliato like Shikamaru.
But  Shikamaru is already chunin!
It must obey to its orders.
They have been the advanced ones of the village
to consider it in a position to being a leader.
Then made to be worth and it introduces your plan or your strategy.
To how much it seems there are of the adversaries and there are good probability of an ambush.
Being a rescue plan we to having are to chase them.
To the beginning we will have to be to attack.
Therefore we will grant the first movement easy to the adversaries.
Consequently  I will elaborate  one formation in a position to answering
with prontezza to the attacks of the enemy during our movements.
If you will ignore my indications on behalf muovendovi yours.
É we will end all in order to die!
We will be left over maintaining one linear formation.
The role more important will be given to the conductor of the rowÉ
É and this you will be Kiba.
Walking all the year with Akamaru, you know very well
geography and the morphology of the land of the country of the fire.
Your moreover optimal one olfattoÉ
six in a position to following Sasuke fiutando its odoreÉ
and you could easy discover the traps placed from our enemies.
A linear formation is weak person against the frontal attacks,
it is in consideration of this,
É perfect you six why with Akamaru forms a pair.
Behind of you there will be the group leader, that I would be.
In second of the situation,  I will succeed  in giving immediately
the orders to Kiba, than precede to meÉ
While to that they are behind me it will be enough to supply the directives
through gestures of the hand.
In third position you will be, Naruto.
Inasmuch as six fulmineo,
you will be able to give an aid in every direction.
You will be the best one to the centerÉ
É in order to help.
The six moreover only one to know it technical of multiplication.
In quarter position you will be, Choji.
Not six sure fast oneÉ
É but six that one with the more powerful attacks.
Even if a six  awkward  P˜ I and the others will use to you like base,
To close the row you will be Neji.
You will have to be taken care of the more difficult part.
You six in a position to controlling constantly
the situation with the Byakungan.
You have understood?Ora I will explain  you  better with one outline.
Controlled your field of surveillance on this outline.
Kiba will watch ahead,
and cos “  I  will make anch', but in a wider way.
Naruto will carry out the left part,
and Choji the right,
and you, Neji I ask to use the Byakungan in order to hold
of eye all the rear zone.
I would want also to verify our war potentialities puts into effect them.
Fatemi to control all the crews and the remedies that you have with you.
3 minuteren will be enough to me.
There is some question ?
In a moment a lot is successful to develop one formation
efficient with of the persons who have re-united random.
Then, if not there is some are, I will say  to you  for last the thing
more important.
Sasuke is not sure a my great friend.>.
É and it is not not even a type that me piaccia particularly.
But  Sasuke is a ninja of the leaf like we.
E' a our companion!
E' for that ce we will put it all in order to save it.
E' this the creed of the leaf.
E' then is from saying that although,
I am svogliato of nature.
But they are also responsible of your screw.
Now it is similar vaguely a chunin!
Then we will leave after that   I will have controlled
your equipment.
Pulled all outside.
Sasuke will not never accept invites of the sort from a ceffo.
E' end too much strongly in order to have need of Orochimaru!
I guarantee!
Accidents to you Sasuke!Perchè you have made it?
Bene!Andiamo.
Waited for!.
Sakura-chan.
I have known all from the hokage.
Me dispiace but I cannot carry to you in mission.
You six resolution not to convince Sasuke.
Hour does not remain to us that to stop it with the force.
Sakura,  that  that you could make you have already made it.
Then you were with Sasuke when if n' has gone!
Sakura-saint.
NarutoÉ
É you I prayÉ filler Sasuke behind!
I not have succeeded!
I have not been able it to stop!
Perhaps the six only NarutoÉ
É that  it can  stopÉ
and to save Sasuke.>.
You adore Sasuke.
In this moment you are sufferingÉ
and I understand to youÉ
Sakura I would want makes a question you.
What of tasks of Naruto?
It is found perfectly to its comfort in the part of who wants
to intralciare history of other people's loveÉ
and it is amused to see that I make myself in four for you.
Naruto does not understand null of me.
Indeed insopportabile E'.
NarutoÉ thanks.
You will see that Sasuke you the bringing back behind I!
You I promise!
Naruto has always understood to meÉ
Me it has always helpedÉ
Naruto!
Hey Naruto!
Indeed you can promise one what of the sort ?
He!
I say the things as they are.
It makes part of my creed ninja.
Departure!
We have lost  a time  P˜ muoviamoci.
Naruto was much sure one of if when has said it.
You can be calmÉ
Sure.
All good will go.
Sasuke nobleman you goes this zone well ?
We are already far from the village of the leaf.
About what it speaks?
Important what is one that it has been ordered from our getlteman
Orochimaru.
You want to say of what draft to me ?
You must die.
Subbed by
Shinji 89 (NFS)
You must die.
To die?
Stimulating tonic.
You have need to take it.
Stimulating tonic?
To what it would serve?
Yours I seal is in the first phase.
Those prepared will force seals to carry itself in the second one
phase.
ButÉ
to that condition the speed of erosion of I seal
it will increase remarkablly....
É until killing to you.
Therefore.>.
In order to control the power of the second phaseÉ
É it must accustom the body for along time
to this new state.
when you arrive to the second phaseÉ
É probably you will succeed to catch up our same one
force.
É but once risvegliatoÉ
É in little minuteren morirete.
After the dead women whom it succeeds ?
You do not have preoccuparvi.
We are here for this.
We would contrast the effects collaterals
with our magical barrierÉ
É and the dead women eternal will become only one died appearing.
But I can myself be trusted
É of this your magical barrier ?
Sasuke Nobleman.>.
We four are of the ninja of elite that they escort
Orochimaru.
therefore we are expert in the magical art to construct
barriers and protectionsÉ
I cannot still die.
I entrust you.
Hei!Se been l “  impalati morirˆ the Sasuke nobleman.
All in position.
We begin!
Shikokumujin!
Outline of four black clouds!
I seal black!
First part is finished.
That fatigue.
I did not imagine that this mission
a lot would be duration cos  “.
I go to giving a glance.
Raido, you follow to me.
Complications in arrival.
One?
Not, two!
They are arriving!
You are the ninja of Orochimaru.>.
To judge from your direction,
he seems that you are returning from the village of the leaf.
What is within that barrel?
E'  a hard  P˜ against two Jonin.
How many have all seal of potenziamento.
The other time you have taken to us of surprise.
but it will not be repeated.
Zitta, whore.
Burattini di Orochimaru.>.
you would better make not to underrate the ninja of the leaf.
Those two are putting  a P˜  too much.
What we make Shizune-saint?
We try to catch up them!
Of agreement.
Shikamaru!
What is ?
In the vicinities there is odore of blood.
Cos' has happened ?
Raido, Genma!
Accidents!
Com' is possible that they two have been struck !
Here I can only make an participation temporary.
Shizune-saint,
I chase them.
Not!
But.>.
He waits for Iwashi!
Their techniques.>.
É they are not those of a ninja.
If you follow them alone,
Genma,
Not to speak.
It smells of 4 individuals accompanies to you from that one of Sasuke had been mischiati with
with those of others 2 men.
But hour the five are going away from the odore of
blood!
What we make!
I knew.
Sasuke is accompanied gives of the guides.
The things are complicated.
Muoviamoci to chase Sasuke!
Zitto Naruto!
These things decide them Shikamaru!
Not to give orders!
Shikamaru.
If there is odore of bloodÉ
É it wants to say that it has been a combat.
If we go in that place, we will be able to have some
information.
But we will have to be attention in approaching to us
we will have to walk slowly and with caution.
And in the meantime
Sasuke will pass the border of the country of the fire
What is made ?
We chase Sasuke!
Optimal!
I said!
ButÉ
Inasmuch as they have been been involved in a combat
they will be allerta.
They will be also thinking next to the possibility to have others
ninja to the ribs.
Therefore probably guati traps wait for us or to.
We must lend principle attention to   that
we see and we feel.
It must scovar them before enduring an ambush.
Moreover, if we characterize of the traces sospetteÉ
É we do not have to avoid them but to analyze them!
Optimal!
When we will find them, I will make  them  to pieces with mine
technical new!
Every time that Naruto encounter, has one technical new.
I thought to have finally caught up it,
perhaps but I mistook myself.
Hei, around is full here of smells of the enemies!
Firm all!
Watched well lassù.
E' one paper bomb.
And ce 5 are others.
This is the shape of one perimetrica barrier.
Perimetrica barrier ?
E' one tipologia of trap ninja.
An active trap that when the adversary enters
in the area circumscribed from these papers bomb
It was described on a book that it has made to read my father me.
It must go around other.
Lee,
you must make what you feel yourself to make.
Lee!
E' too much soon!
5  hokage-sama!
I have always thought that you pits one spericolato.
But to little make this after the operation.>.
Which need is to make of haste?
I want to go of hasteÉ
And therefore to train to me.>.
And IÉ IÉ
To train itself is not all!
You do not know it ?
The ninja they say of being persons that they go
against every type of danger.
I understand as you feel yourself,
but this is alone training.
Training?
If you efforts too much you will not recover.
Cosè ?
E' a medicinal one that I have made.
You drink this and you will be better, Lee.
We go.
Ok!
This place is full of traps.
S “,  but I went of haste, is obvious that not
they have put these traps with much cure.
Hei Naruto!C' is a thread close to your feet!
Not to fall to us!
I know.
It waits for Naruto!
Control of the shadow.
They are successful hardly in timeÉ
Naruto!Ti I had said to be careful!
I have understood.
In thread it reflects the light and it jumps to the eyes, while
the other has been painted of green so as to to camouflage itself.
Knot  cannot be seen easy to eye.
E' one double trap.
They are of haste but they use of the elaborated traps a lot.
ThereforeÉ
É they have need of rest.
Or they are hurt or is an other trap?
Byakugan!
Taken!
Optimal!
I will bring back  Sasuke to the village!
Naruto me dispiace,
but I will introduce   my technical new here.
Also mine.
Not churned to you.
We will only approach ourselves the target after that we will have
prepared my strategy.
We are of hasteÉ
É but we must be stopped to risposare.
Unavoidable E'....
To fight in the second phase demands effort too much.
RatherÉ the difficulty is in the fact that for  a P˜  we will not be able to make efforts.
We did not have alternatives against two Jonin.
If there were saves to you, they would have defeated to us.
Kiba,
In that case you do not have to mistake the tempismo
in the launch of the smoke-producing one.
Then we will divide ourselves in two groups.
It seems that they are not still shrewed of we.
Eh?
Sasuke not is.
It seems that it is found to the inside of the barrel.
Dead E' ?
It seems that barrier around the barrel is one.
E' difficult to notice it.
But considered how much they wanted itÉ
É not task that has killed it.
Also this is true.
Boku Tamani, Boku tamani
Yume ni hito Afureru not kakeraga
yamano yonimaru
kamisama nihotoke samani
tsutae naiteruhito not kakeraga
yamano yonimaru
dan dan dan suran nan deru
borushoino it placed ninarandara
shake shake shake sagaso janainowa
yamano yonimaru
Cosè, Shikamaru?
Six completely useless one!
You see ?
But this is not one ugly situation ?
Levamelo of I return, is simple!
In this case, it will be good.
What means this ?
It seems that it will be difficult.
Akamaru, zitto!
What you are saying ?
You put them via, Akamaru!
In this situation, I must use
my last technique, the Rasengan!
Next episodio:Disputa between the members !