http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
Surprised Akamaru!
The incredible force of Gaara!
Dov' is he!
You hide all!
Been in guard!
But where one has hidden!
Naruto
That idiot has waked up alone hour!
A just six beautiful type.
To only watch me to you the nervous one comes.
Sakura-chan!!
That there is?
Yours tuoi Sakura!
Your hats!
Oh
I have decided
for a change of image.
Only a change of image!
I prefer them long, but you know
in this forest they are only of impiccio.
On purpose, than us fairies here?
I do not have wants to explain it to you.
All they have saved to us.
Sakura is hiding its
feelings an other time.
Now us task I.
It goes well.
Waked up! Lee!
Tenten
that you make us here?
They have come to help you.
Hey
And the ninja of the sound?
Sasuke has them defeats.
I understand
Why you have I churn alone?
Six one rag.
Sakura-saint it was in danger and how much man
I had to help it.
Absurdity.
Lee would not have never lost
if they had not been in three.
Six just stupid one!
Task that you have reason.
The sopracciglione!
Naruto !
How it dares to maltrattare Lee?
Ahi
Goodness knows cos' it has happened while I slept.
Naruto is without hope.
E' the type that could not never become
the protagonist of one history.
Lee-saint.
Thanks.
Thanks to you I have found the spirit just.
I feel of being pochino a more fort.
Sakura-saint!
I have understood of having to me to engage more.
Sasuke-kun.
The Uchiha clan is indeed remarkable.
Six cos   powerful that alone
you have defeated the ninja of the sound
when I have been impotent.
What!
E' be defeated?
What means?
They were indeed cos   strong?
Sakura-saint.
The Loto of the village
of Konoha it blooms two times.
The next time that
we will meet ourselves  I will be  stronger.
You I promise.
Of agreement!
Hey, Sakura!
You come here!
I arrange you hats!
Thanks.
You would have give one to you washed!
Wide forehead that you have also embraced Sasuke.
It makes figurone who executes
the first attack, Ino-porcella.
Uchiha
Sasuke.
A formidable adversary.
You are well, Akamaru?
Akamaru, you are shaking
already from average day.
Akamaru?
You cannot.blame it.
To see one of the sort what
Yahoo!
This s   that it is a examination
of survival!
Just Akamaru!
Fortune that the boys who are ended
in the trap they had the coil of the earth.
At this rate we will arrive
for first to the tower.
We are calm.
Dangerous E'.
Also the smallest bug
it is always careful to proteggersi.
We must be cautious not to meet to us
against other adversaries.
E' the surer way.
I know!
Perche you must always be cos   serious?
Insettone!
M but
Task that Shino has reason.
Of agreement. I have understood.
I hope that Naruto-kun is well.
Hey! Firm!
Cautious and without to attract
the attention of the enemy eh?
Then Hinata
you succeed to see to approximately
a kilometer in that direction?
Sure. Endured.
Byakugan!
There is someone here....
It seems that
ce they are six.
Okay! We go to control!
Eh?
Kiba! But that you are saying?
We do not have.
The esaminatrice has only said to carry
the coil of the sky and the earth.
But it has not specified
not to take any in excess.
If we take other coils
more squares will come bocciate.
M ma
While we see who are.
If they are dangerous types we will not fight.
From i, we go!
Insopportabile Dannaz che!
That there is Akamaru?
What happens? It has been stopped of blow.
Akamaru is shaking.
Why?
Akamaru fiuta the chakra of the avverasario
and of it it perceives the force.
Never it has not been put to shake cos .
The boys who are fighting here
they are tutt' other that mediocre.
Mocciosi of the sand you are just stupid
in order to come encounter to us.
That type....
That it will have in the zucca
in order to attack briga with those.
What is saying Akamaru?
It has an ugly prefeeling
for the spilungone.
They seem just dangerous.
Hey, boy!
You would have to deal your adversaries more kindly.
Morirai.
Enough with chiacchere.
We go endured to the kernel, straccione.
Who of they has the coil?
Hey, Gaara.
E' better to inform to us before
If they have our same coil
not there is need to fight.
Better to avoid useless crashs.
It does not interest to me.
Those that encounter
they must die.
For this hatred to be with he.
We begin endured!
You die, mocciosi!
Ninpo! Jouro Senban!
Direzionabili nail!
Not there is way to escape to this technique.
Moreover my nail are address to you
from the chakra towards the target.
Too much easy.
All here?
N..non is possible....
It has not hit it neanche a nail!
Impossible.
One rain of nail, eh?
Then....
I will show  you  one blood rain.
Che chakra immense.
In more
that sand has a pungente odore.
Odore?
A odore fort of blood.
A sand wall?
Exact.
The sand is one absolute protection.
Gaara controls the sand to the inside of the giara
and the pressed one with a chakra immense
in order protect he and the surrounding area.
In more, it does not happen for simple will of Gaara,
but it happens automatically.
That is, against Gaara
every attack is useless.
This is not possible!
You cannot defeat our Gaara.
You close the spout!
Dead E'!
Here what you obtain to put to you
in its road.
* Sabaku Kyuu.
(Sand Cage)
I do not succeed to move to me!
T you
I could limit to me to fill up to you
of sand the mouth
but he would be too much cruel.
* Sabaku SouSou.
(Funeral of the desert)
It has not suffered.
Not there was need that suffered seen
the difference of force between me and he.
The blood of defeated the fray
with the sand that flows
donating more power to me.
T we will give the coil to you!
I pray to you lasciaci to go!
Not!
Oh not!
Endured Scappiamo!
If they find to us, we are died!
That fortune, the coil of the "Sky ".
Well, we head towards the tower.
You are zitto.
Still they are not satisfied.
I haul!
It has to us uncovered?
We stop It, Gaara.
You have for case fear?
Codardo.
Gaara!
Perhaps for you not there will be problems
but for we it is dangerous.
Us servants only this brace of coils!
Any other is....
They do not give orders to me, incapable.
They give a cut to us!
Some time listens
your greater brother!
I have not never considered you my siblings.
Intralciatemi, and....
I will kill  to you.
G..Gaara, from you stop it.
Not to make the scontroso.
From at least I listen to your sister.
And '?
Gaara!
Of agreement.
Here why hatred the children.
I have understood what you meant Akamaru
Merda potevi to say it before!
Not there is nobody here.
We are first?
Not! Averto other presences.
Akamaru you are well?
E' from before that it does not stop to shake.
First Akamaru has said something?
Akamaru said that it saw the spilungone badly
in the sense that that one of the sand would have killed it.
Not there is still nobody.
They will make us to wait for all the day?
But how much will be along?
In any case
the boy of the village of the sand
I do not know who is, but
it is indeed dangerous.
The situation is falling.
Moreover we cannot suspend the examination.
What wants to say?
Me excuses.
What is?
We are a lot occupied!
Me excuses
but it must watch this!
A video?
Here now!
It gives a glance to the timetable.
But
E' a record an hour and 37 minuteren
from the beginning of the second test!
The three ninja of the village of the sand....
they have exceeded the second test.
But as it is possible?
In solo 97 minuteren
Never it had not happened.
Decidedly unusual E'.
Their level exceeds that one of a genin.
Absurd E' that we have exceeded
the old record of four hours.
It is not all.
What you want to say?
From the entrance to the arena
to the tower there are approximately 10 Km.
Wild beasts, velenosi bugs, arduous territories.
They have crossed like if not
they had met null of  that.
Especially that one with brown hats....
Cos' has this boy?
You have not noticed it?
I understand. Incredible E'.
What is of incredible?
It observes its body.
I understand....
neanche a scratch.
And neanche
one spot of dirt on the dressed ones.
Neanch' I indeed
no chunin
it would be in a position to arriving
to the tower without a scratch.
Perhaps this fact derives
from some its ability
A lot promising seems a boy.
Even if it does not appeal to its look to me.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII