http://naruteamplus.alterista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
The secret village of Konoha.
Here they are you form many good ones to you ninja.
Between this Uzumaki Naruto
more biricchino between all!
Zitti!
Hengen!
Its preferred technique:
the technique of the seduzione.
For Naruto it hides a secret
that same it does not know
It regards the Vixen from the Nine Tails that port
to the destruction the village of Konoha.
The same Demon was imprisoned
to the inside of the body of Naruto.
For this reason the adults of the village
they hate and they call it Demon Vixen.
Very it he is.
If he became ninja we will have alone problems.
Well, hour you can open the eyes.
Six promoted congratulations.
However Naruto, thanks to my abilities
it came promoted to the school of ninja.
Cheese!
Its first step like ninja.
The square ninja is composed from three persons
Uchiha Sasuke.
Descendant of the noble Uchiha family,
of the secret village of Konoha.
C$r-he who Naruto sees as it avails again.
Haruno Sakura is one girl ninja
of which Naruto it is in love.
With to these matriculations, Naruto
it has completed several missions ninja.
C$r-he who them protegge and them guide is
the famous "Ninja Copy",
the best specialist in techniques.
Hatake Kakashi.
A day, Naruto and the others
they will receive the mission
to escort Tazuna, expert
constructor of bridges of the country of the Wave.
We leave!
However Tazuna was under sight of a man
called Gatoo, that it wants to dominate the country of the Wave.
You see to calm you.
Gatoo contatt   a man
terrible in order to kill Tazuna.
Momochi Zabuza.
A ninja esiliato from the country of the fog.
An expert man in the silent homicide
and that he has realized many homicides.
Naruto and the others guided
a hard battle against Zabuza.
Hey you ninja without eyelash
you add on yours cursed booklet
the man who a day will become
the Hokage of the secret country of Konoha
Uzumaki Naruto!
Too much easy!
(a hidden second shuriken from the first one?!)
Thanks to the square job, Sasuke and Naruto
rivoltarono the situation.
Kakashi utilizz   the Sharingan
and it copies   the techniques of Zabuza.
Which been strange.
(I!)
(pu   not to be!)
(One technical illusory!)
Suiton Daibakufuu not jutsu!
It is not possible!!!
E' the end
It gave to the grace blow a young person ninja
hunter of the village of the Fog.
I must makes me loaded with this body.
E' a full body of secrets.
Therefore you excuse to me.
For   this boy, Haku,
it was from the part of Zabuza.
The next time will go well?
The next time
Sapr   to face the Sharingan.
Kakashi felt that Zabuza was still alive
And prepar   Naruto and the others
for the final crash against Zabuza.
Therefore, one week after
(This fog)
Sasuke, Sakura
St arriving!
You have found avails again Haku.
Sembrerebbe.
Joined E' the hour.
Supreme technique
Makyouhyoushou!
Well, then, I go
You take this!
Uzumaki Naruto!
Arrived E'!
The first surprise,
Naruto takes part!
Hour that has arrived, all will go well.
Naruto!
The personage of one history
he appears always in this way
and resolving the situation in a moment!
E' the last child.
It speaks too much.
That stupid!
It was better to hit the enemy than been strange
instead making all it is scene.
That boy
You made what here us cos   soon?
A training!
Why you are training yourself?
I want to become stronger.
Daccordo, arrival!
Kage bunshin not!
Oh, not!
Schivali, Naruto!
What!
E' but
That fortune, the attacks of
enemy is itself meets to you between they.
But what you are arranging, Naruto!?
Which stupid race would execute
one technical just in front of the enemy?
The essence of the ninja resides in the deceit.
In your ability to trick the enemy.
You must execute one technical
when the enemy is distracted.
You must anticipate its movements.
As six appeared before become
only an easy target.
Eternal damnation
And I that I had come to help you.
But hour the one which to more preoccupies me is
Those tizio!
Haku, what means?
Zabuza-saint, it leaves me this boy
I want to lead the combat to way mine.
How?
You want that not me intrometta
Haku?
As usual six too much clement one.
The so'!
Clement!
It is indeed.
To judge from the wounds it is obvious that
it is attacking to me using its spits.
But it has not still aimed at the vital points.
What wants to torture to me?
Well!
Me occuper   of you before.
E' a too much difficult adversary for Naruto.
I must make it
Hey, not to make sciocchezze.
Sai what will succeed to the old one if you move.
If I go towards Naruto
Zabuza Will kill Tazuna.
Sakura would not be in degree
to face it alone.
That of tasks to see that combat
they will carry the boys ahead?
That mask
after all you were from the part of Zabuza.
How you have dared to trick to us!?
The so'.
Your sensei have reason.
The objective of the ninja is to trick.
I pray not to take you it
like a personal fact.
Neanche you
you have time in order to speak!
Sasuke?
They are not forgotten to me about you.
It has thought to attack of surprise
and instead it has seen it.
I would have preferred that pits
remained calm l
but it seems that it is not possible, true?
It goes well.
Before we will end our duel.
Then
Naruto-kun after you and I.
Who is this tizio?
E' here!
originate It them
he is them.
They are here.
It has been moved!?
How?
Sasuke-kun!
Sasuke!
Which thing is happening here?
In a Sasuke moment it is remained torn to pieces.
Which type of trick is never this?
Which type of technique is using?
Posiziona its copies in the mirrors
and with those it delivers a simultaneous attack?
Not, he is however too much fast.
Why I do not succeed to see its blows?
Even if they were only of the copies
which it would be the necessity of these mirrors?
E' clearly that they are the mirrors
the key of its attacks.
The only thing to make is
to attack it is from the inside that gives the outside.
To that what serves the mirrors?
I
I hope not to mistake to me.
It does not remain that to make to me to try to Naruto
to attack from the outside.
Hey, has come to save to you!
You are Sasuke well?
That sense has to take
the surprise companions?
the idiot one!
Inasmuch as a six Ninja you move
with more attention!
That ungrateful!
And I that I had come to help you!
Because come devil six
to the inside of the mirrors!
Merda!
I have some enough, stupid!
"Stupid"!
That you want to say with "stupid"!
E' just the ninja more unforeseeable.
Also it will have come to help us,
but the continuous situation to get worse.
It does not remain that to destroy the mirrors!
Katon!
What you want to make?
These mirrors are made with frozen water.
Therefore
Goukakyuu not jutsu!!!
You have not made it null!
They will not melt with one light flame cos  ?.
Eternal damnation! From where it attacks!
It will have been multiplied!
Dov' is originates it them!
E' useless to try to follow to me with the eyes
you will not succeed to take to me.
Kage bunshin not jutsu!
You stop it!
To destroy   to all the mirrors
and we will see qual' is the authentic one!
This is a technique of transfer in
which only I am reflected in the mirrors.
Regarding my speed,
he is like if you were firm.
As I thought!
E' one innata specialty!
Innata specialty?
E' like my Sharingan.
There are technical
that they can be single
inherited from the ancestors
In a generalized manner from those who they have
one advanced physical structure.
Then!
! Neanche I can copy this technique.
and neanche to neutralize it.
Maledizione
And.
then?
I cannot be stopped here.
I have a dream to realize!
In my village all
they will recognize my force.
Diventer   Hokage!
(Dream)
That boy wretch.
Like you not servants to nobody.
Morirai here, like an abandoned dog,
without freedom of dreams.
You have my same eyes.
For me it is difficult to think it as a ninja.
If possible, I would want to avoid to kill to you
and of being killed from you.
For , if you face to me
you would tread on my feelings
and diventer   a ninja.
This bridge is the battlefield
that it connects many dreams.
Lotter   for me, my dream.
You will fight for yours
for your dream.
I pray you not to serbare rancor.
I want protect
one important person to me.
For he job.
For he I fight.
And for he realizzer   on desires.
This is my dream.
In order to succeed to us I would become pitiless
and to kill to you!
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
The ice mirrors will be destroyed!?
To the end trover  the way in order to make it.
Well Sasuke
We exit and we will go here to help master Kakashi.
I have an ugly prefeeling.
Master, Sakura-kun,
you resist finch not arrival!
The next time:
The battle with zero of visibility,
the destruction of the Sharingan.
Also in this understood it avr
a part a lot important.