sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni
jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
mayoinagarademo II
arukidashite
mou ikkai
NaruTeaM
It introduces
http://naruteamplus.altervista.org /
dareka not kitai ni zutto kotae
homerarerunoga suki dwarf desuka?
naritai jibun wo surikaetemo
egao wa itsudemo suteki desuka?
hajimaridake yume mild okiru
they are saki nara itsuka
jibun not ude de
souda daiji na mono wa itsumo
katachi not nai mono dake
you ni iretemo nakushitemo
kizukanumama
sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni
jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
mayoinagarademo II
arukidashite
mou ikkai
Perche '....!
You have made us to wait for cos ì  a lot, and that sense
it has that spectacular entrance cos  ì!
Not to try to make feint of nothing,
six dannatamente in delay!
Diglielo, Naruto.
Left that glielo it says once for all, ok?
Sakura indeed was preoccupied for you!
Sasuke!
Me it does not seem preoccupied more than a lot,
indeed he seems happy now.
Sasuke, has been the more spectacular entrance! Che figata!
I thought pits scappato perche '
you had fear to fight against of me.
It seems that it is putting to you to cry.
not… but that you say…
That it is cos ì.
Perche '....!
Perche '....
I feel myself raised....
Welcome, Sasuke.
Naruto, the six type of person who will not never be able
to be the protagonist of one history.
You are zitto!!! That the special one of Naruto begins!
Name?
Uchiha Sasuke.
An important hour....
The wild force of Sasuke
Finally it has beginning....
The rules are the same ones of the preliminary matters.
The crash will go ahead until when
one of you dies or it is withdrawn.
If the superiority of one of the two
challengers are crushing,  will stop  the crash…
But  I  will be alone to take this decision.
The man who  recalled  one storm!!
The Taijutsu di Sasuke Sopracciglione Style!
Hey Gai…
Ehi, Lee, as you feel yourself?
kakashi…
Master Kakashi!
Oh, excuse excuse.
You must have been in thought.
Me dispiace not to before have you of put to the current.
( Now Sakura Will drive crazy.)
It does not have more importance....
( I do not succeed to see it from here…)
( Sasuke…)
Master Kakashi
Was one spot on the neck of Sasuke, just?
That thing.>.
Not preoccupartene more.
( Spot? )
Just cos ì.
( One)
(Two)
(Three )
( Four )
( Five…)
( Six )
( Seven )
( Eight )
Eight members of the special square in this enormous stage.
Two platoons are not sufficient in order to cover this area.
Cos' will have in mind the Hokage?
Be', until when we do not know as muoverà the enemy…
e' obliged to distribute the members of the special square
around the more critical areas in this village.
It is in order to begin.
We cannot lower the guard, but we will have
lend attention also to this encounter.
Kakashi, now we will see to that type of
training you have it subordinate....
Inasmuch as they are your eternal one avails again.
You have said something?
Just typical E' of you this, Kakashi!
Perche' continuous to answer to me cos ì!
Challenging, to the center.
Begun!
( This must be the sand about which Kakashi spoke  )
It does not make me to drive crazy…
Mother…
( But about what she is speaking )
Before… prima… ti I have made to taste disgustoso blood…
Me dispiace
But… this time…
it will have a better sapore.
It has begun to speak now already.
It is not a good sign.
I have not never seen Gaara
to become cos ì before an encounter.
It will want to say that the adversary is strong…
It seems that it has been calmed.
You come.
Hey,
Memories cos' have said to you yesterday?
To the end it had said…
" I will kill  to You  once for all, boys  "
" You must only wait for  "
You memories?
But it has not made it.
And to say that it had also an optimal opportunity.
We were not its objective.
" Fatemi to feel…"
It does not take to us neanche in consideration.
The only boy who  can  excite it is…
Sasuke!
" I only fight for same me and love alone same me  "
"From when task that the others only exist
in order it makes to feel alive....."me
" For me the world is wonderful  "
( Naruto.>.)
We begin!
The sand shield has become one sand copy.
( fast E'…)
( one moves just like....)
( fast E' )
( It has the same natural speed of Lee  )
( Moreover )
( it turns to It round using… il my style
of combat body to body )
That one must be the sand armor, eh?
Facts under.
Ringrazio, member of the special square.
They have said that Hinata to me
it will be on condition that cares well.
Sure....
Mh? You know?
But that you say?
It makes part of the special square.
", it is not what we have met to the examination…"
What you want to say?
Here what meant…
Facts under.
If you do not want to come, then  I  will come.
Fast E'…
What is that it does not go?
E' all here what you know to make?
( incredible E'....)
I will tear  you  of back that armor.
( one is muovendo to the same speed
of Lee when it removes the weights…)
( its movements are equal to those of Lee…)
( and its speed is various from before. )
( Sasuke....)
( a Six undoubtedly incredible genius.)
( Me many years are intentional in order to acquire that speed…)
( and.... and you have it acquired in a single month.)
( But it seems that consumptions a bag
of stamina in order to maintain that speed )
( What you are planning, Gaara? )
( the sand armor consumes too much chakra. )
( it will still not last to along. )
To that type of training you have it subordinate?
Com' can become cos ì  in a single month?
Sasuke has copied the style
body to body of Lee with the Sharingan.
Ecco perche' during the training
of the combat body to body....
I have made in Sasuke way focused all movements of Lee.
Sasuke knew Lee…
Ecco perche' has been in a position to acquiring of the movements.
Useless to dirsi, we have met a bag of difficulty.
( But…)
( Only with that one… solo with the combat body to body
it will not succeed to defeat the ninja of the sand. )
( Kakashi has observed the crash between
the abominable Gaara and the adorabile Lee. )
( Someone that neanche Lee could defeat…)
(  he cannot  be struck simply acquiring
one style body to body. )
( It would have to know it.)
( But then…)
( Perche' has made it to acquire only that style? )
" Perche' I exist and alive? "
" I have need to try it finche alive  "
" Or it would be like being died. "
" But about what it is speaking? "
" This is the conclusion to which they have arrived…"
" I exist in order to kill all the others except me."
" To the end I have found comfort in the fear of
to be able to be assassinated in every moment  "
Shikamaru…
We go from master Kakashi.
What you have intention to make?
Hey!
Fargli to interrupt the encounter.
( But Gaara…)
( it will not want to use that technique? )
( its sand is using all in order to defend itself)
( I did not think could vary the density of
sand until rendering it cos ì  hard)
This dev' to be what
the others call "defended absolute ".
All the sand has envelopped its body.>.
( It will be difficult to pull down )
( That it will make Sasuke, now? )
Master Kakashi!
Naruto!
That there is?
Master, it I pray firm this endured encounter!!
He…
Totally various E' from we.
It is not normal!
Naruto!
But about what you are speaking?
It only lives for being able
to kill persons. In any case…
To this point, Sasuke is in order to be killed!
( Not there is more no doubt. E' just that technique. )
( This is not a good)
( Gaara has lost completely sight the plan…!)
( Eternal damnation…!)
Master Kakashi!
Master, it I pray firm this endured encounter!
What?
Not to worry to you.
We are arrives in delay for one reason to you.
I was not for nothing in delay!
Definitive Movement - Chidori!!
( the third eye. )
( Not there is more no doubt. E' just that technique. )
Gaara....
( Nothing to make )
( completely it has been closed in if same…)
( I do not know what you are escogitando, but....)
( But this is the moment that I waited for. )
( For this movement I have need of time )
Hey, something does not go?
Not
It must have been my imagination.
Sbrighiamoci.
Master.
What you wanted to say with "we have come
in delay for a reason "?
You want to know it?
We do not have time for this!
Zitto and watches!
You you will make under.
( All this is absurd!)
( That Gaara… we do not know when we will receive marks them! )
( .... between little I will make  it  pieces.)
( Then, it leaves it to exit…)
( But about that it speaks? )
( Of the deeper part, and than cos' other )
( it will come some outside beautiful po' a true one? )
( I will give  all  to Them you. )
( They are always Bravo child.)
( , we make it)
( Mother, I  will be  to watch )
( Eternal damnation…  cannot  be made nothing
now that it is in that state. )
It has intention to perhaps ruin the plan and all the rest?
Damned Gaara…
( Devil… Forse would have to scappare…)
( Slowly? )
How it proceeds?
All it goes the plans second.
Tried of sbrigarvi with the rituale of the evocation.
We would want to be in a position to
to move to us anytime.
I have understood!
Then, I leave all in hand yours here.
It will not be....
Supervisionato Ho the training of Sasuke…
just perche' it is similar to me.
Activation of the body....
I understand now…
this is the reason for which you have taught the technique to it of
combat body to body. In order to increase its speed!
Exact.
Amazing… riesco to see
clearly the chakra with my eyes!
But as it succeeds to us?
( That technique, will not be…)
( the force of the Uchiha clan Must be this )
Undoubtedly.
But cos' it is that one ?
It emits the strongest noise. Which race of movement is?
Simply a direct attack.
What?
But one is the better attack of the number
of the village of the leaf....
The only movement originates them of Kakashi the copy-ninja.
What?
E' one moved secret only used with fine homicides.
Its secret hides in the speed of the blow…
and in the activation of the body in order to generate
one great amount of chakra.
Therefore it concentrates all the chakra in the arm with which it attacks.
And because of the enormous speed to which one moves…
it emits a cinguettio similar to that one of hundred of birds
Ecco perche' that movement is called....
Chidori. (Flock of birds)
Dev' to be one joke…
The absolute defense of Gaara....
It cannot  be true....
P uò  not to be.....
Not bad.
That one is the movement of kakashi....
Chidori… chiamata also "cut of the lightning ".
"Cut of the lightning "?
That name was given to it when once Kakashi  cut
in two a lightning with that movement.
( it cut  a lightning? )
( What? )
( it knows Me of hauled....)
( incredible....)
Its true name is Chidori…
And its secret resides in the maximum speed that a body
human  can  catch up; The speed of the attack…
and the amount of accumulated Chakra in the arm.
Cos ì  the arm transforms in one sword
that  it can  cut any thing.
Sure that you have taught one to it moved much dangerous one.
You would not have to say them these things to me just,
True, Lee?
I just do not succeed to understand of logic…
But it is indeed one moved incredible!
( I understand instead.....)
( If pits be in he, I would not have thrown myself on the enemy
only after to have acquired speed.)
( Indeed, for being preciser, I cannot. )
( the direct attacks are easy expectable from the enemy.)
( and my eyes do not succeed
to find the attack and to counterattack. )
( I envy to You, Sasuke. )
( When we have fought, I have said to you that…)
" useless E' that your eyes succeed to follow to me, when
your body  cannot  answer to the same speed  "
( For a moment indeed they are felt me advanced. )
( But you six successful one to obtain
a high speed, just like me )
( and you....)
( oltretutto you have your Sharingan. )
Six mine.
Third company, ready to move.
We are ready finally.
All the prepared ones are complete to you.
Received.
We will pass to the action after marks them.
Arrived E' the moment.
( the boy who until to one
moment it makes was preoccupied for Sasuke....)
( Now it is geloso of he. )
Sasuke....
" E' this the feeling…"
" Technical of the evocation! "
( they have become stronger…)
( for being able to become Hokage, and I do not want
to lose against nobody.)
" sasuke! "
( Therefore  I will not lose  neanche with you. )
" I want to fight also against of you "
( But you…)
" I know It  "
What… cos' is this warm thing?
Mother… what…
Blood! My blood!
But like…
Gaara will not have been hurt?
But cos' it is that one?
E' "the its" arm!
This was not previewed…!
It will not have been transformed in its complete shape?
Of it I do not have idea.
It seems hurt… Never it has not happened before.
( Only the memory of that thing, gives the brividi to me....)
( they are not successful to eat for a beautiful one po '
after to have seen it for before the time. )
That thing seems just....
( Cos' is this feeling? )
Wounded E'!
The shield has been broken prematurely.
… quelli they were not the eyes that I have seen before.
( Cos' was those eyes, then? )
But what is happening?
My eyes are....
Kakashi, this is…
, one technical illusory.
Cancel !
* Liberation
But that it is happening?
Cancel !
* Liberation
( One technical illusory? Kabuto has been put already to the work? )
( Then they would have already....)
(  You come )
That he begins myself!
This is marks them!
The mission has beginning!
to give datte shippai wa suru nda
hazukashii koto janai
kono kizu or muda ni shinai de
waratte arukereba II
sou shizuka na kuuki suikomi
hiroki sora ni kao age tobikomi
toki ni ame ga futtara hito yasumi
jaa yukusaki wa kaze fuku mama ni
takusan not matotteru koukai
kono kizu or muda ni shicha shounai
ude ni kunshou kizami ikoukai shougai
sou kokkara ga Show Time
to give datte shippai wa suru nda
hazukashii koto janai
kono kizu or muda ni shinai de
waratte arukereba II
kanashimi mo kaze ni kaete
tsuyoku susunde ikereba II