That terrifying tension omicida.
It seems that it even picks up the movement of the eyes
and that it can kill to you…
… from a moment to the other.
To remain here also for short time door to the madness
Here what succeeds when a Jonin wants your dead women.
The feeling is had that the own life is in their hands.
To this point it is worth dying endured
and to place aim to this I torment.
Sasuke…
… not to worry to you.
I you protegger ò  to cost of my life.
Not lascer ò  never that mine
companions come killed!
Of six sure one?
You are all dead men.
Master! Behind of you!
You die!
The Technique of the Aquatic Multiplication of the Body!
Successful E' to…
Not to move to you
The determination behind the fear.
The combat is ended.
WOW!
It would be ended eh?
You have not understood.
You will not then succeed never and never to strike to me…
… imitating to me
For ò  I admit that six Bravo.
In that moment you had already copied my technique
of the aquatic multiplication of the body.
"Not lascer ò  never that my companions come killed!"
Making to say something of natural to your copy,
you have attracted my attention on she…
… while hidden you six with
the "Mist Concealment" to observe to me.
For ò…
… I am not cos ì  ingenuous.
Also that one is a false one!
Now!
Of the makibishi!
(Description of the movement)
Pathetic one…
Sensei!!!
With a soccer it has made to fly Kakashi-sensei!
The strongest E' also in the martial limbs!
Cos' has this water? Strangely heavy E'…
Stupid!
The technique of the aquatic prison!
It has fregato to me!
E' be an error to scappare in water!
Six falled to us. E' a prison from which is impossible to escape!
You would complicate me the life if you muovessi
Kakashi, our challenge will end after.
Now sistemer ò  the others.
The technique of the aquatic multiplication of I cover.
I did not think that he was cos ì  strong!
Capacities the coprifronte with pompous air…
… but in truth a true one is said that ninja
she is who has exceeded various crises.
In practical, single who so much strongly becomes to appear
in mine * bingo-book pu ò  to be considered a ninja.
* (black list)
And of sure it they are not of the incapable ones like you.
E' disappeared of new!
Six solo a moccioso!
Naruto!
Boys! You take Tazuna and scappate!
You cannot strike it!
Finchè holds to me closed in this prison,
pu ò  not to move from here!
Also the technique of the aquatic multiplication
sure distance from the true body is not usable to one.
Escaped now!
To escape?
You want to joke?
Free Finchè six we will not have possibiltà.
Even if scappiamo Zabuza will catch up to us
sooner or later, and without of you sensei…
If us schieriamo it will not be impossible to stop its attacks.
Therefore to the end, we have not chosen.
In order to survive, we must save to you!
We must make it!
You take this!!!
Too much easy
Sasuke-kun!!!
Sasuke has been…!
This is a Jonin… a true one ninja.
We must scappare, senn ò…
… it goes to end…
… that we…
… we moriremo all.
I swear on the pain that I have to the left hand!
I swear that not to make me ò  never more to help!
I swear that not me spaventer ò  or scapper ò  more!
Six hurt…
… fifone?
Not sar ò  inferior to Sasuke.
Sensei, I would want to try the Coprifronte of the Leaf.
Oh, this?
Not. This is a test of your degree,
and it indicates that a six true one ninja.
Naruto, you come a second here.
I want give to you one what.
It compliments for your diploma.
"Why you are all of the inadatti plump children
to become ninja.
The missions are of the rischiosi jobs!
Promossi.
But I more am not more the dispettoso child who tasks!
Superer ò  in ability all the Hokage…
… and to make ò  to understand to people of the village how much they are strong.
True E'… I have become a ninja.
And then I have decided not to scappare more.
And not scapper ò!
Stupid! Not to make it!
Naruto! That you have in the brain!
Idiot.
As cabbage jumps to you in mind to attack alone!
Also Sasuke has not been able null against of he.
We Genin do not have no possibility
to win against a similar adversary!
The coprifronte!
I say you, bruttone without sopracciglia.
You add to yours * bingo-book…
* (black list)
… the man who will become the Hokage of the village of the leaf.
The ninja of the leaf…
… Uzumaki Naruto!
Naruto…
Nevertheless before the time that I saw
he seemed cos ì  inaffidabile.
Sasuke! It listens to me
That there is?
I have a plan.
Has elaborated a plan in this situation?
Incredible that like you tasks to the square job.
That strange feeling.
Naruto never has not been cos ì…
… risoluto?
Good…
… then we get loose ourselves.
Beautiful declaration, but you have of the possibilities?
I see badly.
What been making? I have said to you of scappare!
When it has captured to me you would have had to understand endured it!
You run!
Our mission consists in the protect Mr. Tazuna!
You have perhaps forgotten!
Getlteman…
It makes nothing…
They are I it cause of all.
To this point not to put to me ò
to pray you to save the life to me.
You excuse to me, boys…
… you also fight giving the maximum.
Cos ì  stan the things.
Six ready one?
You are just of the children.
What!
Until when you play to make the ninja?
I to your age…
… I had already the dirty hands of blood.
The Zabuza Demon!
Of it you know something, to how much seems.
Time makes, in the village of the fog, that it was called
the "village of the insanguinata fog"…
… there was a greatest obstacle
to face in order to become ninja.
Sai pure of that diploma examination…
Which diploma examination?
That type of examination would be!
A omiciodio of mass between the students.
(To The Battle Royale)
Companions accustom to you to even eat from the same one
ciotola is put in brace and they defy themselves…
… until when one of the two dies.
Companions who before the examination helped themselves,
the own dreams were told and they supported themselves between of they.
Atrocious one…
Ten years ago the diploma examination of the village
of the fog it had to be reformed…
… why that year, appeared a demon.
One reform?
Cos' has arranged that demon
in order to obligate them to one reform!
A boy who had not still received the title it of ninja…
… without no hesitation and to cold blood…
… it made outside more than one hundred students…
… that they had to face the examination
As that time is amused me!
Sasuke!!!
Muori.
Cursed!!!
Advanced technique of the multiplication of the body.
For ò! The advanced technique of the multiplication of the body…
… and cos ì  many cloni you have created.
You take this!
I knew that it was impossible. Pu ò  not to strike itself like he!
We have only this way in order to defeat it!
Sasuke!!
I have understood, Naruto! Optimal idea!
From you me I did not wait for.
Shuriken of the demonic wind…
… the Shadow Of the Wind!
The Shuriken does not work on me!
Capisco.
You have aimed at the true body, for ò…
… not of six to the height!
An other Shuriken hidden from the shadow of the first one?
E' the technique of the Shuriken d' Ombra!
E' too much close in order to avoid it!
For ò  he is not still sufficient!
It has avoided!!!
You take this!