http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Oh! Well, six come also you, Sakura.
Now s   that you can be enrolled
officially to the Chunin examination.
What you want to say?
Pu   to support the examination
only to groups of three.
But master.....
you had said that cascuno of we it could
to choose if to participate less or.
, it is true.
Why you have said one to us lie?
Because
Because if you had said the truth to you
Sasuke and Naruto would have to you sure
convinced to support the examination
even if you you do not feel to you
and in order to only come encounter to Sasuke and Naruto.
Therefore if Sasuke and Naruto
they were introduces to you here alone
the examination would have been suspended
and I would have made them to return behind.
But you have come of your will,
Sakura
Naruto
and you Sasuke.
Very made.
Boys are fierce of you.
Hour gone!
He begins himself!
He sweeps via you avail again!
The nine re-united esordienti.
W Wow
C Cos' is this?
But how many are?
Possible that they will support all the examination?
They seem all.....cos   strong.
Sasuke! Six in delay!!
How much time!
I waited for to you with anxiety!
Ino, you remove the hands from Sasuke! Scostumata!
Why, otherwise that you will make Sakura?
Wide forehead like always, eh bruttona?
What you have said!
Thing....
You are pure to support
this stupid examination?
Oh! The trio of the cretino!
Not to call to us cos !
Uffa! That balls!
Nara Shikamaru:
A svogliato and polemico boy.
Akimichi Choji:
It eats always something.
Dumb Ciccione.
Sasuke-kun is mine!
Yamanaka Ino:
It avails again of Sakura.
It always litigates with she for Sasuke.
Sasuke, Idiot.
Yahoo! We have finds to you to you!
Well! Well! There are all I see.
Hello.
Hyuga Hinata:
E' one strange girl, timid and uncertain
that it always lowers
the look of forehead to me.
Inuzuka Kiba and Akamaru
E' casinista than me
One stronzo with annexed dog that
it always involves like if he were the head.
Aburame Shino:
Umm in effects I do not know any very of he!
I never do not know what dirgli.
Azz.... you are also Bah.
Therefore
all and the nine esordienti
of this year they will support the examination.
I ask end where we will arrive.
That of Sasuke-kun tasks?
It seems sure of you, Kiba.
We are we train to you tantissimo.
We will exceed you senz' other.
You close the spout!
An account is Sasuke, but I
not you sar   from less!
Excuse, Naruto
Kiba has not said it in that sense.
Eh?
* Akamaru seems good indeed.
* (the dog of Kiba)
That there is?
Eh?
Not to tread on it.
That?
I have said to you not to tread on it.
You want to eat it?
Ehi, Boys.
It would be better if you made more Hush.
You are the ninja esordienti hardly
escapes from the academy, true?
You are all moves to you and sorridenti.
That it shocks.
You remember yourselves that this is not a pic-NIC.
But who you being creeds?
I call Yakushi Kabuto.
You watch yourselves round.
Those behind of you are of the village
of the rain and they are not much friendly.
They are all nervous ones for the examination.
I have thought to perceive to you before
that you made one ugly end.
Of other part I cannot
to.blame of the esordienti.
You remember me much time makes me.
It calls to you Kabuto-saint, just?
S .
Therefore this is your second time?
Not.
This is seventh.
This examination keeps alone two times the year
therefore this is my fourth year.
Then you know many things on this examination.
Exact E'.
Wow, impressive Kabuto.
But this does not want to say that it has not exceeded it?
S , also this is true.
E' cos   difficult the examination in order to become chunin?
Cabbage, than breach of scato them.
To give ? some information well,  then to you
through these informative papers-ninja.
Informative Carte-ninja?
In order to make it short, they are of the papers with of
codified information recorded through the chakra.
Here I have four years of information
collections during the examinations
In total they are beyond 200 papers.
They seem papers white women, but for
to render them leggibili
What you are making?
there is need that uses mine chakra.
As an example this.
Which information are?
Here they are indicates the countries to you
participants to this examination
and the corrispettivo number of candidates.
According to you because the countries support
this examination all together?
They make in order to reinforce the alliances between of they
and at the same time to increase
the level and quality of the ninja.
They support?
S , the true reason is that one
to measure the force of the ninja
cos   from being able to maintain balanced
the forces between the adjacent countries.
To maintain la force
Why they would make one stupid what cos  ??
If they do not make it, the county more weak person would come
attacked endured from that more strongly.
For this it is important that
fact comes together all.
Beh, sure.
You have papers also on everyone of we?
Sure!
There is someone in particular that it interests to you?
S .
Sure....
The Database is not perfect
but something I have raccattato.
Boys comprised you.
Dimmi all the one which you know of
this tizio and to execute   the search.
Gaara Of the Desert, and Rock Lee di Konoha.
Well! You know also their names
cos   it is still easier.
Here here.
Mostramele.
I have not understood much good,
for   I make feint that it is all clear.
Ok, for first Rock Lee.
E' a year greater than you boys.
Directory of the completed missions:
20 Missions of D Level
12 Missions of Level C
Its master is Gai.
Its Taijutsu is a lot grown in this year,
for the impressive rest nothing.
They have slid was considered
a esordiente of high profile
but it has not participated to the examination of the Chunin.
Like you, it is before the time
that it takes part to the examination.
In its square there are Tenten and Hyuga Neji.
Eh? Hyuga?
The next one is Gaara of the desert.
Directory completed missions:
8 of Level C
1 of B Level
Impressive that a Genin
it carries out missions of B level.
I do not have other information, being he
debuttante of an other country.
But....
She seems that she is returned from every
mission without not even a scratch.
One mission of B level without a scratch?
Who is this boy?
Leaf, sand, rain, grass, cascade, sound
Many genin of the other villages
they are here in order to support the examination.
The village of the sound is a small
created village only a year makes
therefore not there are many information but
it is useless to say that the other villages can
to boast the presence of numerous young people of talent.
It makes you to lose the emergency....
Therefore all the present persons
Exact!
they are like Lee and Gaara.
They are best genin the coming from ones from several the villages.
You have understood that it will not be cos   easy.
"they are not of agreement! "
"They could also be your soldiers
but they have been my students."
"I know them well"
- "He has reason!"
- "you are underrating the thing."
- "the examination is not cos  ? easy."
- "Not there is some haste."
- "same I have delayed of a year
the examination of my group for the training "
- "It makes to participate them when they will be more mature."
- "They will be still of the children"
" but they improve every day more."
- "Now enough!"
- "Enough to speak about the esordienti."
- "We begin to take the candidacies
of the genin not esordienti."
- "However not intrometterti."
Even if I have said cos
although they have liver to sell,
now they even are scares to you.
Also Naruto is nervous
of forehead to all these persons.
Normal E' even if we are all here genin
we are those with little experience.
Same I am full of doubts, but
he seems that for Naruto it is worse.
Prover   to console it a po'.
Naruto, is not the case to scare cos   a lot
My name is Uzumaki Naruto!
You straccer   all!!!
You have understood?
But it is stupid?
Too much stupid E' that is demoralized
Why it is screaming to all?
And because you ask it me?
And who others I could ask it?
What?
Ahhh. Now that I feel myself better.
Hey, but that one is not the boy before?
More six weak person and more outcries eh?
But that it is stupid?
It seems beautiful cargo
and raggiante.
You have not stepped on it enough, Lee.
You have felt? It has said that the village of the sound
it is a smaller village of a small country.
E' cos ?
We go to play a po' with they
Good idea.
Approval does not know to us....
diamogli the information that
the ninja of the village of the sound
they can be revealed much dangerous.
Us straccerai all, eh?
That stupid.
If it is made them all enemies in a moment.
But that devil you are making!
I have only said the truth!!
Sc you excuse to us!
It was alone joking  cretino
like poch   existing!
You I pray not dategli weight!
But that it is jumped to you in mind....!
We make?
Andiamo.
You would better make to learn....
They are of the village of the sound
It has schivato!
Considerable speed has one
Capisco
it uses this type of attack.
That it has happened!
The blow has schivato,
nevertheless it glances at them to it are routes.
It will have grazed the nose
That type confida too much in if same.
Ah! Vomitato!
Kabuto-saint!
Kabuto! You are well?
I am myself well.
Pathetic one
also seeing that a six veteran of the fourth year.
You write on your papers
that the three of the village
of the sound they will become chunin.
Kabuto it had decidedly schivato
but then because it has accused the blow?
Lee who of tasks of that attack?
Not draft of schivare the blow.
There is qualcos' other.
Fairies Hush, bastards without hope.
Excused for the wait.
They are the examiner of first part
of the examination of selection of the Chunin
Morino Ibiki.
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.