http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
Special Version:
Kage Bunshin of the Fisherman!
It still makes it.
Ce others to conserve want some.
Three are little.
Others three times, cretino.
But you know how much to it is laborious?
You come!
Sasuke-kun!
I have prepared the firewood for the fire!
Can ignite it you to me?
Then three fish will go well.
It waits for a moment!
Prohibited Sbirciare!
The secret parchment.
They are already four days
that the second test is begun.
You have reason.
E' begun to the three of the afternoon.
Us hours remain 25-26
Many groups will have already ended.
If it were cos
I cannot wait for that it cooks.
It does not go at all well.
Most large it is mine to the large one
Probably they are not remained
many adversaries to chase.
What we make?
Many will have finished the test.
Already, we are to the fourth day.
However it is
noon is past, eats.
You rest yourselves.
I go to try something.
Hey!
Mmh?
The other coil had written "Sky ",
and it had the edges white men, true?
I have not made case us when
it has shown them before the examination.
Why what you are thinking?
N you will not want at all
Even
ce they are not any more than coils of the Sky.
What you would want to say, Sakura?
Four of the five days
of According to Examination they are already passes to you.
This means that we have
used 80% of the time available.
There are 78 participants, uniforms in 26 squares
with 13 coils of Sky and 13 of the Earth
and only 13 squares can be promoted.
Moreover memories, Sasuke-kun?
Orochimaru has burnt
our coil of the Sky.
This means
that only 12 squares can be promoted.
Moreover, I do not have guarantees that
the other coils are intact.
There are separates to you from
other boys of Konoha
and we have used two days in order to recover to us.
We must begin to increase the step.
The next enemy
it will be our last possibility!
I go to take other water.
You feel listens
We can have the coil
also without to fight.
Eh?
You will not want at all
And instead!
I have many coils with me.
One for the Ninja techniques,
one of the poisons and the other for the notes.
If of ritocchiamo one
identical to the coil of the sky
It waits for! As you can make it if not
you know what is written within?
If the esaminatrice watches
to the inner one it discovers us of sure! Dumb!
There will be sure some word of order
incomprensibile without the other coil.
Therefore the word of order for being promoted serves us.
I bet to us!
We do not know which it is the content
therefore not there is way to make of a false one!
Dumb! inasmuch as you were much sure one of you
I thought you said something of intelligent.
But
we could assume of the content.
Through the coil of the Earth.
You would want therefore
We will try to open the coil.
Not!!
Six forgotten the rule, idiot to you!
We cannot watch the content
of the coil before arriving to the tower.
But we are in the troubles, not?
There is even some type of trap.
You are careful!
I know it!
Hey! Cos' has happened? Hey!
Which thing has happened?
Hey!
You say something!
Better than not.
An enemy!?
Dumb! You do not have hope.
Fortune that I was near.
Me dispiace
Those that smash the rule
they are obligates to you to withdraw itself.
In the previous examination, who opened the coil
he came ipnotizzato from one magical formula.
Cos   slept until expiring of the time.
Calls you Kabuto, true?
What here you are making alone?
Calm, I do not want your coil.
Probable
inasmuch as you could have stolen it to Naruto.
Then also you are
trying the coil of the Sky?
I do not have Them entrambi.Guarda.
What?
Of it I have passages of all the colors
but hour I was heading towards
the tower in order to meet my companions.
Therefore you excuse to me.
It waits for!!
I defy to you to duel.
That fortune!!
You would want to defy to me?
Sasuke-kun
That you are saying, idiot!!
He speaks seriously?
Me dispiace, but us it does not remain much time!
Hey Sasuke!
Kabuto-saint it has to us as soon as helped!!
Sasuke-kun, anch' I am of I come to an agreement with
Tacete!!
Sasuke-kun
We do not have alternative.
Ve I have already said it before
it is the only way that we have
in order to survive in this forest!
Bugiardo!
Bugiardo?
Not six much coherent one
as you want to make to believe.
If you thought it truly cos
why you would have to defy to me?
You would not have to announce this challenge
But to attack me to the unexpected one, in order to take me of surprise!
Cos   acts a ninja.
Com' is deep.
Not me dispiace this side of your character.
For this I will say  what  to make to you.
But we speak road making.
The smoke of the fire and the odore of the fish
they were felt from enough far away.
The enemies and the wild beasts will notice us.
Six sure one that there are still opposing?
-, of they are sure. -
You must only think a po' in order to understand it to us.
Sai qual' is the better way in order to fight in means
to giungla or in one the forest like this?
Not
The objective of all the candidates
it is the tower to the center of the forest.
Therefore when the place arrives the last day
easier in order to collect the coils it is
around to the tower.
I have understood!
We must stretch an ambush to the squares
that they possess already the two coils.
Just E' for 1/3.
Eh?
Why you are not the only ones
to think it in this way.
Probable E' that already has been posizionate
traps close to the tower.
It wants to say that they will be in many to wait for to us!
E' as well as dangerous exciting how much.
I do not see the hour!
It will be enough to defeat them and we will take
the coil of the sky exceeding the test!
Cos   is right for 2/3
Which it would be the third lacking element?
Draft of the collectors always
present in this examination.
Collectors?
Also with the near tower,
this remains a difficult examination.
This situation creates the collectors.
That is those who tries to collect
of the coils in more
to offer to eventual
adversaries of advanced force.
Or passing it to the companions of the same country
to the aim to obtain favors in the successive tests.
Or there are those that think
to take advantage of an ambush
simply in order to eliminate of the candidates.
As you will have understood
the collectors are many forts.
They are gets worse enemies who you can meet
poich never they are not satisfied.
Hour I understand.
E' for that you come with we!?
You have fear of they, true?
Exact.
Finally. Here the tower.
Now we must be indeed attention.
EVVAI!!! WE GO!!!
There is an enemy!
E' l !!
Eh, is only thousand feet.
Enormous E'. Its legs are orripilanti.
Naruto-kun.
Of hour in then it is better to avoid
it sets in action and inopportune noises.
To advance in the forest fecendo noises from elephant
it is equivalent to perceive
to high voice that you are arriving.
You would have cos   an acceptance much warm one.
-  C I understand -
We will hide and be left over slowly
time to disposition allowing.
They are all much good.
Well, we will pass from here.
One trap
E' cos  beginning from hard hour will be a lot.
Kabuto-onii-chan!
There is lacked little, Naruto-kun.
Kawarimi not Jutsu!
(Technical of the Substitution)
I had said to you that of hour in then it will be hard.
Ce I do not make it more.
Sakura-chan!
For how much we have walked?
The tower does not seem to be nearer!
E' like if it remained of forehead to we is strange
Obvious.
It seems that someone
warm acceptance has prepared us one.
Watched l !
But that one is
What is happening?
It cannot  be!!
Genjutsu?
(illusory Art)
It would seem.
There are completely falls to you.
Too much it engages to you to attend to the ambushes
we have continued to turn
around to the same place.
They are observing.
Sure they are trying
to tire to us most possible
in order to attack us when we are to the extreme.
Therefore we are making the game of the enemy.
They will attack to us soon.
Eccoli here.
A lot is being made interesting.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
Who is these tizi?
They are escapes from the null one.
The number does not import!
We will equal them with the Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
In the next episode:
The Combat of the Cloni! I am the protagonist!