Subbed by NW_aTi _
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not
fukinukeru Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda Yeah!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite
kanashimi mo hoho tsutatte
namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa
tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Episode #124
As it projects them
talked nonsense for trafiggere!
Sasuke!
Why?
Why you are scappando via?
Sasuke!
The persons do not fix cos  ?!
E' faster than before!
The medicine that has taken…
it will have been made with some special ingredient?
Six… truly Bravo…
When I move, I feel myself indeed strange…
Thing…? Cos ì  to the unexpected one?
It will be indeed sleeping?
Six falled to us!
It seemed same sleeping
but I did not sleep at all!
This is what it is called
the plan of one shinobi.
Gai-sensei!
Ce I have made it!
I… am....
Six falled to us.
..ancora!
If tasks that I am the type of person who would sleep of the sort in place
you are mistaking of large!
I…
are…
cos…
Why I find myself
in a place like this?
huh?
why?
Sake?
Drunk E'?
In this case…
you will feel the pain soon
for like sending to you ò  in the oltretomba.
Eternal damnation.
I do not have enough chakra!
At this rate…
Better not to remain still in water
with this wound…
Why.
..non I succeed to hit it?
Just when I was in the better part of my sleep…
Me you are truly seccando!
You take this!
Ehi
it goes via from here!
That type
of movements they are those?
As it knows
As it will know, the Kenpou is a style in which more it is drunk
and more he is become strong.
I know.
To the restaurant
exchanges ò  mine sake for water
and of it single drop has drunk one…
What? What you want?
Gai-sensei… I feel myself…
to the Neji end and I am resolutions to fermarlo..
You could not stop it alone?
If you had fought normally s ì,
but I could not hurt my preferred student.
I suspected
All this for one drop of sake…
If an entire bottle of sake had to drink…
Its force will be inconceivable?
But still it has not been resumed of all!
I do not know how much its body can resist…
A drunk combatant?
it is before the time that of it I see one.
If not attacks you.
..lo to make ò  I!
Its style of attack is too much spigoloso, as usual.
It makes badly…
it is all guilt yours!
I.
are…
… in the spring of the giovinezza!
Unforeseeable E'…
And he is fast!
Tsubaki not Never!
Eccolo!
I do not succeed to preview its movements.
For he to deliver an attack…
And then this taijutsu is rather powerful.
I do not have other choice.
My ability is that one to manipulate my boneses.
You have felt from the marmocchio of the cloni.
To put ò  soon fine to your drunkeness
I am not
drunk!
After that you sveglier ò  from your state you trance.
They are not drunk!
I am under-age!
to the boys drink is not allowed sake!
Incredible, it does not find?
This is my innata ability.
Calm.
It thinks to a plan…
I must pull outside
all the possibilities!
with those wounds
will not have gone a lot far away, not?
I have caught up my limit.
I cannot move.
Eternal damnation
It has nearly caught up me!
and…
It makes the head badly me…
And this cut…
I suppose pits drunk after all.
That aspect!
It seems that you are not drunker.
This is my innata ability.
Innata ability…?
My innata ability
the cellular structure of my boneses consists in manipulating.
As you succeed to kick, I am in a position to creating boneses.
there are approximately two hundred boneses in your body,
but I am not limited to that number.
However…
A bone is also always a bone!
Once broken, it is ended!
that resistance!
They are truly human boneses!
In this case!
Karamatsu not Never!
They are to the limit…
It lacks little…
bastard…
Time makes, when arriv ò  Asuma…
Asuma!
To think that every time can come that is in danger....
This of sure will not happen!
E' useless to think next to things that they will not happen!
Calm....
The odore is going via.
They are but…
You creeds?
Like devil…
Cos ì  is true…
My jacket…
From the moment that you have used it, you would not have never recognized your same odore.
Cos ì  you have used it in order to hide your odore?
You know well as they work smells to it,
ce not to be astonished if I have not felt your odore.
If you will still divide yourselves
in order to fight to me
it will be hard.
Eternal damnation.
Aspetta.
Of hour in ahead
it is mean it.
I must try to resist more to along possible.
My task is to slow down it.
In some way they are successful
to schivare the attacks it gets worse.
But my enemy is not cos ì  weak person
I must use my techniques
Arrival!
Hardly they have been operated, are not to the maximum of my force.
But I can perlomeno open the first door.
First door
release!
Omote Renge!
It has used its boneses in order to stop my soccer!
That impressive speed
but it is ended.
Eternal damnation.
It does not import how much I tasks, I do not succeed to find a good ones slowly!
This is the end.
I cannot make other.
Hour that they are of forehead to you, you want to implorare aid?
You die!
Six mine!
Not to dare to laugh before dying!
What?
Who six?
It seems that this time you are ours allies to you.
It allies you of Konoha…
..shinobi…
..della sand.
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
bokura kara shaberi kaketure
meiwaku ni omou kara
sonna fuan wo kakaetie
yuuki wo dashite mitayo
umaku shaerinai bokuno
bukiyou na hanashi
kimi wa mimi wo sorasazuni
chanto kiite kuretayo
soredaked bokuwa ukarete shimaunosa
dakedo kimi wa boku nante
nantomo omottenai yone
setsunai yo
dakedo
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
It seems that the village of the Sand is returned to being our allying.
It is not that it amuses to me to help Konoha. E' only one mission.
E' only one mission.
Capisco.
In any case
you three have come together.
Us puo' not to make oneself null, eh?
E' why you are weak people.
Fool.
Not to underrate them!
They are not of the average cartridges!
Next episode:
It allies you of Konoha, the shinobi of the Sand.