Subtitles By: BakaSan
Kuchiyose-no-jutsu
(Summon Technique)
This time it should be a frog for sure.
What is a frog anyways?
From what point is it called a frog?!
Alive or Dead!? Risking life for learning a Jutsu!
Hey!
Can't you even be a little bit helpful?!
He's passed out again.
It's to be expected...
He's been training only with his guts for the last three weeks.
Hokage-sama...
That you Anko?
I'm sorry...
I...
You regret that you came back alive from the Forest of Death?
Am I right?
It's needless to worry...
Orochimaru and you have no more relations.
There's no ninja in Konoha who can match up with him.
I'm afraid that even I... won't be able to.
If the Fourth was still alive...
Don't say that to him...
He already died to save this village.
It's already been 13-years.
He's not here anymore.
We have to do something with our own power.
Yes.
I'm going outside to get some fresh air.
Don't blame yourself... Ok?
Hey!
Wake up already!
What?
To be honest, you've got zero talent.
Ero Sennin!
It's a waste of time if you are only at...
this level after three weeks of training.
That won't be true.
I'm doing my best even though it may not seem like it.
I know that.
But if you really want to
do the Kuchiyose-no-jutsu...
you need to do it with your life on the line.
I'm doing that!
I've been channeling chakra with my life on the line!
If you talk like that, give me one trick to do this!
A Trick?
The trick is...
Are you gonna tell me one?
It's to risk your life.
My life?
It's not a joke.
Do you still want to do it?
Of course!
I always risk my life!
I see.
Then, follow me.
What are we going to do at a place like this?
Don't tell me you're going to peek again.
Well, that may be good.
But we're going to bathe today.
We need to purify our bodies first.
Huh?
Something strange is going on here...
The hot water feels so nice!
So nice!
This is heaven!
Hey Ero Sennin...
It's Gama Sennin (Toad Sennin)
I don't care which...
But what's the relationship between...
taking a bath and doing Kuchiyose?
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What is it?
Hey, Naruto.
Do you have something you want to eat?
Itadakimasu!
So tasty!
If training is like this, I can do it everyday!
Eat up.
Because this will be the last...
Huh?
Oh, Nothing...
Eat up... eat more!
Eat like you won't have anything to regret.
I don't get it, but all I need to do is to eat, right?
Ok, then...
Another bowl. Miso again!
Alright.
Another one!
Miso Chashu again.
I'm so stuffed!
Thank you Ero Sennin...
What?!
Thank you!
Can't squeeze even a drop of blood...
Hey!
Are you full?
Don't mess with me Ero Sennin!
Weren't you supposed to treat me there?
Stupid.
Who said I would treat you?
Are you a grown up talking to me like that?
By the way, Naruto.
Do you have somebody in your mind?
Huh?
I'm asking if you have a lovely girl you like.
Well, I could say I like...
I have somebody...
So you have someone?
It's Sakura-chan!
Great!
Then immediately go hug that girl tightly!
Is that part of my training?
Yeah, it's something like that.
Alright!
Then I'll go right now!
But if I do such a thing, Sakura-chan would...
No!
This is training!
If I don't, I can't be strong!
But if I do such a thing, Sakura-chan...
won't talk to me for a while afterwards.
No!
In order to do the
Kuchiyose-no-Jutsu...
this is a task I have to do!
But Sakura-chan...
No!
But...
Go already!
What do you want?
Well... ah...
I won't lend you any money.
I'm greedy despite how I look like.
It's not that... well....
She'll definitely punch me if I ask to hug her for my training.
I'm going if you don't have anything to tell me.
Hey, wait a second!
This is my chance!
Sorry, Sakura-chan!
What are you trying to do to me!
Goddamnit!
That really hurt.
This is an incident of youthful days.
Hey...
Is a frog actually coming out doing things like this?
Yeah, that's for sure.
Really?
Is there nothing you will reget anymore?
Huh?
Is there?
What are you talking...
To pull out and use a large amount of chakra...
it sure is hard just to control it.
Also his body is too small to accept Kyubi's chakra.
I suppose his body normally refuses the...
Kyubi's chakra to avoid the extra burden.
If the key to pull out Kyubi's chakra is to risk his life...
then I need to have him learn how to use the key with his body.
Don't hold a grudge...
Fourth Hokage.
Huh?
Where is this place?
Stand up!
What?
Your training is to end now.
You haven't done anything yet!
Naruto!
Go die from now.
Die?
Try pulling out the big chakra from the fear of the death.
And experience it with your body and get the trick.
If you don't want to die, do something by yourself. OK?
Show me whether the power given to you is really for you.
If I don't grab it...
I'll die!
Now!
It's useless.
The cliff is slippery because of the water from the water fall.
Also, falling down with that speed...
it's impossible to stick to the rocks with your chakra control.
Naruto...
Only one thing is left to depend on the Kyubi's chakra.
Open the key...
this time you're the one commanding it.
If it's like this...
like this...
I'll really die!
I'll die.
Today, it's History class outside.
As you know already...
those faces on the cliff are successive Hokage's faces.
From the left, the First...
the Second...
the Third...
and the Fourth.
There's a big difference between that and the old man now.
Especially the hair-line.
Iruka sensi!
Who'll be the Fifth?
It's not decided yet but...
most likely it will your teacher, me!
You're holding a class with some jokes, Iruka.
Hokage-sama.
It's the Third!
Hey, Old man!
What did you come here for?
I wanted to see those rock faces.
You came here at good time.
Please come here.
This person is the real one for the third face on the cliff,
The Third Hokage.
People said he was the strongest of all the Hokage...
and they called him the genius Professor.
Hey, Iruka.
Don't talk in the past tense.
I'm sorry.
Are you really that strong?
You don't seem like it.
Yup, I agree.
Hey!
To recieve the name Hokage means...
he is the #1 strongest in this village.
Alright.
Then I'll become the fifth Hokage...
because it means strong and handsome right?
It won't happen with your current grade.
You're all very promising.
You all are very young unlike me.
It may be one of you who will receive the name Hokage.
You only live once...
so there's no need to force yourself to go on a certain path.
It is okay to live and die the way you wish.
However...
To protect the people precious to you can't be...
forgotten no matter what way you choose to live.
Precious people?
People who you truly recognize,
trust, and love from bottom of your heart.
Do you have somebody like that?
Yes.
My Dad, Mom, and Brother, even though I dislike him a little.
and my pet dog, Gonta.
In my case, that's my friends.
Me too.
So, Hokage-sama, you have somebody like that?
Sure, of course I do.
Who are they?
My grandson, Konohamaru over there, and...
everybody in this village.
Just like you were once.
This feeling...
It's that chakra.
This is...!
[sealed]
It's huge...
What is it?
Hey Kid...
Come a bit closer.
I want to eat you up, but this gate doesn't open.
It's because of this annoying seal.
You are...
Kyubi!
I see.
The red chakra is his.
You finally have come down here to see me...
What brought you here?
Hey, stupid fox!
Since I'm letting you stay in my body...
lend me your chakra as rent.
You're saying if you die, I'll die too in the end.
You got some guts to threaten me.
Alright.
I'll give you some as a reward for you coming down here.
This feeling!
Kuchiyose-no-jutsu!
Good job.
Where the fuck is this?
Alright! This time I summoned the real frog!
Hey, big frog! I'm your boss from today!
Ah, that was nothing. I'm going to be your subordinate.
That makes me happy...
Next Episode. Fly! Jump! Dive! Gama Oyabun Appear!
I'm really scared. I've never seen a frog like this before.