Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
With this, you've woken up, right?
We had a hindrance back then...
but it won't be like
that this time.
I'll show you...
the true power of Sharingan.
Fine... Then I'll go all out too!
You take a good look
with your Sharingan...
at my Way of Ninja!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You can't beat me by just pointlessly...
increasing the number!
You little!
I can spot the real body in
one shot with my Sharingan.
I deliberately went along
with your game...
I won't go easy on you now!
Fire Style. Fire Ball Jutsu!
Father Son.
The Broken Crest
What was up...
with those eyes of Big Brother's?
That wasn't...
just an ordinary Sharingan.
And...quite a bit of time's
passed since then...
but things are still kind of awkward
between him and Father.
Good morning, Father...
Yeah, good morning.
Sasuke... how have things
been going at the Academy lately?
It's boring with just school classes.
I'm always number one, so...
Fire Style: Fire Ball Jutsu!
W Wow...
This is the fundamental
Jutsu of the Uchiha.
The Sign is as I taught you earlier.
You build up Chakra,
stop it once at around between
the mouth and the chest area,
and spew it out at once after that.
Try it.
Okay!
Father...is teaching me Jutsu himself.
Finally... Father has also recognized me!
I must live up to his expectations!
I too can...!
Fire Style. Fire Ball Jutsu!
Sure enough, it won't go like
it did with Itachi, huh?
It might've still been
too soon for you.
A member of the Uchiha Clan
is not recognized as full fledged
until they can use the Fire Style.
The Uchiha crest...
means those who possess
the Uchiha that controls fire.
Fire Style. Fire Ball Jutsu!
Damn it! One more time!
Today for sure!
Fire Style. Fire Ball Jutsu!
Sasuke...!
Wait a minute.
What is it?
What...?
Oh... Don't move.
Okay, finished!
Mother...
Hmm?
No... It's nothing.
Okay...
Fire Style. Fire Ball Jutsu!
Sure enough, it won't go
like it did with Itachi, huh?
It might've still been
too soon for you...
I'm just, getting started.
Damn it! One more time!
Fire Style. Fire Ball Jutsu!
Father!
Hmm?
One more time...
Please join me.
It's still too soon for you.
Even if I were to teach you
for only after a week...
It's not that...
I've gotten... the hang of the Jutsu.
So I want you to see it.
Failure is not an option!
Fire Style. Fire Ball Jutsu!
That's my boy.
You've done well.
From now on, improve yourself
and soar large
so as not to bring shame
to the crest on your back.
Right!
And... let me say one thing.
Don't chase after
your older brother anymore.
Mother...?
Hmm?
What does Father really think of
Big Brother and me?
What is it all of a sudden?
The other day, Father said to me,
"That's my boy.
He'd always said that only
to Big Brother.
So I was really happy.
I see... Good for you.
But lately, Father and Brother
haven't been getting along, so...
I was thinking...
that I might just be
a replacement for Big Brother.
Your older brother's your older brother.
And you are you.
Your father cares deeply
about you both.
Then why does he only think
about Big Brother?!
That's not it...
Your father has to protect
the Uchiha Clan
as a representative of the clan.
What about it?!
Itachi is just bigger than you
and is your elder.
He'll naturally be entrusted
with that much more work
for the clan, right?
Your father is the supervisor
of the work, so...
it might be that his eyes were
likely to go towards your older brother.
But, this is just between us.
When he's with me,
your father does nothing
but talk about you.
He's just always sullen
and awkward, so...
I'll catch up to Big Brother
no matter what!
Damn it...!
Big Brother's back is still
far out of reach.
Forgive me, Sasuke...
Maybe another time.
Clan...Clan...
You measure incorrectly
the size of your own "vessels"
and don't know the depth of mine,
so you grovel there.
My "vessel" is
dismayed at this foolish clan.
I feel like...ever since that day,
he hasn't been the same
as he was before.
Big Brother...
Today, when school's finished,
will you join me for
some Shuriken Jutsu training?
I'm busy.
You should have Father teach you.
But even I know that you're better
at Shuriken Jutsu than Father is.
You always treat me like
a nuisance like that.
Forgive me, Sasuke.
Maybe next time...
I don't have the time to
be dealing with you today.
You always say, "Forgive me, Sasuke,"
and poke me on the forehead.
And you say "today,"
but it never happens.
Thank goodness...
he's the same as before.
Big Brother...
His eyes looking back
at Father that time...
It wasn't just an ordinary Sharingan...
And...
Father?
Hmm?
Are there several types
of Sharingan?
Oh... You're already interested
in Sharingan?
However, it's still too soon for you.
It's totally different from
the Fire Style Jutsu.
But someday, I too!
After all... I'm your kid, so.
Indeed, there is a Visual Jutsu
above the Sharingan,
the Mangekyo Sharingan.
Mangekyo Sharingan...
In the long history of the Uchiha,
it's a legendary Visual Jutsu
that only a few develop.
And it's said that it only opened
under a particular condition.
A particular condition... ?
Don't chase after your
older brother anymore.
I wonder what he thinks of my
relationship with Brother?
Father...
Why doesn't Big Brother care
about me?
He's a bit peculiar...
He's a type of person who doesn't
care for making friends with people.
Why?
Who knows...?
Even I, his father, can't read that boy.
Here I spoke because I wanted
more of Big Brother's attention.
Father isn't against it.
Here, Sasuke!
Your box lunch.
I'll watch your Shuriken practice
after you come home.
It's not practice, it's training!
I'm off!
That's good...
It's not that Father dislikes
Big Brother, after all.
Big Brother graduated from the Academy
at the top of his class at age seven.
He learned to use
the Sharingan at age eight.
And he was promoted
to Chunin at age ten.
But, I've got the same Uchiha blood
flowing inside me as he does.
I won't lose to him!
You're not gonna tell me this is
the best you can do, are you?
You boast about your Way of Ninja
and this is all you've got?
Are you still thinking that
I'm a member of your comrade game?
If that's the case, you're...
a hopeless fool!
Stop wasting time!
Give me all you've got,
you number one hyperactive,
knucklehead Ninja!
When I recalled the parts one by one,
I felt as though
I had understood everything
Faded words which I kept so close to me
Speechless nights, a hint of warmth,
and this distant yearning for you
I live, simply repeating this cycle
Held in my two hands
A droplet of time
Softly clutching forgotten memories
Lost words
I'll keep these thoughts...
Just as Neji said,
it seems Sasuke's in
the darkness right now.
Damn it.
He really did hit me with
all his might.
Hey Sasuke, am I not your comrade
or anything anymore?!
Don't all those things we
did together in Squad Seven
mean anything to you?!
Next episode,
"The Secrets of the Mangekyo Sharingan!