Sub by # [ Fabry ]
Tnx 2 BigJim
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not
fukinukeru Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda Yeah!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite
kanashimi mo hoho tsutatte
namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa
tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Dove' is ended the other?
Hey.
Who you are trying?
I of he take care.
Vai to wash the eyes to you in the river.
This is my ability special assasina.
Also using yours fiuto
and your astuteness
you will not be never in a position to striking to me.
Against my abilities, this is the result.
Akamaru…
Me dispiace, Akamaru.
They have been with you till now.
In every moment, every place
Always we have been together.
But this time…
I will have  to surrender....
My cells are turning
free in your body,
and I am in a position to isolating of a part.
He means that we are in one be of fusion.
I suppose can be said that
we are sharing the same body
Sharing?
Exact.
I can even kill to you
tearing via all the cells to you from the body
I understand.
In this case…
If I make cos ì,  what will happen ?
You want to kill? Six one stupid!
Moriremo together.
Episode #121
Everyone in just the crash.
Bastard! What is jumped to you in mind?
Just as I thought.
You have said that ours
bodies are arrange to you, just?
Merda
To enter in the body of an other person
for being invulnerabile to its attacks…
it was the point of force of my technique.
Nobody had never made it before hour.
You are suffering?
Well. We end it hour.
Six one stupid! Enough with the stabbings!
Too much late!
I am losing too much blood…
Merda!
Where it is ended!
It has abandoned its dog and it is escaped…
It tests decision.
E' quite more cynical than me.
What. not us creed!
Thanks to God still breathe.
Thanks to God.>.
Akamaru, today six state
truly Bravo.
Thanks to you are successful
to slow down the enemy…
and to hurt it seriously.
It can  be enough. You have made
more of the necessary one.
Akamaru is called.
Mother.? Sorellina.>.?
From this moment you will take care yourself of he.
Clearly?
I?
I am Kiba!
Happy for knowing to you, Akamaru.
You have arranged large, small plague.
Always we have been entirety…
Beautiful taken, Akamaru!
Bravo. Very made.
We go!
Be more responsible!
You cannot pass entire days to play.
Mother…
Kiba Listens To Me…
Not draft only of you…
you and Akamaru must become strong together.
With to Akamaru ?
Akamaru…
It goes well.
Large, Akamaru!
Dynamic air marking!
You make one capriola triple the next time!
not to lose the target!
Yahoo!
We will be entirety also hour.
I cannot make other that proteggerti.
That bastard…
How has dared to stretch one to me trap?
I will kill!!
Hey, Sakon!
Where six?
Sakon!
How much six rowdy one, brother…
Yours urla is perforating I the eardrums.
Brother…
I want to kill it, ovunque he is,
but for me it is hour to sleep.
You take them you live those bastards.
And when  I am  wide awake, me of it  I will occupy  I.
It assures you to take them you live, Sakon!
It goes well… but we will kill them together.
It succeeds to avoid every my attack.
I always end with hitting to me!
It watches. Yanagi not Never!
Ugly bastard!!
Boneses.>.
This is my innata ability.
This type. who is ?
It lets out boneses from the body in order to attack?
A its bone has afferato!
Still a po' longer.>.
It is using like if it were a katana…
Useless E'.
It is not a simple bone.
Its density renders it hard like the steel.
Therefore? Me  I will clear up some  equally!
I have acquired full load control
of the five dances.
You would better make not to be deceived
of knowing all on me.
What?
Now you will know my Tsubaki not Never.
You come.
It makes rò  pieces!
Taken.
Kawarimi?
Laggiù.
Eternal damnation.
Those types. they are always approached more.
Merda!
To not it wanted us. The wake of the blood!
Eternal damnation. also having saved Akamaru
I fear to have exaggerated.
This odore…
what means!
Why. Why they head here ?
I do not succeed to understand it.
I must go via from here in a hurry.
I do not succeed to move to me.
My sight is dimmed from the pain
and from the blood that I have lost.
My body refuses to move.
Akamaru…
It has left here the dressed ones.
Six escaped through the river, eh?
Maledizione.
Merda.
Eccoti here.
Finally in trap, lurido worm.>.
Six good one. You have broken the trees and
attacked with perfect tempismo.
You must it are trained much.
It seems one melodia complicated.
You have understood that I succeeded in
to control them with my song.
Far from negligible for a bastard dirt like
you to pick the complexity of the melodia.
But it is impossible that you can
to understand it completely.
The art does not appeal to to me for nothing.
But, if it succeeds to control them with those flauto,
it must it are to us something in the song
that it controls their single actions.
It must it are to us some structure under.
Confido in my abilities of observation.
But stavolta the things seem to put themselves badly.
I do not know null on the manipulation
of the sound and its he aims weak people.
Nobody is not never survivor
after to have felt this melodia.
Supreme Melodia n°9 - Lair of the demon
Music is changed!
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
bokura kara shaberi kaketure
meiwaku ni omou kara
sonna fuan wo kakaetie
yuuki wo dashite mitayo
umaku shaerinai bokuno
bukiyou na hanashi
kimi wa mimi wo sorasazuni
chanto kiite kuretayo
soredaked bokuwa ukarete shimaunosa
dakedo kimi wa boku nante
nantomo omottenai yone
setsunai yo
dakedo
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de!
hajimete kimi to shabereta
It has evoked those three…
and its attack and its defense
they are practically perfect.
Even if it does not appeal to to me at all, creed that can be much good one with the Shougi.
The mission is in order to conclude itself…
Cabbage, seems that you are of divine humor.
Well, we proceed.
Or it goes it or it cracks it.
I will head  all at this!
Next Episode:
Shikamaru is entrusted to
resurrezione of the dead men.