http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
If we had ourselves to be separated, not reliable to you
of nobody, neanche of one of we.
The enemy could use the Henge like little ago.
What we must make?
We will use one order word.
One order word?
Listened carefully.
Saying   only once.
The melodia of the ninja, "Ninki".
When ce we ask it we will answer cos :
"the shinobi it is found to its comfort in the confusion of the enemy.
It must hide and remain in Hush.
The shinobi it must know the opportune time
of when the enemy is tired and disattento."
C what?
Enormous E'!
I haul!
Been trying the parchment
of the "Earth". Just?
Hour has beginning
the battle to the last blood
for the coil.
If not me sputa outside
obbligher ?  to make it you!
Kage Bunshin Not Jutsu!
I do not succeed to move to me!!
I hoped you would have made me to amuse a p more  ?.
Sin.
You move!!
It has been hurt alone
in order to cancel the fear with the pain!
Stammi far away!
You cannot lower
the guard neanche a moment.
A preda she would have to scappare
with all its forces
in front of the predator.
Scusami Sasuke!
Naruto!
The order word
I have scordata it!
The counterattack of Naruto!I cannot scappare via!
The order word....
I have scordata it!
Grande Naruto! Optimal job!
Naruto! I know that strong you creeds
and six come in order to save to us but
scordalo! Scappa via!
This enemy is too much strong!
He seems that you are successful to
to defeat that giant snake.
Naruto-kun.
That boy seems just rectums them.
Therefore
also that snake was operates its!
Arrived E' Naruto but does not seem
that the situation is changed.
What I make?
Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey!
You you always take with more the weak people!
But now that Uzumaki Naruto is here,
you are in order to be taken to soccer!
But it is driven crazy!
Hour we will come killed all and three!
What I can make?
Sasuke-kun
It is put badly.
Not there is other way.
Aspetta.
To give ?  the coil to you.
I pray, you take it to you and you go via.
Hey, Sasuke! What devil you want to make!?
Why you want to give the coil to the enemy?
You close the spout!
What?
Capisco.
Much sly one.
The only way that has one preda
in order to escape to a predator
it is that one of offrirgli a meal
various and to put itself in but.
You take it!
Ugly bastard!
That devil you make!
You do not comprise the situation?
But But what passes you for the head?
I have forgotten the order word
and I cannot demonstrate who are indeed, but
but you you a six sure impostore!
Naruto.
What you are saying?
Cretino!
I am that true one!
Bugiardo.
The Sasuke that I know
of sure it is not cos   dumb and codardo!
I do not know how much I am strongly this boy, but
who assures once to us that
delivered the coil, lascer to go to us?
Six you that six cos   scared
not to understand the situation!
Naruto-kun
you have just reason!
The coil ve I can take it
after to have to you it kills to you.
You close the spout!
Not! Naruto scappa!
Eternal damnation
you have disappointed me Sasuke!
kuchiyose not jutsu!
* Technique of the callback
Naruto!!!
Three corpses.
E' a some type of ninjitsu.
Orribile E'.
There is already a problem.
Cabbage!
Anko informs, the second esaminatrice.
Endured!
The Dango is perfect with the Oshiruko.
Ended to eat
I approach the tower
to wait for the contenders.
The faster group would have
nearly to have arrived.
Symbol of the complete leaf!
Anko, we have a problem!
Cos' has happened?
There are three corpses!
They have been disfigures to you!
You must come endured!
It disfigures to you?
Watching their things and documents
we have understood that they are ninja
of the village of the grass.
As you see
they do not have the face.
E' like if the faces had been melted.
They are sure that....
this technique is its!
But that it makes us
he in this examination?
Mostrami the registration modules
with the photos of these three boys!
They would have to be in the archives!
Sure!
He has stolen the face.
Therefore he
Here its Kunai.
Thanks.
We are in the troubles!
You go to report all to the hokage-sama!
At least sent two squares anbu in the forest!
I andr   to their pursuit! You have understood?
!!
It is
it is in this village.
Pretty one
davvera pretty like preda.
Naruto!
Ahead it eats it.
It eats the merda!
This boy could be
But
com' it is possible that Naruto is cos   strong!
Those eyes I cannot be mistaken.
That one is indeed Naruto!
The game has been made amusing
Now it is your turn.
Sasuke-kun, what you will make?
Sasuke-kun!
I must sbrigarmi.
I have
one ugly feeling!!
Hey!
You are well
fifone?
Naruto!
Hey!
You are well
fifone?
Sasuke!
It is not possible that one stupid
codardo like you
it is the Sasuke that I know!
Eternal damnation!
Bastard!
Damned!
He leaves me to go monster of a snake!
Qundi the child of the vixen
to nine tails it is still alive.
When your emotions are to the extreme
the force of the vixen to nine tails fuoriesce!
One interesting development.
Eh s  I seal is being melted!
Sigillo
pentastico!
Sasuke-kun! Naruto!
Twelve years after that I seal it has been impresso
chakra of Naruto and the that one
of the demon they are acting together.
But now the problem not sussiste more!
It will fall!
Naruto!
Cos' you have Sasuke-kun?
Sasuke-kun
it is true that Naruto is one
confusionario and is not strong, but
at least it is not a codardo!
Just?
Stupid brother
if me you want to kill me you must hate.
You must survive from wretch!
and to continue to scappare
and to grab hold of you to the life.
Not!
Just as I expected from the Uchiha clan.
It seems that its blood is ribollendo.
Sasuke!
I want to take it with calm
and to amuse a po' to me with you.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
nee kikoe masu ka?