Subbed by Kyubi
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
Aoi-sama, than is made?
I  will salt  with Fukusuke.
You Idate continuations.
S ì!
Ehi, Idate!
The sea is from the other part!
Where you are going? It returns here!
You are zitto, I want goes around me single!
We go.
What will be planning that parasite?
One would say that it is scappando. -
Idate always has been this type of boy.
You know well?
Creed of.>.
Episode #103
Naruto is drowning!
Trap up sea.
There was from expecting it, Idate is escaped.
He was expectable, enough to think next to all the problems that it has caused.
E' be an error to authorize it to participate to the race.>.
Race of idiots!
Idate is not that kind of person.
But Head!..
I believe in he.
He will have a plan sure
Jirochou.
Gokaro!?
How counted to resolve this problem?
This historical festivity has taken to a fold ridicule.
It has made in front of your eyes.
Gokaro-sama,
The race as soon as is begun.
You remain to watch it until the end, ve I pray some.
If me the been ones asking, mean that you are sure to win.
But if you lose..
Your clan will be destroyed.
I accept.
They are a word man.
If Idate loses, will be to your service.
Good idea, Jirochou.
Good  solution is one.
I hope that it is to the height of my hopes.
Ripongo my confidence in you, Idate.
Head…
They give all the moneies to me!
You make as you it has been said!
A ladro starved?
You are firm!
A worm with a knife…
I bet that you would not succeed not to peel one potato with this.
A gift.>.
The appuntiti objects are not made in order to hurt the persons.
You do not have a place where to be?
Sono Jirochou, head of the Wasabi clan, the Degarashi village.
Wasabi?
Jirochou?
S ì,  you would want to come from me for a po of time?
I do not know nothing of you…
It does not import, a person who is dying of hunger  can  make something of stupid
Not to take it to you
Euh…
It is  a gift.
You hold it.
To leave now, enough with the thefts and the crimes.
Mine.... Getlteman!
Ve of supplico!
I want to be your subordinated one!
Not.... You want to accept to me like subordinate, Head!
How it calls to you?
Idate. My name is Morino Idate.
We go, Idate.
Trusted you me, head.
Ce I will make  it!
We are recovering.
But it is too much late.
After to have lost cos ì  a lot to the departure, it does not have more possibility than to recover.
Not.
It had probably previewed all from the beginning.
What!?
Joined E' its hour.
S ì  but…
They always follow in order to escort it.
Still better!
This time, we go to pareggiare the accounts…
Of the Chuunin examination.
Gone ahead.
I withhold them here
We have resumed to you finally!
It waits for!
Ehi! Cursed.... Why you are making this road?
Vattene!
They are not transactions yours
But what is that it does not go in you!?
I have said to you to plant it!
You are careful!
But they are not shrewed.>.
of the Genjutsu?
It waits for a moment!
This place…
, it is just a Genjutsu.
Which thing?
In this case…
Kai!
[ Release ]
Laggiù!
Ehi!
It waits for!
But that it happens?
Here made!
Not to move to you.
They withdraw to us on.
What has happened?
It was a double Genjutsu.
Me they are broken.
Race of idiot!
It is  guilt yours if we are here.
But what you are saying!?
Enough! Stopped!
Stopped!
Aaaaaaaah! My crews!
Tzk.. Here your instinct…
Our instinct!
You we have saved the life and ringrazi to us not even.
It is not your mission to help me?
Therefore I do not have ringraziare to you.
But ch.>.!?
Detention, Naruto.
What it has said is true.
But if you do not want to die,
You would better make to remain close to we.
Ehi! Where you go?
Not lathes to Degarashi?
Idiot.
I head towards north.
North?
This road is faster?
Task.
Truly?
Us  it cannot  be trusted this boy.
Also the Ninja does not serve to nothing.
During the war, a powerful wind  blew  very strongly on the ocean.
On the starting line, watching the movement of clouds, I have understood…
that the wind was arriving.
In more, from the port of the north, one marine current heads directly towards the island of Nagi.
E' this the difference between me and you
Is in order to arrive one storm.
Ehi, not to go encounter to the storm!
We have all the time that we want.
We would not have to save our time?
Once it arrives to you on the island, my speed in race will make the rest.
My Victoria is assured!
I have understood.
The wind becomes salato.>.
The sea!
This house is abandoned?
It is  the Tempio Modoroki, is to goal road from the island of Nagi.
In less than an hour, we will catch up the other side.
Waited for a second.
Getlteman, there are. Sono Idate, of the Wasabi clan.
Oh, I waited for to you.
I imagined.
I ask your boat on loan.
Sure.  It is  already ready.
You take the boat that is laggiù.
It is  my faster boat.
Thanks.
It is  an honor.
It is  also mine it must towards Jirochou.
This is the reason for which I ask you not to lose against the Wagarashi clan.
I do not accept their methods.
You can count on me.
Any thing happens, is also always Idate, the faster runner of the Wasabi clan!
You must be trusted me!
Che sbruffone!
It would not have to want a lot to us why the port of Nagi is caught a glimpse.
I hope to have a good margin on Fukusuke.
Ehi, Naruto. Which thing of tasks?
Eh? Of that what?
Of Idate-Saint.
He is not a normal boy.
Its speed is tutt' other that normal.
It must have received a special training.
Type?
As an example, it could come from some hidden village.
How it is possible that a stupid person cos  ì is a Ninja?
Just you.>.!?
The not six person more adapted in order to say it!
But, but…
They are survivor to the Chuunin examination, not?
You?
The Chuunin examination?
Ehi, ehi! Not to interrupt to us.
I have conquered the title it to the torneo. They have become Chuunin
Probably your examiner must itself be distracted.
Eternal damnation, as it can fall cos ì  the Chuunin examination low …
Idate-saint, then you are…
Hour memory.>.
Morino Idate…
Morino?
I have understood.>.
If me memory well, the examiner of before the test…
Fairies Hush! Cos' is this confusion?
I have made you to wait for?
They are the examiner of before the test of the Chuunin examination.
Morino Ibiki.
Which thing you have said?
My brother greater Ibiki is still alive ?
S ì.
Sure! That man has made us to support a just difficult test.
Truly? It is  truly alive?
Qu.... Cos' has been?
It is  an ambush!
Then?
You see?
It is  just here
The operation  can  begin.
I and Naruto remain here in order to stop those persons.>.
Sakura, account on you. You take cure of Idate.
It would not be better to escape?
E' too much late in order to escape!
I try to hold occupied them.
You ransom the ropes.
I have understood!
Merda, I must cut them at all costs.
Eternal damnation! I have lost them all before!
Ehi! It lend yours to me.
Which thing?
Gone, sbrigate to you!
Six crazy one?
For me this is worth more of my same life.
I do not have time for these cavolate!
Idiot! Stopped!
You move, cretino!
Easier than how much you thought.
Sakura-chan!
They are only of the cloni!
Those true ones can only attack from their boat, not preoccuparti.
SHARINGAN
Sakura, Naruto!
Those true ones hide in the cloni.
You are prudent!
Sasuke-kun, you cover to us!
Idate, remained close to me.
Creeds that the aid of a Ninja wants?
Also in a situation of the sort.... but as you allow yourself?
Naruto behind of you!
Naruto!
A clone?
Merda!
The cloni arrive!
Scappa.
Beautiful job, Naruto!
This Kage Bunshin is bothering.
This time we will make it ended with they.
Suiton, Kokuyou not Jutsu
[ Technical of the black rain ]
Sasuke, is transforms to you in cloni of water
I have seen!
Piove?
Not, it is of the oil.
They are I stew.... is hour to make ended it.
This is.... I seal of the tiger!
Firm, Sasuke-kun!
It has been stopped?
That misfortune.
Not ago nothing.
One heated arrow?
Brother!
Vai! If you remain here, you will be only of impiccio.
Idate-saint?
It is not nothing.
Sasuke, than what we make now?
The flames are too much high!
We must be thrown in water.
We will swim until the coast of Nagi.
You have reason. We do not have other choice.
Idate-saint, sapete to swim?
Sbrigatevi! Gone you for first, or risked the asphyxia.
In order now it is only of the smoke, we can escape without being wounded.
Idate-saint?
You take game of me?
You want that it leaves for first in order makes to make me from decoy!
But that you say?
You want to attract the enemy on me!
Idiot, not to say stupidaggini!
Me refusal! I cannot be trusted a Ninja!
Which thing you make? You move! If you remain here, you will be only of impiccio.
Vai via! If it remains here, you will be only one ball to the foot.
Sbrigati!
To use you like a decoy? It does not have no sense!
I cannot…
Pig miseriaaa!!!
Idate-saint, you lower yourselves!
Give Idate-saint confidence to us! You proteggeremo at all costs!
Attention!
Sakura-chan!
S-Sa.... Sakura-saint.
Vai ahead you…
we will catch up to you soon.
Well. We can go.
To go via?
The best must still come.
They are more tenacious of the previewed one.
But one what is sure. lasceremo not to scappare them.
There are nearly.
Last E' much time, Idate.
Tu!
That disappointment. I have always said you that it does not have to trust itself the others.
Six cos ì  stupid.
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
In that period you were a bad boy. But now it does not import!
The race still is not ended!
We have confidence in you. It tries us until the end!
The head believes in you. And if you have the time to make one pause and to hide to you,
Then it is the moment to show that  to us  that goes them.
Next episode
You run, Idate!