Subtitles By: BakaSan
I will become the Hokage!
I can't lose a battle like this!
Shut up! You can't even keep up with my speed at all!!
U!
Zu! Ma! Ki!
Naruto Combo!
The winner is Uzumaki Naruto.
I am... getting stronger!
Wow! Good! Great job!
That Naruto beat Kiba!
This is a big surprise, isn't it?
Opening of the Byakugan!! A big decision of Shy Hinata!
This medicine is really good!
Hey, don't you want to use this, too, Sakura-chan?
It's only you to have your wounds heal that quickly...Naruto.
I've been surprised by Kyubi (nine-tails) power, as always.
He..hey...
This is a medicine cream for your wounds... for you and Akamaru
You’d better start worrying about
yourself, instead of somebody else.
The rest is you, Choji, Neji, Lee, the Sand (Suna)
ninja, and one Oto (Sound) ninja... Only 6 people left.
Listen, Hinata
If your opponent is the Sand guy, forfeit immediately
And one more...
do the same if it's a match against Neji,
forfeit immediately
that guy is too harsh for you
you'll be beaten up like an old rag
Alright... I'll announce the next match
Hyuga Hinata VS. Huga Neji
Dammit!
Hinata
This is a very interesting match up...
I never imagined I'd go against you, Hinata-sama
Neji-brother
Brother?!
What? Those two are ... siblings?
They are from the oldest distinguished
family in Konoha, the Hyuga clan
but, they're not siblings
Then, what kind of relationship do they have?
Hmm... well... I probably can say
that... they are Hyuga's Souke and Bunke.
Souke and Bunke?
Yes. Hinata-san is from Hyuga's
Souke, the main stream of the Hyuga family
and Neji is from Bunke, the branch
family that shares the same blood.
That means, this match is between relatives.
This would be a hard one for those two to fight.
Exactly... But..
But what?
There have been so many things between Souke (main
family) and Bunke (branch family) for a long time.
They are not in a good relationship these days.
Hmmm... Why?
I don't know exactly why...
But...
the old distinguished Shinobi (ninja)
families such as the Hyuga and the Uchiha,
have the clan's special techniques and capabilities
To protect and pass down those, I've
heard that the Hyuga set some rules...
but many of those rules are advantages for the Souke...
There've been so many problems between Souke and
Bunke, because of those rules... That's what I've heard.
Then, this would be a battle of their fate.
Hey... It'll begin.
Please begin the match now.
Before we start the match ...
I want to warn one thing to Hinata-sama.
Forfeit!
Being a Shinobi is not for you!
You're too kind...
You desire peace, avoid conflicts, and don't
hesitate to agree with somebody else's opinions.
And, you don't have self confidence.
You always feel that you're inferior.
That's why you don't mind just being a Genin.
But the Chunin exam requires three
people together in the team to take.
You couldn't say no to your teammates Kiba.
The truth is you are taking this
exam even though you don't want to.
Am I wrong?
You're wrong! That's wrong...
I... I just wanted to...
...wanted to change myself from what
you just described. I voluntarily...
Hinata...
Stand up, Hanabi.
Hinata will start working under my supervision...
But, is it really ok for you?
Isn't Hinata the heir to the Huyga clan?
The missions done by Genin always are close to death.
Do whatever you like!
This failure, who is inferior to the 5-year younger Hanabi...
is not wanted in this Hyuga clan!
If you've finished your business, please leave now.
You're disturbing us.
Hinata is trying to change herself in her own way...
Hinata-sama... You're surely just
a overprotected brat from Souke.
It's never possible for a person to change!
A looser is always a looser...
Your character and power will never change!
That guy...!
Because a person can never change, they are born as they are...
...terms like elite and looser are created.
Everybody judges others by how good the person's
face, brain, skills, body structures, and character..
and will always be judged by these.
These are unchangeable factors...
People struggle and live with these factors in their own way.
Just like we can't change the fact
that you're from Souke and I'm from Bunke.
I've seen through so many things with my Byakudan...
That's why I know!
You're pretending to be strong...
Your real desire is to run away from here immediately.
No! You're wrong! I really want to...!
Byakudan?
It's said that Uchiha clan's origin
can traced back to the Hyuga clan.
The Byakugan is one of the traits that
the Hyuga clan has passed down.
It's the special-eye similar to Sharingan.
But if you talk only about the power to see through
things, it's much more powerful than Sharingan.
Byakugan!
Hyuga Hinata VS Hyuga Neji
You can't fool my eyes!
Just now, your eye went to upper-left due to my will.
This is the sign that you're recalling
your past... your unpleasant past!
And your eyes moved down to lower right immediately after that.
That is the sign that you're
imagining physical and mental pains.
Your loss, that's what you imagined!
The reaction that you put your arms in front of your body...
...shows that you want to create a wall
and want to have some distance between me.
These movements you make tells me that you don't
want me to dig into your real thoughts anymore...
Because all that I've said was all true!
Furthermore...
Your finger touching your lips is one
way to show that you're relentless.
It's an instinct to protect yourself, trying
to soften the tension and stress.
In fact, aren't you aware about this?
Changing yourself can NEVER...
...be done! Can be DONE!
Don't decide what the other person is, dumbass!
Beat this guy up, Hinata!
Hinata! Say something back to him a little!
It makes ME agitated!
That's a noisy guy...
Naruto-kun... Thank you.
Her eyes changed.
So, you won't forfeit? I'm not
responsible what'll happen to you.
I...
I won't run away!
...never again...
I will never bend my words. That's my Ninja way!
Don't want to run away!
Byakugan!
Neji-brother...
Let's fight!
Ah... that is...
OK
As I thought... the same Hyuga style
Her stance is exactly same as Neji's
Hyuga style?
The Konoha's strongest Taijutsu style ...
Didn't I tell you before...
that the most strongest Genin in Konoha is in my team.
That guy is ... Hyuga Neji!
HERE!
She got him!
No. It's too soft!
No. It's enough to just blush.
That's why the Hyuga clan is called the strongest in Konoha.
What do you mean?
The Hyuga has its own special Taijutsu that's been passed down.
The Taijutsu that I and Lee specialize in...
is breaking opponents bones and
injuring them from outside by attacking.
It's called Goken (Iron fist).  On the other hand...
the Hyuga gives internal damages
to the channel that Chakura flows...
and destroy from the inside.
They are the clan to use the Soft-hand.
It's not flashy to watch, but it
will get you little by little later.
Well... nobody can train their organs.
Even a strongest guy will be at the
risk with one hit of the Soft-hand.
Even I can ...
Hinata's in advantage!
You're doing Great! Hinata!
Attacking the inner channel?
What are those people?
Hey, hey... Ah.. What is the Chakura channel?
Again? Another question from the stupid one...
I will explain.
The Chakura channel is like pipes that carries Chakura
to everywhere in one's body, just like blood vessels.
Ah.. it's like a Chakura highway.
Yes. Plus, those channels are closely wrapping
the inner organs that build up the Chakura.
So, if the channels are attacked, those
inner organs also get damaged.
Oh, you've got some smarts!
Hey! Don't talk like that to your sempai(older person)!
Understandable...
The biggest opponent to Lee is... that boy.
Sensei, why can they do such a thing?
The Chakura channel can't be visible to eyes...
How do they attack the Chakura channel within one's body?
No. With the eyes of those two...
the channels can be seen by using the Byakugan.
Also, the Soft-hand attack is a
bit different from the regular ones.
They release their own Chakura from the hole in their hand...
and make it flow into the other's body which gives
the damage directly to the opponent’s chakura channel.
Alright!
Did she do it?