http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Who you being creeds!
The decisive battle to the bridge!
The arrival of Zabuza!
Good day…
Here you take.
Thanks.
Naruto is not returned this night?
That idiot is remained to climb
trees alone all the night.
It will be died in order to have too much used Chakra.
It will be Naruto-kun well?
A child who remains
outside all the night…
Not there is of that preoccuparsi.
Even if it does not seem is also always a ninja.
Goodness knows.
Even that idiot…
… he is died truly.
Sasuke-kun?
I make two steps.
For ò  we are in order to eat.
That speed.
You will take a cold if you sleep here.
Who six?
Ah…
Me have waked up you!?
And what you make us from these you leave?
I collect grass.
Grass?
Exact one.
They are in order to cure wounded and diseases.
Jobs cos ì  hardly of first mattino.
Also you what made here cos ì  soon?
A training!
From the coprifronte six would be said that…
… ninja or a something of the sort?
I am similar to us? I seem?
Exact, they are a ninja!
Wow, then six fort!
And because you are training yourself?
I want to become stronger.
For ò  he seems already enough strong.
Not! Not enough.
I want to become still more fort.
In order which reason?
For being ninja the number
one of my village.
I want that all recognize my force.
Moreover, I must demonstrate one
what to one sure person.
You make all this for someone…
… or for same you?
Ah?
What is of amusing?
You have someone a lot important?
Important…
Where you want to arrive?
(Than it takes to it)
A person becomes truly strong…
… only when she wants protect
something of important.
Your papà loves the city where six been born.
Not lascer ò  never that
my companions die.
You will not put a finger on Iruka-sensei.
Or morirai!
On this, they are daccordissimo.
You will become very strong.
!
I hope to still meet to you.
Ah…
… know that I am a male.
(pu ò  not to be!)
(E' also prettier than Sakura-chan!)
How much is strange…
… the world.
Indeed full E' of mysteries.
What you are making?
Stupid, six forgotten to you
what is hour of breakfast?
Naruto.
What will be making Naruto?
Sasuke-kun has said that it went
to make a walk and it is disappeared.
It is not possible!
Naruto is successful to arrive up cos  ??
Incredible!
That you say some?
Hour they are able to arrive end up here.
Stupid!
(If he falls from l ì…!)
Scherzetto.
I have fregato to you!
You have scared to me!
Stupid!
After I kill it!
Cursed idiot!
It seems is a po' improved.
Naruto, idiot!
Here that it happens to make the braggart!
The stupid usual.
Sasuke…
Cos ì  fà Sasuke-kun!
Six fantastic one!
(These boys are improve a lot to you.)
Uzumaki…
… Naruto…
You have recovered good part of the force.
Well!
Joined E' the moment, Haku!
Of agreement.
We return to house?
Yeah!
They are being late.
I understand Naruto, but also Sasuke-kun…
That it has happened to you for being
cos ì  destroyed and it soil?
We are arrives to you in top to the tree.
Ok.
Naruto, Sasuke…
… from proteggerete tomorrow Tazusa-saint.
Of agreement!
The idiot usual.
Thanks to you the bridge…
… nearly it is finished.
For ò  you not to excite a lot.
E' for a long time that I want to ask one to you what.
Why continued to remain here even if…
… I have mentito on the content of the mission?
"not to make the thing just, when you know that this
it is the road of the codardi."
"Not being is soldier weak person who pu  ?
a good commander "
Eh?
They are the instructions of the fourth Hokage.
You must protect us ò  that it considers
important with both the arms.
Not to cry, Inari.
Because…
What?
Because you efforts a lot!
Also training to you you will not have
possibility against the men of Gatoo!
It does not import how much you efforts…
… how many heroic words you say some.
The weak people will always lose against strongest!
Taci!
I am various from you.
You taci!
You still more make me to anger!
You do not know null of this country,
six solo a impiccione!
What pu ò  to know some of me…
… one that laughs all the time…
..e it does not have idea of what is the suffering.
E' for that you expect of being…
… the protagonist of the tragedy
and to always cry?
An idiot like you pu ò
to only continue to cry!
Six solo a piagnucolone!
Naruto!
You have exaggerated.
Naruto…
It goes you to speak?
Naruto has not said to you
those things with badness.
E' a testone.
Tazuna-saint it has spoken to us about your father.
Naruto like you and without father from birth.
Currently it does not know who were its parents.
Neanche it has not never had a friend.
However, I have not never seen it
to make the scontroso or to cry.
It tries constantly…
… to earn the respect of the others.
And always he has been able to lead
its life towards its dream.
Sure it is tired to cry.
E' for that it knows what means
to be strong, just as your father.
Naruto is what it understands to you better.
Sure first Naruto…
… it has tried to dirti this.
That it also it has repeated
to if same many times.
Please, it is taken care of Naruto.
Spremuto its body to the maximum.
Task that in order today will not succeed to move.
Kakashi-saint, hour you feel yourself better?
, more or less.
On we go!
What you are making?
Six ready one for the onslaught?
Hey, Zabuza, you are listening to me?
Hey!
We go, Haku.
.
I have slept too much!
Hey, where has gone all?
Oh, Naruto-kun.
The master has said that you must
to rest all the day.
I knew!
If they have gone some without of me!
Good bye!
Maledizione, had to wait for to me!
?
Co… what has happened!?
What happens? Who has been?
(pu ò  not to be…)
Inari, you come to help me!
Inari!
Sbrigati…
(This fog…)
Sasuke, Sakura…
It is arriving!
(still alive E'.)
(And eccolo here.)
Master Kakashi…
This is the technique of the fog veil, true?
Me dispiace to have made to you to wait for, Kakashi.
And it continues to carry those mocciosi.
It is shaking of new, than painful.
E' why they are excited.
Vai pure, Sasuke.
(I can see them!)
Successful E' to defeat the cloni of water.
This boy has become much fort.
You have avails again, Haku.
It seems just of s ì.
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
Just in time. There is lacked little.
I was in order to arrive late.
For ò  very made, Inari.
Six successful one to save your mother, why
you have shown your value.
It waits for, if they have attacked here…
He means that also master Kakashi is in danger!?
The technical master of Haku.
The ice mirrors.
Avr ò  one great part this time!