http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I have used too much the sharingan, eh?
It goes all good, Sensei?
Insomma. Potr ˜  not to move me for
one week approximately.
It would have to still remain to bed for a po'.
S “.
Oh! Wide awake Sensei six!
AccidentsÉ
É sure that the Sharingan is much powerful oneÉ
É but if it makes this effect you..
É better to think two times to us before using it!
You excuse to meÉ
It compliments, you have defeated
those ninja cos “  strongly.
Cos “  at least for hour we will be calm!
Goodness knowsÉ
É who was that masked boy?
He wore the mask
of the Anbu of the FogÉ
É special murderous troops.
Special troops?
They are known also with
the name of "eliminatori of corpses".
They have the task to cancel every
trace of the existence of those ninja.
The body of a ninja encloses the characteristicsÉ
É of the chakra, of the substances of which one used....
É and the secrets of the magical limbs
formed in its village.
As an example, in the case I diedÉ
É all the secrets of
characteristics of the sharinganÉ
É they would come examines to youÉ
É and in worse of the cases the that one
technique would pass to the enemy.
For this ninja the hunters eliminate corpses
of the ninja traitor after to have them murdered.
They are of the specialistsÉ
É that they prevent the spillage of powers
of just the village hiding them to the strangers.
Per.primo.cosa cut the bende
_ on the the mouth facendogli sputare the blood.
Lascia. I make alone.
Oh! Already you have resumed yourselves?
How much sixÉ irruento.
You would not have to remove them with that violenceÉ
É otherwise morirete truly.
For how much time still you will carry
that stupid mask?
You remove it!
By now they are accustomed to us.
The use often in order to trick.
If you had not saved to youÉ
É they would sure have killed you.
In order to put to me in letargoÉ
É not there was need to aim at the neck.
Unpleasant like always.
I admit.
E' that I did not want to sfregiare
your beautiful body.
Moreover, being to us on the neck little musclesÉ
É l “  it is easier to hit
one tsubo with precision.
You would not have to succeed to move
in order at least one week.
But they are sure that you will succeedÉ
É to return in forces in men that it is not said.
Six cosi pure and sincereÉ
E' for that you appeal to to me.
Why they are still a child.
The fog is passing.
Ce you will make itÉ the next time?
S “.
The next time to succeed ˜  in
to answer to the Sharingan.
The forest of the Chakra
What happens to me?
Zabuza is diedÉ
É but pursued me this indefinite anxiety.
I have likeÉ
É the feeling is not to me
shrewed of something of important.
That it succeeds SenseiÉ
Then, you listen to me!
The eliminatori of corpsesÉ
É they are taken care directly on the place
of the corpse of R-he who they have killed.
And therefore?
You have seen that child as he has
arranged the corpse of Zabuza?
And that I know some!
If it is carried it via.
Exactly.
If it were for having the test to have it murderedÉ
É he would have been sufficient
to carry of via solo the head.
An other problem is the arm
that it has used in order to kill it.
Only of the needles.
It is not possible!
And insteadÉ
É unfortunately.
But of that devil been speaking!
Of the fact thatÉ
É probably Zabuza is still alive!
But that it wants to say!
Kakashi Sensei, you have controlled
that he was dead man, not!
S “, I have controlledÉ
É evidentlyÉ
É its was one died appearing.
The needle that has used the ninja-hunter
it comes called "senbon"É
And less than it does not hit the vital organsÉ
É it is an arm from the low potentialities omicide.
Moreover medical instrument is also one
used for the acupuncture.
Ninja the hunters have one deep
acquaintance of the human body.
To carry one person in letargo
he is easy what for they.
First oneÉ
É that boy has carried itself via the body
of Zabuza, than hung much more than heÉ
SecondÉ
É it has used of the needles that are one
little effective arm in order to kill.
These two factsÉ
É they make to think that the boy
Zabuza did not want to killÉ
É but to help it.
You will not be running with the fantasy?
Not.
When you perceive somethingÉ
É you must yourself be prepared before that it is too much late.
Also this and a rule of the shinobi.
E' happy for knowing that Zabuza
probably it is alive.
SenseiÉ
É as we prepare ourselves
before that it is too much late?
It for a po' will not succeed to move.
To give ?  a training to you to make.
Aspects a moment!
A training? but to that it will serve to train to us now?
The adversary is a ninja against which same you
you have faticato also using the Sharingan!
Vera Sakura
You are trying to kill to us!
* Sandaroooo!!
* (it burns to hell!)
SakuraÉ
É you have been to save to me
from that difficult situation.
Been all making of the expresses progresses.
Especially Naruto!
You are improving more than all.
Now that us task, seems more strongly than before.
Finally you have noticed it, Kakashi Sensei!
Me beginning to amuse!
To amuse? Not creed.
And you who six!
Oh, Inari!
dov' you were ended!
Very returned, grandfather!
Inari, greets them well in order!
They are the ninja that they have accompanied the grandfather.
All Inari good goes, ago nothing!
MotherÉ they will moriranno.
Not there is possibility to win against Gatoo.
Moccioso cursed what!
Hey, listens to me well!
I am a ninja cos “  strongly that in future
diventer ˜  the called superhero Hokage!!
M' he does not import not to know who is Gatoo.
Of sure he is not to my height!
Hero? Six stupid?
The heroes do not exist!
What!?
Stopped!
If you do not want to dieÉ
É it is better than ve you go some.
Where you go Inari?
To admire the sea from my room.
Me dispiace.
Eternal damnation!
Dov' has gone that idiot!
Gliela to make ˜  to pay.
It is crying!
PapˆÉ
Well!
Now we begin the training.
S “, getlteman!
But beforeÉ
É you parler ˜  of the Chakra,
a power that has all the ninja.
just now?
Excused but that cos' it is I am catra?
The Chakra!!
I pray, Sakura-Kun.
Then, Naruto!
You the spiegher ˜  in simple way.
* coil: The beautifulst girl ninja Sakura!
Lesson of Chakra.
The chakra it is the necessary energy to one shinobi
in order to carry out one technical.
This composed energy and from two elements:
the accumulated corporea energy from ciascuna
of the million present cells in the bodyÉ
É and the developed spiritual energy
through training and several experiences.
In practicalÉ
É with the techniques they are pulled outside from the bodyÉ
É these two energies adding themÉ
É to the magical position of the hands.
Exactly.
Iruka Sensei has had an optimal student.
But that me it imports some!
I do not understand the complicated explanations cos  ?.
To me enough to learn with the body!
Naruto has reason.
We already know to use the techniques.
Not.
Still not succeeded to maneuver the chakra.
What!
AscoltateÉ
As Sakura has said before,
in order to paste the chakraÉ
É it is necessary to take the energy corporea
and that spiritual and miscelarle within the body.
spiritual energy  corporea energy
Obviously to second of the used techniqueÉ
= > earth water fire lightning vento< =
É the amount of the necessary energy changes.
You are not able of
to control it with effectiveness!
Even if succeeded to paste one
large amount of ChakraÉ
É you are not able to control it wellÉ
É to second of the technique
of halved the power.
And inasmuch as wasted the energyÉ
É not succeeded to fight to along.
Then what we would have to make?
Learned to control it with the body.
Draft of the hardest training
that you must exceed at all costs.
And in that it consists?
To scramble up on the trees!
Just.
You do not have simply
to scramble up to you on the trees....
É you must scramble up without to use the hands.
And like?
Been to see.
One is scrambling upÉ
only using the legs.
More or less cos “!
The chakra is accumulateed on the plant of the feetÉ
É and they are made to join the tree.
Using the chakra well
they make also things of the sort.
It waits for a moment!
As we make to become stronger
learning to scramble up to us on the trees!
E' this the point.
The main objective of this training isÉ
É to learn to concentrate the correct amount
of chakra in a determined point.
Spiritual energy  Corporea Energy
Difficult E' also for a ninja expert.
The amount of chakra necessary in order to scramble up
on a tree it is small, but it must be precise.
Moreover it is much difficult to accumulate
the chakra on the plant of the feet.
É if padroneggia the control of the chakra,
pu ˜  to use any technique.
At least in theory!
According to objective of this training
it is to increase the abilities to maintain the chakra.
A ninja it pastes the chakra
continuously during a battle.
In this situation the control and the maintenance
of the chakra they are complicated ulteriorly.
It does not have sense to continue to speak.
You must learn directly with your body.
Used these kunai in order to make a sign on the log
in the point in which succeeded to arrive.
Later on you put yourselves in head to record
an other sign to one advanced height.
You are not still in a position to going up walkingÉ
É therefore tried to help you running
and taking the run-up.
Ready?
for me this training
and a childs' play!
To end ˜  before breakfast!
Inasmuch as they are the more promising!
Six boasted to you enoughÉ
Force! Tried to scramble up to you
on a tree whichever.
Okay, per.primo.cosa paste
the chakra in my feet.
Part!!
We go!
I did not think was cos “  difficult to maintain
one sure amount of chakra.
If there is too much chakra, comes pushed viaÉ
É but to the contrary if ce n' it is too much little
you do not succeed to remain attacked to the log.
GoodÉ
É it was expectable that between Naruto
and Sasuke was this difference.
It is not then cos “  difficult!
SÉ Sakura-chan!
It seems that that one is Sakura that succeeds betterÉ
É to control the chakra.
Wow six great Sakura!
I knew that you were one promising girl!
Even if this me innervosisce....
Accidents!
And I that I wanted to receive
it compliments from Sasuke-kun.
Why it ends always cos “?
For ˜! You possess great acquaintances
theoretical of the chakraÉ
É and it even boasts a good ones
control and one good resistance.
All consideringÉ
É it seems that that one is Sakura that one
that it is approached the Hokage moreÉ
É with the exception of others.
Unexpectedly also the Uchiha clan
it is not nothing of special.
You stop It Sensei!
Otherwise Sasuke will take to me in aversion!
But in spite of everything it is Naruto that SasukeÉ
É amounts of chakra possess one
incomparable with that one of Sakura.
If this training will give bonds it yieldsÉ
É usciranno some strongest.
Okay!
Per.primo.cosa I must catch up Sasuke!
I swear that ce making ˜!
A lot is all useless!
You six state even defeated.
It seems that the ninja of the fog
they are just of the bonds to null.
As they make to call devil to you if you do not succeed
neanche to revenge your subordinates?
You make me to laugh.
They will attack?
Aspettate.
Hey!
Me it does not seem the case of startene in Hush.
You do not say nothing?
Not to touch Zabuza-saint
with yours luride hands!
As it dares!!!
But likeÉ
É and mosso..in a momentÉ
You council to stop it.
They are much angry one!
the next time!
If you will fail of new, you put in head that
not there will be more place for you.
Haku, I know alone cavarmela.
I know.
ButÉ
É it is too much soon in order to kill Gatoo.
Creating disorderÉ
É we would have to scappare of new.
We must carry patience, for hour.
You have reason.
Those two have one crazy resistance.
For ˜  Naruto a po' is not improved neanche.
Probably soon
it will stew and begin to complain itself.
Maledizione!
I knew!
Expectable E' cos  ?É
Hey, hey?
Qual' is your secret?
But not to say it to Sasuke, we go!
He becomes more and more strong.
I ask only which are its limits.
Why NarutoÉ
É latent amount of chakra has one
advanced to that one of SasukeÉ
É andÉ
É also to mine.
I do not see the hour that
monster all its force.
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears