Much time makes existed
a demon vixen with nine tails.
When they oscillated, they could destroy
one mountain and to raise one "tsunami".
In order to contrast it, the persons
they called the ninja.
Blocchiamolo here until
the fourth Hokage does not arrive!
Lasciamolo not to approach cos ì
to our village
Ninja sigill ò  a monster in a life battle
and of dead women, in order then to perish same he.
This ninja was known like the fourth Hokage.
Ehi, Naruto!
What you have made?
You will pay!!
Zitti!!
You could not never have made it, just?
But I can! I am the best one!
Third party, we have one emergency.
Hokage-sama!
That there is? Naruto of it has arranged an other of its?
, it has made something to the dedicated faces the Hokage.
It has disfigured!
Stopped!
Too much easy.
Ehi, Naruto!
From where sbuchi cos ì  to the unexpected one, Iruka-sensei?
What you have made during the lesson?
It listens to Naruto, six state to me bocciato to the last examination
and also to that before.
You would not have to make these sciocchezze.
Now we will rifare the test on
Technique of the Transformation!
In row! Also those that have already passed it!
What!
Haruno ready Sakura!
Transformation!
Much good.
Ce I have made it!
Evvai!
You have seen, Sasuke-kun?
The next one, Uchiha Sasuke.
S ì.
Much good.
The next one, Uzumaki Naruto.
The poppante.
E' all guilt yours.
That it imports to me.
Naruto-kun, you make of your best.
Com' is this?
I call it the Technique of the Erotismo.
Idiot! Not to invent stupid techniques cos  ?!
Eternal damnation, eternal damnation.
You will not return to house until
you will not have cleaned up all in order well.
That it imports to me, a lot to house
not there is nobody that me aspects.
Naruto…
What is now?
Be', not, nothing…
If you end in a hurry,
to offer ? one  cup to you of ramen this evening.
Ok, to make ò  of my best!
#01 - It arrives
Uzumaki Naruto!
Naruto…
Why you have soiled those statues?
You know who to it you are the Hokage, true?
Sure that I know it!
In practical they take to the title it of Hokage
the best ones ninja of the village.
In particular, the fourth Hokage is said that
he is the hero who has protect the village from the demon vixen.
Then because you have made it?
A day also I sar ò  a Hokage and superer ò  in force
all the Hokage that never have been.
Then verr ò  here to the village,
so that all can recognize my power.
However, sensei, I would have a favor to ask to you.
You want an other plate?
Uhm..No! I would want to try
the Coprifronte of the Leaf
Oh, this?
Not.
This is a test of your degree,
and it indicates that a six true one ninja.
You will have tomorrow your.
Unpleasant!
E' for that you do not carry yours glances at them?
I want an other plate!
Now we will begin the final examination.
If chiamer ò  your name, you raise yourselves and gone in the class I place side by side.
It will be on the technique of the MULTIPLICATION of the body.
Oh, NOT! E' the tecnica..che..mi succeeds worse…
For ò  I must make it us!
Technique of the Multiplication.
Bocciato!
Iruka-sensei, its movements and the resistance are good,
and more or less copy has created one…
..forse you could make to pass it.
Mizuki-sensei, all are in degree
to create three cloni at least.
But Naruto sdoppia only,
without to count that the copy is only an obstacle.
I cannot make to pass it.
They are true ninja a now true one?
Beautiful job! It was what I expected from my son
Congratulations for your promotion.
The mother will cook you something of bond this evening in order
Ehi, that boy is the only one who has failed.
The lesson servant.
If it will become a ninja he will be able to only create problems.
Because in truth he is…
Ehi, you know it that it is forbidden to speak of!
Iruka…
Necessary E' that it speaks to you after.
.
Iruka-sensei ce does not have it with you.
But then… because always I?
In truth it wants that you become strong indeed, Naruto-Kun.
You as he you do not have the parents.
Pear tree…
I want "to graduate myself".
Well, I have then not chosen…
What?
To say ?  a great secret to you.
A secret?
Iruka…
It reports, Hokage-sama?
I understand as you feel yourself, but Naruto has grown
without to know the love of its parents, like you.
It leaves me to go!
My father and my mother are still fighting!
Iruka-sensei, raises to you!
What is?
For it appeal to you come endured to the palace of Hokage-sama.
It seems that Naruto has
stolen the forbidden parchment.
Thing.! The forbidden parchment?
We see a po', the first technique is…
Multiple shadows replying.
What?
My technique worse!
Hokage-sama, we cannot consider
this fact like one monellata!
The forbidden parchment that the first Hokage sigill ò  is much dangerous one.
If used in mistaken way, it pu ò…
If it will carry it outside from the village,
it will become a beautiful problem!
Portatemi here Naruto.
.
Where six hunted to you, Naruto?
After to have scattered the voice in the village,
to kill ò  Naruto…
Cos ì… the forbidden parchment will be mine!
Ehi, Naruto.
Oh, already has been captured.
I have learned one single technique.
One has practiced here…
until it has been reduced cos ì?
Ehi, you monster one greatest technique,
therefore you promote to me if I succeed to execute it!
If you monster one technical from this parchment,
potr ò  to give a degree to to me, just?
Who has said this to you?
Mizuki-sensei.
It has said to me of this place and the parchment.
Mizuki has made this!
It is strange to me that you have to us
found in this place.
Hour I understand as they are the things.
Naruto, gives the parchment to me.
Ehi, what is happening here?
Naruto, not dargli the parchment,
any thing happens.
That one is one dangerous parchment,
it contains forbidden techniques.
Mizuki has used to you in order to get hold of!
Naruto, Iruka has fear because
six you to having the parchment.
What?
What you are saying, Mizuki!?
Not credergli, Naruto.
To say ?  the truth to you.
Not to make it!
After an incident that 12 years succeeded ago
a rule was established.
A rule?
A rule that only you,
Naruto, you did not have to know.
Only I?
Qual' is this rule?
Stopped, Mizuki!
The rule that it prohibits to say that YOU,
in truth, the six Vixen to Nine Tails.
What?
In other words, in you it lives
the spirit of the Demon Vixen to nine tails…
… that killed the parents of Iruka
and he destroyed our village!
Stopped!
Six state deceived from the persons
of the village the entire time.
Not tasks that are bizzarro
that all hate you cos ì  a lot?
Eternal damnation…!
Eternal damnation! Eternal damnation!
Eternal damnation!
Naruto…
Nobody will never accept to you!
Iruka has always hated you!
Iruka, Naruto has grown without to try the love of i
parents and will be hated because of the incident.
Cos ì, it makes all these dispetti for
to attract the attention of the persons.
He does not import like. It wants that someone
he recognizes the value of its existence.
Even if ago the hard one,
Continuous Naruto to suffer a lot.
You die, Naruto!
Naruto!
P-because…
Because six like me.
After that my parents died,
nobody never made me compliments or it spurred to me.
I made always things stupid,
during the lessons…
..solo in order to attract the attention of the companions.
Nobody would have noticed to me
if pits involved to me well.
Cos ì  to the fine all thought
that I was only an idiot.
E' be hard…
You understand, Naruto?
You were alone!
Hard, true E' be?
Me dispiace, Naruto.
It pardons To Me, Naruto. If you pits be
more neighbor you would not have suffered cos ì  a lot.
It does not make me to laugh! Iruka has always hated you
because you have killed it the parents.
It wants to only have the parchment.
Naruto!
Naruto!!
Naruto will not never change!
It will go to take its vendetta
to the village with that parchment.
You have seen its eyes, true?
The eyes of a demon.
Naruto is not like tasks you.
It will be enough to me to kill Naruto
and to recover the parchment.
Me occuper ò  after you.
You lascer ò  not to go…
It does not go well.
Mizuki has said to it of the secret.
Naruto now is cos ì  unstable.
It could free the power
that it it has been sealed.
It has also the forbidden parchment.
The possibilities that it is transformed in the vixen to nine
tails are low… but I must consider the eventuality.
If ? it will happen  to us…
Naruto!
Those that have said to you before
Mizuki was of the menzogne!
The parchment passes to me! Mizuki aimed at that one!
C-thing…
How… Naruto?
Like…
How you have understood that I was not Iruka?
Why they are I Iruka.
I see.
What is of bond in the protect
who has killed your parents?
Not lascer ò  that an idiot like you
he takes the parchment.
Six you idiot it,
Naruto is such and which to me.
Equal to you?
You can make us ò  that you want
thanks to the techniques in the parchment.
E' clearly that that demon
it will use the techniques to its favor!
You have reason.
I knew.
Iruka-sensei does not succeed to accept to me.
! The vixen to nine tails would make it.
but of sure not Naruto.
Why Naruto…
it is one of my better students.
Determined and sincere E', but for its
goffaggine never does not come praised from nobody.
By now it knows well the suffering
of the human mind.
It is not more the demon vixen.
It is only Uzumaki Naruto
of the Village of the Leaf!
That stupid.
Iruka, I had said to you that I would have killed to you after,
but I must myself be ricredere.
You die now!
This is the end…
Naruto!
You will not touch not even with a Iruka-sensei finger.
If us tests to kill to you ò.
Che sbruffone! It will be a game give
boys to kill a child like you.
He tries to us bastard. To make you ò  to try thousands
times the pain that you have provoked.
Because to not tests if you want us, demon vixen!
Multiplication of the body!
Naruto…
You have used the Multiplication of the Body?
E' one technical complex where
it is succeeded to create real bodies.
Thing…
Qual' is the problem?
Ahead.
If you do not come…
We will come!
Perhaps I have hit it too many times.
Iruka-sensei, You are well?
…
That boy… could truly
to exceed all previous the Hokage…
Naruto, you come a second here.
I want give to you one what.
Someone has found Naruto?
Not.
Malezione, does not go well for nothing!
Not there is need of preoccuparsi oltremodo.
Hokage-sama!
It will come soon to house.
Sensei, I can open them hour?
Much good, you open the eyes.
It compliments for your diploma.
Ok, we go to celebrate.
To offer to you ò  of the ramen.
Iruka-sensei!
Ouch! You make me badly!
I would want to say to Naruto that the true difficulties
of the being a ninja they begin just hour.
..ma..aspetter ò  of to have arrived to
Kiosk of the Ramen for fargli foretells it.