I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long way to go
on that road.
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star lit sky with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that...
What were you gazing at?
Hmm, what?
A wanted flyer.
"This man who calls himself
Tokichi is a major criminal
who has killed a family of three..."
"He has a bird shaped birthmark
on his chest."
A bird shaped birthmark...?
It couldn't be...
What is it, Hinata?
I can't tell because
his face is covered with scars.
But he has... a bird -shaped birthmark!
He has a bounty on his head too?
What the heck is going on
with everything?
Hunt or Be Hunted?!
Showdown at the OK Temple
Where are you going, old man?
Just rest quietly.
Let go!
Stay out of my way! Gosunkugi is mine...
What the heck can you do in that condition,
you wanted man?!
A bounty hunter who was
in the bar attacked last night...
What's the idea of a bounty
chasing after a bounty?
It's none of your concern!
Your wound again...
Stop!
D-Don't move!
I didn't do it...
Then, how do you explain
this wanted flyer?
That Gosunkugi did it...
He killed an innocent family
of three...
just to steal money.
What do you mean by that?
I was a swordsmith in a tiny village...
in a small country sandwiched
between two large countries.
I was poor,
but for me it was a happy life.
But on that festival day...
I was about to go deliver a sword
that a customer had ordered.
I wanted to participate in the festival
right away, so I was hurrying.
At that very moment...
For some reason,
the door was half open.
It's Tokichi...
I'm delivering the sword you ordered...
I told everyone everything
as it happened.
But... the people in the village
wouldn't believe me.
It's because I was the only one
who hadn't shown up at the festival.
And the particular shape of the sword
that stabbed through the family...
A swordsmith should be able
to make any kind of weapon...
That was the reason.
Stand up, Tokichi!
Tokichi!
Don't let him get away! After him!
And ever since...
I wandered aimlessly from town to town.
BOUNTY
One million ryo
It was something
the villagers had issued.
And there was one more
wanted flyer besides mine...
BOUNTY
Threee million yen
...of the man who killed the family.
I resolved to capture Gosunkugi
with my own hands.
I would clear my name and
return to my village...
And... to get some information about him,
if even just a little...
I became a bounty hunter despite
having a price on my own head.
So that's why we were in the way, huh?
The only way to prove my innocence
is for me to capture him myself.
I want to go home.
Will you... concede him to me?
We're Ninja.
We carry out missions we've received,
no matter what!
Even if the worst were to happen,
we can't let him get away.
Let's go...
Was that okay, Naruto?
That Gosunkugi jerk!
We have to capture him,
no matter what.
That's right.
And if that old man, Sazanami,
pushes it too far in his condition,
not only will he fail in capturing Gosunkugi,
he could end up getting killed instead.
Don't hold back.
I'll give you...
the likes of my head.
You're wounded,
so I can kill you whenever I want.
Before that, I'll be taking Gosunkugi.
Well, I guess I'll just have
those Shinobi kids do their best.
The Land of Stone,
Post Station Two...
It seems everything in this town...
politics, economics, military,
is conducted by monks.
It really is. Nothing but temples...
The temple, which could be
called the head temple,
is the OK Temple on that mountain.
Hey, Hinata. What's that bell?
That was created as
the sightseeing crown jewel
to recruit people to live in their temple...
The Golden Bell!
It's just like it is saying,
"Please steal me."
I know...
Gosunkugi is after that bell!
- Yeah.
But how does that Gosunkugi guy
intend to steal that bell?
Naruto!
Huh?
You guys... are Gosunkugi's...!
Are these guys going to corral us?!
Just like the time with Sazanami...
Byakugan.
Look out! Run!
Old Man Sazanami?!
Leave this to me!
All right!
Eat this!
What're you doing here...?
I just came to settle the score.
But... your wound is still...
I won't get in your way.
I'll pursue the target on my own.
This is a competition!
I guess it can't be helped.
I accept!
But we can't even start
as things stand now!
There are still nails in the ground...
He's waiting for the best moment.
Gosunkugi!
The bell... is at the top!
What...?! Could it be...?!
Oh, no...!
The nails in the ground aren't moving.
The Jutsu has worn off!
What?!
Damn it! When did he...?!
So as the words say,
we've been "nailed down," huh?
They're by the bell!
Why that!
Wait! Don't forget the bounty hunter
from last night is also after Gosunkugi!
No problem...! We'll get there first,
no matter what!
Let's go!
How awful...
That Gosunkugi jerk...!
Unforgivable!
Hey! Where's Gosunkugi?!
Naruto! He'll get away if we're too slow!
We don't have any time to think.
Let's take care of this in one shot!
Gentle Fist!
Akamaru!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry...
Man Beast Clone!
Fang Over Fang!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
U zu ma ki
Naruto Barrage!
Here I go...
I hit you with the back of the sword...
Where's Gosunkugi?
That way!
Gosunkugi!
He's ours!
Old man, you're going to prove
your innocence, right?!
If you're a bounty hunter,
then show your pride!
Ninja Art. Flying Nail Mist!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Eat this!
Too slow!
Farewell!
Damn it...!
It's not over yet!
What?!
Prepare yourself!
W Wait!
Don't be hasty...
If I kill you, the one who can prove
my innocence will be gone!
We lose...
That's right...
What?!
Bounty Sazanami,
otherwise known as Tokichi...
I, Gatsu, have apprehended you!
And you, bounty Gosunkugi!
Your spree of evil deeds...
The number of charges
against you is incalculable...
A government official has ordered
you hauled in for questioning!
Old man...
Damn it. There's nothing we can do
if the opposition is a bureaucrat...
You murderer!
Give back the family you killed!
We'll kill you in the same way!
Damn it...!
Hey, hey, you guys!
You've got nerve to put up wanted flyers
without doing a decent investigation!
This man is the true culprit behind
the murder that occurred in this village!
This Gosunkugi has already been
apprehended and has confessed.
And the weapon has been seized...
Therefore this individual Tokichi
shall be acquitted!
You jerks!
You made me work for free!
What're you going to do about it?!
Why'd you do that for me?
I overheard some stupid tale
of woe, you see.
It makes no difference
to a bounty hunter...
But I overheard it,
and so I had no choice.
It was necessary to verify whether
or not you really are a wanted man...
You...
Not "you. Gatsu!
I'm also a bounty hunter...
I'm in the same trade as you!
Gatsu...
Tokichi... We're sorry.
Forgive us, Tokichi.
Good for you... Old Man Sazanami.
Let's go.
I've kind of gotten homesick and
really miss the Leaf Village...
But you know, a failed mission
means failure...
The Fifth Hokage's going
to scold you good, Naruto.
What?!
You failed another mission?!
I... don't want to go home...
So many things happen
on this endless road, huh?
Although you're strong willed,
your voice wavered on the phone today
What dreams did you chase to get here?
Even I have times when
I just don't understand, baby
When you're sad, I'll be close to you
Even on nights when we're apart,
I'll be close to you
Creeping up noisily,
a round, fat guy and a skinny one!
Beneath the scorching rain,
a disastrous tranquility ensues.
Tsunade hits the jackpot!
Kakashi's guess is a huge bust!
Heard it somewhere,
this unprecented event!
The great acts of
Monday and Pocha!
Then comes Naruto...
Let me join in
the training too!
Next time:
"The Appearance of Strange Visitors"