That driven in fog!
It is not succeeded to see nothing.
Hour we would have to begin to notice the bridge.
Costeggiando the bridge we will arrive
to the Country of the Waves.
Enormous E'!!!
_ Ehi, not urlare!
We are hiding in means to the fog.
We also proceed to extinguished motor.
If they discover to us it will go to end badly.
Tazuna-saint one…
Before that the boat you berth, what is one
that I must ask them.
Who is the persons who want died it
and qual' it is the reason?
Otherwise we consider the finished mission,
Tazuna-saint.
The Assassin of the Fog!
E' hour that you storys all the truth.
In practical, I would want that you listened to my history.
As you have said, this job esula clearly
from us ò  that it has been demanded.
The truth is that there is a terrifying man
that she wants to kill to me.
A terrifying man?
Of who draft?
You must have felt its name.
A millionaire who possesses
one society of marine transports.
Its name is Gatoo.
Eh! Gatoo would be…
… that one of the Gatoo Company?
One of the richer men to the world?
Who would be?
Who? Who?
S ì. Officially it manages marine transports…
… but secretly it trades drug and others
illegal products using of ninja and announced publicly.
With its traffics loschi it tries
to get hold of entire countries and enterprises.
A year it makes put the eyes on the Country Of the Waves.
It has invaded the country having used of the violence
and of its it revives financial institutions…
… and in a moment it has taken the control of all
the transports and the marine traffics of the island.
Gatoo has monopolized the transports…
… that they are essential for one be to insulare,
and now of it the wealth controls all.
The only thing that Gatoo fears is the bridge…
..ancora in phase of construction.
That we began much time ago.
I understand! And inasmuch as you are constructing
the bridge considers you an obstacle.
Then those ninja have been send to you from Gatoo.
One what is not clear.
If you have to that to make with one the most dangerous person
that it even assumes of the ninja…
… because you have forwarded yours
demand hiding these facts?
The Country Of the Waves is a poor country.
Neanche the Daimyo is rich… (king)
… and obviously neanche we have the moneies…
… in order to advance one demanded
of mission of B level.
If you will abandon this mission
I verr ò  sure killed.
But of this you do not have at all preoccuparvi!
Even if you had to die…
… there would be only a beloved nipotino of 10 years…
… to cry all the day to me!
And my daughter would continue
to living sadly serbando…
… in order always rancor towards the ninja of the Leaf.
For ò, not… It would not be sure guilt yours!
Not left us choice, eh?
The proteggeremo at least until the arrival to your country.
This s ì  that beautiful news is one!
(I have won!)
There are nearly.
Tazuna, seems that up to now not if of they are shrewed.
Thanks.
This is the maximum that can make. To the next one.
Calm one. Thanks of new.
Fairies attention.
Well! Portatemi to house safe and sound!
Sure.
If we of new had to attack…
… this time would come
of the Jonin, not of the Chunin.
Badly badly!
Not to allow ò  that this capellone
it is of new the protagonist…
Laggiù!
Macché! It was only a rat.
And because you it goes some to you?
Not never it has been nothing laggiù!
Wretch! You stop to use the Shuriken cos ì!
Truly dangerous E'!
Tu! Marmocchio! Not to scare to us cos ì!
Ah? It has seemed to see a shadow to me!
Not! Here!
Laggiù!
I have said to you to stop it, stupid!
There was truly someone that it observed to us.
Zitto!
Not to say lies!
Naruto! It watches what you have made!
A rabbit!
Pardon to me… I did not want…
Poor rabbit.
It was only a rabbit.
That one is a rabbit of snows.
We are in spring…
Because it has the hair of that color!
The white man is the color that takes in winter when the sun tramonta soon.
This rabbit…
… it has been held to the closed one without sun for being
used in the technique of the substitution.
Our enemy finally has arrived.
Me dispiace…
… he was an impossible adversary for of the ninja
of the level of the siblings devil.
The ninja-copy of the Village of the Leaf…
Kakashi of the Sharingan!
All to earth!
I know.
Very well!
Arrived E' our adversary!
This time touches me!
Not to make me ò  to exceed from Sasuke!
But who watches is, Zabuza Momochi,
the traitor of the Village of the Fog!
Traitor!
But what imports to me. Ready…
Departure…
Via!
Been behind.
Me you would be of impiccio.
Why?
This is completely various
regarding those before.
Against a similar adversary…
… it will be hard to continue cos ì.
Who would have never said it that I would be myself
imbattuto in Kakashi of the Sharingan.
Dispiacerebbe to you…
… to deliver the old one to me?
What? Sharingan? What would be?
About what it is speaking?
It will be truly cos ì  strongly?
Sharingan?
You arrange yourselves to cross…
… and proteggete Tazuna-saint.
You do not have to participate to the battle.
What?
E' this the square job who this situation demands.
You will fight with me.
Cos' is that eye!
Remarkable one. I can see the famous Sharingan.
That honor.
Continued to say "Sharingan"…
… but that cos' it is?
Who possesses the Sharingan…
… he has the power to preview…
… all the illusory, martial and magical limbs…
… that the adversary means to use.
E' a special eye of which only least they decide.
For ò  this it is not the only ability of the Sharingan.
Beautiful answer. Indeed…
… us ò  that he is still more frightening, it is that with that eye it is gone
to know to bottom the technique of the adversary until copying it.
When I was in the murderous square of the Fog…
… there were information on you in the list
of it searches to you that I had to disposition.
Quite it was marked you…
… that the Kakashi ninja-copy had
reproduced more than thousand techniques.
Possible E' that Kakashi is a ninja cos ì  strongly?
Fantastic!
But that it means?
The Sharingan is a peculiarity that possesses
only a part of the Uchiha Clan.
Perhaps it wants to say that he.?
We give one moved.
I must kill those
old the first possible one.
But Kakashi, before seems that dovr ò  to strike to you.
E' l ì!
E' suspended on the water!
It is taking advantage of a chakra considerable.
Technique of the Fog Veil.
Disappeared E'!
Master!
Before he will come to make me outside.
What?
Zabuza Momochi…
… in the murderous square of the Fog it was
known like the expert of the silent homicide.
S… silent?
Like indicated from its name, this technique allows
to kill quickly and in the maximum Hush.
One says that when you notice
of he already six to the other world.
Neanch' I am in a position to using
to the perfection the Sharingan.
Been well attention!
If you fail morirete.
Six much optimist!
The continuous fog to become more driven in.
The Country of the Waves is encircled from the sea and
cos ì  often understood that there is this fog.
Sensei!
Eight points.
That it happens!
Laringe, dorsal thorn, lung, liver…
… vein to giugulare, kidney, skull and heart.
You say to me, that it leave vital preferred?
That terrifying tension omicida.
It seems that it even picks up the movement of the eyes
and that it can kill to you…
… from a moment to the other.
To remain here also for short time door to the madness.
Here what succeeds when a Jonin wants your dead women.
The feeling is had that the own life is in their hands.
To this point it is worth dying endured
and to place aim to this I torment.
Sasuke…
… not to worry to you.
I you protegger ò  to cost of my life.
Not lascer ò  never that mine
companions come killed!
Of six sure one?
You are all dead men.
Master! Behind of you!
You die!!!
The Technique of the Aquatic Multiplication of the Body!
Successful E'…
… to copy it…
… in means to this fog!
Not to move to you!
The combat is ended.
Cos ì  does not go…
Also Kakashi-sensei has fallen in the trap of Zabuza.
We must escape… or we will be…
We will be massacres to you!
This pain…
What I am making!!
I have juror that more I would not be scappato!
In the next episode: The Determination Due to the Pain.
Avr ò  one great possibility this time!