The cry of the tears! You are my friend!
It is really Naruto?
Which is this force?
And which was this will chakra red presently?
Is this a monster?
But be to you what with the Juste?
Your friend!
This is why I said that
I will not let myself go towards Orochimaru!
I will break you the arms and the legs if I owed it!
Katon Goukakyuu No Jutsu!
[note: Fireball]
You finally taken again ace your spirits? Dumb!
If not, I will continue to strike you until you donot can
to move more and will trail you at the house, Sasuke!
Close it!
What you know about me,
whereas you had neither brothers nor parents?
You are alone since the beginning!
Then what can you know well!? Hein!?
We suffer because of our bonds…
Do you know only what that made lose them!?
It is true that I do not know anything about the parents nor the brothers.
But…
Today it is me which levels! Eat!
Oh that yes!
When I am with Iruka-Sensei I wonder whether…
Itadakimasu!
[note: Says itself by starting a meal]
A ninja should eat above all!
He! He! Do not eat too either.
… If it is like having a father…
… And when I am with you…
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
What do you want stunned?
I will not lose against you!
Always cause.
Was Héhé, how it?
Release me.
… If it is like having a brother…
Why Naruto?
Why be gone so far for me?
Because it was the first bond which I wove…
This is why I will stop you!
It is Naruto too late.
Much too late…
More no return is possible for me.
Approaches! Naruto!
If it is like that, then I will break these bonds!
To break?
Then why to have put your stringcourse?
I recognize it.
You are strong.
It is because you know the same pain as me, that caused by loneliness.
And this pain returns to us more extremely.
By breaking these bonds…
I will obtain a capacity much more powerful.
Now we fight equal.
But, you will not be able to touch me.
Ca did not change since time.
No matter what I say, it is useless…
Sasuke!
Trève of chatterings.
From now, we will fight!
Approaches!
I see it!
These same movements which were invisible for me presently, I see them!
I see them!
Its movements are completely different!
But it does not matter!
I cannot lose here!
Shit!
Is my body as powerful as when it was under the influence of the seal?
With the power which it releases when it moves…
… The image of its next movement appears to me very clearly!
As a long time as I will have this sight…
… I will be able to preserve my will chakra.
The cursed seal consumes too much much.
If I can see as well…
I can predict the movements of Naruto.
And to use it with my advantage.
They are not good…
It anticipates my movements perfectly.
Shit!
Finally here you is.
You are sure that it is well by there?
We would make better dispatch us.
I have a very bad presentiment.
Sasuke!
Katon, Ryuuka No Jutsu!
[note: Fire of the Dragon]
Incredible…
Close it, Naruto.
It is already too late, Naruto!
You are so weak, kid…
You should be grateful…
… Towards me.
And towards that which sealed me…
Hokage Yondaime!
What is it still?
What was it?
Even if I can predict his movements…
… Its bulge in different directions will chakra.
As if its will chakra thought by itself…
I cannot follow it.
This will chakra red…
… Ca is not one will chakra normal.
Then really have you after Naruto.
We want to capture it for our group, Akatsuki.
It is an order of our chief.
I see…
Then you have special capacities.
Now I include/understand!
Katon, Goukakyuu No Jutsu!
[note: Fireball]
Its will chakra protects it?
The calm one…
If I keep my distances, I could nothing make.
Shit…
This dumb!
I hardly could dodge them.
Provided that I arrive in time.
It would be said that I do not have the choice.
Eh well…
Since I started to use this capacity…
… I did not know what could arrive to me.
But I the choice, isn't this does not have Naruto?
Very well, you are special.
But you see,
I am special than you!
Sasuke…
Shit, that hurt…
And as if that were not enough, I do not feel my left hand…
It would be said that I cannot use this capacity too a long time.
But I will not give up!
The next blow will be the last!
Next episode
Conclusion, rain of tears.