http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
They said that we have eliminated
the more insufficient contenders.
We can begin with the strong piece
inasmuch as they are passed
quarantacinque tiny.
Well!!
To say   the question to you number 10!
There are!
E' my last hope.
The ace in the sleeve!
The question number 10.
How much the ago long one.
Finally the last question.
Sbrigati to return Kankuro!
You must take to all the answers before
of the presentation of the 10 question.
Before beginning
I must dirvi that.....
hour we have one new rule
for this last question.
Six lucky person.
He is served to you to something to play to the dolls?
He knew of karasu!
It makes null.
Repair to you.
Hour I explain to you.
This last one....
it is a deprived of hope rule.
Hour that ours subordinates to you not there am.
we are boring.
Not to worry to you.
Soon we will be occupied.
Why?
This year the examiner of before
test will be Morino Ibiki
Cos   also first part of the examination will be difficult.
Why they have chosen just that sadist?
Sadist?
Kurenai
Six anchor one jonin novizia
and therefore you cannot know it.
Who would be this tizio?
E' a professional.
A professional?
Of what?
Of the torture and the interrogation.
What?
Even if in the examination not there are physical tortures....
the boys will be subordinates to violence
psychological dates its abilities of inquisitore.
E' the commander
of the group of torture and interrogation
Morino Ibiki.
A deprived of hope rule!
Everyone of you will decide if to support
or less this last question.
To decide if to support it or not?
Like "deciding"!
That it succeeds if we refused
of giving the last question?
If you decide not to answer
your points will go to zero
that is you will come bocciati
obviously with to the others two of the group.
What means?
Obvious E' that we will choose to support it!
E' hauling that all the group fails!
Moreover
there is an other rule.
Still!
Enough now!
If you will decide to support it
and the answer will be wrong
it will be removed to you
in order always I privilege to participate
to the examination of selection of the chunin.
That absurdity is never this!
Moreover there is who here has participated
piu times to this examination!
You have been ill-fated.
This year I make them rules them.
And for that I have given to you
the possibility to go some to you.
Those that do not have the courage,
enough that they decide not to support it
and to give to the examination the next year
or the year after anchor.
Therefore
if it is withdrawn
also the rest group
it will be bocciato.
But if you decide to support it and
they do not give the exact answer
you remain genin for all a life.
However it goes is put badly.
A normal person would not be able
to face one similar chosen.
Cominciamo.
Who does not want to support this question
he raises the hand.
After that we will have controlled
your number you will exit from here.
Which type of question will be?
Eternal damnation!
If mistake rimarr   genin an all the life.
I do not want!
But if to choose   not to support it
falliranno Sasuke and Sakura-chan
for guilt mine and does not have to happen.
I do not want to raise the hand
why they are sure to make it us.
But
But Naruto, for you is various.
You not.
You would have to ignore to us and to raise the hand
and to try again an other time.
I
I withdraw myself!
I do not want to make this examination!
Number 50, you have failed.
Bocciati numbers 130 and 111.
Me dispiace....
January, Inaho.
Maledizione
also I!
also I
Naruto!
Why it does not raise the hand?
He
I am a genius and a day
to receive   the title it of hokage.
My name is Uzumaki Naruto.
It remembers to you!
You are zitto!!
I am ready to cross whichever
danger also to become hokage
I diventer   a lot piu strongly of the hokage!
I to make   to recognize to all
the village my value.
It always continues to repeat.
like an idiot
that you will become hokage.
Me dispiace, Naruto.
I do not want
to ruin this to you
unattainable dream.
You
Hibiki knows to bottom the psiche human.
The terrible thing is that
the maneuver attacks them psychologically and
making weight on their weaknesses.
You underrate me!
I not scapper !
To answer   to the question!
He does not import to me if rester
genin an all the life
why in any case diventer   hokage!
I do not have fear!
That character.
He does not think neanche a po' next to we.
Neanche a moment.
S
hour I recognize its stupidity.
You I repeat the last time.
This will be the choice
that it will decide of your life.
If you decide to withdraw itself it makes it now.
I do not want to withdraw in behind my words.
It makes part of my "creed ninja".
That interesting boy.
In a moment he has eliminated
the uncertainty of all the present ones.
They are remained 78 students, eh?
They are much more than how much you waited for to me.
By now not there is more nobody that wants to be gone some.
That determination!
Then
I communicate to all the present ones
that before the test
it is exceeded!
Aspects! That it means!
We have been promoted?
And the tenth question that fine it has made!
Not never it has been.
Your decision little ago pu
to be considered the 10 question.
What?
hey!
Then the 9 problems
that we have resolved until hour!
They have been useless!
Nothing at all.
The first 9 questions are served to the scope.
to verify your dowries it characterizes them
in collecting information.
To collect information?
Exact!
In the first place the juice of this test
it was in the first rules
that it previewed a system
of appraisal to squares.
This has put you an anxiety
I lean making to think you
of being one ballast
for your group.
S ! S !
It was what I imagined.
Bugiardo!
But the questions of the test were
too much difficult for you genin.
For which the greater part of you
it will have thought that in order to maintain the score
it was necessary to copy.
Therefore this examination gave
for discounted copying.
E' for that we have
inserted between of you two chunin
that the answers knew all.
Truly!
I have put us a po' in order to find it.
yeah.
It was cos   obvious.
Strange E', indeed,
that not if notices some!
Vero Hinata?
I bet that
not if n' it were shrewed.
For
it is obvious that who copy
badly it comes bocciato.
Why
to times the information are
more important of our life.
In the missions and the battlefields
information to cost of living are collected.
Terrible!
There are signs of ustioni,
holes of lives and scars.
They are signs of torture.
However it is not said that the obtained information
making oneself to discover from the adversary
or from thirds party they are corrected.
It remembers to you!
To have of the information mistaken
pu   to have destructive consequences
for the country and the companions.
for this reason we have made you
to collect information copying
and we have eliminated those that
they are remained behind.
For
continuous not to understand the sense
of this last question.
This tenth one
it was the main question of this examination.
What you want to say?
I explain to you.
The tenth one consists in "supporting"
or in "not supporting".
E' clearly that it is one chosen
difficult and suffered.
Who has decided not to support it
he failed with its team.
If instead you support the question and mistakes
you always come private in order of the possibility
to rifare the examination of Chunin selection.
E' just one demanded infida.
Imagined this situation
We suppose that you are resolutions
to become chunin.
Your mission is to recover
a secret document.
The number and the abilities are not known
of ninja opposing neither the their equipments.
Moreover us they could even be traps.
And now what fairies?
Executed or refused the mission?
You could put in danger
your life and that one
of your group.
Pu   to go itself ahead avoiding
the dangerous missions?
The answer is
Not!
There are missions that involve many risks
but that you cannot leave to lose.
It must demonstrate courage to the companions
and to have the abilities for
to exceed these dangers.
E' this requirement for being
a chunin, that is a group leader.
Who does not succeed to put to risk
the own life in the crucial moments
or who loses occasions thinking to.
uncertain future opportunities.
All those shock that they succeed to take
only this type of superficial decisions
they do not deserve, to my warning, to become chunin!
You that you have chosen to support
pu   to say that you have given
the answer corrected to the tenth question.
They are sure that you will succeed to go encounter
to the difficolta that they will be introduced to you.
You have exceeded the income.
Before the test of selection
of the chunin it is finished.
I augur you to fight bravely.
Just! It augurs to us!
S ! S ! Yeah! Yeah!
That amusing boy.
Cos' is?
It will not never change
You!
Me it does not seem the case to celebrate.
I am the second esaminatrice, Mitarashi Anko.
(According to Examiner, Mitarashi Anko is here)
We begin with according to examination!
Seguitemi!
Beautiful show.
The esaminatrice is similar naruto.
78 persons?
Ibiki! You have promoted 26 squares very?
In this test six too much indulgente state.
It seems that this time is
many excellent students.
Oh, goes well
With the second test of eliminer   more of the half.
More of the half?
I am exciting myself.
You spiegher   the details tomorrow.
you ask yours teaching
jonin the place and the exact hour.
This is all.
Gone!
Someone is passed leaving the sheet in.bianco.
Uzumaki Naruto, eh?
It appeals to this boy to me.
Cos' is this place?
- Forbidden Area
Here it is where it will take to place the second test
the esercirtazione field number 44
better known like
"la forest of the dead women"!
the forest of the dead women?
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
E' here! E' here! E' here! E' here!
Great notizie!Ggrandi news!
Naruto is muovendo for golden the Time!
From you open them naruto will go in wave
all the Wednesdays to the 7:27 pm.
and
Wednesday 2 you open them.
There will be one aimed special of
an hour that comincier to the 7:00 pm!
You do not get lost my adventures!