Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking NFS
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the fire!BANG!
The great Jiraya… is not the type that runs behind the beautiful women! They are not cos ì  stupid.
When you arrive to my age....
The women impazziranno for your fascination.
Ah? When that woman has made the occhiolino you seems to you a fish lesso…
You would not have to make the fico so much, Ero-Sennin.
It goes well… but you stop it to call to me in that way before all.
It is zitto!
We speak of other. These tizi are dangerous, Ero-Sennin.
Eh? Ero-Sennin?
You stop it to call Ero-Sennin to me.
Not me wonder that you are one of the three leggendari Sannin, Jiraiya-sama…
Even if a six greatest lover of the women....
I was sure that we would not be resolutions to distrarti more than a lot.
You know the true identity of Ero-Sennin?
Beh… is not that I have one true identity and one false....
However… it seems that you have cancelled the Genjutsu that we had made that woman.
In order to remove to me from Naruto…
Thanks to the Sharingan you have used a Genjutsu on this poor woman…
E' truly an attitude from codardi.
To remove?
Why they have made it?
Then is truly Naruto your objective?
Your objective…
E' the one which has within Naruto, the Kyubi, true?
Why here Kakashi-saint it was some to the current…
You are …
The source of the information, you are.
"You take Naruto with you "
These are the orders of our organization, Akatsuki.
E' one mission of extreme importance.
What is saying?
You will not carry Naruto from no part.
We will see…
Much good.
I will personally get rid  of you two, just now.
Not interfered…
What that man will kill…
They are I!
Episode #85
Stupid fratellino. Hatred and depreciation!
Sasuke…
Vendetta?
I do not have time to lose now with you.
You close that mouth!
Sasuke !
Eternal damnation!
Naruto !
T' I have said not to interfere!
As you have said to me …
They are survivor until to hour…
Waiting for this moment!
Sasuke!
Not still…
It more does not succeed neanche to form seals with the hands.
This is… my combat!
Much good…
You have felt, not?
This is their combat!
We do not have to interfere.
You take this!
Why?
The difference between of we is remained the same one then… How it is possible?
Without mercy, eh?
Which thing I have made… until now?
What I have made?
A six weak person.
You want to know why?
Why it lacks to you …
…  hatred!
This is…?
This is…
It can  be?
Exactly…
This is our house.
Madre! Father!
A six weak person.
For next the 24 hours…
Stopped.
You will see again the scene of that day…
Stopped!
Uncle, Aunt.
You merits not to die.
Stupid fratellino.
If you have intention to kill to me.
You curse to me, hates to me.
You survive in this atrocious world.
You run, you run.
It grabs hold of you to your life.
Cruel like always…
Infernal World of the Moon has used the Tsukiyomi on its brother ( )
Now you stop it! Bastard!
That… that he happens?
Ninpou: Gamaguchi Shibari
(Trap of the stomach of Rospo)
Me dispiace for you… Itachi, Kisame. Found within to my stomach now.
I have evoked the esophagus of a rospo giant of the caverns of the Yougoku mount.
However you are two criminal ones you search to you…
You will be an optimal food for the rospo of mountains.
What… What devil is?
Naruto, you are calm!
Not to worry to you, this is one my technique.>.
Kisame, we go!
Useless E'. Nobody is never successful to scappare from here, up to now.
The muscle walls are being closed.
They are faster than we.
At this rate…
But…
Ero-Sennin
What happens?
They are you escape yourself.
I cannot believe that they are resolutions to penetrate these walls.
Why we are withdrawing?
You could…
Not there is haste, Naruto still is not dangerous.
Moreover I must be stopped from some part in order to rest.
I have used the Tsukiyomi, and have been forced to use also the Amaterasu
[  Amaterasu = God of the Sun  ]
What is these flames?
They are black!
Not to approach to you too much!
How devil is resolutions to scappare?
Moreover…
What is those black flames?
As it is possible to burn the stomach of Iwagama that normally sputa flames.... (Name of the rospo of Mountains)
Well!
Fuin Jutsu: Fuukahouin
[  Technical sealing: Control of Flames  ]
Well!
Hour would have to be lies in wait for.
Hour we must be taken care of Sasuke.
Sasuke …
Dynamic Entry! (Scenografica Entrance)
Dispiace to have to me to you hit.
I went of haste, and I have forgotten my small mirror.
I have used mine coprifronte, but it is not the same one.
I have confused your shadow for that one of an enemy…
I have left to go my impetuous combative spirit, and I have not made attention …
Me dispiace.
These would have to be your excuses?
They are not Bravo with the words…
Vabbè, lasciamo to lose…
Sasuke door from the medical square.
!
It has an arm and the fractured ribs…
Moreover, it has endured a mental attack from a Dojutsu and has lost acquaintance. (Dojutsu: Technique with the eyes)
Also he that technique?
Ero-Sennin, Sasuke Will recover?
It seems that it has endured serious psychological damages.
I will kill  to you!
You die !
It leaves me …
Six of intralcio.
Eternal damnation!
What devil has made Sasuke…
What has made that bastard… Ero-Sennin ?
Change of plan!
Before I had much fear…
But now I want to go to try those tizi the black cape and to fill up them of legnate.
They are I what they try, true?
Then they are I that  I will go  from they for first!
If you went from they to yours puts into effect them level, sure you would be killed.
There is too much difference between they and you.
In order now we can only try to hold them far from you.
Therefore we would have to scappare and to hide!
You want makes to pass the rest me of the life to shake of fear?
You are zitto a moment!
Six too much weak person.
Me dispiace, Gai.
I have left that its anger vented all… but I would have had to take part before.
Kakashi has been attacked with the same technique, and now it is in coma.
Goodness knows when it is waked up…
Kakashi-Sensei?
When one student comes hurt…
From the deep one of my heart I would want that…
… that person, the specialist of the medical limbs, was with we.
E' for that  I will go  to try it personally.
What?
Just she…
It is not possible… how many moneies !
, I speak just about "she ".
An other Sannin like me, great guaritrice and domatrice of snails.
Perfect!
Now  I will be able  to recover all the losses and to win more also.
The woman with the written "gambler" on the back…
Tsunade-hime!
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete
Festivity! Festivity! Festivity!
I will spend  a bag of moneies today.
It waits for Naruto!
I  will guard your wallett.
The three sins forbidden for the ninja are: the moneies, the alcool and the women.
They are the ruin of one shinobi.
They are various from you, Ero-Sennin.
Optimal! I am in order to go to make purchases the stalls of the fair!
Next episode:
The beginning of the training!
I will succeed  to become stronger!