http://naruteamplus.alterista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Well, I succeed to catch a glimpse its movements.
Not pu   being.
It has followed
my movements?
Eternal damnation, we were cos   near....
Naruto, ce you make it to continue?
Sure, I am very well!
Exhausted E'.
I cannot.blame it.
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu
it consumes much Chakra
but it is thanks to he if I have found
a way in order to strike it.
Impossible E'.
It has had
only fortune.
Naruto, you run!
You exit from here and attacks it from the outside!
Of agreement!
It will not be able to never happen.
I not to lose !
Now!
Katon Goukakyuu not Jutsu.
Maledizione!
They have gone to us near.
We try of new.
It goes well.
It will have to remain without Chakra between a p
inasmuch as it is slowing down.
It will not go as it hopes.
Before, fermer   you!
Sasuke!
E' for a long time
that I did not fight in one situation much difficult one.
Also they are preoccupied for Sasuke and Naruto.
I must be calm, think
what will make hour!
Oh not!
Too much slow!
I seal melted
This was
the voice of Sakura.
Succeeded E' something!
What will be making Kakashi-sensei!
S Sakura-cha....
Merda, I must make something.
I must make something in order to resolve
He!
Andiamo
it is useless.
Naruto, behind of you!
Naruto!
E' impossible to exit here.
You I can assure.
You can yourself be raised, Naruto?
Not to waste your Chakra cos !
E' the one which wants makes to make us.
I know.
Maledizione, we cannot continue cos .
I must
I must make something!
My eyes are
accustoming to its movements.
We make ended it.
What?
It raises to you, idiot!
I have attacked in its aims discoveries
but it is successful to schivarli.
!
You stop it to annoy to me!
A case?
Not, not pu   being.
It is fighting
and at the same time
it preoccupies of its companion.
It succeeds to see my movements?
That boy
it is intuendo my movements.
How he succeeds to us?
Well, then....
Disappeared E'!
Where? Dov' has gone?
Naruto! Better not distrarci!
Not to succeed   to cover to you to along!
I do not have need of your aid!
He seems that the boy cannot more move.
Wonderful one.
You move well.
You move too much.
You fermer   with my next attack.
Motorie abilities
the glares
and the concentration
in you they would have
to be exausted.
It will attack to me!
Rilassati
concentrate to you
and
it anticipates it!
It has anticipated to me!
Impossible!
Those two
eyes
they have the Sharingan!!
You six....
E' be only for a moment
but I have seen it.
I have understood!
Also you possess one innata specialty.
That boy.
However it is incomplete.
He has developed during the combat.
If it were true
I could not still fight to along.
My technique uses much Chakra
and I cannot maintain
this speed in eternal.
If the continuous battle to along
he will be able to preview my movements.
Its eyes
they begin to overwhelm to me.
It would be foolish to attack it directly.
Then
user   he
in order to hit it.
What!
I must sbrigarmi!
Kakashi-sensei!
Six slow state to defend to you, Kakashi.
In order to help those boys you have lost
the concentration.
Even if you have a formidable eye
six always too much slow one
to see my movements.
We go, makes me to still amuse a po', Kakashi.
You ricompenser   in one way a lot amusing.
Not preoccuparti of the mocciosi
because Haku will kill them.
You will catch up the other world and cos
you will ask they excuse for your weakness!
Sasuke-kun...... will be defeated?
This will not happen!
Sasuke-kun not
You are cursed!
he will lose against!
You are cursed!!
a boy like that one!
You are cursed!!!
Neanche Naruto!
Sure!
Eh?
I
I have flood confidence in they.
Naruto
it is the ninja more unforeseeable,
number one in being strange people
and Sasuke, than ago part
of one of the best clans than Konoha.
Then it is
Exact one. Its name is Uchiha Sasuke.
Beyond that to be a ninja brilliant,
it has the innata ability
of the Uchiha clan.
E' a survivor of that tragic clan
For this it is improved cos   fastly.
But for Haku it does not make some difference.
Nobody is successful never to strike
the technique of Haku Nobody.
Well, hour we will put aim to all this.
Sakura not to move to you!
What?
Of agreement.
To give   endured one fine
to this crash!
Six state
one ball to the foot
the entire time!
Ce you have made it Sasuke.
Cos' is that face
from idiot!
Why?
It has defended to me.
s Who......
why
(I want to obtain the title it of Hokage
and it introduces me all over the world)
(the Six wounded, pollo)
(we are arrives you to the top)
(Sasuke, Sasuke, Sasuke!)
I you
I hated.
Why?
Then why you have saved to me!
Why
you have protect to me?
You I have not asked!
Who knows it.
My body has moved alone.
Idiot.
Sasuke!!!
That man
I did not want to die
before having murdered my brother.
You
not to die.
He
one has moved although it knew
that trap was one
it has made it in order protect
one person to he beloved.
It was a ninja admirable.
E' before the time that you see to die a friend?
This is the way of a ninja.
Taci!
Also I
I hated to you.
You will pay!
To kill to you !
Cos' is this Chakra?
It is not possible!
The Chakra st taking shape.
But.
that ripugnante Chakra!
The wounds of the hand
they are being healed!
Who is
this boy?
What is Zabuza?
Not! Ho gia felt this chakra terrifying.
But it is not possible!
Cos' is this Chakra?
That ugly feeling.
Kakashi?
Not, he is too much large for being that one of Kakashi.
Of who it is then?
Naruto!
That disaster.
I seal is broken in a moment as this!
I must sbrigarmi!
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
As you have dared to kill Sasuke!
Not to put to you against of me!!!
Sasuke had a dream
Dream?
Not to put to you against of me!
For guilt of your dream hour Sasuke is
The Past White man, The Feelings Secrets.