Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
A Lesson Learned!
The Iron Fist of Love
Please don't die...
I'll get you out now.
Hey!
What are you doing there?
Curry of Life Shop
One, two...
Hope they're all right.
I'm sure they'll be able
to bring Karashi back.
Definitely, Definitely.
One, two...
That's the Katabami Gold Mine...
Instead of just getting
Rokusuke and Karashi back,
let's finish the Kurosuki Family
once and for all!
Don't get carried away, Naruto.
So, what are we gonna do then?
I'm kind of worried about
what Guy Sensei told us.
The boss of the Kurosuki Family
may be
one of the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist.
Who knows what
they'll do to Rokusuke?
Yeah, but how seriously
can we take Guy Sensei's info?
What are you talking about?!
Guy Sensei is always right!
Calm down, Lee.
We should investigate first.
Yeah!
Sir Raiga, we were able
to capture Rokusuke,
one of the three that
slipped out of the village.
Well done.
It seems that they went to ask
for some help from a Ninja village.
Where did you go?!
I'm sorry.
Don't bother, rookie.
Yes sir!
Rokusuke, I thought we had
a good relationship
with everybody in the Gold Mine.
Well, that's...
Why is it? I'm so deeply sorry
to hear that you left the village.
I can't remember how things
were in the past,
when everything was going well.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I won't do it again!
Yeah, I have a good idea.
I'm going to arrange
for your funeral.
Please don't! Please let me go!
I won't do it again,
so please forgive me!
Why? Don't you like funerals?
No, I don't wanna die yet!
You know, I really like funerals...
Think about it.
When they are alive, humans speak ill
of each other,
they betray each other,
and they hate each other.
But at a funeral,
they forget all the hatred
they had for the other.
They even remember
the good times they had together.
Right?
You have to be kidding me!
No! Please don't do it.
Hey!
Let me go!
It's a done deal then.
Let's have a big funeral for Rokusuke.
- Yeah!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Is that gold?
There's nothing shiny about it.
They have to melt
that ore into mercury.
After that they evaporate it
and only then does it turn into pure gold.
I don't get it.
Well, there is no need
for you to understand it.
Oh!
Huh? What are you doing
Hurry up!
If you don't hurry up,
I'm gonna ask the boss
to let me hold your funeral!
Please forgive me!
I'm getting really mad now.
I won't forgive them!
Calm down, Naruto...
We don't know anything
about them yet.
That's right. We should do
what Neji is telling us.
Yeah but...
if we don't do something,
that poor old guy is going to die!
Naruto, leave things to me here.
Wait, Lee!
Hey, hey.
Hurry up and pick them up!
Yeah! Way to go, Lee!
Are you okay, old man?
Oh my gosh!
What have you done?!
Here. Drink some water.
What are you doing?!
I beg you.
Please punch me, kick me.
Please knock me around
like the way you just did
with those guys.
What are you saying?
If you won't do it,
I'll do it myself!
What are you doing?!
Stop!
I'm scared.
Just think what they'll do
if they knew I was
the only one that was safe.
What was that sound?
Did they find us?
Oh my, that's the sound
of the funeral bell.
Funeral?
Yeah.
Raiga, the boss of the Kurosuki family
which rules this town,
arranges a funeral for
those who betray him.
He buries them alive.
What? They bury them alive?
That's so cruel!
Yeah but...
Raiga always cries sadly
during the funeral.
That's one weird guy.
But...
That doesn't seem to be
the sound of the bell for you.
Yeah, I heard that Rokusuke
was caught this morning, so...
What?!
I'm so happy, I remember
the first day I met that guy.
Yeah? That's nice.
Yeah... When I told him we were taking
over the mountain from the magistrate,
he was so relieved to be freed from
the high taxes that he was paying.
He was laughing out of pure joy...
He was a really nice guy.
I like funerals.
Makes me feel nostalgic.
Would you put on
a big funeral for me too?
Fool! I'm not putting on
a funeral for you.
You are not going
to die before me.
I don't have to have a funeral for you
to think of the good times
because you are always a good boy.
Raiga.
What is it?
They're coming.
They'll show up anytime now.
Yeah... I'm excited to see
what kind of help he sought.
Okay! Let's save the guy.
Let's do it, Neji.
Okay.
Byakugan!
It's all right. He's still alive.
If we can get rid of
the guys around him,
we can save him.
Okay! Let's get rid
of them quickly!
Yeah!
Okay, let's go!
No! Let me out!
An enemy attack!
You...!
Tenten, you take the right!
Okay!
Gentle Fist!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Na -ru -to...
Uzumaki Barrage!
That's the way!
- Watch out!
- Huh?
There are three more!
Here comes the Leaf Village's
Handsome Devil, Rock Lee!
I found the last one!
You are...
Who is this guy?
Well...
This is Karashi.
The one Grandma Sansho
was talking about...
This is Karashi?
Karashi, was it your own decision
to join the Kurosuki Family...
just like Grandma Sansho said it was?
So what if it was?
What?!
Sir Raiga is great!
He dethroned the old evil government
of the Katabami Gold Mine,
and he liberated everybody
from the village!
One, two, one two...
Umm, Grandma...
Oh my...
You are so greedy!
They are fighting their lives
out there by going into the gold mine...
Can't you just wait at least
while I'm cooking the curry?
I don't mind waiting but...
I think something is burning.
What?
Oh my, oh my...
Oops...
Yeah, it burned...
Karashi, did you know that
Grandma Sansho worries about you
everyday while cooking curry?
Naruto, leave things to me here.
Karashi, you saved my life
with your curry of life.
If you can make such
a wonderful curry,
how can you stay with the family of
a man with no respect for life?!
Why?
Nobody cares to compliment me
even if I can make that curry.
As a man born in this world,
I should gain more power and
try to take over the world!
Instead of sitting around in that store
that no one patronizes anymore.
What? I can't take this anymore!
Lee!
Karashi, not only did you and
Grandma Sansho's curry save my life...
But you also taught me that
if you make it from the heart,
just one serving of curry
could save lives,
and that even somebody like me
could do anything just by trying hard.
You looked much stronger
and dignified then than you do now.
Karashi!
I've never seen anybody
who tries this hard.
I see. You want to save
this boy too, huh...
Please promise me...
Please get cut of the Kurosuki Family!
You're right...
I'm sorry... I'm so sorry!
Oh, I'm so relieved.
Hey! Please get me out of here.
It's dark and I can't breathe.
Oh yeah!
We almost forgot
about Rokusuke.
Mmm? You guys...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's all right now.
I'm sorry. Thinking that maybe
I could still save my friend
who got buried alive...
I just couldn't stay still.
Yeah, I understand.
Neji, what is it?
What is this?
This feeling of danger...
Hey Neji, what is it?
We are being watched.
It's probably Raiga.
What?
From the top of that cliff...
Okay. Let's go!
Karashi, please take care of Rokusuke.
All right.
No one's here.
Where did he go?
Mmm? What is that?
This mist...
Ninja Art: Hidden Mist Jutsu!
Hidden Mist Jutsu...
A specialty of Mist Village Ninja.
So, what Guy Sensei said was true?
Damn, I can't see anything!
Neji, try to find the enemy
with your Byakugan.
I've been trying...!
Uh... Can't see a thing!
That's impossible.
Even Neji' s Byakugan
that's supposed to let him
see 360 degrees won't work!
What's going on?
There isn't supposed to be
a Jutsu that can break Byakugan!
What do you think, Ranmaru?
It's amazing...
One of them can see through
the Chakra Network.
He probably has some sort
of Kekkei Genkai power.
He can see us?
It's all right,
my power is superior to his...
So, what are you going to do?
Everybody in the Katabami
Gold Mine is depending on me.
I'm the one who has to
keep the peace of this village.
Are you going to hold a funeral?
No, even if I hold a funeral,
I have no memories of them.
I'll just get rid of them!
Look,
Ninja Art: Lightning Fang!
Wh What is it?!
Lighting! Drop!
What do you think, Ranmaru?
It's great, Raiga!
Crappy news pass us by
And you become speechless
My voice is way too soft
So you don't answer
You're crying Crying alone
What can I do? I'm crying too
"Let my lonely scream ring out
through the night"
I'll thrash this confused era
with my speed Yeah
And I'll thrash this confused night
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar
and my speed Yeah
This sinking world and its evil bastards,
I'll kick their butt Yeah
Naruto Barrage! What?
Leaf Hurricane! Mm?
Here I come! Huh?
Impossible!
Hey! The enemy disappeared!
I have nobody either!
What? There is no enemy!
Neji! Are you using
your Byakugan correctly?!
I am doing it right!
It's impossible, but my Byakugan
is picking up Chakra!
Next time: "The Enemy of the Byakugan"