Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking NFS
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh!  Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the fire!BANG!
E' this! The water that turns!
to make it to burst is simpler than how much I believed!
Then while aspect that arrives to us, I go myself to rest  a Pò.
.. with this, obviously.>.
Hu?Cos' is, that one?
.. this helps to pass the time.
Bene.Io I sleep.
You  lascerò  the time not to close the eyes.
Ah s ì? You perceive to me when it arrives to us.
It waits for and vedrai!Ci   I will have arrived before the aim of the day!
Episode #87
It goes well!!!  I will make  to explode this balloon!
Ahh… But because it does not want to burst!
Successful Uhm?Ci six?
Eh? Heu… Successful? Which thing?
Ahh.. in place of one small siesta, I have slept all the afternoon.
Ah, then, dimmi, as I make in order to make to explode the balloon?
I will not say  nothing  to you finche you I do not arrive to us.
he goes well, I have understood.
You must learn this technique for same you, advancing step to step.
S ì,  s ì!
Well, I can speak of a po to you '.
In order to begin, it begins therefore to make to turn the water.
Hm? Ok.
Then, left right or?
According to you, in which sense it turns?
Huh? Then… Left back.
It approaches you of a po '.
E' as it was seemed to me.
Eh? which thing?
Your sense of spin is the right, visibly.
Right?
When you produce of the chakra, you transform at the same time of the energy of the body and the spirit.
For  that, you make to turn yours unconsciously chakra, while it accumulates it.
There are two possible senses of spin.
Therefore, manipulating the water in the football, you make it to turn in the opposite direction to the spin of the chakra.
Consequently, the forces are cancelled.
You would have already had to notice some, you know to you alone.
But. but. as you have understood that the spin sense is to right?
Observing your head.
If the roots of your hats turn towards left right or, yours chakra it goes in the same direction.
Simple E' cos  ì.
Then for me it is the right.
Exactly, you must visualize the water that wheel towards the right.
Uff.. Task never to this type of does not make up.
This technique is suited to you perfectly.
Nothing difficult signs, you do not have need that of chakra.
That  means, nothing complicated combinations of seals.
Also one weak person arrives to us.
Ehi, I am not weak person !
A day,  I will become  Hokage!
When I   will have understood what I must make,  I will dominate  this technique in 3 days !
3  days?
This technique is a Ninjutsu that Yondaime has left behind if.
It has been engaged for 3 years in order to learn it.
This technique is of class To, just under to the highest level.
In order to dominate it, there are 3 necessary stages.
To make to burst this water balloon is before.
This ninja.. this genius. Yondaime.>.
.., 3 years have put us.
Servants to nothing dirmi in how much you will not succeed to us if you have not still caught up before the stage.
You must make it for same you.
Well. Return in city. I must always collect information.
Which thing you count to make?
One technical of high class. A NinJutsu that Yondaime has left behind if…
Not task that  I will re-enter  endured.
Later, then. Not to strain to you too much.
Well, I ask myself as it will go to end. I am being bored.
Getlteman. You have a moment? We have some promotion this month.
Ouah! of the promotions !?
More you will come, more you will take cure than.
Here your ticket. It gives straight to numerous services.
Hi hi hi.. Arrival, arrival!
We go Shu, we must go.
Ditemi.. Where they are the baths?
I do not have 3 years to lose.
We go! Today  I will have  to still sgobbare very!
You explode. you explode. you explode.>.
Because it does not explode..
Ohh, Jira-chan, my pervertito small.
All the men are a po' pervertiti!
Merda!
they are passes already 3 days to you that Ero-sennin have given explanations to me.
I have so crushed this football. Why it does not burst?
Which thing I have forgotten?
Perfect, Perfect!
Che cos' is?
It smells of sake.>.
Itadakimasu!
[ Good appetite ]
Ehi mah?
Merda!Che cos' I have!
This means, nothing complicated combinations of seals.
Nothing signs…
Eh? Ehi.. is not yours giocattolo.
I have understood!
We go. you wake up yourselves! ehi, Ero-senin!
You. have fortune… you have carried of the water.
Of the water? Ehi.>.
before caught up stage!
Ended? Bah, you make to see a po '.
Well! It watches well!
The left hand?
Part!
And vaaaai!! you have seen! you have seen!?
Ahhh… It sleeps!
Me dispiace, me dispiace.. they are tired out for to have tried information.
like if it were not clear.>.
.. it still smells of sake.
In any case, it holds the football in the left hand in order to make to turn the water with the right.>.
it is originates them, is interesting this boy.
They are been strange that it has finally understood the principle of this exercise. And these thanks to me.
it is rather. thanks to he.
I have seen it to play with the water balloon, and I have observed it.
It made to ruotare to right and on the left inverting the spin, and the water moved in all the directions.
And cos ì  I have understood the trick.
And what you have understood?
I have remembered myself that before the time that I have seen to you to burst the balloon, was of all the deformed one.
Before, I made to turn the single water in one direction.
But yours it was completely deformed, because the water within turned in all the directions.
Then I have made some test to way mine. And it is burst!
It still does not succeed to make to turn its effectively chakra.
But it has tried and found a method in order to hide its difficulties.
They are clever. eh?
And well, one would say that you have caught up before the succeeding stage with.
Super! dimmi, you want to still see it one volta?Solo once?
It has been sovraffaticato and one is tax great pressure.
But we are not still to the second stage.
Well. stage is time to start second back to us.
Yeah!! finally, it begins the true training!
Hey!
Eh.. one ball in caucciù?
Ehi, still one ball to make to explode?
This time, must explode cos ì.>.
It is  100  times more difficult that with the water balloon.
It is not easy!
Before the stage was the spin. The second one is the power.
Not this time is water.  It is  the much most difficult one to visualize the motion of the chakra.
It is  true.>.
And well, good fortune.
I will have  need of an other method for this.>.
I go. I return in tries of information!
Ehi, waits for! it waits for! we could not train to us together?
Not to begin to piagnucolare.
You do not have need of knowing other.
I have said to you that t' I will teach  one technical.
Not that you  lascerò  always to count on me.
If it does not arrive to us alone, then not six ready one.
It involves to you like a child.
It remembers to you that six one shinobi!
S ì,  well. you can at least. give an other indication to me?
It pays to me?
And you say to involve to me from shinobi! not six that an old volture!
You do not have nothing of a large one shinobi!!
It is  terribly more difficult that with the other balloon.
And also.>.
My hands and my arm make me badly.
Merda.. is days that I make always the same thing.
This technique is of class To, just little under the highest level.
Not to begin to piagnucolare. You do not have need of knowing other.
Merda!
Ehi, Naruto…
Which thing six come to make?
Vai to buy to eat in city.
Eh? Why I?
Ehi, remembers to you that they are I that t' I teach this technique.
Here, you hold.
Thanks, getlteman.
Not m' standard nearly nothing. And one poses from university professor.
Papà, Papà, buy I a ghiacciolo.
I want that one, what it is fallen apart in 2.
You hold.
Ehi, I can eat it all.
Not of sure. Mother has already prepared the lunch for house.
.
Heu, dimmi.
you want to help me with the exercises today?
I do not have time to lose. I must return in city.
It thinks to find the solution for same you. Otherwise you will not progress never.
You I have said already: there are 3 weeks, not to begin to piagnucolare.
You a six ninja.
I knew already! I wanted to only feel to say it. Gone to eat, Ero-sennin.
We go, Jira-chan, you are incredible!
That there is? All this is true!
Merda!  I will not never succeed  to make to explode it.
Arrival to only empty me of the chakra.
In more.>.
More I use it, more ago badly.
it will not explode if arrival not to make to explode mine chakra!
I have understood!
The pain m' indicates the amount of chakra that free,
therefore if the pain to the maximum grows.>.
Not still, not still.>.
Still not.>.
Hour !
Aiiiiiiie!!
Oh? You would say yourself that improved a six po'.
Bah, is just successful to make to deflate it.>.
succeeding is not still one large.
We go, not to make the stubborn one.
You hold.
It goes well that six arrived to us alone.
Ah s ì,  makes me to try this.
Which thing? Which thing?
They give your right hand to me.
And. which thing is?
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete