Subbed by Shinji 89
Katon!Tecnica of the supreme fire ball!
Che cos' is.
Merda.>.
Chidori
I will win  sure!
It are not of cos ì  sure!
Enough!
The blow never seen.
Every time that we come here,
peace is always one
It seems that they are recovers to you completely.
We would have to only destroy this pathetic village.
Calm, Sakon.
We are not here in order to fight.
Zitto
bastard mangione!
If you have fear, you go to house to hide to you.
Here why I have said to you to calm to you, Tayuya!
Sai qualè your job in this moment, just ?
We go,
it is the moment to escort our special host.
Enough!
Merda.>.
I cannot!
Kakashi-sensei!
Naruto,
that technique was…
What  can be known was arranging on the roof
of a hospital ?
It was  a Pò  exaggerated for a litigio…
not thoughts ?
those jutsu (technical) was…
Not me mistake, that technique was
Rasengan.
What makes us here?
Com' is possible? Why Naruto knows that movement?
You were trying to kill Naruto
Sasuke?
Why six cos ì  angry?
The power of that Chidori
it was not adapted to being turned against
a companion of your village.
Six involved to you in infantile way.
As I thought.>.
the crash against Itachi
it has induced to make these sciocchezze.
Sasuke-kun…
Eternal damnation!
Naruto.>.
How many progresses you have made?
Kakashi-sensei.>.
Dov' is ended the square spirit?
You have been
to teach them that technique?
I task that Naruto
he is still too much young for padroneggiarla.
It could even have killed Sasuke.
Even if it has been in order to contrast the Alba group
me it seems exaggerated
that you have taught that Jutsu to it
This is worth also for you
That Chidori (thousand hawks) was rather powerful.
But  I thought that Naruto.>.
it would not have never used that technique against a its companion
For case
it has succeeded something of serious between they ?
Various things.
Various things ?
In poor words
those two have the same relationship that once
it tied to you to Orochimaru.
For he sasuke he is a companion but
at the same time it avails again.
E' a figure with which wants constantly to be
at par.
Probably it is not successful to resist to its provocazioni
E' from the times of the academy,
that it disperatamente tries to catch up it.
It makes you badly ?
frightening?
Sasuke!
I will not lose  more against than you.
In this moment to Naruto it does not interest to be estimated
from you or me.
it wants ottenere..più of whichever other thing.>.
the respect of Sasuke.
E' sasuke observing gives the progresses of Naruto close
hour tries an inferiority complex.
naruto he has become cos ì  strong
from fargli thinking not to be improved.
Frightening!
Tajyuu Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
Kuchiyose not jutsu!
Naruto has become cos ì  strong, but Sasuke.>.
My objective and that one to kill one sure person.
Vendetta?
Itachi is putting haste
to that boy.
E' for that sasuke it does not want to recognize the abilities to Naruto.
If it made it it would admit the own inferiority
The relationships between you avail again are much complicates to you.
We are not going in the just direction.
I go to fargli one foretells.
Then Naruto I entrust you.
I would have one mission to complete…
and I must say four to Sasuke R-with regard to the Chidori.
Sakura.>.
Not to worry to you.
It will return all like to the old times.
We look at ourselves!
Thanks, master Kakashi…
Naruto…
Sakura-chan…
Not to interfere more.
Six weak person.
Why six weak person ?
Why not tests enough hatred.
Cos' I have
concluded till now?
It appeals to its look to me.
We go.
That intentions you have!
If you did not make cos ì  scapperesti true?
You the not six type that is to listen to the prediche.
But that one is Kakashi… the copy ninja.
Sasuke.
it abandons the vendetta.
What?
I have seen some until nausea of types like you.
They make always one fine wretch…
those who speaks about vendetta.
Other is not obtained that to suffer more.
also when it is succeeded to carry it a.termine,
it remains large only an empty one.
Zitto!Che of it you know!
Of it he speaks like if you understood all!
It calm to you.
Then that of it you say if now…
you killed the more important person for you ?
Cos ì  you would succeed to comprise how much is foolish
that  that you are saying.>!
For me it would go well also…
but ill-fatedly
I do not have one of the sort person.
Already they have been all victims of a murder.
I have lived more than you.
mine was also one ugly age.
I know end too much well the suffering of the loss.
Neither I neither you have been fortunate this are sure.
True E'
But  our condition is not of does not get worse,
Both we have found of the precious companions, not?
Just in how much you have lost the persons beloveds, you would have to understand it.
The Chidori is a power that I have given to you only why
hour you have something of precious in which believing.
That power is not from turning against your companions, of
it is from putting to the service of the vendetta.
You know very well to what you serve
he thinks well if  that  that I say is indeed foolish.
To have between the feet a ninja of that level  he can  be problematic
E' better to wait for  a Pò.
Even if for merdosi you it would be impossible.>.
I me of sbarazzeri in a moment.
Goodness knows?
According to me, they two together would reduce to you in pezzetti.
Who has asked your opinion stronzo?
Tayuya
a girl would not have to use sure words.
Zitto grassone.
Still
We go to house.
We are resolutions to arrive in top.
Sakura-chan.>.
I have need to speak to you.
We go outside, you come with me.
Eternal damnation.
Maledizione.
During the Chuunin examination, I seal that Orochimaru has given to it.>.
Kakashi-sensei has said that it is to place,
but…
Orochimaru-sama…
It was necessary to send them all and 4?
It seems that
those boys are interested to sasuke.
I ask myself when he is strong?
In this moment,
to this level,
Sasuke-kun is not at par with they.
And it is just for that it will come
from me to the search of the power.
Who you are ?
The quartet of the sound.
I am Kidomaru of the east door.
I am Sakon of the door the west.
I am Jirobo of the door south.
I am Tayuya of the door north.
Hour they are of bad humor.
If you decide to go ahead, you know that  I will not have  cares!
Sometimes I,
Sometimes I
The flowing dreams of to person' s fragment
it looks like to mountain to me
to god, To the God Buddha,
To spread the crying peaple' s fragment
It looks like to mountain to me
More More and, until the end
to linens up the big placed
Shake Shake Shake, let' s find it
Bey bye bye, let' s go
It looks like to mountain to me
Appuntamento!Un an appointment!
Sakura-chan, you want something to eat?
Oh well. However, Kakashi-sensei has perceived it
I have intentional to only make a small crash with Sasuke
but if not firm Kakashi-Sensei you boys in time…
Sure!
We want to know who we are strongest!
Hey… You feel, Naruto.
Prossimamente:L' I invite of the sound.
I have felt that it is becoming one promised useless…