Subtitles By: BakaSan
You shouldn't ever relax, Sensei.
I'll correct my past mistake and finish you now.
It's too late for you to do anything now. My victory has already been decided. Konoha will be crushed.
I am the man who inherited the will of the First and the Second to protect Konoha.
I am the Third Hokage!
Orochimaru, from now I'll show you a special Jutsu that even you don't know.
Take this! Fuuin-jutsu (sealing jutsu)
Forbidden Secret Jutsu! Shiki-Fujin
A jutsu that I don't know?
I need to hurry up... this darkness is dangerous.
Please show me...
What's wrong? Are you planning to be tortured to death by the former Hokage's?
So, please show me your Jutsu soon.
He's not ready yet?
It's about time.
What's wrong? You seem to be beaten up already.
All that's left to do is just catch them.
Gotcha!
I won't let go...
Come out!
The darkness is gone. What is that Jutsu?
Sarutobi!
I'm sorry, Sarutobi.
Sorry for the trouble.
Please forgive me, the First, the Second.
Fuuin (Seal)
Your own subordinates.
Each person in Konoha is a part of my soul.
The people in the village believe in me and I believe in them.
That's what it's all about to be Hokage.
Saru. Protect those who love this village and believe in you.
And raise those whom you can trust for the future.
From tomorrow, you are the Hokage.
You even played around with my own subordinates lives.
The lives of our subordinates? You're still talking nonsense.
These guys believed in you!
Come, Enma!
I got you!
Senei Jashu
Damn you!
This is the end.
What's this feeling?
It's hot!
Die!
Somehow we have to stop them here!
Where's our backup?
That's out of my control.
Ninpo Kuchiyose Yatai-Kuzushi-no-Jutsu
(Booth Crusher Summonning)
That Jutsu is...
Long time no see, Ibiki.
Is it only your body that grew up? I can't even look at you.
Jiraiya sama...
Jiraiya? Is that one of the Three-Ninja's?
Hey you greenhorns! Have your small eyes open as wide as possible and watch very carefully!
Oh, Be thankful! The legendary special Ninja Jiraiya,
has arrived to perform a violent dance.
Hey you snakes! Are you scared by my Frog? Come get some!
I see Orochimaru finally decided to start things.
Where's the Third?
He's in the exam arena.
I see.
Don't die, old man.
Why didn't you dodge it?
Shit!
Shiki-Fujin... in return for this Jutsu power, you hand your soul over to Death. The price of this jutsu is your life.
My Jutsu doesn't start!
There's no need for me to dodge it.
I'll die anyway.
At the same time this jutsu completes, my soul is also eaten.
This is the Jutsu of the hero who saved this village once.
And from now, with this Jutsu, you'll die too.
So, this is the Jutsu that sealed the Kyubi.
I'll pull out your soul out from your body and seal it!
I can't control my body!
You can see it now, can't you? Your soul is half way out.
Those whose souls are sealed by Jutsu will never die peacefully. They will continue to suffer inside of Death's stomach forever.
The souls of those who performed the seal, and those who were sealed are locked in a never ending battle.
What?
That is Death?!
Don't mess with me, you old man. I won't let you do as you wish.
Die already!
Everybody stay in the line.
Everyone, be quiet.
Konohamaru-kun this place won't get crushed, will it?
Don't worry.
This hallway is under the old Rock faces. They're old but it's still a very strong structure.
That's what my grandpa told me.
So, there's absolutely no need to worry about it.
Someone's coming... which one is it?
It's Uchiha!
So, what happened to Temari?
You shouldn't run away from me so fast.
That's super.
I'll guess I'll play with you this time.
Wait!
Temari! I thought you were finished by him. You're ok?
Well, somewhat.
But I couldn't even hold him back for a minute.
No, it bought more time that Gaara needs to recover.
Also, you've forced him to use more of his chakra.
This smell is...
The shampoo again?!
No. It's Sasuke.
And there are some other smells around him. We've caught up with him.
Finally.
Their movement has completely stopped. Is he going to fight?
Hurry up.
What is that mass of countless smells coming from another direction?
Hey, there's somebody other than us chasing Sasuke.
What?
Is it our side or the enemy?
I don't know... but...
But?
It's not a human being.
Go, Kankuro. I'll take care of him again.
Temari, go ahead with Gaara.
You're already at your limit. I don't need another burden.
But...
Go!
Go already!
I understand.
Look's like I'll be the one to play with you.
I don't care either way.
NO.
You're going to deal with me.
You are...
Shino.
Why are you here?
Before you left the arena, I put female bugs on you.
The scent of the females is almost nothing.
Only the males of the same kind can smell the faint scent of the female.
The scent of the males are much stronger.
Uchiha Sasuke... you go follow Gaara.
The battle between you and him is not yet over.
I'll fight against this guy.
He was my match opponent after all.
I forfeit. Please continue the other matches.
Leave this to me. Go.
You seem to be confident, but are you going to be ok?
Don't worry. Give me 10 minutes and I'll go back you up.
By then I'll have finished my fight too.
You two know nothing. I guess you guys don't even know what real fear is in this world.
Then, are you going to teach me that fear?
No. If you win here and catch up with the others, then you'll find out even if you don't want to.
That's only if you can do that.
You, who are strong...
You, who are called Uchiha...
You, who have friends...
You, who are determined...
You, who is like me...
I exist to kill you.
Uchiha, you are my game!
Next Episode
Astonishment! Gaara's true character.