Conclusion, rain of the tears.
When you look at a cartoon, take care to light
part and try not too to approach you the television set.
Specia
What do you want to say by special?
It is impossible that I would be overcome.
Sasuke… You…
As you use this cursed seal, it will take possession of your body.
But if the seal devours you completely,…
You will lose the control of your spirit… For always.
This body…
I do not have time to lose.
I do not feel any more my left hand…
For you also…
To use isn't this capacity is risked?
You knew it?
This place is called… The Valley of the End.
Isn't this the perfect place?
Hein, Naruto.
Ah, it is true…
I had said to you that the time of the discussions was finished.
Then let us stop.
This combat…
Let us stop now!
Following, team 7
Uzumaki Naruto.
Haruno Sakura.
Super!
I am with Naruto?
Lastly, Uchiha Sasuke.
Super!
I am with Sasuke?
I hope that you will not be a ball, dunce.
You!
But, but, but!
Sensei, you said it yourself! It is for that it…
We are a team of 3, not?
It is true! We 3 form only one!
He!
You are not wounded…
Wet hen?
He…
You are not wounded…
Wet hen?
I want to fight with you.
Sasuke!
Me also…
I want to fight with you.
I want never again but
expensive beings die under my eyes.
[Invocation]
Kuchiyose No Jutsu
Sakura-chan…
I will protect it!
What is there the funny one?
There is nothing funny.
I am content.
To think that I finally will be able to beat you here.
What!? A ball as should not speak to you like that!
At least, I am not a ball which leaves the others behind him.
Let us stop.
Before that, mets your stringcourse. I await you.
I do not need any.
I don't care. Put it!
You will not be able to even pose the little finger on my face.
It is not the question!
You must put it to prove that one fights between Ninjas of of the same Konoha level.
Naruto!
Sasuke!
I will crush you!
You are only one ball!
Arrteeeeez!
And from there…
Chidori
Rasengan
This will chakra is…
Ca fears!
Naruto…
I am…
It rains!
You lost their trace?
They is good.
They are close.
By here!
I thus arrived too late…
Naruto…
How the things could finish thus?
Ca belongs to Sasuke.
I could not arrive in time…
I am sorry.
Naruto…
You did all that for…
Sasuke…
You are well my son.
When we are together,
your father does nothing but speak about you.
We are single brothers.
I am the obstacle which you must cross, then
that we must continue to live together.
Even if you hate me.
You also, you are able to activate Mangekyou Sharingan.
But for that there is a condition…
Your friend nearest…
The Valley of the End…
Theater of the combat between Naruto and Sasuke…
Isn't this ironic?
If…
If you observe the flow of the river… It seems to go without stopping like carrying out a combat.
Just like the destiny of 2 which
founded the village of Konoha formerly…
Naruto and Sasuke…
Your lives are like theirs…
Your friend nearest…
You must kill it.
I…
Will not let to me handle by you!
I will obtain the capacity with my way.
I will exceed you with my way!
You will see!
The rain stopped…
Because of the rain I do not feel any more his odor…
In any event, to look after Naruto is
priority before continuing Sasuke.
Yes.
All that becomes interesting…
Afflicted.
I am really afflicted, Sakura-chan.
I had promised to you to bring back Sasuke.
But it is not finished.
I will honor this promise!
Isn't this what I say all the time?
I never reconsider my word, it is
as I conceive my way of Ninja.
Next episode
The broken promise