Subbed by Gandelr
Chekked by Kyubi
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers
takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers
narifuri kamawazu
shinjiru ga mamani
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
kewashi not hito shura not michi naka not
chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
gokusai shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro memi not hiraite
shikato ima wo mikiwamero "yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa
iza mairou!
we to are fighting dreamers
takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers
narifuri kamawazu
shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire! "bam!"
Episode #92
Or Not!
The answer of Tsunade
It is  useless.
Merda. I go…
You are the only one to being able to recover the arms of Orochimaru-sama.
Why we do not make an agreement?
Your brother and the man who you loved…
I can bring back them while still alive.
With a "Kinjustu" that I have developed.
[ Technical Forbidden ]
You would not want to be of new with they, Tsunade?
You stop yourselves! Not listened to theirs menzogne!
Their dreams.... Your dreams. You have forgotten your dreams?
The village has to you chosen, Tsunade…
So that it becomes the Fifth Hokage di Konoha.
In the past the Hokage has always protect Konoha and its inhabitants.
For preservare the things and the village as they were. It was their dream.
They put their life in game for this dream.
You are not held to answer to me immediately.
However,
We would want your answer between one week.
In order to realize this prohibited technique, there is need of a sacrifice.
You will have to prepare two bodies when it is the moment.
You approach yourselves!
Fairies your game!
Then, than what you bet?
Someone? Gone! Played!
I ask myself which it will be its decision.
If it is of agreement with what we have proposed to it, your arms will be recovered, Orochimaru-sama.
Cos ì  we will be able to destroy Konoha.
And Tsunade-sama will be able to find again the persons whom it loves.
But.... If it refuses…
In this case, we will have impossessarci of she with the force in order to recover my arms.
It will not be easy.
Sai that…
Not there is no reason to preoccuparsi.
They are the solo to know its force and its weaknesses.
It will accept our conditions, sure.
Well, in this third exercise, you will have to be remembered of all the one which you have learned.
It uses 100% of your power.
Like with the football, you make a symbol, and imagines yours chakra focusing to you on that point.
Still and still in my head, I know it!
But arrival always not to extract correctly the totality of mine chakra.
That technique is useless.... What hopes to make?
It cannot  be serious.
This is because this child says that she dreams to become Hokage and other stupidities.
Tomorrow?
E' be a pleasure.
The old man will return!
You want to still meet Orochimaru?
If it has hesitated to rispodermi…
reason must is to us one.
I ask myself what it has made during one week.
Naruto is not returned, is alarming.
Perhaps I must have an other argument with Tsunade.
Useless…
I do not have… the time....  I will not be able  to make it in time.
This is…
Which thing is happened, Naruto-kun? You are well?
Which thing is?
There is the full moon, you know?
And if a glass were gone to drink?
Tomorrow it is the end of the promised week to Naruto.
I ask myself if Naruto is improved.
Who  can  say it…
Perhaps I would have to order some other thing.
Of the ravanelli, please.
Endured.
Getlteman…
Oh! These have the delicious air.
Tsunade-sama!
Naruto-kun is…
Its state is critical.
Its right hand has been burnt from the chakra.
In these conditions, it will not be waked up before tomorrow.
Jiraiya had reason. I would not have never had to make this bet stupid.
All and two.... What we go to earn to us to work hardly cos  ì?
That  seems cos ì  stupid.
Tomorrow…
Tomorrow, gone ve I do not pray any!
Why you do not answer?
Tsunade-sama, you answer to me, ve I pray some!
If gone …
Which thing you will make?
Even if I must sacrifice my life, I will stop  to you.
Shizune! To who creeds to speak!?
Getlteman, is morning.
Returned to house.
Cabbage…
Ehi, getlteman, you wake up yourselves!
Ehi! Which thing you have?
If it dulled an unexpected, we would be in the troubles.
Which thing you want that make?
You kill it …
the girl who accompanies Tsunade.
I have the impression that you do not have confidence of me entire.
Since I have confidence in you…
You can be awake on Sasuke-kun?
Much good…
Kabuto, if you want to stop to me,
You must kill Sasuke-kun immediately.
You cannot kill to me, this you know it?
Ehi. Ehi!
Naruto-kun?
Cabbage! Which hours are now?
Not! Which day is?
It is  luned ì....  But…
Which thing is?
You are well?
You would have had to sleep two days at least…
For how much me memories, import the wound little,
A night of sleep is sufficient so that recoveries.
I see. This would be Kyuubi?
It does not import to me, dov' has gone the old woman?
It is  the day of our bet today.
And on purpose of that technique?
It is not still to point! But…
When the moment will come,  I will use  an other method in order to make it.
I would not have to remain here without to make nothing.
Naruto-kun, remains here.
You are…
Which thing? Eh?
It waits for, Shizune.
Cursed Tsunade.... it has put of the drug in mine sakè…
I cannot concentrate mine correctly chakra,
And my body partially is paralyzed .
I cannot launch correctly not even a Kunai.
Which thing would have made if it had hit to me?
It is  pietoso!
In spite of all continuing to boast you of being a great Ninja…
You are made to fregare with one technical perversa, Ero-senin!
You close the spout!
Even if it is old, is always a specialist doctor.
E' the only person who  can  paralyze a Ninja with the medicine.
In this state, not even a person as me  she can  make nothing…
Jiraiya-sama, as felt?
Better than what you thought.
They are perhaps to a third party of my normal state.
I would not have never thought that Jiraiya-sama was here…
Me I would not be waited for…
I would have to return now.
And in more, Naruto-kun…
us six also you.
Ehi, Shizune!
S ì!
Which type of conversation you have had with Orochimaru?
Only come E' in order to speak?
Orochimaru?
I wanted to believe in Tsunade-sama.
This is the reason for which I did not want to speak of.
But…
We do not have time! Seguitemi, ve I pray some!
I will explain  you  road making!
Much good!
I come anch'!
Which it is your answer?
Which thing?
For this kind of things, the answer would have to be "not!"
Thus it does not go well…
It only lives for its memories…
The worse one that it could succeed, is that Tsunade is made to kill.
Merda!
I will recover  your arms.
But, you warning not to touch the village, if not…
Why not?
Now…
As soon as its arms will be recovered, Konoha will attack.
We must stop it immediately.
Otherwise, the situation will become still more dangerous.
Not jokes!
You are l ì,  not is no need of preoccuparsi.
Which thing means all this?
Six come in order to betray to me?
Tsunade!
The Believe your promised, it' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kado ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aru ka
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
yume it has ryuusei not you ni
ameagari of niji of you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoui tsudzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naru yo
gomakashitari shinai to chikau yo
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
One would say that Tsunade has refused the agreement.
Ero-Sennin! Large outbreak has been one!
Cabbage, has been truly strong!
We are the next ones, Naruto!
Next episode
The end of negotiates to you