Subbed by NW_aTi _
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not fukinukeru
Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda YEAH!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite kanashimi mo
hoho tsutatte namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Baby
I will let out  you  here.
Moreover  esaudirò  also an other desire.
Not preoccuparti. This your strong will
it will continue to survive within of me.
All it will not go lost.
Then I take your body.
For some years it will have a body
in which the resurrezione will not work.
But there will be an other occasion.
Effectively…
… I am not worth null like container
for the technique of the resurrezione.
Having lost all…
… it was difficult to find the scope to me of my life.
Hour  but  they are successful finally
to understand which it is.
Even if  I will not make  from container
I  will be to carry that new one here.
Also to cost of living....
E' my thanks for
my getlteman, Orochimaru-sama.
E' the last thing that  can  make a useless being like me.
Episode #119
A serious error! A new enemy!
They are fast!
Akamaru!
Idiot, you come as soon as you have made.
Oh not!
Perfect.
Ce we have made it!
Akamaru! Optimal job!
You stop it to turn to me around!
Akamaru!
You stop it of piagnucolare, six dead bastard!
I will kill  to you!
It waits for to me!
Kiba!
Akamaru!
Eternal damnation.>.
Cos' has happened?
Idiots!
Where are ended Kiba and Akamaru?
It is selling also the other.
It cannot  be helped.
I  will fight  us.
You you take the barrel and you go ahead.
Shikamaru.>.
Sbrigati, you go!
Why six.>.?
Me spiace, Naruto…
I suppose to have made the calculations badly.
Kimimaro.
Six in delay, Tayuya.
And then, cos' it is happened to the others three?
You, once you made part of the five
Because six…
Your body.>.
Your body is not more.>.
I do not move more using my body.
I move with the force of my spirit.
Fool.>.
You are living more of the due.>.
I am beginning to understand.
The feeling that test existing itself with the single mind
without the constriction of the body.
E' like if same touching a part
of the dreams of Orochimaru-sama.
Orochimaru!
This container is essential for those dreams.
The body that Orochimaru wishes truly.
But you boys were a po' in delay.
Arrived E' an other dangerous enemy.
This feeling… Whichever is not one.
In any case, I must study the situation.
If we distracted ourselves
and we attacked without to think
Because!
About what devil you are speaking?
Naruto!
They give Sasuke behind to us!
It waits for!
Tayuya.>.
The reason for which I still do not have victim of a murder to you,
it is why you must survive in order to complete one mission.
And my mission,
it is to carry that one to Orochimaru-sama.
It is not too much late?
You I have said.
That one is the body that Orochimaru-sama
it wishes truly.
You want to say that it will be the next container?
Exactly.
And this is the maximum that I can make.
Those average cartridges, I leave them you.
Sasuke…
That bastard!
It calm Naruto To You.
As I can be calmed!
In this way,
Sasuke will be to outside of our capacity!
What Naruto says is true.
This is one mission in order to bring back Sasuke to Konoha.
For the resolution of this mission,
I must think next to the better strategy to take.
It shocks!
I will kill  to you  endured!
Naruto, listens.
It makes as I say to you.
Kage Bunshin is its single dangerous movement,
a typical combat body to body from idiots.
And it is a mediocre utilizzatore
of the techniques of the shadow.
I suppose is rather an acute and shrewed head.
Understood?
We go, losing!
We are two against one.
We exceed in number!
If there are two of we, we can make it us!
We go, Naruto!
We begin!
Stupid pieces of merda! It does not import how many you are
it will not make some difference.
Not to underrate our job of square.
We go!
Force!
Hour, Naruto!
I will take  to you  to soccer in seating!
Completed mission.
Goodbye!
Eternal damnation, you have brailed up to me!
Job of square! Idiot!
Eternal damnation.
I imagine you would not fall
in the same technique an other time, eh?
Marmocchio!
Beh, I imagine that to leave it to go via
good idea has been one!
It remembers.>.
.. the techniques are not the single way in order to fight.
I leave you, Shikamaru.
Arrival, Sasuke!
It succeeded to move
truly well with that body.
Kabuto.>.
I do not know what you you have asked to make to it,
but he seems cruel.
It is not like seems,
I have not given some order to it.
It does not appeal to to me to force
the persons to make the things.
It has made of its spontaneous will.
Only for you, the solo that he esteem.
Kabuto,
you have one sure twisted personality.
Orochimaru-sama, for you, Kimimaro was a perfect being.
Its ideas were spotted with the dusk
like yours.
It has idolizzato to you.
It adored to you and it admired to you like a fanatic.
For more, it was one shinobi coming from from the clan
that it possessed the bodies nearer the perfection.
and their abilities have inherit all.
Cos ì, he exists for being…
S ì.>.
the single thought to lose it
it makes me to rabbrividire.
Task still to the man
that my spirit has truly wished.
The body that more I wanted,
Kimimaro…
And if it had not been infected from that disease,
the murder of the Hokage would have been completed.
I seal!
My arms.>.
You will not be more in a position to using your arms.
Hour that both your arms are unusable,
you will not be more in a position to completing seals.
I have taken your Ninjutsu!
You that you would want to destroy Konoha, have lost!
Orochimaru, six one foolish…
That sin, we will not be able to die together
.. my student.
We see again the other world.
Sasuke.>.
Still it has not arrived?
It would want not to have last all those suffering?
In this world, it seems that not always the things
they go like presupposed.
E' only one time issue,
Orochimaru-sama.
If Tayuya will make return,
I will kill.
It waits for!
Hey!
We see, as I would have to defeat it?
You.>.
Those eyes.>.
It seems has one strange chakra.
What has intention to make Orochimaru!
Why it wants Sasuke!
Orochimaru-sama has already perfected
the technique of immortality.
To acquire all the techniques,
it demands much time.
What must make us with Sasuke!
Although he is immortale,
its body  cannot  last in eternal.
Before that the body is decomposed,
new and a more strong body is maintained within a container of spirits.
And that body e' Sasuke!
Exactly.
Like if.>.
.. you left to happen!
Fool.
Insignificant small man, cos' you have intention to make?
And then, it watches cos' is happened.
Every time, in order to go ahead
you have sacrificed one of your members.
Sasuke..quel boy is cos ì  precious for you?
For one single person,
how many members of your square you will lose?
A six worm.
It could be true.
This is my first mission
like squad leader.
Obviously they are preoccupied, seeing like the number
of my companions of square it has decreased.
I do not know neanche if my actions
they are corrected or less.
And I know of accounting for their screw.
And they are more than preoccupied for the kidnapped boy.
I would have to think next to the other four.
To interrupt the mission would have been second the rules.
Then because you have not made it?
In this world,
all it does not work as a game of the scappa via.>.
After all, we are not the type of persons,
that they would abandon one kidnapped person,
for our single salvation.
Included me.
For the exactitude, they are a lazy one that it loves to watch clouds.
They are not the type of person who says to the other thing to make.
The only thing that I can make for they is…
… to believe in they.
It listens,
I have not never thought to sacrifice them.
Neanche I have not thought that they are died.
I have not never underrated my companions of square.
Found!
Kuchiyose not Jutsu!
It does not go well.
I will play  you  a funeral song.
You would not have to underrate us, bastard!
I will succeed  to carry to me via Sasuke
Interesting.
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
bokura kara shaberi kaketure meiwaku ni omou kara
sonna fuan wo dashite kakaetie yuuki wo mitayo
umaku shaerinai bokuno bukiyou na hanashi
kimi wa mimi wo sorasazuni chanto kiite kuretayo
soredaked bokuwa ukarete shimaunosa
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yone
setsunai yo dakedo
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de!
hajimete kimi to shabereta