You feel, Kakashi-sensei has said to me that
only some species of living beings is in a position to speaking, true?
But that you say ?
The moment also for Akamaru will arrive
Indeed?
I have always known that
Pakkun put us tantissimo time before
to pronounce the name of Kakashi-sensei
Beh, we do not have much choice
With a master like you.>.
What you have said!?
What you would want to say !
Also I can speak
You do not have to be strained.>.
A six cat!!
Bravo, Akamaru!
Fagli to feel qualcos' other!
Ooh! It continues to try, Akamaru!
Happy new year!
Aaaaah!!!
Terrible E'!
Happy new year!
This year we will make of our best,
therefore you do not stop to follow to us!
Well.>.
Special nose-dive!
* An other year with Naruto *
The furious battle between the two genin in the Dattebayo Special
.. it is in order to begin!
Subbed by # [ Fabry]
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na
not fukinukeru
Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda Yeah!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite
kanashimi mo hoho tsutatte
namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa tsuyoi
uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Baby
Jyuukenhou
Hakke Rokujyuu Yonshou!
[ Technical of the 64 closings ]
It does not go well!
Hakke Ni-Sho (2¡)
Yon-sho (4¡)
Has-sho (8¡)
Juroku-sho (16¡)
Sanju-ni-sho (32¡)
Rokuju-yon-sho (64¡)
That it meansÉ
One golden shield.
Made E' of the same fuoriusciva substance that from its mouth
Too much dangerous.>.
I knew that if pits be hurt seriously
my nervous system would have been damaged
and I could not more have pasted the chakra
Six gone to us close.>.
A six monster!
To how much it seems not of you produce solo from the mouth
Once rilasciato in the air, my Kumo Nenkin
metallic alloy is transformed in one
And it prevents to the chakra to pass to us through
Moreover.>.
É I not only succeed in rilasciarlo from my mouth
but also from all the pori of my body
Then the attacks to the escape pointsÉ
É they are useless.
With he I cannot use the ragnatela
and I cannot not use
the attacks draw near to you
This means that I must by force
to kill it from far away
This attack does not make some noiseÉ
me it will want a moment to us.
Game Over (ended game)
The kunai trap is one!
What!
Hakkeshou Kaiten!
M-Ma.. likeÉ?
This boyÉ
É he sees to us also behind!
And that one its defenseÉ
It succeeds to use the chakra
in order to have an attack direct?
If we do not fight one against one
it will be the end for we
Of it we have not already spoken?
Sbrigatevi to continue.
I will catch up  you  more late.
We must fight one against oneÉ
NarutoÉ
You have of the better eyes of mine
NejiÉ
it tries to catch up to us!
How  it can  see to me?
What hides behind that boyÉ
I know that six l “
You come outside!
Those eyesÉ
they do not only succeed to see the flow of the chakra
Eccomi of forehead to a boy unexpectedly equipped
This combat at a distance does not go well
I must succeed to fight more give near
Why not?
WellÉ
I must admit that the difficulty
of this game rather it is elevated
It will want to say that  I  will put myself mean it anch'.
Completely various E' from before.
The activity of its chakra has grown
MoreoverÉ
those signsÉ
With that one its defenseÉ
my attack has schivato gives behindÉ
É and it is even successful to understand my position.
This means that it has is one seen normal
that one to wide beam arranged together
Moreover it has also that technique from its part....
thereforeÉ
Kuchiyose not Jutsu!
I will find  a system in order to face
your abilities!
It succeeds to use the chakra in order to avoid
with the spin the direct attacks
I must only stop it!
You come outside!
Kaiten!
It has begun to slow down.
Hour!
You die!
As soon as in kunai it has been approached
it has used the chakra in order to have it
It wanted to stop the Hakkeshou Kaiten with the threads of chakra
That type.>.
I must succeed to cut them!
Since the spin does not work,
I will have  to avoid them one by one in order now!
E' more strongly in the drawn near combat
If I take care myself of he from far away, it will not be a problem
And hour. it makes to see like you cables me
Hakke Rokujyuu Yonshou!
Ce is too many!
Its position is changed.
Hakke Hyaku ni Ju Hashou
[ Technical dele 128 closings ]
Fast E'!
The speed of its hands is doubled
If you had to receive a critical blow, would be the end
If you have intention to fight in this way.>.
I will defy  to you  to equal crews!
Ce is too many!
I cannot make it us
I do not succeed more in ruotare.
It seems that it has one visual to 360¡.
It examines the things through the visual one drawn near,
and it succeeds to see also to long distancesÉ
Arranging these two succeed in
to contrast the enemy attacks
Moreover, with its visual one to 360¡
it possesses a frightful field of vision
From its precente reaction, it seems justÉ
..  that it is in a position to localizing all the kunai
in a beam of 50 meters
But for some reason,
it has been a kunai that it is not successful to avoid
Well then!
Hakke RokujyuuÉ
I have understoodÉ
Stavolta ce will be some still more!
Hour I will hit  it  with two.>.
For your information, me I waited for.
To how much it seemsÉ
É your defensive techniques
they have a pair of points weak people.
This means that yours doujutsu it is not complete!
That tenacityÉ
the end is being approached!
Hey hey.
You want to continue to strain to you uselessly?
More the weak person in one easy challenge cos  “
he must die for first. E' its destiny.
You cannot defeat to me!
Not stillÉ not stillÉ
LeeÉ
How much six stubborn one.
You do not have no possibility to win.
Tu and Neji you are various.
It is a genius.
A genius?
Cos' is a genius!?
Even if I do not have some talent,  dimoster˜  to that with the engagement  I will succeed  to strike a genius!
Not servants to nothing, Lee
She does not import how much engagement you will put to us.
You will not be able to never strike to me.
Our destiny already is established
Hinata-samaÉ
Six too much ingenuous one
The persons cannot change
In this crashÉ
your destiny already had been decided sin from the beginning
Cavolate!
If you did not try,
how I would make knowing the truth?
And this will be the last one.
Jyuuken!
Personage weak person #1:
complete destruction
Even if it was be a matter of losing,
they are amused to me equally.
It has intercepted my attack.>.
perhaps why I have lacked little its blind point
or perhaps why I find myself to the inside
of the beam of 50 meters
Well
Therefore you will make me to still amuse a po, true?
You of they are pleasing.
We omit that bastard ciccione of Jiroubou,
É but what is making Kidoumaru?
Che stronzo.
.. Its usual defect to put itself to play.
Perhaps it has met someone of interesting
When that idiot plays too much
he ends for having problems
and he enters too much soon in that state
But when he catches up according to stage
for the adversary it is the end!
Nejuu seigo
100%
Damages.>.
to the maximum!
You die!
Ended E'.
What!
There is lacked little.
It could be lethalÉ
É but they are successful to have it little
Therefore it is trueÉ
Also it has uncovered the secret of the Byakugan
That he happens!
M-Ma like.>.?
Why it has hit it 15cm over the critical point?
I have understood.>.
Those chakraÉ
For all this time it has not made other that
to rilasciare continuously of the chakra around to its body
In a great area cos  “É
I am not astonished that it is successful to
to intercept the arrow
É and to modify of the distance
with all those chakra
In order to emit of one such amount
it must have made one mortal effort them
It could not makes nothing us
without this espediente
Therefore, I do not have store clerk no error.
As I thought, it was not in degree
to see the arrow.
Its are not useless attacks.
He is using them in order to acquire information.
He is beginning to understand the defects of my eyes
Impressive.
E' more strongly between all the enemies with which I have fought
It has a field of vision of 360¡
É  and it succeeds to localize with precision
all the attacks in the beam of 50 meters
But for some reasonÉ
É it has been a kunai that it is not successful to avoid.
Why it is not successful to schivarlo of all?
Simply why  it cannot  see it.
In other wordsÉ
its doujutsu has a blind point
The kunai that he catches up he does not come seen
É therefore it  cannot  opporvi resistance
Here why it uses that technique when are attacks directed to the blind point
I have analyzed to all the attacks and I have understood them completely
Its blind point is found
under one small zone under its before vertebra
True E' that muovendosi
it changes the position of that point
É  and it becomes more difficult to predere the sight
But with me it is all useless.
The jyuuken it does not have no effect if
it does not find to you near the enemy
And however you cannot allow the lusso you
to think next to like approaching to you me.
E' the moment to only think to scappare.
That you oppose yourself or not, morirai equally.
It seems that it it is remained least chakra.
In a challenge more the weak person is the first one to die
E' its destiny.
Useless E' all.
A thread!
I have understood. using that threadÉ
I have lacked little.
I will have  to give more spin the next one.
Even if it hit a tree, it would cut it,
therefore the distance will not come had
I will use  like before
a thread filled up of chakra
and I will control  it  for 50 meters
aiming towards the target.
I will characterize  the blind zone and  I will launch  the arrow to its inside
You still succeed to raise to you?
Strong E'É
much more strongly than meÉ
Me it is remained least chakra
Not creed that  I will succeed  to avoid
of the all next attack
Therefore the truth is this!
I will strike  to you.
NarutoÉ
what you would make?
Ok.>.
Creed that ce I would not make it howeverÉ
Mmm. It has been stopped.
One will have surrendered?
I must be assessed some.
Precision: 120%
Destructive power: principle!
Taken!
Eccoti.
Jyuuken!
C-Cosa?
It is a-ancora.>.
But that blow would have had to kill it.
I have destroyed riversandoci within mine chakra.
Useless E' all against mine jyuuken.
Jyuuken.>.
It has made to flow remained its chakra in the thread
Eight birdsÉ
I more do not succeed to see it
E-eccoÉ
I have various organs damages to you
but in some way
I still succeed to move to me
Six losing.
You I have said
I will not never surrender .
Why you want at all costs
to go against your destiny?
Why you have called to me losing!
If tasks that one what is impossible,
you would not have more to make nothing!
When  I am  hokage,
I will transform  the Hyuuga clan!
Preferred yours ninjutsu.>.
They have been imprudent.
The Bunshin jutsu was not
technique that I hated more.
And it plants to speak about those cavolate
on the destiny and not being able to change it
With the exception of me, you not six losing.
Naruto!
I have fear that we are only remained three.
Not preoccuparti of these things.
Chouji and Neji will catch up to us soon.
Chouji had its secret movements
and Neji.. beh, I know it why I have to us
combattutto to the Chuunin examination
What you know?
HeÉ
it is a true genius!
I do not have intention to lose!
Even if my adversary
he is much more strongly than me!
Even if my body had to yield!
You will not succeed to strike to me.
This is the reason for which
I cannot lose!
Stavolta I have store clerk an error.
Six one that plays too muchÉ
Its chakraÉ
É why?
It would have had to die to the moment
How  it can  be still alive?
Any thing you had tried
É I would not be successful however to avoid it
MoreoverÉ
.. I knew also my points weak people
They were eight birds?
Blind zone in this is one byakugan
ButÉ
knowing that all your attacks
they are directed in that zone
I have been able to rilasciare mine chakra
l “  in order to only have the attack
To move a pair of centimeters
in order to receive the attack
it has not been cos “  laborious.
I would have been hurt seriously,
but I would have avoided one dead women instantaneous
Therefore you have chosen to receive the blowÉ
You knew of having to die howeverÉ
É why to push to you cos “  beyond?
YouÉ
six one of the stronger enemies
with which it has fought.
But there is a reason for which I cannot lose.
One of the stronger adversaries
with which I have fought
it has said to me:
With the exception of me, you not six losing
WhatÉ
Genius has always called me
For this I cannot lose,
for all those that believe that I am a genius.
You have said that the destiny of more the weak person
it is to die for first, true?
It watches hour the situzione.
The destiny is not something
that the persons decide!
We will seeÉ
Are in order to die also you.
NejiÉ
you must living.
Six the one which has more talent
in all the Hyuuga clan.
IÉ
I cannot die easy cos  “.
Even if you oppose yourself,
you cannot change the flow of the time
Sasuke-sama is scappato of its
spontaneous will with the ninja of the sound.
Sasuke by now is wrapped from the dusk
Not.
NarutoÉ
Your eyes are better of mine.
There is someone that  can  find Sasuke
and to save it from the darknesses.
Sasuke-sama is property of Orochimaru
It does not import who goes. He not ver -
They will save!
Why. Naruto.>.
you.>.
..  t-you .>.
..  you have saved to me from the dusk.
It speaks to vanvera until to the end.
But never they have not been struck cos “
except with Kimimaro
Eternal damnationÉ
BoysÉ
I leave all the rest you