Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh!  Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the fire!BANG!
Suiton !
(Technical of Water)
Suikodan not Jutsu!
(Technical of the Squalo d' Acqua)
My same technique?
In order which reason devil you have caught up to us?
Beh, before I had asked you two to follow them…
But I was being bored…
What makes in this rinnegato village a ninja us like you?
Hatake Kakashi…
Epiosdio #82
Sharingan VS Sharingan !!
What!
Why I would have to follow in one search mission to you, Erosennin?
(Pervertito Hermit)
Not, normal search mission will not be one.
There is a woman to which I want to turn some questions,
therefore I must find it at all costs.
I do not have time to lose with your sciocchezze from pervertito.
I must train to me !!
To train to you?
Kakashi-sensei…
It must teach many things to me, the Chidori as an example…
In truth it is a pessimo teaching, Kakashi-sensei.
Well, uhm…
Creed that you will not be able to never padroneggiare that technique…
Eh!
Other important thing…
… the woman of which I spoke to you is truly
a lot sexy. You do not want to know it?
For nothing!
They are not a boy who makes itself to convince a lot
easy from a EroSennin like you!
However.... NOT !!
Then I do not have other choice.>.
That sin… I know one technical the much most powerful one of the Chidori.
Task that  I will carry  Sasuke with me.
I have changed idea!  I will come!
I go to prepare the suitcases!
EroSennin, waits for to me here!
Eh… E' truly a likeable child.
Its eyes are still the same ones once, in fact…
… she is the true heir of the Sharingan.
This is worse the situation in which we could ourselves be found.
That beautiful surprise. I am not astonished
that you have copied my Jutsu.(Tecnica)
Beyond to Itachi-saint other exists qualcun that has the same look…
Its name is.... the Ninja Kakashi Copy.
The surprise is also mine.
The two men suspiciones to the store of dolciumi…
… they are themselves demonstrates to you to be Uchiha Itachi…
… and from the village of the Fog, Hoshigaki Kisame, the searched one.
Well, well… You know also my name. They are honored.
If not me mistake… you six one of the 7 shinobi-katana of the village of the Fog…
… and that large katana must be the Samehada (Skin Squalo).
I have felt to say that six met to you with that child of Yabuza.
.>.
Task that we will have of that to amuse to us…
Stopped, Kisame!
If you had to meet to you against of he…
… you would remain hurt sure.
Moreover, if we lose still other time, others ninja will arrive.
But…
Not to lose sight our objective…
… we have not come in order makes other enemies here us.
Then you say which to us are your scopes.
We have come to try something that it interests to us.
To try.>.?
What been exactly trying?
You are careful, I have said that only Kisame does not have to be struck.
Ninpou: Suiton Suijinheki!
(Ninja Art: Water wall)
That incredible speed…
My eyes do not succeed to follow it.
It has used the shuriken in the right hand like decoy…
… for distrarmi from its Suiton (Water Attack)
that it aimed at my legs.
Much good, Kakashi-saint…
Your intuito one is impressive.... not creeds?
Kage Bushin! (Cloni d' Ombra)
The speed of its Jutsu is incredible!
It was a Mizu Bushin! (Clone d' Acqua)
It seems that ninja the copy has learned from ours
village much Suiton not Jutsu. (Technical of Water)
Nice (Well), Kakashi.
You are Down, Kurenai!
This is a Kage Bushin.
Kakashi! Kurenai!
It has made to explode the Kage Bushin?
Technical new tecniche..nuove!!!
Sakura-chan finally innamorerà of me.
Kakashi-sensei and Sasuke will be surprises also they.
Kakashi !
Not to lower your guard.
This man has become a commander ANBU when he had still 13 years.
I did not think was much fort.
Not. It has not still shown its true power.
Although do not make part of the Uchiha clan…
You possess the Sharingan and its powers…
But you will not be able to never take advantage of its true power inasmuch as a not six Uchiha.
Exactly. It has made center easy.
Why creeds that the Uchiha clan is feared and considered the best one?
The answer is…
Sharingan.
I will show  you  the real power of this Kekkei Genkai.
(To be able inherited with the blood)
It cannot  be… is put badly.
You two! It in the eyes does not watch to you!
For no reason you open the eyes, if you made it would be fine yours.
Of hour in then, only someone that has the Sharingan  can  face it.
Even if you possess the Sharingan…
…  to my Mangekyou Sharingan you will be able to resist very little.
(Sharingan Kaleidoscope)
In fact…
The Sharingan has one special DouJutsu…
(Technical with the eyes)
The Genjutsu Tsukuyomi is one its prerogative.
(illusory Art of the God of the Moon)
In order to strike to me, there is need of someone that possesses
my same Kekkei Genkai Sharingan.
Sasuke?
Without the Kekkei Genkai how much you will be able to resist to me?
This is… a Genjutsu? (illusory Art)
In the world of the Tsukuyomi…
I control space and the time…
… and even the mass of the objects.
Beginning from now, you will be subordinate to 72 hours of tortures.
This is....
In the world of the Tsukuyomi…
I control space and the time…
… and even the mass of the objects.
It calm to you…
E' only a Genjutsu.
Not to underrate this world only why creeds illusion is one.
These suffering are real for your spirit.
These suffering are real even if come from a Genjutsu.
For how much time your spirit will succeed sopportar it?
59 minuteren and 59 second ones lack still 71 hours.
This is…
This is only…
What succeeds arrived Kakashi?E' the moment to open our eyes?
N-Non still…
What has happened?
Six collapsed down without warning hardly he have ended to speak !
Three entire days in that illusion… The Genjutsu is lasted
less than a second in the real world.
But… Why it has not killed to me?
It would have been easy for he.
Oh! That Jutsu only serves to stremare the spirit of the enemy…
But for Itachi-saint it would be dangerous to use to along those eyes.
What you are trying… è Sasuke, is not true?
We are not trying the inheritance of the Fourth Hokage.
These two… what want?
Naruto?
E' a lot that is not looked at to us.
How many years are that lathes not to visit the village?
Kakashi.
I  of Naruto will take to cure.
The task of star behind Naruto you
it has been given from the Third party…
perhaps… but to the state they of the things puts into effect
your level is not enough high.
About what you are speaking?
I have controlled the acts of Orochimaru
sin from when it has left the village.
E' clearly that sooner or later it will try
to return in this village.
But this is not the main problem that plagues to me…
That is?
Entered E' to make part of one organization…
Organization?
Which type of organization is?
I do not know the details…
Nine shinobi they have formed one small organization
Akatsuki call (Red Moon).
Until they have not arranged nothing of worrisome now....
They have continued to collect information.
But the real problem is the members…
Many of they are sly criminals signal to you
in the Bingo Book. (Book of Searches to you).
Of they it would only make to become one
mission of S class much difficult one.
To the inside of the organization… there is also Itachi.
E' difficult to believe those nine is not
I hand on nothing of dangerous.
You must have understood where I want to arrive with my speech…
However Orochimaru has left of recent the organization.
From that moment… the members are puttinges in travel in groups
of two learning Jutsu and trying something other.
Tasks are trying Kyubi?
(the vixen to Nine Tails)
E' the more reasonable hypothesis….
After all it is the Youma that possesses the more imposing Chakra.
(Stirpe di Mythical Demoni)
Kakashi…
Naruto must be prepared.....
They will find sooner or later.
This is its destiny.
Of hour in then occupied only of Sasuke.
It must learn to use R-al.meglio its Sharingan.
I will take  Naruto with me and I will guide  it  personally.
Been trying… Naruto and its Kyubi?
You have made the first movement… but you know that
we were to acquaintance of your arrival.
The name of the organization is Akatsuki, is not true?
Akatsuki?
Kisame, occupied of Kakashi-saint.
These persons must disappear.
Konoha Gouriki Senpou!
(Powerful cyclone of the leaf of Konoha)
Who devil six?
They are the noble green flower of Konoha…
Maito Gai!
I thought pits one wild beast!
(NdT the Kanji of the flower and the beast is similar)
The thing is made interesting.
Not to underrate it.
As I thought… Itachi.
It watches as they have reduced Kakashi…
Not to watch in the eyes of Itachi, Gai.
You will come caught in its Jutsu.
I know very well.
Considering that I trained myself with Kakashi…
They are accustomed to fight an adversary who uses the Sharingan.
You two… open the eyes.
But…
When you fight against a Sharingan, you must
to only avoid to watch it in the eyes.
The better trick is to concentrate the look
on its feet, in order to foretell the movements.
To think to us well, your reasoning is corrected…
But you the six only one who succeed to make one similar what.
Well. I must teach an other trick to you in order to understand
the movements of the enemy solo from its feet…
But we do not have time in this moment enough.
In order now, we think the enemy!
What we make?
Kurenai, you Kakashi door in hospital.
Asuma, you cover to me.
He goes well.
In order now, until that they will not arrive
he reinforces ANBU that I have called…
… we will hold them to we attend… two.
Interesting… Six truly kind one.
Kisame. We withdraw ourselves.
We have not come in order to begin one here war.
Ill-fatedly… ogni ulterior effort would not have sense.
Ce we go some.
I was in order to begin to amuse to me…
… it does not have sense however.
Ready!
We go!!
Six sure one that you want to carry with you all that one roba?
We are not going in train through mountains.
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete
Uh!Uh!Uh!Uh!Guarda that one
beautifulst laggiù girl!
She is winking.
She watches, Naruto! E' sure interested me!
Not! Sakura-chan is sure prettier!
We go, Naruto!
Yeah!
It alone returns to house to train to you now.
Hey! Che stupidaggini you go saying!
Next Nose-dive: Ohh Not!
Gabbato Jiraya! The problem of Naruto!
My training, diamine!!