Subbed by Kyubi
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
Even if they are not equipped in the Ninjutsu and the Genjutsu…
I will try  that I can become an excellent Ninja!
E' the more important thing for me!
Well.
Today, I will give  to us  within!
Ehi Sopracciglione!
Buongiorno, Naruto-kun.
Ah! Then!? The Old one has controlled to you?
Com' has gone? Com' has gone?
Konoha is in difficulty…
It is necessary to work hard in order to replace it in sixth.
S ì  is true…
Sopracciglione, is sure that you will recover quickly. And you will come to us to aiut…
-  Naruto nii-chan!
What happens ?
Draft of Konohamaru-chan…
Eh? Konohamaru?
It has been locked in.
Eh? Locked up?
Episode #99
What it had inherited the will of the Fire
Konohamaru, not to obligate to us to smash in the door.
Tried to enter!
For who you have taken to me?
They are the grandson of the Sandaime
If you face to me it wants to say that…
Grandfather…
He wants to say that you will face the same Hokage!
Perhaps it is the case that Tsunade-sama arranges this matter.>.
I introduce you my bombs to the pepper!
You still try to us and ve of it you will repent.>.
Even if six its grandson…
Sure behaviors cannot be accepted!
You close the spout!
E' morning soon and is already all this din.>.
I felt to you from the other part of the palace.>.
Tsunade-sama…
Ah?
He is  a child who you da' all these problems?
S ì.
Better for you that the facades to exit from l ì.>.
The problem is that she is the grandson of the Sandaime.
M' it does not interest that she is its grandson!
They are the grandaughter of the Shodaime!
I must become bad?
Sbrigatevi and portatelo outside!
S ì!
Waited for!
Naruto-kun!
Ehi! Waited for!
I do not know what has happened, but…
Please, you are not hard with Konohamaru, Old.
It is  one of your friends?
S ì.
I  will speak!
Left to make me!
Much good, but I want that it is outside before the aim of the day!
Tsunade-sama!
Waited for!
You excuse to me.
Oh Sakura-chan.
Sasuke-kun has left yesterday.
Today they have come to find Lee.
It is  to the rieducazione center?
Not, it is not returned.
It is not from he to be cos ì  in delay.
Already.>.
There is a 50% of probability that goes to good aim
If you had to fail, moriresti
Ehi! Konohamaru! Six driven crazy?
From you exit of and we go to eat of the ramen.
Not you preoccuparti.>.
satisfied I!!
Also of the toasted pig!
Ah? Then also an egg!
Then?
You want to answer to me!
You are zitto! Idiot!
Which thing?
I have understood well? '' idiot  ' '?
You open this door!
Otherwise the background!
If six convinced to make it us, repair to you!!
Maledizione!
Naruto nii-chan…
Ah! Lee-saint.
You were here therefore.
It knows.... Sakura-saint.
You hold.
For.... me?
Thanks thousands!
Scusami, Sakura-Saint.
It is not nothing.
It seems that Sasuke-kun is of new in feet
It is  thanks to Tsunade-sama.
If it is taken care of you, you will be able to return soon to your missions.
Indeed?
It makes it appeal to to feel it me.
As I imagined, Tsunade-sama is extraordinary.
You would have to see it also you, Lee-saint.
It will cure to you, is sure!
S ì.
If I can make any thing …
Dimmelo.
Thanks thousands.
Sakura-saint.
Well, we look at ourselves.
Not there is a bar opened to this hour…
Why it would have to be opened to this hour ?
Which hour thoughts that are?
I cannot drink.
and not to play.>.
That village boring.
One acknowledges well …
the infuence of the Sandaime.
Tsunade-sama!
Tired Sono cos  ì…
I have wants of rilassarmi…
To beautiful sakè a hot one
Much good.
I will carry  to you  where you can have all
Eh?
But in exchange you will have to make qualche.cosa.
Gone! You drink until is warm!
Shizune.
Six become without warning a lot demanding.
They have not become demanding.
But  it can  be that you to being are incosciente.
Incosciente?
If not gone in your office, not fairies never nothing.
This is because does not want to make nothing, true ?
Same reason for which you have left Naruto-kun to resolve that problem
Perhaps.
Ecco! The directory of all new the Ninja.
They have been many changes from the last time that we have been here.
Watched this directory therefore, I pray to you.
I have said all the directory!
And well, and well…
There is also of the dango!
[ dango: Bullets sweetened to the rice paste ]
Not me piacciono this kind of things…
Ehi Konohamaru! You exit here!
Or at least, it explains to me because you make all this!
Konohamaru-chan…
All are preoccupied for you.
If it does not interest to you…
I will let out  you  with the force!
Naruto ougi, Oiroke not Jutsu
[  Secret of Naruto, Transformation sexy! ]
Konohamaru-kun!
You exit here from…
Sbrigati…
Maledizione, di' at least something!
He is  cos ì  embarrassing!
We end it with the cavolate ones!
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu
I am arriving! You are careful Konohamaru!
Ready…
Via!
Che cos' has happened?
How it goes? Naruto nii-chan!
It is  the office of the Grandfather.
Missions of D category: 8
Missions of category C: 3?
I see draft of Kurenai.
Now I comprise to what thought the Sandaime.
E' much similar one with this square?
Already
This square is not balanced with the special abilities.>.
I have badly to the back.
I would make better to take a po' of air.
Happening…
Naruto nii-chan!
Merda!
If six serious then it  I  will be anch'!
It is  the office of the Grandfather!
The lascerei not to use to nobody except he!
Eh?
Grandfather?
He is  for that its grandson the protegge!
Imbecille! How you can say this!?
In this moment also Konoha it is weakened!
Why it would have to interest to me?
I do not have nothing to make!
Tasks truly what you have said?
Grrr! Tu!
Me you have innervosito truly this time.
Here,  I will use  my technical new in order to break off this door!
Naruto nii-chan!
Tsunade-obachan!
To.... Attention!
Impressive…
Sai Konohamaru…
The village is weakened…
Our power has been reduced to half.
But we must acquit our missions equally.
They are I that you I have said
And well…
Ah.... Bond.... Then…
If we refuse the missions the other countries they will think that we are weak people.
And this is of Iruka-sensei.
Why it dislikes Tsunade-obachan?
It is not this.
Then that what?
A day or the other the persons will stop to call the grandson to me of the Third Hokage
And I would be only the ordinary Konohamaru.
And to become an ordinary Konohamaru is not good?
Not!
Why therefore?
Me memory still when this dislikes it to you!
All are beginning to forget the Grandfather…
They are forgetting that it was a great Ninja.
and lasceranno its memory in one scato it…
Cos ì  the new Hokage…
it will replace!
Sure that not!
Konoha Will remain Konoha.
And nobody will be able to forget your grandfather!
Not! Nobody will forget it!
They will make…
It is  sure.
I say you not!
Minds!
Sure that not!
Not me creeds!?
Not!
Aaaaaaaah! Enough!
You come with me, Konohamaru!
We go to make to promise the old one not to change Konoha.
And then…
We will make to promise to all not to forget your grandfather.
cos ì  we have resolved the problem not?
How I have been able to lose Tsunade-sama sight!?
You have found? Tom-tom!
Regeneration of the cells…
I have found to you finally, Tsunade-sama!
Tsunade-sama that studies!?
You close the spout, I cannot be concentrated.
To concentrate itself!?
It is  before the time that ve I feel it to say to the infuori of one commedia!
It is  the voice of Shizune?
Shizune…
You memories of that medical Ninja, Kabuto?
S ì  because?
And well…
Its ability to create of the cells.
I was trying in arches to you.
It is  for Lee-kun?
If  it can  be passed from 50% to 51% R-di.fortuna that it can work then because not to try?
And well…
But it remains equally rischioso.
Even if you are Tsunade-sama…
I do not know if of you are able…
Well, I must make it.
Because…
They are the Fifth Hokage after all.
I cannot makes nothing us.
Konohamaru.
They are the Third Hokage after all.
If it loves to me stopped!
The village is like one family.
And the role of the Hokage is protect this family.
Grandfather!
Today…
E' a special day!
Which thing is Konohamaru?
Six sure one not to have need to speak the Old one?
Not.
I must make it.
They are the Fifth Hokage after all.
I must make it, Konohamaru.
They are the Third Hokage after all.
I must make it.
They are its grandson after all.
Eh?
After all, I make part of this village!
Ehi! Konohamaru!
It waits for to me!
Which thing is taken to it? Ehi!
Konohamaru!?
Tsunade-sama?
Not…
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
My Sensei has taught to me…
That to train itself with it avails again allows to become a great Ninja.
Next episode
The warm ties between a master and its pupils!