http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
In the world of the ninja for friendship one agrees
to improve itself to vicissitude fighting
to risk of the own life.
This will be a mortal crash them that you will face
in name of your dreams and the honor of the village.
Beautiful speech.
Not me of frega nothing.
Sbrigati to speak us about the details of quest
Examination where we risk our life.
It would appeal to to me to illustrate to you in the detail
the Third Test but is a task that
I Gekkou Hayate, in how much arbitrator
designated  I  will be to occupy some to me.
You proceed.>.
There is something that I will make  to make  you....
before beginning the Third Test.
Draft of the preliminary crashs in order to approach itself
to the main part of the third test.
The preliminary crashs?
The preliminary crashs!
But that it means!
Sensei, I do not understand the meant one
of these preliminary crashs.
We cannot simply begin
the Third Test with all the genin remained?
Perhaps the first and second test
they have been too much easy this time
the fact is that they are remained too many candidates.
It must sfoltire the number of the candidates following
the regulations of selection of the Chunin.
But not
Like mentioned from Hokage-sama many hosts
they will be introduced from spectators.
There will be a time limit and we cannot
to allow us to combats borings.
We have time little,  therefore
who feels itself little well
And you you are well?
Rather it is not well, sensei.
You excuse to me.
If someone wants to renounce
after these explanations
it is prayed to declare it now
why the preliminary matters will begin endured.
Endured!
But if we have ended only hour the second test.
That banging
Eh? What? And my meal !
-  the CANDIDATES MUST HALVE THEMSELVES  -
An unexpected battle !
Ce I will put  it  all.
Also I have promised Kabuto-saint.
They are scordato to me of dirvi that
of hour in then you will have
only duels one against one.
You withdraw yourselves if you think it opportune.
I will not withdraw myself.
Sasuke-kun.
The driven in ones more and more often come.
Sasuke-kun, therefore six
Sasuke-kun, task that you would have to be withdrawn.
Eh?
From when six met to you
with strange Orochimaru six cos  .
That sign makes you badly also now, true!
Sign?
In this state
I have donated a goodbye gift.
Sasuke-kun will try to me made thirsty to be able.
Six only remained you.
I pray to you
I pray to you withdraws to you.
I have fear.
Sakura-chan.
As I feared.
What we must make?
It must isolate it
making to watch it from the Ambu.
We must exhort it to withdraw itself and
Not task that it will accept easy cos  .
Inasmuch as she is a descendant of the Uchiha clan.
Not to joke!
We will make to withdraw also to cost to use the force!
Enough to paste the chakra that the sign
it reacts making to fuoriuscire too much energy.
E' one technical forbidden that it destroys the body!
It is strange to me that one stands in feet.
A normal man would be died.
Hokage-sama!
Not six in condition for fighting.
Hush!
I know!
You are calm.
You are resisting to the pain.
I pray to you, you are zitta!
M' it does not import those that tasks.
I will say  to the sensei of the sign, and they
Then
What is ?
What?
I withdraw to me.
K-Kabuto-saint?
Then we see a po '
Six Yakushi Kabuto-kun di Konoha, just?
Well.
You can go.
It goes well
Kabuto-saint, why rinunci!
Why!
He
Scusami, Naruto-kun, but mine
physicist is to the extreme.
E' from when they are met to me
with the ninja of the Sound
that I more do not succeed to feel
from the left ear.
I cannot continue cos
above all hour in crashs
where it is risked to die.
Its face me is not new.
If not erro, also the past time has been withdrawn
during the main competition.
Goodness knows that it has in the zucca.
Anko.
Just
According to our data Yakushi Kabuto
it is bocciato for six times of row.
What we know of he?
To the academy it has been one student not
particularly shining with ballots in the average.
It has exceeded the diploma examination
to its third attempt.
It has executed 2 missions
of class ' There and 14 of class ' D '.
It has not never disputed
worthy combats of famous.
But
But?
Laughed them before that it entered in the academy.
It continues.
It is remembered of the child who was brought back
from the battle of the step of Kikyo?
Memory.
A Jonin of the medical square  brought back
with himself from the battlefield
the survival child of the enemy faction.
Cos   would be he that child.
You cannot act as it seems to you.
You have forgotten the orders about Orochimaru-sama?
I leave all in your hands.
Especially to you, Yoroi-saint.
With your abilities not
they would have it are to us problems.
E' the occasion in order to demonstrate your value.
Inasmuch as six irritateed anchor
for the fact that I have surpassed to you.
Even if the six coconut of Orochimaru-sama
not to mount the head to you child
He goes well, senpai.
Naruto-kun, Sasuke-kun
I would have intentional to play with you an other po '
but if you continued
my old blood would betray to me.
They are also always a spy.
I cannot allow me to discover to me.
Inasmuch as you are here to observe
not there is more need that
I collect information, just
Orochimaru-sama ?
We keep the divertimento to after.
Sasuke-kun, Naruto-kun, also you two.
Task that nobody wants more to be withdrawn.
I must make to know to the Sensei
of the sign of Sasuke-kun
Not to say to nobody of the brand.
Why six cos   stubborn?
I do not want to see to you to still suffer.
I
They are not made yours !
I have not never asked you
of preoccuparti of me!
You I have already said once.
I am a vendicatore.
For me this is not a examination whichever.
For me it does not have not even
importance to become Chunin.
They are truly strong?
This is the only question to which I must answer.
I want to fight against the best ones ninja
Gaara of the Desert.
Ehi, you.
It introduces to you.
You announcement who you are not
to my height.
If we had to fight an other
time in this examination
we will not escape any we will hide.
And the stronger adversaries are here !
I  will not allow  you not even
of intrometterti in my way!
Sasuke-kun
Ehi!
You stop it to make the figo, stupid!
Sakura-chan only is preoccupied for you.
Naruto.
I want to fight also against of you.
That preoccupies  me  that has said Orochimaru.
We will forward Sasuke
and we will observe the situation.
But Hokage-sama!
But if the brand had to be opened giving off
also the minimum to be able, fermatelo.
It will be made !
But
I understand.
Then, we begin with the preliminary encounter.
They will be duels characterizes them
similar to real combats.
There are 20 candidates for
a total of 10 encounter.
The vincitori of you respect combats to you
they will take part to the Third Test.
Rules do not exist.
To fight until when
the adversary dies, loses the senses
or proclama defeated.
If you do not want to die,
declared endured the defeat.
If you had to decide that not more he has left
me  intrometter  and  I will stop  the combat
in order to avoid useless dead men.
Finally,  that  that will decide your future
You open.
it is this.
Tabellone the electrical worker will announce
of time in time the two challengers.
We do not lose time and we reveal
the first two names.
AKADOU YOROY
UCHIHA SASUKE
Just just for first!
I did not ask better.
Oh not!
Why Sasuke-kun?
The two are made extracted ahead.
The challengers of the first encounter are
Akadou Yoroy and Uchiha Sasuke.
There are objections?
Not! - Not !
I can only remain to watch.
Sasuke-kun
Sasuke, if you want to fight
against of me not losing.
Sasuke-kun seems strange.
It will be for via of the sign?
Sasuke-kun, from the maximum!
We see of cos' is able.
. . .
The pain does not diminish.
It seems that the Juin Jutsu makes it badly.
Now the first encounter begins.
To part the two challengers, the others
they must be moved lass.
Hey !
Kakashi-sensei !
Sasuke.
Not to use the Sharingan.
Then you knew it.
If that sign on the neck began
to expand itself you would find yourself in life danger.
Probable.
If it had to happen,
the encounter would come suspended
and I would take part in order to stop to you
He would come Suspended!
This sign seems that
it reacts to my Chakra.
I am exausting my Chakra !
Sharingan !
Sasuke-kun, you do not have more to use the Sharingan!
If you had to paste the Chakra incautious
it would make me to lose the control and
the energy would give off all that I have in body
Therefore in this encounter
other that Sharingan,  I will not be able
to use not even the normal techniques.
Moreover the power of Yoroi
.. how much is worse could capitare to you
Sasuke-kun
To this point
like the attack?
Not to strafare
Sasuke.
Well, begun also.
Six ready one?
S !
Not!
Evvai !
My forces
That it happens !
The forces abandon to me
Sasuke-kun !
Sasuke !
Six you
That it steals the Chakra to me
Of six shrewed you only hour ?
nee kikoe masu ka ?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
OF KIKOEMASUKAA
Dannazione..questo sign
.. it reacts with all!
Lascer  not to overwhelm  to me !
I will not make  it  to suspend the test !
-  NEXT EPISODE  -
-  CIGLIONE GELOSO! -
The birth of the concatenato attack of the lion !