http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Inari, you come to me to help?
Arrival!
(This fog.....)
Sasuke, Sakura!
It is arriving!
(still alive E'.)
(And eccolo here.)
Master Kakashi…
This is the technique…
… *del fog veil, true?
* justu hiding fog
Me dispiace to have made to you to wait for, Kakashi.
And it continues to carry those mocciosi.
It is shaking of new, than painful.
E' because they are excited.
Vai pure, Sasuke.
(I can see them!)
Milimeter? Successful E' to defeat
the cloni of water.
This boy has become much fort.
You have avails again, Haku.
It seems just of s ì.
Eternal damnation!
They are completely in delay.
Eh, accidents…
It seems just that I had reason.
What you want to say?
That one masked…
Eh?
Just as we thought.
Therefore the fact to be a hunter
ninja was only one super lie?
E' clearly that he is a man of Zabuza…
… inasmuch as it is to its flank.
How much fierezza extension after
what it has made.
To nobody it appeals to that attitude.
Master Kakashi, watches that it is better than you…
Oh..
To fight ò  I with he!
Huh?
Schernendoci with that behavior....
The bastards as it is
those that hatred more.
Six fantastic Sasuke-kun!
But because Sakura must
to always favour…
… Sasuke in all which says?
An indeed impressive boy.
Even if the cloni of water…
… they have only a tenth one
of the force of it originates them…
… to outside make them cos ì  in that way…
However we have picked them of surprise.
Hour you go!
!
What!
Secret Justu of Haku: * Makyouhyoushou
* Demonic ice mirrors!
The six daughter of Tazuna?
Spiacente, but you must come with we.
Mother!!!!
Not to approach to you! Scappa!!
What? A boy?
We take also he?
Us servants only a hostage.
A hostage!
Then…
… I kill it?
Firm!
If touched that boy…
… to bite me ò  the language and to kill to me ò!
You want a hostage, not?
Boy, ringrazia your mother!
Mpf! I had wants to slice something.
They give a cut to us!
Six not vented to you before?
Enough to chiacchiere.
We carry it via.
Me dispiace, Mother.
Me dispiace a lot!
They are weak person…
… and they are not able of proteggerti!
I do not want to die!
I have too much fear!
Tu! Piece of piagnone!
You cry like an actor in one tragedy!
An idiot as you he would have
to only continue to cry!
You, piece of piagnone!
Sure it is tired to cry.
E' for that it knows what means
to be strong…
… just like your father.
You must protect us ò  that it considers important…
… with both the arms…
… even if you had to die.
Inari.
Sar ò....
Able Sar  ? to become stronger?
Papà!
Watching this faccino pretty
it comes to me wants to slice it.
From it walks.
Firm!
Inari!
What? Still that boy?
You remove… Togliete the hands from my mother!
That stupid boy…
… slice it.
It makes it and me you taglier.....
You are zitta and you go to sleep.
Remarkable one. It holds head to the fast attacks.
Sakura! Proteggi sig the Tazuna
and you remain to me near.
Next to that one Sasuke thinks to us.
I would prefer not to have to you to kill…
… but you not desisterai, true?
Sciocchezze.
Capisco.
My next attack
he will be too much fast for you.
In more I have two advantages respect you.
Two advantages?
The first one regards the water on the pavement.
The second is that I hold occupied
one of your hands.
Now you will only be able
to defend to you from my attacks.
What? With one single hand?
Magical positions with one single hand?
I had not never seen it before.
Secret Justu:
Flying water pricks!
No intention to kill eh?
It will be true?
Sasuke-kun!
I must Remember the training!
Rilasciare mine chakra!
Justu of the corporea commutation?
And the woman…
Excused the delay.
But a hero always arrives
at the last moment.
Naruto!
Inari…
Optimal job!
Eh?
Thanks to the fact that you have distracted them…
… I have been able to save your mother!
Naruto, as you knew that those two
samurai they were coming here?
In the forest there was a wild boar
covered of cuts.
Moreover there were signs of Katana on the trees…
… in house direction yours.
Cos ì  is preoccupied to me.
Here like…
Well, well....
But it is not one of the Ninja losing
what has engaged Tazuna?
We make it.
!
They are arriving!
And tasks that these functions?
Heh, than idiot!
Moccioso!
It makes… Fantastic!
There is I have made it!
Naruto, seems to you a ninja indeed!
Dumb, it they are since the beginning!
I concentrate mine chakra....
… in the feet!
It has been saved!
Six truly slow one.
Now six you....
… that you can be only defended
from my attacks.
It has exceeded the speed of Haku?
It seems that I am benefitted in speed.
Not to underrate the single square
because there are of the children.
Sasuke is equipped of the village of the leaf.
Sakura is the more dazzling of the village.
Eternal damnation!
While the other is Naruto…
… the more exhibitionist, noisy…
… and hyperactive of the village.
Cooled?
Not, I am well.
Speaking of other, Inari....
Excuse in order yesterday.
Eh?
Scusami in order to have to you called "Piagnone".
Forget it.
Six fort!
Eternal damnation!
I had decided not to cry never more!
Now you will take me of new in turn....
… calling to me piagnone of new!
But that you are saying?
Eh?
E' all to place if six happy one.
When six happy one....
… you can cry how much you want!
Naruto.....
Then, I can count on you, here true?
Sure!
From the bridge is much here far away.
Boy, I assure to you that it is hard to be a hero!
Sure that it is!
Haku, you have understood?
It will have to engage us more in order to exit some.
Already!
What!
Me dispiace.
Cos' is this cold?
Secret Justu:
Makyouhyoushou
Demonic ice mirrors!
Cos' is.....quel justu?
Cos....
These are....
Mirrors....
Ma..in everyone.....
Eternal damnation!
Your adversary… sono I.
He will not be able to save itself…
… against that technique!
Well, I can begin?
Now you mostrer ò  my true speed.
Sasuke!
If you will catch up it…
… to make ò  outside the others two.
Sig. Tazuna, me dispiace.
I must leave for a moment.
Sure! Vai!
(Sakura! )
(Sasuke! )
You take it!
It has taken he!?
Eh?
But who has been?
That idiot…
… exhibitionist…
… noisier and hyperactive…
… ninja.
Uzumaki Naruto
E' finally arrived!
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears