Subtitles By: BakaSan
This isn't good.
Pakkun?
Sakura-chan?
Why did you guys stop so suddenly?!
The smell of Sasuke and two others...
is moving away quickly.
I guess Sasuke is chasing those two.
What?
Sasuke-kun is chasing them?
The others don't seem to be moving from there
but...
Stop wasting time here and let's go after Sasuke.
But what?
Those who were left behind seem to have started fighting.
Though it will be a bit out of our way, we
have to take another route to avoid them.
Why? Doing so will delay us in catching up
with Sasuke. Let's go straight through it.
What're you saying, Naruto?!
You don't know what'll happen in a battle zone.
There's a possibility that we'll be forced into the battle.
That has nothing to do with this.
Kid, if our mission is to retrieve Sasuke. Then, it's
an absolute must that we avoid any battles until then.
Let's get moving!
Roger.
Fine, I get it.
Kugutsu-no-jutsu (puppet)
I am from the Aburame clan of Konoha. When I fight, I never
underestimate the opponent, even if it's a worthless bug. I'll do my best.
You irritate me.
Let me down, Temari.
Can you move now, Gaara?
Gaara!
Kankuro is helping to stop Uchiha now.
While he's doing so,...
I've got to hurry up, otherwise the plan will be...
Temari, wait over there.
What?
Shut up and just go over there now! You stand in my way.
Astonishment! Gaara's true identity
There's poison on that blade.
I won't let you run away.
That's Uchiha Sasuke? How did he get past Kankuro? It can't
be, that was too quick. Did someone else come to chase us?
I don't know what the Sand is planning, but...
I'll put a stop to it!
And...
I'll see your true identity.
Gaara!
Don't tell me he's going to awaken that one here
right how? NO way. This is way out of my hands.
Stop, Gaara. Did you forget about the plan?
You, who are strong...
You, who're called Uchiha...
You, who have friends...
You, who are determined...
You, who are similar...
to ME!
I'll exist in this world as one who
erased everything of you by killing you.
I can then experience "life".
What's the matter?
If you keep releasing that thirst for blood
atmosphere, you're not hiding well. Come on out.
It's you....
What is your purpose? For what do you want the power?
It's none of your business. Leave.
You're disturbing my training.
You have the same eyes that I have. Eyes that show you
want power... eyes full of hate and intention to kill.
You're similar to me. Don't forget that you are my...
You are my...
prey!
It's started....
Kawarimi
You're not good enough.
Got him.
Bugs?!
Creating a clone with bugs to come
around behind me. You're doing good.
You are a mid to long range fighter with that
puppet. I think you as not good in close quarters.
Because, the  Kugutsu-no-jutsu requires you
to focus on controlling a puppet it will...
makes the person who controls it have an blind spot.
You seem to understand the weakness of the Kugutsu-shi (puppet master), but
I'll teach you the real way of
fighting with this Jutsu and...
the real dreadfulness of the Senjutsu
Karakuri Karasu. (war tactics puppet)
This is a poison smoke ball.
I might breath in a bit. And I see, the Jutsusha will hide out.
Listen everyone.
In case one of the enemy Ninja's appears,
don't panic and enter into the hidden rooms.
The Jounin and Chunin sensei's
will protect you with their lives.
Konohamaru-chan!
It's ok.
Everybody's doing their best. We
can make enemies go away quickly.
A crack on the Hokage's face rock...
How ominous...
Grandpa...
I came to this, to this point... and you tell me
I don't have enough power to pull his soul out.
You tell me this old body is still
not enough, even though I die for this?
I believe you could've killed me
if you were ten more years younger.
Sarutobi, if you don't kill this man now, this
village will be destroyed. Do you understand that?
I know that.
You should be dead already.
Let me feel it!
That eye...
That's the eye I saw earlier.
I guess I won't finish until you come, Shino.
I see the poison is taking effect
now. I'll finish you off now.
Bugs again? But I don’t think he can
move around that much with that condition.
I'll end your suffering soon.
What? What's going on?!
What's going on?
No way!
It's useless. This one can't move anymore
I had my bugs go into all the joints.
Disabling it by sticking bugs in joints?
He was planning that from the beginning?
Bugs are coming down on my chakra strings.
Why?
That's right... their food is chakra, if I remember correctly.
My position will be found out with this.
He cut the charka strings.
You got off guard. It's nothing for a first class Kugutsu-shi
(Puppet master) to reconnect the chakra strings after you cut it once.
Plus, Karasu is a Shikomi-Kugutsu (trick puppet), which
has hidden weapons in every single part of the body.
If you were thinking that it's over just
by stopping its movement, You were WRONG!
I put a lot of poison on the tip of that needle...
Die!
What?!
Since when are those bugs here... The chakra strings are already eaten up.
What? Why? Where did those bugs come from?
You didn't notice bugs moving
behind you since you lowered your...
guard after taking care of the decoy,
and the bugs on the chakra strings.
The bugs had been moving all the time, to reach your forehead protector.
What?
That early blow... I pretended
to miss and put the one bug on you.
But how can you could find out
my position with only one bug?
I don't like to explain same thing twice.
Shino? Why you are here?
Before you left the arena, I put a female bug
on you. The scent of female is almost nothing.
Only the male of the same kind can
sense the faint scent of the female.
That means, the one on my forehead is...
Yes, it's female.
Is the poison all over my body?
I guess I can't come to be your
back up. Sorry, Uchiha Sasuke.
He...
Are you afraid of me, Uchiha Sasuke?
Of my existence? Come out, Uchiha Sasuke!
You are my Prey!
Man, what speed and power
I'd be in pieces if I didn't use
my Sharingan to read his movement.
But just defending won't do anything.
What should I do? How should I stop him?
I guess I have to use it...
But Chidori isn't...
Next Episode
Over the limit...
Sasuke's Decision!!