Subtitles By: BakaSan
Hey, where's Sasuke's room?
Nobody is allowed to see Sasuke-sama.
Why's that?
Sorry, I can't tell you.
Hey, lady. Why?
Naruto, be quiet in the hospital.
Hey, hey... I have a favor to ask...
You don't need to tell me the end of your sentence.
I guessed that you'd come to me like that...
I appointed a person who can oversee your training.
Whhhhy? I want Kakashi-sensei to train me!!
I have a little business to take care of.
So, I don't have time to spend on you.
You're going to train Sasuke, aren't you?!
Well... don't say it like that.
I found a more reliable teacher than me for you.
Who is it?
It's me!
Ahhhhhhhh! You're the closet-pervert!!
How dare you.
Ebisu Again! I don't allow shameless deeds!
Ebisu-sensei is
a closet-pervert?
Why? Why is this guy my training teacher?
Besides... this guy is weaker than me!
Why do you say that?
Because! Because! A while back,
with my Harem-no-Jutsu, he was...
Henge! (Transform)
Ebisu-sama!
Is he going to...?!
Harem-no-Jutsu?
No, it's nothing.
I'll treat you as much ramen as you want later...
...so don't tell him about that.
You'd better keep your word.
Who would've guessed you two knew each other.
Well, it's an unintended relationship, though.
Who can forget the humiliation!
But why him? I really don't want him.
If it wasn't for Kakashi-kun...
I don't even want to teach somebody like you voluntarily!
Then, don't do it.
Oh, you two. Don't say that.
Naruto, Ebisu-sensei is a tutor who teaches only Elites.
He's a special Jounin.
He'll teach you better than I would. Seriously.
Naruto, your basic skills are the worst of the three...
...team 7 members I was in charge of.
This time you'll be taught thoroughly.
What's worse compared to Sakura-chan and Sasuke!?
Naruto, it's a fact that your basic skills aren't good.
The basics are important for doing everything.
If you really want to be stronger, be quiet and do what I say.
Well then, Ebisu-sensei. He's all yours.
It seems a bit tough, but you have
the potential to get even stronger.
Do your best.
We're going.
Still... I can't understand it!
Well, it may be true that basics are important.
But I can't get stronger by getting trained by somebody weaker!
Are you saying that I am weak?
Who else is here!?
It's true that I was surprised by such a shameless technique...
but judging my ability with only that incident isn't too smart.
You were completely knocked out.
Alright. Then, let's try something, won't we?
Naruto-kun, run away.
If you can totally get away from me...
I will withdraw from this without saying anything.
Withdraw from this?
Yes. And of course, I'll talk to Kakashi-kun...
so that you can get trained by him directly.
What? Really?
This Elite teacher doesn't lie.
But, this is only if you get away completely.
That's easy. Later!
This is too easy. I'll lose that closet-pervert fast!
I lost him already. I'm such an excellent Ninja...
Who's excellent?
Don't tell me that you think you can lose me with that skill.
What're you talking about.  The chase has...
...just begun!
Finally becoming a Movie! Super Romance! Icha
Icha Paradise  Rated R (Kakashi's favorite book)
That Elite tutor, even though he's a closet-pervert...
...isn't so bad after all.
Anyway...
See, he's the closet-pervert after all!
What are you doing, Naruto-kun?
I see. Your idea wan't bad.
Fine then. How about this?!
Kagebunshin-no-Jutsu! (Shadow Replication)
Let's see you try to catch me now!
You're doing well.
But you're not the only one who
can use Kagebunshin-no-Jutsu.
I won't let you get away!
God...dammit!
Well, next.
Wait!
I see you!
I won't release you!
There!
Here!
You've already reached your limit?
You're so persistent! Give up already!
Why are you getting pissed off at me?
This is a chase, so it's natural that I chase you!
Th..that's true...
You now know how great I am. Give
up already and start training...
Heck no!
I'll win this game against you, and
I'll get trained by Kakashi-sensei!
Even if I have to beat you up!
I see you still have some spirit left.
Coming at me, even though this is a chase.
This is the #1 unpredictable Ninja as Kakashi-kun said.
That's Naruto-kun for you.
Take this!
Bunshin-no-Jutsu (Replication)
Game Over!
Here's your Miso Chasu and Shio Ramen.
After seeing your moves and
analyzing what Kakashi-sensei told me,
I can see that you're not good at controlling chakra.
Control?
That's right.
Now, by comparing Sasuke-kun,
Sakura-kun and you...
I'll explain your weakness in order.
As you know, in case of using Ninjutsu and Genjutsu...
a ninja channels chakra to start the Jutsu.
I know that already!
Ok. then I'll explain how you're the worst of you three.
You say that in a way that irritates me.
Be quiet and listen to me because I'm treating you as promised.
First, if Sakura-kun
uses the Bunshin-no-jutsu,
In her case, since she's perfect at
channeling and controlling chakra.
She can replicate herself without wasting any energy.
Next, in Sasuke-kun's case... he's
a bit bad at channeling chakra.
But his chakra control is perfect.
He can create five replications as Sakura did.
However, he uses up a little more chakra than Sakura-kun does.
Oh, so Sasuke isn't that good.
In your case, you don't have time to laugh at somebody else.
You are very bad at channeling and controlling chakra.
You can't replicate with the same amount of chakra.
If you still try to replicate yourself, you use up way...
more chakra than Sakura-kun
and Sasuke-kun do. Plus...
...you can replicate only two... at most.
By the way, if using the same amount of Chakra...
Sakura-kun and Sasuke-kun
will replicate at least ten.
All three of you are so much
different even doing the same Jutsu.
Well, that was exaggerated to show the difference of you three,
but Naruto-kun uses up too much energy due to...
channelling too much chakra. Also your Jutsu is unstable.
But there were times I was way
better than Sakura-chan or Sasuke...
That's because you happen to have
a way greater amount of stamina!
Well, it's true that controlling chakra is harder because...
of the power the Kyubi(nine-tails) adds to his stamina.
Anyways, you'll get stronger with
the training we'll start from now.
What? Really?
I'll guarantee that. Now, let's go.
Hey, Mister. Your bill!
Oh, yes. that's right.
Thank you very much!
We came quite far... but this is
the hot-spring district, isn't it?
It doesn't seem like we came here to relax in the hot spring...
Hey! Naruto-kun! That's the hot bath for women over there.
I will never allow you to do such shamless deeds!
I'm not you... It's not like I was trying to peep.
Getting that idea is proof of being a closet-pervert.
What is it... your look.
Nothing...
Anyway, why did we come here?
Are we training by getting in the hot spring?
No. We'll do your training here in the hot spring district.
We'll do it here!
What? It's the hot spring after all!
What are you saying?! I told you that it's training! TRAINING!
Are we going to train in a place like this?
What are we going to do anyway?
Walk on this hot water.
What is it?
Walk on the hot water? Can you really do that?
Of Course!
I heard from Kakashi-sensei that you've already...
done the tree-climbing without using your hands.
The same applies here.
What do you mean? I don't remember much about that.
For climbing tree, you channel
the neccessary amount of chakra...
concentrate it to the appropriate part of your body...
and just hold the fixed amount of chakra continuously.
Because a tree is solid, you just need to adsorb it.
It's training to channel the fixed amount of chakra.
To float on water, you continuously release the appropriate...
amount of chakra into water from the bottom of your feet...
and you need to balance it with your body to float.
This chakra control is more difficult...
than just using an unknown amount of chakra.
This is training you to release a controlled...
amount of chakra while using a Jutsu.
I don't understand very well.
Well, it's better to show it, in your case.
First, concentrate chakra to my feet.
Then, balance with my body weight
by releasing a certain amount.
It's like this!
I'm going to try it too!
First, concentrate chakra to my feet.
Then, he said that I need to keep releasing the fixed amount...
As I thought...
Hoooooot!
I fogot to mention this, but the water is 60 degrees. (140 F)
If you keep failing, you'll be boiled.
I'll master this no matter what!
You're more focused than usual today, grandkid-sama.
Finally he's understood my guidance.
It's the time you normally go surprise attack Hokage-sama.
I stopped doing such things...
Oh, yes. you finally understand.
Doing what I say is the quickest...
...short-cut to becoming the Hokage.
There's no short-cut.
Naruto, my big bro told me.
If I want to be Hokage, I need to keep that in mind!
I think I'm starting to understand a little bit...
I'm surprised that he started to grasp...
the trick of chakra control this quickly.
I never thought you'd grow this much...
That's true that there is no short-cut for anything.
I really misunderstood who you were.
You are a much smarter teacher than I am.
You were not just a demon fox...
You are a great Ninja of the Konoha!
That is...
I don't know who or where you are from but...
I won't allow you to do such shameless thing!
That is...!
Keep the noise down! What will you do if people find us?
The closet-pervert lost?
Who is that open-pervert?!
Hey hey hey hey! What can the open-pervert do for me?!
I was trained by the closet-pervert.. and he beat him up!
And he was so quick to get away!
Is he prehaps a really great Ninja?
Next Episode Long time! Pervert-Sennin Appears!
I'll find him and let him train me no matter what!