Subtitles By: BakaSan
The mission begins.
Start of the Konoha-Kuzushi (Crush the Leaf)
Hokage-Sama!
Leave him to us!
Kazekage-dono... What're you starting?
Hokage-Sama!
Team I is up there, Team Ro is
down there. Protect the Daiymo's.
Get out of my way!
Hokage-sama, please get away from here...
It's finally my turn to play.
That was boring doing Henge for a long time.
You guys stink like sweat.
Stop it. You guys are teammates, right?
Oto-nin (Sound Ninjas)
Raido was... We're going to protect Hokage-sama. Move out!
Do it.
Ninpo Shishi Enjin (Four Point Purple Fire Shield)
Damn it... That's Kekkai (area protection jutsu).
That's Kekkai Ninjutsu, I see.
They aren't regular level because
they could outwit (outrun) the ANBU.
What're you doing! Hokage-sama's in a critical situation.
I give it to them...
Who'd think that our enemy turned himself into one of ANBU.
I guess he must be the one who used the Genjutsu.
Right. He must be the one.
I never thought the Sand would betray the Leaf.
A treaty is like a disguise to catch the other off guard.
The stupid match games will end now.
From this point on, history shall change.
Are you saying you're going to start something like a war?
That's right.
You should avoid resorting to force
and seek a resolution with dialogue.
It's still not too late, Kazekage-dono.
I wonder if a person would really
know only peace as they get older...
Sarutobi Sensei
You are...
I'm out of luck because I have watch duty on a day like this.
Me too, I wanted to go see the Chunin exam.
Stop complaining. There're two Chunin exams each
year. You'll have plenty of chances to see it.
But this time, that Uchiha kid is in it. Having to
miss that match is one thing I'll regret if I die.
What was that?
It's time now. Begin!
The summoning has succeeded.
Large snakes...
Go report to Hokage-sama ASAP!
I won't let you come into the village!
Hurry up and go get reinforcements!
Yes, sir!
Suna Nin (Sand Ninjas)
What the heck is this?
Stop it, Gaara!
I'm gonna kill him!
There's no reason to fight with him any further!
Don't forget about our orders!
Get out my way!
What're you guys doing here?
The plan has already started.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
His wound is deeper than I thought.
Plus, he has consumed lots of chakra.
Then, he won't be able to use "that".
It's impossible to do it so soon.
Idiot. That's what you get for trying to turn into
the complete form without waiting for the order.
What are we supposed to do now? Are you
gonna tell us to do it without Gaara?
Where's Gaara?
Gaara is the ace of the Sand. We
need him working no matter what.
You guys get out of here for now, and treat his wound.
As soon as Gaara's chakra has recharged,
we'll carry out the plan again.
Understood.
How about you, Sensei?
I'll hold them here.
You think everything will go by your plan?
I will make it happen.
Go!
Is Orochimaru hosting this party?
I don't know. But, let's have fun for the time being.
Sorry, but the Chunin exam ends now.
You're already at Chunin level. If you're a
Shinobi of Konoha, make yourself helpful for Konoha.
So, you're saying that I should beat up
Gaara... like the continuation of the match.
Don't get in too deep. It's real, not an exam, from now.
The things that needs to be done is still the same.
I won't let you go!
Oh well... I was planning to take Sasuke-kun
while Gaara started doing his stuff.
But I guess everything won't be the way I planned.
I see. I get it.
Konoha and Sasuke are your purpose.
Whether Konoha is actually worth that much...
Put that aside. If our Gaara can become fully awake,
then I can show you a much more interesting thing, but...
Anyway's, your stupidity forced Konoha
into this situation. This is my victory.
You will not know everything until it's over.
I believe that's how I taught you....
Orochimaru.
I knew that someday, a day like this would come, but...
it's not so easy to get my head.
I told you this... you'd better decide the Fifth soon...
because you, the Third, will die here today!
I wonder what's going on with the Chunin
Exam... Is Naruto's match already finished?
I remember that his first match is against Neji.
I want him to win it somehow...
No! no! no! It's not good that a
teacher cheers for only one student!
Everybody loves the graduates of this
academy. I have to cheer for everybody equally!
But, after all, I want Naruto to win.
Are you anxious about Naruto?
Yes, Of course!
As I thought.
You guys...
I told you to run ten times around the track!
We finished that already.
While you were daydreaming.
With you being like that, it's not gonna be a
good class. We're going to finish early for today.
No way! I'm starting the class again now!
What is that smoke?
It's in the direction of Chunin Exam arena.
Isn't it noisy in the East?
I wonder if something is happening.
Damn, Orochimaru.
What do you think? Should we go for reinforcement?
No. It's dangerous to move when you don't know the situation.
It's truer especially when the mastermind is Orochimaru.
Is Orochimaru really that dangerous of a guy?
He was a student of the Third.
So why did he become a
Nuke-nin (runaway-ninja)?
I've heard that he demanded that he should be the one to be the
Hokage, when the decision for the Fourth was made a long time ago.
But his demand wasn't accepted.
A little after that, he ran away from this Village. He
probably has a grudge against the Third because of that.
Revenge.
Most likely.
When I was still a kid, I thought
only one thing when I saw him.
It's like he was not a human, but
something that form looks like a human...
It's scary... it's just scary.
Report. Large snakes have appeared
near the West Gate of Konoha.
Followed by an invasion of about one hundred Sand ninja's.
Currently, shinobis who're guarding
near there are fighting against them.
Sand, eh...
Leave Team 1 and 2 here... the rest go to the West Gate. Hurry!
Yes, sir!
I won't let you pass here!
That's a lot of them...
We were careless... Plus even Hokage-sama...
Kakashi, look inside of the Kekkai.
What is it?
Why is he here? Is he trying again for Sasuke-kun?
What? Sasuke-kun isn't there anymore.
Sakura, stay like that for a bit.
I'll reduce the number of enemies.
Damn it... I'm worried about Hokage-sama.
Leave it to the ANBU. Plus Hokage-sama
is not a person who's easily killed.
But...
After all, he is the Hokage of the Hidden Konoha.
Is it that much fun to shed a tear?
Or do you have a heart to feel a little
bit of sadness to kill me, your teacher?
No.
I was sleepy... but I finally woke up now.
I knew it was something like that.
I knew you're not a man who makes a move based on hate.
You have neither purpose nor motivation.
Well, I have something you can call
a purpose... If I put it in a word...
It's fun to watch things that
move. It's not fun if they're still.
A windmill that's not turning isn't worth watching,
even though it's a good atmosphere sometimes.
I want to turn the windmill with
a wind called Konoha Kuzushi now.
You haven't changed.
It was worth it teaching you Genjutsu during the
Survival training for deciding if you pass for the Genin.
You have the talent for Genjutsu, as I thought.
Release the Genjutsu, and wake Naruto and Shikamaru up.
Naruto's gonna be happy. It's going
to be a mission after a long time.
A mission?
Begin with care.
It's the first A-rank mission after the Wave country mission.
Alright! I've been waiting for this!
Finally, it's my first A-rank mission!
Sakura-chan, Shikamaru. This
mission isn't anything with me in it.
I'm a great hero so that even a sleeping kid will wake up.
Take a good look at Naruto-sama's chasing story
Next episode:
I've been waiting for it!
It's an A-rank Mission!!
Here I go!