Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh!  Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
The Third party, definitive leave…!!
Sarutobi!
At least this sword.>.
Even if you were a master in the art of the Shinobi,
the end also for you has arrived.
I feel like if the arms they were burning.
Orochimaru-sama!
The plan ends here.
I do not have more need of the Kekkai (protected area)
We go ourselves some!
, getlteman!
Kai!
(Free)
The Kekkai has been…
As it will be…
Hokage-sama?
We go!
Lascerò  not to scappare  to you!
Ninpo Kumoshibari
(Burlap of Spider)
This is one ragnatela sticky made of Chakra.
Kakashi! They are muovendo. We follow them!
It does not wait for.
Just.
To move without no information on the general situation…
… it could makes you to fall in one enemy trap.
I know very well.
But we cannot leave to escape
the enemies in one situation like this.
This is the style of the Shinobi di Konoha.
And you? You are only to watch?
Kabuto?
You had already understood that pits I eh?
Hey, that we must make?
We withdraw ourselves for the moment.
You are of new escaping via from me?
, for the moment.
If my techniques only showed you in order little,
you would succeed to copy them to the perfection.
Although it seems that you are not in degree
to use R-al.meglio your eye, contrarily to those of the Uchiha clan
Soon.
Temari…
Kankuro…
You take cure of Sakura.
Hey!
How ago to being cos ì  strong?
My existence will not be cancelled.
It will not be cancelled.
I will not allow  that it is cancelled!
I had said to you that you did not have neanche parlargli!
We go ourselves some!
Laggiù!
That one is…
Outside from the feet!
MONSTER!
Monster!
You die!
Not impicciarti, stupid!
It does not watch to you!
Vattene from some other part!
I am an error of their past,
that they want to cancel!
Therefore, which it is the reason for which
I exist and are while still alive?
Also I thought the same things of same me…
Indeed I was forced to think it cos ì…
I had understood that pain does not exist peggior…
My presence was not appreciate
to nobody in this world.
Not to come here!
That pain that who tries is completely single
it is not common in this world, is not true?
I can understand your feelings, in some way
they are similar to the suffering that I have tried.
But now I have of the persons to which I hold.
I will not allow  that you can hurt my precious friends!
Otherwise, also to stop to you,
I will be forced to kill to you!
Why?
Why you make this for the others?
Why they have saved to me from the suffering of the solitudine…
They have given sense to my existence…
They are my more precious affections.
The love is a pure emotion, makes you protect
the precious persons whom they encircle to you.
Love…
Here the reason for which he is cos ì  strong.
Hour enough, Naruto.
Sakura is to the sure one now.
Probably it has used all the its Chakra.
The sand that withheld Sakura not is more.
Truly…
We have made enough.
I withdraw to me
Gaara!
This is before the time that I see it cos ì  malridotto.
It goes well.
Uzumaki Naruto, eh.
A day also I…
Temari, Kankuro…
Me dispiace.
Not to worry to you…
Rain…
The sky has begun to cry…
We are because of the battle here,
in order to begin this leave…
… in honor of the Third Hokage and many other victims.
Begun E'.
After all, we can only remain to watch…
Why?
Why it has had to die the Hokage?
At this point a year is passed nearly.
It is not easy to hide the own one
_ sadness and sorridere, true?
I have felt from teaching yours that
the always six craftsman of all the risate ones.
They are not sad!
E' an honor for one shinobi to die during the own mission.
My father and my mother are heroes who have saved this
village from the monstrous vixen, putting in game their screw!
They are the son of these heroes!
They are not sad even if they are remained alone.
These are joy tears…
Hour enough.
I know that tests to go ahead only with your forces.
But it remembers to you that not six solo.
All the ninja of the Leaf have "the volonta of the fire ".
The will of the fire?
E' strong desire protect Konoha.
Until to when it has this fire will,
all people of Konoha will be one family.
Iruka, you ce have it this determination?
.
They are for Hayate?
The funeral of the Third party already is begun. Sbrigati.
Kakashi-senpai,
six here for Obito-saint?
Inasmuch as you are always to invent excuses for your delays,
why you do not come before?
I come always all the mornings from there…
But I come here only for
to remember the sciocchezze to me of the past.
A ninja it would not have to reveal its emotions in no occasion.
To make that the own mission is one priority and
not to never cry for no reason.
Iruka-sensei?
Why people risk the own life for the next one?
The dead women of a person go beyond to how much can seem…
Door with if the screw of the past, the present and the future.
Much people die during the missions or in war…
Easy…
Hayate is one of these.
Also a dying person has a dream or a objective…
But all how many have something that joins them.
Parents…
Siblings…
Affections and friends…
The persons who you think precious.
The uni are helped and believed in the others…
They are the relations with the persons who you know sin from when six been born.
The thread that joins they to you has become
often and strongly with passing of the time.
Logical E' therefore…
… that a person whom this holds
thread is behaved in such a way…
… inasmuch as it is precious.
Also I in some way had understood I was cos ì.
But…
… to die it is painful.
The Third party is not dead man invano.
It has left something that thought precious.
Beh, a day you to it will understand also.
. In part I succeed to understand it.
The rain has been stopped.
To after, Iruka-sensei.
.
The small leaves of the Village of the Leaf seem
truly to carry in they the will of the fire about which Hokage speaks to you.
A small fire that has ignited on one leaf,
that with the time it will burn strong and large, and that…
… it will illuminate and proteggerà the village.
A day, I  will become  an other Hokage.
The damages seem to be huge,
although they are resolutions to avoid the destruction total.
E' a sin for a village that
once it were much prosperoso.
This is not from you.
Tests still cos ì  much attachment…
… to your village natio?
Not, not of sure.
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete
The memories of infancy live again…
A called wheel destiny is slowly beginning to turn.
Next Episode.
Return to house in the fog early riser.
"21 August begins the mission "
I cannot wait for until to this summer!
"Mission of Class To "
Protect the Prince of the Country of Neve!
Ce I must make!
Creed in same me!
"the film of Naruto: Yukihime Ninpocho & Konoha Undokai "
Two film special in one only during the summery vacations.