Subbed by Shinji 89
Cheked by Cartone
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not fukinukeru
Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda YEAH!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite kanashimi mo
hoho tsutatte namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Baby
It depends all on you, Chouji!!
Baika not Jutsu
Technique of the expansion!
Nikudan Sensha
[  It projects them human sweeping  ]
Choji
the six truly best one.
Episode #113
To be able massimo!Brucia Chouji!
You are resolutions to scappare from mine kekka?
Only remained E' he.
He seems that its companions are already leave themselves.
S .
By now they are far.
Just when we thought to have it recovers them to you.
What you are resolutions to make is not not bad
for one band of failed
Which thing?
Who is the failed one!?
Not to move to you,  I will take care myself  of you!
I I will make  it! !
Waited for! All and two!
E' dangerous to defy it in this way.
The kekkai it has yielded! But I can rifare it !
Tsuuga
[ Zanne distruttrici ]
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu
You take this!
You will be a good meal!
Merda!
Tokken
[ Blow of shoulder ]
Shoushitsu
[ Blow of ginocchio ]
Not grazed me evete neanche!
Been attention! It is in order to arrange an other diavoleria!
Doton Kekka Doru Domu
[ Earth Barrier: Wave in fury ]
Baika not Jutsu
Nikudan Sensha
E' be useless
We do not have time.
We will divide ourselves in two groups.
Why?
Control
We are five against one
Because of little chakra remained, we will not be able to win fastly.
More we pass time with he, more Sasuke is approached the frontier.
If it exceeded it, we would be incapable to make whichever thing.
Therefore, a group will be struck against he, while the other will follow Sasuke.
.
Vicecapo six you, Neji.
I have found to you.
Neji, Kiba and Choji, left to the pursuit of Sasuke.
Of agreement.
Next to he I and Naruto will be believed.
You will try to use of new that technique of connection of the shadows ?
Kage Shibari not Jutsu
That technical fool. Enough to see it once in order to avoid it.
The six solo that can fall in one trap much obvious one.
It is  disappeared?
Behind we!
Doton Doryuu Dango
[ Earth Element: Full of rocks Disc ]
Is  one joke!?
Fairies attention! An other is arriving some!
You the six their commander
To have a similar idiot like leader, he does not have to be easy for the others
Occupero me of your stupid head.
Baika not Jutsu
Nikudan Sensha
Thanks, Choji.
What?Non you want that it comes hit ?
If the captain is stupid, also its subordinate to you are stupid.
Well, of the refuse like you, that they are to follow a maniaco of the shadows
,  they are a bocconcino for me.
You have to me broken with your sciochezze!
I  will strike  you!
It is mine!
Choji !
What you say? It is not someone that you can strike!
Us pense r  I to he!
Choji, you
Shikamaru, you distribute these tonics.
Choji,
you will not want at all
S ,  I will play  my last paper.
But that one is!
Which band of failed! Like if ve you left it to make!
It arrives!
E' hour to regulate the accounts !
You take the others and spins via!
They are of tonics of three various colors and they are not of reconstituting
but then of what draft !
Before the green, the tonic to the spinaci.
Eccomi, failed!
Impossible, it has stopped to me!
Shikamaru, and the others! Sbrigatevi to go !
Choji
Which it is our objective?
If we lose the traces of Sasuke We It will be like has said he.
We will be only of the useless ones commands to you from an idiot.
This will allow us to recover them, Choji!
We go !
Well. We leave all.
Choji
I will make  you  outside in a moment dopodich will touch they!
It will not be cos   easy.
Which thing?
I must
To stop to you!
They are of Choji. You take!
Be prudent, Choji.
Kiba.
Thanks.
Shikamaru
To judge from your speech with Choji
it seemed that it had some ace in the sleeve.
Therefore it has of the possibilities to strike it ?
Has one technical secret ?
In this mission it has carried the most special drug of the Akimachi clan.
They are three tonics that offer an explosive power.
Three types exist: green, red yellow and.
Ciascuna of these pills encloses a great power.
I understand! E' for that it was cos   sure of himself !
True E' that the energy that they offer those tonics is immense
but every prepared effective it has always some effect to collaterlare!
Eternal damnation! E' only the tonic to the spinaci, nevertheless ago an evil of the devil!
I hope must only use the green.
Choji, you do not have assulutamente to use the red one!
I will end  to you  with a single attack!
Baika not Jutsu
Equal Nikudan Sensha
[ It projects them spiny sweeping ]
USA the kunai like nail in order to increase the spin speed
and the destructive power.
Doton Doroku Gaeshi
[ Art of the land terra:Rovescamento! ]
What?
There are successful?
Also I was being believed the same thing.
What has said Akamaru?
Sapete also you that Akamaru succeeds to determine
the force of an adversary from the odore.
My friend is preoccupied.
He asks himself if those tonics will be enough indeed in order to defeat that monster
In effects reasoning to cold mind the true one remains an incognito
force of that big beast.
It can  are given that Choji does not have no possibility to strike it alone.
But this is the meant one of the combat!
Not to mount the testa!Sei to you only a refuse!
Ronshou
[ destructive Palm ]
You knew that if five persons assemble themselves
between of they there is sure failing?
one that always comes taken in turn and to the occasion used like pawn
sacrificabile.
One description that you paint-brush stocking.
Choji, you only engage yourself in eating
you would have to train a P  more  to you .
E' for that six taken in turn from all
only six us -
You had spoken about someone of valido!Dovresti to call people like Shino!
Here an other bond to null.
Perhaps the number of tried to you imports little
I
It seems that I have hit in the sign.
The village of the leaf is just short of ninja
if it must insert a refuse like you in the square ninja.
I will end  all hour!
Shoushitsu
Tokken
Not six nothing other that a refuse after all.
You have only had in force principle little.
Typical of failing.
The six kind of boy who is in the mistaken place.
You would have to hate your stupid leader.
Shikamaru
As Neji has said this mission is all!
This mission is not a game.
E' one issue of life or dead women.
Hei, Shikamaru
I had even imagined a situation worse in which we would have
had to fight separately.
And sincerely we must be ready just to this, in order to arrive to Sasuke.
Choji is Bravo boy
but it does not have confidence in if same.
It thinks to be more the weak person between than we.
Bhe enough one look in order to understand it.
E' for that it has decided of rimarere l :  in order to become useful for first.
I imagined
But
I and Choji have been in the same square in order much time .
It is that one with which I can cooperate better.
But Shikamaru
If I and you defied yourself, perhaps you would gain.
Not?
Probably even if you had met you, I would have withdrawn myself.
I am I and you six you.
But
Shikamaru always has
Shikamaru has always believed in me!
Choji, six ready one?
It believes truly that I am strong !
E' for that it has only entrusted me to you!
I knew
The thoughts all cos .
But I succeed to understand
that it is stronger
of me, Neji and anyone here present other.
I
creed in he.
A chakra remarkable
but however not sufficient like main capacity.
Facts under ciccione!
You feel who speaks !
Bubun Baika not Jutsu
[  Technical of the perziale expansion  ]
Get out sumimasen
boku tamani boku tamani
yume ni afureru hito not kakeraga
yama not yoni mieru
kami sama ni hotoke sama ni
tsutae naiteru hito not kakeraga
yama not yoni mieru
dan dan dan sura nanderu
borushoi it did not place ni narandara
shake shake shake sagaso janainowa
bye bye bye not let' s of
yama not yoni mieru
So painful E' that I cannot myself be more moved
I did not know that the secondary effects were cos   intense.
Which thing to make? Me pill remains only one.
But if I take it If I take it
I will go  truly
Next episode:
Goodbye friend mine!  I will always believe  in you! I will not never forget  to you !