Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
Huh, it's Lady Tsunade.
Huh? You guys are...
Hey, are you visiting someone
at the hospital too?
Yes.
You too, Lady Tsunade?
Well, I guess...
She just doesn't want to stay
in the executive office...
Shut up!
Hinata, don't faint when
you see Kurenai Sensei.
P-Please let's not talk about that.
Did something happen?
When we were visiting Naruto
in the hospital in the past...
Shino!
This girl fainted when she saw Naruto
all covered with bandages.
Kiba!
I'II... I'll be fine this time!
I finally found you...!
Old Lady Tsunade, I need
to talk to you!
Huh? Hinata!
Naruto...
- Naruto is...so close!
- Hinata? Hinata! What's wrong?
Your face looks a little red...
Do you have a fever or something? Huh?
Hey...
H-Hey, Hinata?!
Hey Hinata!
Are you okay?!
Get a hold of yourself!
Hinata!
Naruto...
The Search for
the Rare Bikochu Beetle
Hey, you woke up.
So Mizuki didn't know anything,
you said?
Tsunade interrogated him herself.
He didn't have any information
that would lead to Orochimaru's
current whereabouts...
After all, that guy was nothing but
a disposable pawn to Orochimaru, huh.
So it seems...
We still don't know where
Sasuke went...
And that's the result after
a desperate fight with Mizuki...
That can't sit right with
Naruto either... huh?
Please Old Lady Tsunade,
say it's okay!
When I say no, I mean no!
As a result, Lady Tsunade wasn't able
to concentrate on her work!
Naruto's been breathing down
her neck the whole time
asking her to let him go off
in search of Sasuke.
So she sneaked out
of her office, but...
He was lying in wait for her here.
Naruto...
I've asked you numerous times already!
Please let me go in search
of Sasuke!
I've told you numerous times already.
Impossible!
Why!
You have some training to do!
I can't because Pervy Sage
isn't around!
We have zero leads on either
Orochimaru and Sasuke.
So how are you planning
to search for him?
I can figure it out somehow!
If there aren't any leads,
I'll go find some!
So please let me go do it!
You're stubborn, aren't you?
You're stubborn too,
Old Lady Tsunade!
- Please let me go!
- No, you may not!
If I say I'm going, I'm going!
Shut up! No means no!
Byakugan!
All right! Good work, Neji!
Move in another half step
right there!
Yes sir!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's take a break, Neji.
Yes.
Have some tea too.
Thank you...
If Hinata was here,
she should have observed a little.
Hinata prepared this...?
It would supplement her training
by observing...
Byakugan!
Let's take a break.
Yes.
Food! Food!
That was pretty well done.
I would say that you're getting closer
to perfecting the technique.
It's thanks to you both.
You're so kind to join me
in my special training every day...
We're a team.
When a comrade in the team
is in a fix,
one offers a helping hand.
That's only natural...
A comrade...
If a comrade suddenly disappears,
it must be awfully hard.
You're talking about Naruto,
aren't you?
Isn't there some way
we could help him?
I'd like to help him out in
some way too... but...
Lady Hokage was telling Naruto...
that there are no leads at all.
There may be one resource...
Really?!
I'm talking about Bikochu.
Bikochu?
Are you talking about
those rare insects?!
I have heard that they had
become extinct some time ago.
Since there was a possibility
that they could become extinct,
the Aburame Clan discontinued
using them,
so a miniscule number of them
should still be alive.
Lady Tsunade, what are Bikochu?
Well... it's not surprising that
you don't know about them.
The last time that Bikochu
were used
was before the last Great War...
Bikochu are one kind of insect
used by insect handlers.
Larvae which have hatched from eggs
become chrysalises in no time at all,
then emerge and turn
into imagos.
They are then made to
recognize scents...
and they are able to track
even the faintest scent...
to its source.
Their olfactory sense is several thousand
times greater than a Ninja Hound's.
They are insects capable of
exhibiting that skill in an exceptional way.
However, Bikochu lay eggs
only once every several years...
This year is actually the year
in which they lay eggs.
And right now is exactly
the time when they hatch.
I see.
There are still some of
Sasuke's belongings left in the village...
Right?
If one makes the Bikochu,
recognize that scent...
We may be able to locate
Sasuke's whereabouts, right?
What is the probability
of finding a Bikochu?
Frankly speaking, not very high.
Perhaps 10%.
10% huh...
As you guys know,
the situation in the village
is currently very grave...
We don't have the leeway of allowing
even Genin to sit around and play.
However, fortunately or unfortunately,
Kurenai has been hospitalized,
so you guys, Squad Eight,
no longer have a mission.
Rather than just letting
you sit around and play,
I'd rather place my bet
on that 10% possibility.
Huh... you mean...
Shino Aburame. Kiba Inuzuka.
Hinata Hyuga.
I order you to search for
the Bikochu!
- All right!
I designate Shino
as the leader this time.
And... that spy up there!
Oww...!
Naruto...
You're going to go even if
I try to stop you, right?
Yup!
In that case, I have no choice
but to let you go...
However...
This is your last chance.
If you don't find the Bikochu...
you must give up on Sasuke!
Wha?
You understand?!
It'll be fine...
I'll find it without fail.
All right. You won't go back
on your word, right?
Yeah! Leave it to me!
You're easily pleased, aren't you?
Owww!
Naruto...
Sasuke...
Hinata.
Good morning.
Neji will be here soon
for his training...
Please prepare tea as always.
Well...
Huh? What's the matter?
I need to go...
on a mission starting now...
A mission, huh...
In that case, it can't be helped...
I'm heading out...
Don't be a burden to the others.
Yes, sir!
I'm... I'm sorry! I'm in a hurry...
The way she handled
her physical response just now...
Hinata...
You're late, Hinata!
I'm sorry!
All right then! Let's head out!
Let's go!
Huh?
Why are you walking at
such a leisurely pace?!
It takes a Shinobi two days on foot
to get to the habitat of
the Bikochu...
There's no need to make haste
from the very start.
But what if the eggs hatch
before we get there?
The eggs of Bikochu only hatch
on the day after it's rained...
There's no sign of it
raining any time soon...
But... if by some remote chance...
Naruto.
Wh What is it?
I am the leader of this team.
While we are on this mission,
you will obey the orders of your leader.
Kiba, I can't believe you're able
to work with that kind of guy...
Well, I've gotten used to it...
I'm sure you'll bond with him too, Naruto.
I wonder about that...
Naruto and the others
left a while ago.
I see.
Didn't you want to go too?
When it comes to searching
for insects,
Shino, who's an insect handler,
is number one...
And then Hinata who has Byakugan...
and Kiba and Akamaru who have
sensitive noses are there too...
So there's really no role that
I could play!
What I must do right now...
is to become a Medical Ninja
as soon as I possibly can!
What's the matter, Shino?!
The sun's going down.
We're setting up camp.
Got it.
- Huh?
- Okay.
Huh? What?!
We're gonna set up
camp already?!
I'm not tired at all yet!
Let's go further!
Naruto, the leader of
this team is me.
I I understand!
Okay then... let's sleep.
Huh... we're gonna sleep already?!
Many animals and plants
go to sleep at sunset
and awake at sunrise.
In order to search for insects,
we must understand the rhythm
of living creatures with our own bodies...
But... the sun's just set...
Naruto, I am the leader of this team...
Okay, okay. I got it!
There's no way
I can sleep so early...
Yeah, right...
All that complaining and guess
who's the first one to fall asleep?
I have to pee...
Huh?
What's that?
It's a waterfall...
Hey... Is somebody there?
S Say...
Damn it...!
S Sorry. Did I scare you?
Huh?
There's nobody there...
Huh, Naruto...
Did you catch a cold?
Yeah... a little...
After sleeping so much
you're still tired?
Well, uh...
When I woke up last night to pee,
I saw something awesome...
Did you catch a cold too, Hinata?
No, I'm okay...
And... what was that awesome thing?
It was a beautiful woman
in the middle of the waterfall!
Huh?
When that person moved her arms,
the water would suddenly move too!
It was awesome!
And what happened then...
When I tried to speak to her,
she suddenly vanished.
You must have been dreaming
or something.
It's starting to feel that way...
You idiot!
Your face is red, Hinata.
You might have really
caught a cold.
Huh... really, I'm fine...
This fruit is edible.
This will be our meal today.
Got it.
We can save on
our food supplies too.
There's one thing
I need to warn you about.
On rare occasions, this fruit grows
to the size of a human being.
However, those fruits
are damaged inside.
Don't tamper with them
under any circumstance.
There's nobody who would
eat something that huge.
N -Naruto...!
He's eating it...
Naruto... We're going on ahead...
I'II... I'll be right behind you!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Wait just a second!
Hey... aren't w e there yet?
Yes.
We're here!
What...?
Wow!
I've never seen anything
like this before.
This certainly isn't a place
where humans could inhabit.
That's right...
That's why it's paradise for insects.
D-Don't tell me...
Could it be that... over there...?
You mean that's where
the Bikochu are?
No problem.
It's better than the Chunin Exam.
Damn... The foothold crumbles easily...
- Naruto...
- What?
As the leader, I'm warning you...
At a time like this,
what is it?!
Don't fall.
I already know that
without your telling me!
Naruto!
No way...!
That was close...
Those were insects, huh...
That's why I warned you.
When this mission is over,
I'm definitely gonna kick
that guy's butt!
This is... the Bikochu forest.
Let's go.
There's no mistake.
Those are Leaf Shinobi.
The fact that those guys came to
a place like this
means their objective is...
Yeah... it's the same as ours...
the Bikochu.
We're not gonna let them
take any Bikochu.
The Bikochu...
belong to us, the Kamizuru Clan!
Crappy news pass us by
And you become speechless
My voice is way too soft
So you don't answer
You're crying Crying alone
What can I do? I'm crying too
"Let my lonely scream ring out
through the night"
I'll thrash this confused era
with my speed Yeah
And I'll thrash this confused night
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar
and my speed Yeah
This sinking world and its evil bastards,
I'll kick their butt Yeah
Huh! If you're talking about
the insect in this photograph,
I'm very familiar with it.
- Huh?
- Really?!
Damn... Don't tell me
that was a Bikochu?
Where did you see it?
I heard some rustling in the kitchen
in the middle of the night,
and I unintentionally threw
a slipper at it...
Wait a second...
N -Naruto...
What you're talking about
is an ordinary cockroach.
Next episode: "What's the Difference?
Don't All Insects Look A like?"