Subtitles By: BakaSan
Final Round Chunin Exam
Tomorrow...
Fierce Moo-Chase Moo-Dash
Final Exams Begin
What's up?
Long time no see.
I was in the hospital for a little while.
The hospital?
But, I'm alright now.
It was nothing serious.
Is that so?
Ayame
Yes.
Here you go.
Mister...
Go ahead and just eat it.
The final exam is tomorrow.
You're better off because you've got a daughter.
Most of my money goes towards food.
Stupid.
Your family is a special case.
Daughters are so much trouble eh?
Yeah...
Sometimes I don't know what to do with her.
Yeah, it's hard to be a father raising a girl.
So only I’m the only on saying something bad...
Hey mister!
An additional order...
Bring everything on this right page!
Welcome!
Look's like our powerful ally is here.
Come over here and order something.
Hey old man...
Lets go home.
What?
Shut up...
You're supposed to have fun at this festival.
What festival?
This is so troublesome.
Stupid...
Since the old times...
the final rounds are like a festival.
I have be there for the final round tomorrow.
Don't make this so hard.
You're in the final round?
Are you serious old man?
It's tomorrow...
Yep.
Tomorrow...
will be a full moon.
You didn't even get a scratch...
That was perfect Neji.
That's enough of a warm-up.
Let's go soon.
I couldn't sleep because I was nervous.
The first round is that guy...
Frankly, my sharingan can't even see chakra holes.
I told you before...
The strongest genin in konoha is on my team.
His name is Hyuga Neji.
It's almost time...
The first round starts hyuga neji match.
Yeah, last years #1 rookie. We can't miss it.
Hyuga Neji.
I was able to summon the frog so it will be alright.
Everybody has a such evil looking eyes.
Hinata?
Naruto-kun
Why are you here?
Isn't the final round today?
Yeah, in a little.
I came to see this practice place where I became a genin.
Why?
uh... no reason.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Hey Hinata.
Neji is your cousin right?
Yes.
Is he really that strong?
I see...
But Naruto, you may be able to win.
Yeah, because I'm strong.
Yeah, I think you'll definitely win.
When I was heard you cheering for me...
I felt I was a lot stronger.
Hinata! Do your best!
After the prelims were over I was able...
to like myself a little bit more.
I... don’t... bend... my words.
That's my nindo. (way of the ninja)
To other people I may look like I haven’t changed.
But I think I was able to change...
Thanks to you Naruto-kun.
Hey Hinata.
You really think so?
I may look strong, but I always make mistakes.
I'm so frustrated, looking strong is just an act.
That’s not true.
Naruto, even if you make mistakes...
you were always a proud failure.
Watching you touches my heart. You're not perfect... that’s why.
When you fail you gain the strength to get
better. I think that's the real source of strength.
Naruto-kun, I think you're a really strong person.
Thank you Hinata.
Wasn't I always the last in my class,
eh? I guess I was just trying too hard.
I was down unlike my usual self... but you've cheered me up.
Later. I'm going to the match.
I always thought you were...
a dark, hesitant, and slightly weird person.
But a person like you...
I like the person like you well.
I like you.
Oh yeah. Definitely come to see me beat Neji up.
Damnit. It's already that time?
I'm late. Later, Hinata!
Sorry, Hinata. I'm late.
Well, Shino's battle is later on, so...
Hey, Hinata?
What's up?
Oh. It'll begin!
Get out of my way!
I said get out of my way!
Shit. It's quite far... I'll be late!
Naruto Nichan (big bro)!
I'm here for you when you're in trouble!
Why are you at place like this?
I'll explain later. This way!
There's a special shortcut you can
get to the arena in a straight line.
What? Alright! Good job, Konohamaru!
One who controls an escape controls the time.
Oh, is that right? You're great, Konohamaru.
There must be a hole on a wall somewhere around here...
Here we go...
Huh? What's wrong, Konohamaru?
The escape route was fixed, it seems.
I don't have time anymore.
Bro!
Next hand.
Seriously, it's almost time!
It's a secret, but there is a great
path to get to the arena in one second!
What? Alright! Good job, Konohamaru!
This hole is the shortcut?
One straight line to the arena. It's for sure.
One straight line, eh?
Alright. Let's hurry up!
Yup!
Konohamaru. What's up with this?
Don't worry. In no time we'll be at the arena.
See. We can now see the end of the way.
Hot!
This must be a mistake...
What kind of structure is that?
Plus, we're getting further away!
It was connected to the arena until recently.
I have to find the next hand quickly...
This is it!
If you ride on this, you'll be at the arena in no time.
A cow, eh?
You don't understand, bro.
Once it starts to run seriously, no racing
horse can beat it. It's really a great one.
Bro. Count on this cow, and you'll be at arena soon.
Ok, then. I'm counting on you. Alright, go!
Ouch.
Bro. Do your best!
Hey. So many are missing...
What's going on? It's going to start soon.
What's going on, Sasuke-kun...
Plus even Naruto isn't here yet.
Why is it!
This isn't good.
Oh yeah! Kagebushin no jutsu!
Everyone. Ditch these raging cows!
Alright!
What are you guys doing? Why are you coming back here?!
New ones arrived. They cut off our escape route!
What are you doing increasing the number of cows!
What? Is that Uzumaki Naruto?
Please take care of them!
Hey, everybody else is already in the arena.
What a way to appear...
He's so late.
Troublesome...
Everyone! Run! All the cows in the village are chasing me here!
What are you talking about?
I'm serious. So many of them are...
Where's Sasuke?
My opponent, Dosu isn't here either.
Hey, you two over there... Stop being nervous.
Be proud and show your face well to the audience.
In this final round, you guys are the main event.
Hey Hinata. Look at me beating up this
unpleasant guy with your eyes wide open.
Besides this guy talks about my life like he knows everything.
One's fate is already decided when
he's born? Don't make me laugh.
A person can definitely change!
I'll prove that by defeating this guy!
Next episode
Byakugan VS Kagebushin!
I'll definitely win!!
Stop talking and let's begin!