Subtitles By: BakaSan
Let the tenth match... Begin.
Go for it!
Fatso!
Damn, those two! I'm going to
finish this match quickly and beat them up!
Then I'll make it quick without playing around... Fatso.
You bandage wrapped sushi-roll!
I know your weakness already because we fought you before.
You'll release the shock-wave
from the holes on your arm, so...
Ninpou Baika no Jutsu! (multiply-size)
And! Konoha-ryu
Taiketsu! (konoha-style)
I'll be ok as long as he can't attack my ears!
Nikudan Sensha! (Human-body Tank)
Poccharikei Banzai! (Hail the Chubby)
Alright! Crash him! Choji!
That guy's attack can be done without body contact using sound.
But it's only if his oppenent's ears are exposed.
His ears are within his body, plus he's wearing ear plugs.
Also, his body is spinning at high speed.
So, how're you going to attack with sound?
You can't even move like that. That's what I was waiting for!
That's no use because I'm wearing ear plugs!
No. It's over...
More than 70% of the human body is
made of water which transmits sound.
In other words, your entire body is like an ear.
Winner... Dosu Kinuta.
Orochimaru-sama... No, Orochimaru!
I will show you that I'm not just a tool for testing.
Are you alright?
I want to eat meat.
Oh man. He wasn't even attacked by full power.
He lost the match, but I guess I'll
take him for Yakiniku (Korean BBQ).
It's finally done.
Finally the real final exams.
Now, all the prelims are done.
Shadow Moving in the Darkness Crisis Approaching Sasuke!
I wonder what happened to Naruto...
Let's sneak outside now. Iruka-sensei
has his mind somewhere else these days.
Konohamaru! Are you trying to cut class again?!
No! Just going to the rest room!
Don't lie!
For all of you here, except one that's not here,
who will go to the real exam, congratulations.
I have something I want to ask you...
About Sasuke?  Well...
I'm sorry to say but even I don't
know much.  Don't worry too much.
Everything is all up to Sasuke himself.
Sakura, I'm going to leave here now. So,
please listen to the rules for the final exams.
Including Uchiha Sasuke who's not
here, there are five from Konoha,
three from Sand,
and one from Sound.
Now I'll explain the rules of the final exam.
It's finally here.
I heard that the prelims are done, and
they're going to the final exams.
Anyways... this country is so
peaceful... or I should say it only knows the peace.
Other countries are busy building up their military power.
Can you take it now?
Yeah, I guess I could... but I'm not sure
if it would be fun to take that old-fart's head.
Is that so?
It seems to me that you're still hesitating.
From now, the powers of many Ninja villages
will battle for a long time.
The Sound will be one of them.
You're trying to trigger it.
And he's the bullet for that, right? Uchiha Sasuke right.
It's creepy because you're too perceivable.
Not that much.
I didn't know about Dosu, Zaku, and Kin.
While gathering information about Sasuke-kun, I did a tactless
thing like recieving their attack to learn their abilities.
You overrate me.
I see that I am not fully trusted by you yet.
Was it really necessary for me to tell you,
my right-arm man, about such low level guys?
That is the proof of my trust.
That's why...
...I'll ask you to take care of Sasuke-kun.
The cursed seal I gave to him was sealed
by Kakashi. Well, that's nothing actually.
I want you to abduct him right now, before
the darkness in his mind disappears.
It's not like you to be impatient like that.
There's something I'm worried about...
It's about Uzumaki Naruto, isn't it?
You're so sharp.
Sasuke-kun is full of revenge...he has been
living to revenge his big brother, Itachi.
He cannot die until he acheives his goal.
But when he fought with me, he came at me even though
he knew he couldn't beat me without fearing death.
I thought he wasn't the type of
kid who lives in hurry for death.
According to your information, the relationship with the Kyubi
(nine-tailed) kid has been gradually changing his goal and mind.
Since he has that much of an effect over Sasuke-kun...
...it's better to separate those two early.
I should dye him in my color soon.
Well...
Kabuto, if you...
...want to stop me...
the only way is for you to kill Sasuke-kun now.
You can't kill me because even though you're
stong, you're at the same level as Kakashi.
Just kidding. You can go now. I'm trusting you.
His face... I wonder what he's thinking.
In the real exam, you'll show your fight in front of everybody.
I want each of you to show your ability fully
as a representative of your country.
Therefore, the real exam will take place one month from now.
Aren't we gonna start right now, right here?
It's a suitable preparation period.
What do you mean?
It's a preparation period to inform of the end of the prelims
and to invite the Daimyo and Shinobi Heads of the other countries.
Also, this is a preparation period for you guys.
This old-fart... he always talks in a winding way.
I still don't understand. What does that mean?
It means that it's a preparation
period to learn your opponent and yourself.
It's time to analyze the information you've gathered
during the prelims, and to create tactics for a victory.
Fights up till now were against an unknown
enemy, as if you were in the real war.
That's true. I never imangined that he uses sand as tool.
But the final matches aren't like that. There may be some
of you who've shown everything in front of your rivals.
To be fair, during the one month,
each of you should train and work hard.
It's not good if I stay like this. I don't have time
to play around during the month... really... really.
Being exceptional isn't always a
good thing. We were too visible.
It was bad luck for both of us to
be caught by Orohimaru-sama's eye.
It's surprising that, even at this young
age, he has a demon living inside of him.
That's the part will be used, and at the
end with that Ninjutsu, even this kid...
Kabuto...prehaps he really may kill Sasuke-kun.
That's Kakashi-san, catching my attack in your blind spot...
But the next time, you'd better have at least ten of them.
The Anbu that I prepared were killed this easily.
You're not a regular genin, are you?
You're exceptional because you could
prepare your attack as soon as you sensed me.
No, not that good.
What business do you have with Sasuke? Based on
what it is... I'll capture and interrogate you.
I don't know if it's possible by somebody like you.
Do you want to try that somebody?
I believe you're the son of the head medical team in Konoha.
Your name is Yakushi Kabuto, if I remember right.
Do you have some connection to Orochimaru?
If you catch me here now, you may not be
able to prove my connection to Orochimaru.
Shut up and just answer my question.
What if I say no?
I'm the one asking questions here. Answer my question.
If you leave me alone now, you'll find it out
eventually. So, can you just let me go this time?
You are a spoiled kid, I see...
Don't mess with an adult too much.
Don't talk too big. I have the advantage in this situation.
I see...
Kagebunshin
Shit...I let him get away...
What a guy...
As I thought... this is Shikon No Jutsu, that
controls a dead body by moving its heart temporarily.
And he even changed the face of the dead body thoroughly.
Plus, he removed the smell of his own body
and stopped the sound of the heart beat,
and pretended to be a dead body of
one of the Anbu that he killed...
for preparing to run away.
It's makes sense since he was brought up
as the adopted son of the chief medical Dr.
If a guy like this level is working for Orochimaru...
I can't stay like this...
And now, I want to let you all go already, but...
before that, there is one important thing
that needs to be done before the final matches.
Man, what is it? I need to start training soon!
Don't be so impatient. Take one
from the box that Anko is holding.
I'll go around, so take your turn.
Only one, ok?
Alright. Did everybody take one? Then, tell
me the number on your paper from the left.
It's 8.
Mine is 1.
That means he gets 4.
Now, I'll let you know the tournament
brackets of the real exam.
That's what the drawing was for.
Now, Ibiki...show the tournament matching.
Naruto vs Neji Gaara vs Sasuke Kankuro vs
Shino Temari vs winner below Dos vs Shikamaru
Too far...
The real match is just a tournament?!
Besides, I have one more match than anybody else...
and I don't have any intention to get revenge for Choji.
Phew...I'm saved since I'm in the different block from Gaara.
Uchiha Sasuke
That's perfect.
Hyuga Neji... from the start? I prefer that!
Sasuke-kun is going against that guy?
Can I ask one thing?
There will be only one winner because it's a tournament.
Does that mean there's only one who can become Chunin?
No, that's not true.
The Judges, including me, Kazekage, Daimyo, and Shinobi Heads from
each country that request missions, will watch the final matches.
Those judges will grade you throughout the tournament. For
those who are judged to have enough quality to be Chunin,
even if you lose in the first
match, it is still possible to be Chunin.
That means, it is possible that everybody
here will become Chunin?
Well...on the other hand, it is also
possible that nobody can become Chunin.
To win through the tournament means that you will
get more rounds to appeal your ability to the judges.
Did you understand, Shikamaru-kun?
Damnit... it's so troublesome...
Good job till now. Dismissed until one month later.
My second round would be either no-eyebrow from Sand or Sasuke.
That guy is strong enough to beat up Geji-Mayu (Thick-Eyebrows).
Sabaky-Kyu! (Desert Coffin)
I want to fight against you, too.
Hmmm... I will ask Kakashi-sensei...
Hey, where's Sasuke's room?
Nobody is allowed to see Sasuke-sama.
Wh..why is that?
I cannot tell you...
Hey, lady. Why?
Naruto, be quiet in the hospital.
Kakashi-sensei!
Hey, hey... I have a favor to ask...
You don't need to tell me the end of your sentence.
I guessed that you'll come to me like that...
I appointed a person who can oversee your training.
Whhhhy? I want Kakashi-sensei to train me!!
I have a little business to take care
of. So, I don't have time to spend on you.
You're going to train Sasuke, aren't you?!
Well... don't say it like that.
I found a more reliable teacher than me for you.
Who is it?
It's me!
Ahhhhhhhh! You're the closet-pervert!!
How dare you.
Man, I can't understand. I don't
care if he's an elite teacher or what.
But I don't believe I can get any stronger by getting
trained by a closet-pervert who's weaker than me!
I've got to be stronger no matter what!
If you really are a great Ninja, then
make me understood by your power.
Next Episode. Ebisu Again! I won't
let you do such perveted things!
I will win the next battle, too.