Subtitles By: BakaSan
Hey, Ero Sennin!
Aren't you supposed to be training me?
I'm gathering some material now.
Do it by yourself.
Alright... I'm going to summon a surprisingly huge frog!
Kuchiyose-no-jutsu
(Summon Technique)
Huh? What's up? Was a frog summoned?
Wa... Wait a sec!
What part of that thing is a frog?
Be quiet! I'm seriously trying hard!
If so, then try channeling chakra like you're gonna die!
I'm doing that!
Sasuke-kun...
Sakura!
Stop sleeping in so late and help me down here!
I'm not sleeping! I'm busy now!
Ok, Ok...Then tell me when you're not busy!
Later!
Seriously... Man...
Painful Feeling's A Single Flower With A Wish
Some of you may already heard of this, but...
Gekko Hayate's dead body was found near Kikyo Castle.
Was Hayate...?
No way!
I can't believe it!
Was it done by Orochimaru?
No. We can't come to that conclusion that easily.
Hayate was probably following the Sound spy, Kabuto.
Well, it's for sure that Orochimaru
is trying to do something, but...
Then cancel the Chunin exam, and let's take care of Orochimaru!
No. He revealed himself to Anko,
and threatened us to not stop it...
...the Chunin exam where all the ninja's gather at one place.
What does it mean?
Orochimaru has the ability to crush
a small country by himself alone.
Probably each country has been watching
him since he left this village...
In addition, he conviniently has a grudge against Konoha.
Many countries want him.
Then, you're saying that...
our allies have betrayed Konoha by working with Orochimaru?!
Well, an alliance treaty is same level as verbal promise.
Exactly like the Ninkai Taisen was... (Great Ninja War)
Anyway...
We have too little information. Let's stop guessing needlessly.
We have already sent Anbu to
gather information in each country.
It's dangerous to move thoughtlessly.
It may be exactly what the enemy wants.
Besides...
I have faith in all of you.
In the worst case, all we have to do
is go to war with all of Konoha's power.
At that time...
Don't tell anyone about this mark!
...should I have stopped him regardless of what he said?
No Visitors?
Yes. I'm sorry...
I can understand him being hospitalized,
but what's this about no visitors?
Even we don't know the details...
Being worried about him here doesn't do anything.
Should I bring some flowers to the hospital?
Beautiful!
Dammit!
Oh... It's rare that you come to buy some flowers at my shop.
It's nothing... It's none of your business.
It's rare, too, that you're watching the shop.
I'm gonna quickly choose some...
People don't like flowers with the root
because it says they'll root in the hoptial.
So, the base is cut off flower.
What are you talking about?
It's no use to play innocent! You're
going to see Sasuke-kun, aren't you?
Mom, I'm going out for a while!
I won't allow you to visit him alone. I'm going with you.
Omimai (To visit him in hospital)
Dammit... Ino pig!
I decided to pick this flower! One Rose of Love!
It's a no brainer. I'm choosing this one, the narcissus.
It's a brave flower that stands valiantly even in
the coldness of the winter and waits for the spring.
I make my wish for him to be able to leave hospital soon.
I see that you became a bit more knowledgeable.
I told you that I won't lose to you!
Alright, alright. Then you're getting one narcissus, ok?
Ah... I'll take two.
Why? One is enough.
Well, one for Lee-san, too.
Another one!
Yakiniku (Korean BBQ)
Kalbi for 10 people!
How can you eat that much... I'm
feeling sick just by watching you eat.
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, it's here!
Those are mine. Don't eat them, Shikamaru.
I'm not gonna eat them.
What are you guys doing? Eating Yakiniku for lunch?!
Oh, Ino and Sakura...
Shikamaru, don't you need to do special
training for the final exam match?
I've been doing that every single
day. Asuma doesn't let me get away.
In fact, Choji's helping us for that special training.
You accepted that?
Yup. He promised me
all-I-can-eat Yakiniku, instead.
I see.
I should've not survived for the final exam match.
Don't talk like that.  There' a lot of
people who can't be there even they want to.
He's right!
I heard that Gai and Kurenai are doing very hard ones...
What?
It won't be good to be there if you
get knocked out in one second... eh?
Damn... Tiresome.
It's already above the human's limitation...
I guess I used up too much chakra...
Are you alright? Neji?!
Kuchiyose no jutsu!
Ahhh! A tadpole again?! You haven't improved even an inch!
See! It's bigger than the last time!!
I can't see the difference!
Konoha Hospital
Uchiha Sasuke-san, right?
You can have five minutes. I can't allow any longer than that.
He still needs to lie quietly.
Yes.
Sasuke-kun, visitors.
Two cute girls...
His clothes are gone!
This is not good. His body has't
recovered enough to walk around outside.
Doctor! Doctor!
No way.
Sasuke-kun will definetely look for me.
Sasuke-kun, where did you go?
I'm feeling the task to climb up the cliff this too hard...
man, my body is weakened...
Will I make it in time?
Kai (Open)
Hey.
You finally got here.
We're going to look for Sasuke-kun.
But if you see him, please let us know.
Yes.
And, Lee-kun right?
Yes
He, too, hasn't recovered enough
to move. It's going to be brief. Ok?
Lee-kun, visitors.
Two cute girls...
No, Lee-kun too?
Out there...
Sakura, let's go!
One-armed push ups 200 times. If I
can't do it, I'll do 100 one-leg squats.
Lee-kun, stop it!
Lee-kun, Stop IT!
Please don't touch me!
Please don't disturb my training!
I'll take two.
Why? One is enough.
Well, one for Lee-san, too.
Well, ah... Sakura. Did you hear about Lee-san?
About what?
I heard that Lee-san is seriously injured, and...
with that body he can't live as a Ninja anymore.
I'm not finished yet.
It's not worth it to work hard for those
who don't also believe in themselves.
one... one... one more time!
I'll bring the strecher. Please watch him.
Yes.
Ino...
Why do boys always push themselves to the edge?
Don't ask such question to me, I'm a girl...
Sorry.
Nikudan Sensya! (Human body Tank)
Ninpo Kagemane no.... (Shadow Copy)
Dammit. I don't have enough chakra!
What's up, Shikamaru? Did you already reach your limit?
How annoying...
Alright, Choji. One more time.
Who would that be from...?
This rose was wasted...
My  narcissus, too.
Ah... not fun.
Hey Naruto. No more bikini girls
around, so it's time to go back today.
Eh. We can still stay here... a
little longer.. just a little bit!
I'm hungry... I'm getting tired, too.
You did nothing.
Be grateful that I'm at least being here with you!
He's snapped!
Ok. I got it. Oiroke no
jutsu. (Sexy-no-jutsu)
Oh man... is that it?
What I want to do is not Oiroke
no jutsu, but Kuchiyose no jutsu!
Ok, ok. Then, show it to me.
Here it comes...
Kuchiyose no jutsu!
Alright!
You're dead! You've got no talent!
Look at it closely!
It's got hind legs!
You're super stupid!
Try summoning one with hands, legs, and ears all at once!
Shut up! It's better than before just by having it with legs!
Ah, Ichiraku's ramen is tasty! If
training is like this, I can do it forever.
Eat! Eat up! Eat more! Becasue it's the last...
Huh? Did you say something?
Does it taste good, Naruto?
Hey, another bowl, master!
Eat up like you have nothing to regret.
Next Episode Dead or Alive!? Risking life for learning Jutsu!!
The Sennin seems to be hiding some secrets from me.