Subtitles By: BakaSan
What?
Is that...
an empty shell of sand?
Hot-blooded Loser! Finally the
Forbidden Secret Technique Blossoms!
When did he do that? There is no way...
It was while you were praying with your eyes closed.
The body movement of Lee stopped
for a second because of the pain.
That was when.
Gaara...
Are those...?!
There is no doubt about it. His eyes reveal that...
the demon inside of him...
has been... fully awakened!
Run!
That bobbed-hair is completely exhausted.
Gaara is just playing around with him.
Why... Why doesn't Lee-san dodge those attacks?!
With Lee-san's speed, dodging those attacks
shouldn't have been a problem, right?
It is not that he does not dodge. He cannot dodge them.
What do you mean?
The technique he used, the
Renge (Lotus) is a double-edged sword.
A double-edged sword?
Why do you think the Renge (Lotus)
is treated as a Forbidden technique?
uhh...
The Renge is neither Ninjutsu nor Genjutsu.
It is a Taijutsu that moves at ultra high-speed.
You couldn't imagine exactly
how much damage it does to the body.
His entire body is in a lot of pain
now. It's impossible for him to move.
Am I wrong... Gui?
No way!
He can use no Ninjutsu, and no Genjutsu...
Plus, his only skill, taijustu, is useless in his condition...
There is no way he can win this.
If this continues, Lee will probabaly...
Lee!
Alright! Do your best you guys!
...or I will add two hundred laps!
Idiot! There is no way you can be a Ninja.
Yes, I can!
Besides, a person with no Ninjutsu skills cannot be a Ninja.
Anyway... it doesn't make any sense that you are in the ninja academy
with no Ninjutsu and Genjutsu skills, and below average Taijutsu skill.
Do you know what people call you around here?
Hot-blooded!
Hot-boolded Loser!
Hey, Lee! Calm down! Lee!
He is the Hot-blooded Loser that people are talking about.
He resembles somebody, doesn't he?
Especially, those eyebrows.
Rock Lee, a boy who can do only below average Taijutsu.
But you trained Taijutsu like crazy.
396! 397! 398! 399! 400! 401! 402! 403!
If I cannot kick the log 500 times, then I will do 1000 squats!
413! 414! 415! 416! 417! 418! 419! 420!
Oh, there is somebody already here...
422! 423! 424! 425! 426! ...
I guess I will come back later.
Squat 1000 times! If I cannot finish, I
will do Seiken-Tsuki (punch) 2000 times!
795! 796! 797! 798!
Is he still here?
Seiken-tsuki(Forefist Thrust) 2000 times! If
I cannot finish I will jump rope 2000 times!
After training in only Taijutsu fiercely you have finally...
Alright. You guys become Genin
from today. I want to hear your goals.
Yes! Tenten!
I want to be a very strong Ninja, like the legendary
Kunoichi (female Ninja), Tsunade-sama.
And, how about you, Neji?
I dont want to answer that.
I, I!
I want to prove that a person can be a respectful Ninja,
even if he can use neither Ninjutsu nor Genjutsu!
That is everything to me!
He has nice eyes.
YOU! What is so funny? I am serious! I
will be a great Ninja even only with Taijutsu!
Give up already.
He will just die when Gaara's done playing.
Geji-Mayu (Thick-Eyebrow)!
Not yet! Not yet...
You really do not learn your lesson.
There is no way you can beat him. Neji is a genius, unlike you.
Genius? What is a genius anyway?
Even without natural talent I
will surpass a genius with effort!
That is my everything. That is my Nindo(way of ninja)!
It's useless, Lee.
You cannot beat me, even you make great
efforts. It is decided already.
That's not true! It's not ...
But you never... never think of giving up.
You are wasting your time.
It was a bad luck that the bobbed-hair
got a match against Gaara.
No. Lee is not a guy who gives up so easily.
What?
Because Lee...
Because Lee... you have kept working hard.
If I cannot jump rope 1200 times continuously,
I will kick the log 2000 times!
1116! 1117! 1118! 111...
Hey, Lee! You taking a break already?
Gui-sensei, what brought you here? I already
apologized for my mistake in the last mission.
Lee, it is true that you are different from Neji. You cannot use
Ninjutsu or Genjusu. Plus you are not a genius of Taijutsu.
But Lee, you are a genius who has
the power... the potential to surpass Neji.
Stop saying such things to try to ease my pain.
Its not to sooth your pain... Its because you are...
a genius of efforts!
Is it really... true?
I lived until now in believing that. I can become stronger
if I train two or three times more than Neji.
But recently I started to think
that I cannot compete with a true genius.
I want to know if my hard work really is rewarded in the end so
I challenge Neji to find it out. But the result is always the same...
I cannot even compete with him at all.
Even in our missions my legs still shake.
Im begining to think that I can never be
strong no matter how much effort I make...
I am really... really scared.
What should I do?
A guy who cannot believe in himself is wasting his hard work!
Lee, you are very much like me.
Are you talking about the eyebrows?
No, it's not just eyebrows.
To tell you the truth, I was also a loser a long time ago.
You were?!
But now I surpassed even the genius elite,
Kakashi, because I worked hard.
"I want to prove that a person can be a respectful Ninja,
even if he can use neither Ninjutsu nor Genjutsu!!"
That is your Nindo, isn't it? That is a good
goal. It's a good goal that is worth working hard for.
You just need to believe in yourself and keep going.
Be a strong enough man so that all I need
to do is to is smile when you fight.
You got it, Lee?
Yes!
Thank you, Gui-sensei!
No! Lee-san! If you fight any longer, you will die!
Geji-Mayu (Thick-eyebrow)!
What?
Lee got his speed ..
back!
Sensei is watching me with a smile on his face....
That is all I need to be brought back to life strongly.
Be stronger! Be much stronger!
Lee-san is smiling, even though he is in serious trouble.
No, it is his turn to put the opponent in serious trouble.
The Renge (Lotus) of Konoha blossoms twice.
Blossom twice... Lee-san said the same thing before.
The Renge of Konoha blossoms twice. I promise you that
I will be a stronger man at next time I see you.
You're not talking about...?! Gui!
It is what you are thinking.
That means he will open the Eight Celestial Inner Body
Gates (Hachimon-Tonkou) and do a Ura Renge (Reverse Lotus).
Ura Renge?
That is right.
Oh my...
Gui, how many gates of Hachimon-Tonkou is he able to open now?
Five gates.
What are you guys talking about?
What is the Hachimon-Tonkou and Ura Renge?
Hachimon-Tonkou is to remove
limits as a preparation for Ura Renge.
Removing limits?
That is right.
On the chakra highway from the head to
other parts of the body there is the...
Kai-mon (Initial Gate)
Kyu-Mon (Heal Gate)
Sei-Mon (Life Gate)
Sho-Mon (Harm Gate)
To-Mon (Limit Gate)
Kei-Mon (View Gate)
Kyo-Mon (Wonder Gate)
Shi-Mon (Death Gate)
These eight spots are where chakra holes are
concentrated. These are called the Eight Gates.
The Eight Gates always limit the
amount of chakra flowing throughout the body.
To do the Renge he would breakthrough those limits...
and gain the power a thousand times stronger than normal.
The Omote Renge is a technique
that opens only the first gate, Kai-Mon.
it removes the limit his brain has
on how far he can push his muscles.
Then, how about the Ura Renge?
By opening the second gate, Kyu-Mon, he will
increase the bodys energy unnaturally,
and then the Ura Renge will start
by opening the third gate, Sei-Mon.
No way. The Omote Renge caused a lot of damage to his
body. If he performs a technique above that level...
You are right.
One can briefly gain the power that is above the Hokage by opening
all the eight gates. However, anyone who does will definitely...
...die.
I'm not trying to find out what the boy means to you, nor
am I going to say that you should put your feelings aside.
But there is a limit to
everything. I've lost respect for you, Gui.
You don't understand him at all.
He has an important goal that he wants
to achieve... even if by risking his own life.
I want to prove that a person can be a respectful Ninja, even if
he can use neither Ninjutsu nor Genjutsu! That is everything to me!
That is why... I wanted make him a
guy who can achieve it. That is all...
Lee, I'm going to teach you a new technique.
Hell ya!
This will be your ace in the hole.
Lee! Listen to what I am telling you seriously!
Yes, Sensei!
I will tell you this first. This technique
is more forbidden than the Renge.
And, this will become the most special technique for you.
Special?
Because of that, there is a very
strict rule to use this technique. That is...
That is...
What?
I do not know what you are going to
do. But this is the end for you.
You are right.
No matter what will happen, the next move will be the end.
Neji, Sasuke-kun, and ...
I cannot be the only one who loses here!
Gui-sensei, please acknowledge that...
...this is the time...
to carry out and to protect my own Nindo (the way of Ninja)!
The third gate, Sei-mon OPEN!
I came this far by believing that efforts
will be rewarded at the end.
Neji,
Sasuke-kun, and Naruto-kun!
I cannot be the only one who loses here!
This is my secret technique, but I
will specially show this for you.
This is the ultimate special Taijutsu technique!
Next Episode: Oh Rock Lee! This is the way a man lives!!
This is the end!