http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
The driven in ones more and more often come.
Sasuke-kun
task that you would have to be withdrawn.
Eh?
From when six met to you
with strange Orochimaru six cos  .
-  Akadou Yoroi VS Uchiha Sasuke  -
Just just for first!
I did not ask better.
The challengers of the first encounter are
Akadou Yoroy and Uchiha Sasuke.
There are objections?
-  Not!
The pain not if it goes some!
It seems that the Juin Jutsu makes it badly.
Not to use the Sharingan.
Then you knew it.
If that sign on the neck began
to expand itself you would find yourself in life danger
Probable.
If it had to happen,
the encounter would come suspended
and I would take part in order to stop to you.
He would come Suspended!
This sign seems that
it reacts to my Chakra.
Therefore in this encounter
other that Sharingan,  I will not be able
to use not even the normal techniques.
Moreover the power of Yoroi
.. how much is worse could capitare to you
Sasuke-kun.
Well, begun also.
Six you
That it steals the Chakra to me
Of six shrewed you only hour ?
Super Eyebrows Jealous!
Shishi Rendan!
Six you
That it steals the Chakra to me
Of six shrewed you only hour?
Already, the characteristic of Yoroi
it is to absorb the Chakra.
Its technique is narcotic
from the ability to absorb
the energy of the enemy
only touching it with the palm of the hand
and once that your Chakra will be exausted
you will become succube of my sign, Sasuke-kun.
Cos   freed
sweet to be able.
E' your only one via of salvation!
Vattene!
You still have of the forces.
In any case six solo an unarmed animal.
There is lacked little.
Not to fear
I will put  fastly fine to all.
Cos' you have?
You have already exausted all the energies?
It tries the body to body.
How I must act?
At this rate
I will come  defeated.
Uchiha Sasuke
all here?
Sasuke-kun!
Sasuke!!!
E' cos   that you carry the name of the Uchiha?
If it is cos   not to dare to make these figuracce!
You fight seriously!!
It is
I have understood!
You cannot allow you of distrarti.
Now we close the crash.
Made E'?
E' scomparso?
But this is my technique.
What!
Even if
from this point varying mine is one!
E' the end!!!
The Kage Buyou!
You take this!
Eternal damnation!
Just  hour cannot react!
I pray to you
stopped!
Sasuke!!!
Not to dare to make these figuracce!
I did not think that I would have made them to worry!
E' to the limit?
I will not make myself
to subject
from this diavoleria!
The sign has been withdrawn?
You take this.
It underrates me!
Six you that it underrates it!
I have not still ended!
Shishi Rendan!
Not there is neanche need to control.
The crash ends here.
Consequently
the winner of the first crash is Uchiha Sasuke!
He has exceeded the eliminatoria phase.
Made E'!
Beautiful job.
The technique of the Shishi Rendan
it was * taijutsu of Gai.
* Martial limbs
It must have them memorizza to you with the Sharingan
when it has faced Lee.
Sasuke!
Just you! Just you
that you make one pessima Victoria!
Six pure all broken one!
* BAKA!
* (Stupid)
That idiot!
Sasuke-kun
little evil!
I  will gain anch'!
Lee, is survivor thanks to you.
If you had not seen your blow they give near
ce I would not have made it.
But it does not seem one technical to often use.
I understand.
You have learned the blows that I have used
against of you that time.
Sharingan.
Dev' to be this your innata ability.
Sasuke-kun
.. a six great guerriero!
You will become more and more strong!
Your abilities scare to me.
The multiple blow is a taijutsu
to high speed
and  it cannot  be executed
without a hard training.
It is not learned simply cos
neanche with the use of the Sharingan.
Without to count the improvisation
for that final technique.
Kakashi, this boy remembers me you
from small!
The esordiente n.1 of the slid year was Hyuuga Neji.
This year seems that it is Uchiha Sasuke.
Who of the two will be strongest?
That boy
The Sharingan has taken advantage of
in one unfavorable situation.
The blood of the Uchiha is demonstrated
terrifying once again.
Impietrita Sono.
Successful E' to make to withdraw the sign
in espazione with the single force of will.
Eternal damnation Of new?
Well, otherwise we will not amuse ourselves.
Sasuke-kun is cos   Bravo!
It knows to me that we will stop ourselves here.
I have hunger!
Fantastic!
Nothing of special!
Magnificent!
Uchiha Sasuke
we of the medical group
we will supply you the best cures.
It is not a problem that you can manage.
Uh?
I  of he will take care.
I will carry  to you  in the room on the back
and I seal you the sign.
We can wait for the end of the combats?
I would want to see the encounter.
Not.
They give one to you calmed.
If we do not act to more soon,
you will suffer the most serious consequences.>.
I do not want more to feel your egoist demands.
Force you come.
Sasuke-kun
Sakura-chan
you have not seen something like
one hurt on the neck of Sasuke?
You promise it to me.
Not to say nothing to naruto of this sign!
What?
It makes part of the square job.
It would be stupid causargli
useless worries!
I would not know!
I understand.
Hour
we begin the next encounter!
-  Zaku Abumi VS Aburame Shino  -
Who is the other amateur?
The combatants make themselves ahead.
Well.
Then we begin according to encounter.
It is the ninja of the sound
to which Sasuke-kun he has broken the arm.
It seems proud of yours
arms.
Stopped!!!
It fights in this state?
Shino-kun ce will make it?
Sure! Shino is strong!
Eh?
E' the only one that I would not want to defy.
Begun!
It will be interesting
to see as you will fight, Zaku.
If you will fight now, you will not be able
more to carry out the activity of the ninja.
Renunciation!
I succeed to move po' an arm.
and for as you he is more than sufficient!
You will not succeed to strike to me with a single arm.
You make Hush!
You take this!
* Zankuuha!
* (cutting wave)
Well!
You still resist a moment.
I have nearly ended.
Fuuja Houin!
(Suppressor of the Evil!)
Even if that sign had to react of new
this I seal would have to block!
However
I seal depends very
from your will.
If you lose the confidence in you
and your will wavers
the sign will be expanded of new!
It seems sfinito!
Now you succeed also to use seals.
Six improved, Kakashi.
You six
It is passed some of time, Kakashi-kun.
Orochimaru!
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
nee kikoe masu ka?