Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking NFS
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh!  Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the fire!BANG!
SasukeÉ
NotÉ
But who is?
He possesses like Sasuke the SharinganÉ
ThenÉ
E' this the child who has the Kyubi within of if.
(Demon Vixen to Nine Tails)
These twoÉ
É they are to acquaintance of the Kyubi?
Naruto-kunÉ
You would have to follow to us.
Episode #84:
Tipsy the Chidori. The roar of Sasuke!
It must be nearÉ
I am arrivingÉ
Brother.
After the schoolÉ you could help me to improve my technique with the Shuriken?
I have other to makeÉ
Task is better than it asks it our fatherÉ
I say that six more Bravo is with the technique with the Shuriken youÉ and also it task like he.
He always deals to me like if pits one scocciatura.
Ouch.
It pardons To Me, Sasuke.
Even the next time.
Today I do not have time to dedicate to you.
You always repeat: "It pardons Sasuke To Me "É
É and you hit to me on the forehead.
It never does not dedicate attention to meÉ
Not even today.
Father.
Why my brother does not dedicate never a po' to me of attention?
Changed E'É lately.
It more does not succeedÉ to interact with the others.
Why?
I do not know it.
I do not understand it, that they are its father.
Not moreÉ
Here, Sasuke. Your lunch.
If you want to train to you with the Shuriken, when lathes to house I to you can help.
I do not have to studyÉ
I must train to me.
I go!
Sasuke-chan, you are going to school?
I have as soon as seen Itachi-chan. Grown E' very many.
They say has become one shinobi strongest.
It has been graduated to the Academy to 7 years, with the maximum of the ballotsÉ
É and it has become Chuunin to 10 years, true?
It has learned to use the Sharingan when it had 8 years.
Incredible.
E' the pride of all the Uchiha clan.
I say seriously.
On purposeÉ Sasuke-chan, how many years you have?
I have the same ageÉ of my brother when it has been graduatedÉ unfortunatelyÉ
What is that it does not go?
Hey.
You stop it to say many stupidaggini.
TreasureÉ
SasukeÉ
Tu and Itachi you belong both to the Uchiha clanÉ
One noble family of Konoha.
Have confidence in you.
A day. you will become a large one shinobi like Itachi.
We look at ourselves!
You make of your best!
You see to study hard!
Just.
I have also, like my brother, the blood of the Uchiha.
I will not lose  against my brother.
I have made truly lateÉ
What has been?
It has seemed to have seen someone to me.
All extinguishingÉ
It is not possible that they are already sleeping all.
This isÉ
What happens?
What is happening, eternal damnation?
UncleÉ AuntÉ
FatherÉ MotherÉ
Father? Mother?
You are here?
There is someoneÉ
You moveÉ
You move!
Father! Madre!
Brother!
Brother, Papˆ and Mamma areÉ
Why? In order which reasonÉ
Who has been?
Brother! WhatÉ
What you are making, brother?
Six just stupid one, fratellino.
Mangekyou Sharingan. (Technical of the Sharingan Kaleidoscope)
My legsÉ
Enough!
Brother!
It does not make to see all this me!
Why?
Why just you, brother?
NotÉ
Uncle, AuntÉ
Father, MotherÉ
Stopped, brother!
Those are Papˆ and Mamma.
WhyÉ
É just you.
In order to understandÉ that one of which they are able.
That one of which six able one?
Only for this?
Therefore you have killed all how many, only for this reason?
I find one valid reason.
Eternal damnationÉ
Not to say stronzate!
I have fearÉ
I have fear!
Not to kill to me!
Not to kill to meÉ
Not taskÉ that of it it is worth the pain.
Stupid fratellino.
If you have intention to kill to meÉ he hates to meÉ you curse to meÉ
Above allÉ You survive in this atrocious world.
You run, you run. It grabs hold of you to your life.
We go outside.
These boysÉ are not normalÉ
Mhhh.
Itachi-saint.
It would be unpleasant if it succeeded to escape to usÉ
I could avoid it amputandogli one now leg.
What is saying?
I make?
Last E' much timeÉ
Sasuke.
Uchiha Itachi.
Just like Sasuke, a UchihaÉ
Sharingan.
To moreover it is similar you very manyÉ
Who diamine is?
E' mineÉ smaller brother.
I have felt to say that the entire Uchiha clan had been exterminatedÉ
É from you.
Uchiha Itachi!
We are to the yield of the accounts.
I must kill a man at all costs.
That manÉ
Until thatÉ
É  I will not have killed  itÉ
É not me  rassegner˜É
É I cannot die.
This is the person who tried SasukeÉ
É what it wants to kill!
As you have said to meÉ
I have hated to you and cursedÉ
And in order to succeed to kill to you, I amÉ
É  they areÉ
É survivor!
Sasuke!
Chidori?
Hour I will kill  to you!
You die!
What devil has happened?
It has avoided easy the technique of SasukeÉ
It goes wellÉ
I must make something!
Its Chakra is forming one barrier.
Hour I understand.
This is the Chakra of the Kyubi.
Not to break off.
Sasuke!
Eternal damnation!
Kuchyose not Jutsu! (Technical of Evocation)
Too much slow.
Huh. I do not perceive more the Chakra.
Eternal damnation
Eternal damnation.
Why?
My SamehadaÉ nutre of Chakra! It chews!
Not task that you will use more your techniques after that  I will have made  pieces.
What you prefer you before cutÉ to an arm or one leg?
Why does not exit any neanche a po '?
Useless.
What?
Task that you two.... do not know to me very well.
The great JirayaÉ
É when woman has an appointment with oneÉ
É sottinteso that she succeeds in sedurla quickly.
They are not the type that is made to spool from one beautiful woman.
When you arrive to my age.... the women impazziranno.... for your fascination.
Ga man not renzoku dattaro
kokoro de naite itandaro
jibun de kimeta they are yume dake wa
yuzurenaindaro
wakyaku dake I give
kage not hito dakedo
yume to mimuki au toki oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
mana ka ni izazete
shoujiki ni izazete
imamade nando mo
nantoka aki ramezu ni
imamade na ndomo
tachi agatte kitajanaika
imamade nando mo
bokura
nandomo
shinjite
yume mild
nandomo
imamade nando mo
baka wo mitekita janaika
nando mo
hito kage ni not tattekita janai ka
sou shuya ku dayo
jibun not yume kurai wagamama de izazete
UH!
Careful!
Sasuke!
Naruto, not to intromettere to you.
ButÉ
But SasukeÉ
NarutoÉ
The only thing that you can makeÉ
E' to observe the battle carefully, and not distrarti neanche for a moment.
This is its battle.
It means very for heÉ is all that one for which hour has fought sin'.
Next nose-dive
Stupid fratellino. Hatred and depreciation!