Subtitles By: BakaSan
I can't be the only one who loses here!
Gai-sensei, please acknowledge that...
...this is the time...
...to carry out and to protect my Nindo (way of Ninja)!
Oh, Rock Lee! This is how a man lives!!
His body color turns...
Red!
What is he?!
He's opened the third gate, Sei-Mon.
He'll start!
No, not yet!
What?
Furthermore... forth gate Sho-Mon, open!
What a guy! His hard work had nothing to do with that.
That boy... must be a genius after all.
Fast!
Where are they?
Above!
But I can't see Lee.
Where?
The sand can't even catch up with his speed at all.
He's still wearing that sand armor.
Fine then... how about this?!
What?!  The sand armor is...
...starting to come off.
You don't go down so easy?
If that's the case...!
His muscle just snapped.
Is that really Lee? Since when he become so...
This is the end!
Fifth gate,To-Mon... Open!
I can't defend myself anymore.
Is his movement humanly possible?!
Neji... This special technique I was saving to use on
you. But I'll make an exception... and let you see it!
The sand shield can't catch up with him.
The sand armor has mostly come off.  This isn't good.
Incredible!
Ura Renge (Reverse Lotus)... That is the ultra
high-speed Taijutsu that nobody can touch.
The answer to defeat Neji is this high-speed
combination. It's impossible for the sand to catch up.
This technique will be the last.
Ura Renge!
It's too fast to tell what's going on....
It can't be...!
The gourd turned into sand?!
It is truly over this time!
What is that?
He protected himself with his gourd made of sand?
That technique was...!
Sabaku-Kyu!
No way! He can still attack after receiving Ura Renge?!
I can't...lose at this stage...
I...my Nindo...
This isn't good!
Die!
Why....
Why did you save him?
This boy is...
I'm alright because I'm strong.
Gai-sensei... Just smile and watch during the Chunin exam.
I want to prove that I can be a respectable
Ninja, even if I can use neither Ninjutsu nor Genjutsu!!
That is everything to me!
This boy is...
my precious, beloved subordinate!
His beloved subordinate?
Those are words that Gaara can never comprehend.
I'm done.
He's done...?
When Gai stepped in, Lee lost the match.
The winner, Gaa..
Impossible!
After opening five gates he can't be standing
with his arms and legs crushed!
Lee, it's alright. It's over. Your
body isn't strong enough to standup now.
Lee, you...You are...
...still trying to prove your
Nindo... even after you've lost consciousness.
I see, he's not consciousness anymore.
You are already...
...a respectable Ninja.
The winner, Gaara.
What can you do for him by going down there?
It'll be just painful for him to hear your cheer.
There's no way to defeat Gaara.
He was forced to fight a tougher
match than I expected it would be.
I can't believe Geji-Mayu
(thick-eyebrows) lost to a guy like this.
Medical team, hurry up.
Geji-Mayu!
You're the Jounin who's in charge of this boy, right?
Y..Yes.
Please come over here.
Be gentle.
Don't swing him.
He is breathing, though barely...
...but he's got crushed bones and
snapped muscles throughout his body.
It will take a very long time for him to recover.
It would be fine, if that was all...
The damage to his left arm and leg
that was attacked is severe... very severe.
I don't want to tell you this, but...
He can no longer live as a Ninja with that body.
That...that can't be true!
I'll fight with Geji-Mayu!
It's not you with whom I want to fight. It's Uchiha.
You!
I can understand your feelings...
But a battle must be fought in a real match.
A looser will beat an elite with his hard
work. It's going to be fun in the real final exams.
It may be I who will fight against him.
Lee, I didn't want to think that you were going to lose.
I wanted to help you achieve your Nindo.
Yey! Finally I mastered it! Yahoo! Alright!
Only Lee could master this technique.
Alright! You guys are Genin from
today. I want to hear your goals.
Me! Me!
I want to prove that I can be a respectable
Ninja, even if I can use neither Ninjutsu nor Genjutsu!!
That's everything to me!
Please forgive me, I couldn't stop you.
It can't be true! It must be a lie!
What will Geji-Mayu do if he's told such a thing?!
He said a looser will beat an elite with his hard work!
Can't you do something?
Calm down, Naruto!
But, Kakashi-sensei! He kept saying that he really
wants to fight against Sasuke and Neji!
Or, that caused this tragedy.
To achieve his dream, that boy tried to win this match
desperately, even using a forbidden technique.
This is the result of that.
That boy sacrificed himself to an unspoken promise
with Sasuke, Neji-kun, and you, Naruto.
He risked his life to reach the
stage where he can fight against you guys.
Don't forget that.
I wonder if Lee-san's gonna be alright.
Lee, you never realized it even at the end.
Heaven forbids a guy to go to the next level if the
only way for him to win is to risk his own life.
It's over without any trouble.
Welcome back, Gaara.
Gai! I spoke to you arrogantly
earlier... ...but if I was in your shoes...
I probably couldn't stop the fight either.
Gai, the next match can't be started
if we're here. Let's go back up.
Yeah...
Well... The final tenth match. Both of you, come forward.
It's finally my turn.
I'm gonna eat Yakiniku (Korean BBQ) after I win!
I really need to stay in for the final
matches to fight against Sasuke-kun. Otherwise...
...I can't meet your expectation, Orochimaru-sama.
I can guess the reason why....
...you gave a cursed seal to Sasuke-kun, instead
of killing him, when you meet him before us.
We were just tools to find out Sasuke-kun's
ability during the exam.
What you want is not Sasuke-kun's life, but Sasuke himself.
"Dosu Kinuta vs. Akimichi Choji" but he's underestimated me.
Well, let the tenth match... Begin!
Sakura-chan! Do you know
where Kakashi-sensei is?
I'll ask him to train me until the final real exams.
I think Kakashi-sensei
is where Sasuke-kun is.
What's wrong, Sakura-chan. Aren't you a bit down?
No, not really. But I feel uneasy.
Next episode. A shadow moving in the
darkness. Crisis approaching Sasuke!
For some reason, I feel anxious.