http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
Haruno Sakura VS Yamanka Ino
It arrives you to this pointÉ
É I do not have neanche to fight
with you for Sasuke-kun!
Sakura! You know with who you are speaking?
Sakura, child piagnona!
It seemsÉ Seems
Task that Sakura-chan has exaggerated.
The look of Ino puts fear.
Not creedÉ
Sakura is not type to boast itself of its force
and to hurt someone without reason.
It does not want that Ino is indulgente.
WellÉ
É We use fullyÉ
É our force and we fightÉ
É loyal!
The best battle
it is ok, eternal damnation!!
E' only the Bunshin not Jutsu.
We are not to the final examination of the academy!
Creeds to strike to me with techniques
cos “  elementary?
If I make attention I can easy
to characterize that true one.
I accumulate of blow the Chakra to the feetÉ
É and I hit the pavement!
That speed!
You of it you will repent if it continues
to consider me Sakura the piagnona.
You fight seriously, Ino!
They are content to feel to you to say it.
As you want,  I will fight  seriously.
Cos “  is made, Sakura-chan!
Good!
Truly good!
Better E' of the other esordienti
in the movements that demand the Chakra.
Sakura is a guerriero suit.
Better also than me?
Eh, s “!
In making circular the chakra in all
the body and to use it at the opportune momentÉ
É he is advanced even to Sasuke.
Sakura always has been the best one
in the control of the Chakra.
Sakura-saint wonderful movement!
But also your adversary is strong.
E' a battle at par.
It will be a long combat!
Quand' is that he has become cos “  strong?
I can winÉ I canÉ!
Why youÉ
If they continue cos “  never not finiranno.
It is made long.
They will be already passes 10 minuteren to you.
You will not be never strongly how much me!
A person who loses cos “  much time
in the cure of hats it will not be never my par.
For this you they are advanced!
You are making a large one
error in underrating me!
Stupid, takes the insults too much seriously.
Goodness knows that he arranges now.
He does not appeal to to me when Ino makes cos “.
Poor fool.
Cabbage, completely has gone.
IT WATCHES!!
It pecks this to you!
Fa..Fa fear.>.
Hour  I will conclude  the encounter.
I will make  to declare  you endured the sconfittˆ.
What, she is forÉ
It isÉ
Those I sealÉ!
As I thought wants to use
the Shintenshin not Jutsu.
Accidents, than foolish!
I understand that you are in
difficulty but is useless.
Beh, we will see it.
Ninpo: Shintenshin not JutsuÉ
Who uses it, rilascia the mental energyÉ
É taking the control of the adversaryÉ
É he is of the mind that of the bodyÉ
É for some minuteren.
But this technique has a point weak person:
The rilasciata mental energyÉ
É one moves slowly
and only online straight.
MoreoverÉ
É in the case in which the rilasciata energy
it does not have to hit the adversaryÉ
É it will return behind only after some minuteren.
Therefore during that periodÉ
É your body will be found in condition
of absolute vulnerability.
The Shintenshin Jutsu is not adapted
in the espionage and not to the combat.
Ino, to use that tacnica
it is equivalent to the suicide.
If continuous Sakura to move
it will not run dangers.
If schiverˆ the Jutsu will be able
to make those that it wants of Ino.
In that Hayate case
it will have to suspend the encounter.
And then!
We will only know after that  I will have tried  to us!
Sai that for you it will be the end if mistakes?
In combatÉ
É it is a Jutsu to use after to have immobilized
the adversary with my Kagemane not Jutsu.
But to use it now is absurd.
It will not hit it.
Stupid, not to make it!
Ninpo:Shintenshin not Jutsu!
In which of the two it is?
SinÉ
É Ino.
Now not there is nothing that can make.
It has made large.
Then I have won.
WhatÉ!
Six fall in my trap, Sakura.
To the fine ones I have taken to you.
You have.>.?
Exactly.
Those seal were only one feint.
They served to push to you in this trap.
You do not succeed to move to you, true?
E' one special rope, created making to slide
my Chakra through hats.
The encounter will end as soon as  I will be  within
of you and  I will say  "I surrender ".
This time  I will not mistake!
I understand.
That stupid pretended itself svenuta.
You run, Sakura-chan!
I cannot move!
HourÉ Shintenshin not Jutsu!
SinÉ
It has lacked.
Not.
Sakura-saint.
Sakura-chan.
É Sakura.
What has happened to Ino?
AndÉ Also Sakura-chan is strange!
It is  my occasion.
You strike It, Sakura-chan!
It cannot.
The Shintenshin Jutsu is not conceived
for these cases, but it has worked.
Shintenshin?
It means that Sakura-saint it is.>.?
S “,  Ino has been impossessata of the mind of Sakura.
Within Sakura in this moment there is Ino.
Probably hour InoÉ
Ended E'.
Hello Hello, Sakura.
I, Haruno sakura, meÉ
É arrenÉ
Nooo!!!!
PffÉ noisy E' cos  “.
You six engaged a lot in order to arrive end here!
It will be a shame if you will lose against
that only obsessed matta from Sasuke!
Useless E' that you say "me ".
WhatÉ
This coldÉ
Naruto makes always this casino.
Sakura!
E' a idiocyÉ
What is?
You surrender?
Not me arrendero' never!
Eternal damnation!
But who isÉ
WhatÉ
SakuraÉ
It is not possible.
The technique has failed?
Ino! If you do not exit endured from my body,
you will taste hell!
What happens to Ino?
NotÉ!
I will not resist  to along in this state!
Issolution!
Incredible!
Succeeded E' to contrast the technique of Ino!
It has wasted too many energies
before using the technique.
Cos “  has found not possession
Sufficient Chakra.
You have two personality?
Com' is possible?
I have an equal force to my beauty.
The girls must be
strong in order to survive.
She does not escape herself easy cos  “
to that technique.
True E' that Ino had Chakra littleÉ
É but the combative spirit of SakuraÉ
É in the comparisons of Ino avails againÉ
É it has had a fundamental role.
This last one has been risvegliato
from the words of NarutoÉ
É driving away Ino.
It is not one surprised that SakuraÉ
É like NarutoÉ
É sopporta to lose.
ButÉ
É both short of Chakra are.
This will beÉ
É the last attack.
Both are disabled to continue.
For the double KO, nobody it exceeds
4¡ the eliminatorio encounter.
To the next one then.
Boys.
Ehi Ino!
Sakura-saint!
Sakura-chan!
Goes all good?
They do not have need not even of medical cures.
They will be waked up between a po '.
However they are been strange.
I knew that Naruto and Sasuke
they were becomes to you more fortsÉ
É but from Sakura not me
never I would be waited for.
It has not been easy, but they are content
to have them candidates to this examinationÉ
É of selection of the Chunin.
Tenten
VS
Temari
I feel to explode from when
I have seen that encounter.
Also it comes from the Country of the Sand.
You make of your better Tenten!
It will be an interesting combat.
Finally six alarm clock, Sakura.
Tenten! USA all your force!
Vai! Not there is limit in your life!
Our crash is ended.
I haveÉ I have lost?
Me vien it wants to cryÉ
É to think that I have pareggiato
against like you.
You hold!
Six becomeÉ
É a beautifulst flower.
ButÉ
The next time that we will fight
from there you will not exit with one faint.
Moreover know that I do not have intention
to leave Sasuke-kun you.
The same one is worth for me!
Fifth encounter.
Tenten.
Temari.
A step ahead.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII