http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
It seems a lot bored.
Where are ended the blond man and arrogating?
The trees are training themselves in climbing.
And you do not have to make it?
Not, inasmuch as they are the best one…
… master Kakashi has said to me of proteggervi.
Indeed?
Like…!
Tazuna, you have a moment?
What happens, Giichi?
Beh…
I have thought a lot to us and…
… I would want to stop to work to the bridge.
Cos ì… cos ì  to the unexpected one!
Not also you…!
Tazuna, we know ourselves from a lot.
I would want to work, for ò  if we continue,
you know well of what is able Gatoo!
Nothing will have sense if they kill to us.
Why we do not interrupt the construction of the bridge?
I cannot make it.
This is our bridge.
This is the bridge that we are constructing entirety…
… confidando in the fact that would carry resources…
… to our poor country.
But that sense has if moriremo!
And already noon.
In order today we have worked enough.
Tazuna!
Giichi, from tomorrow not disturbing to you to come.
The country where a hero existed.
Maledizione!
That it is happening!!!
Not to make me ò  to exceed!
Where we go?
I must buy some ingredients for the supper.
- I accept whichever job -
Ladro!
Che cos' has this country?
We are arrives to you.
Welcomes.
Not there is nearly null.
Pervertito!!!
… I was not…
It has been strange to me what
it has happened to you little ago.
Where it will go to end this city?
(Still!)
EHY…!
… you…
?
They give the something to me?
Prendi.
Thanks!
E' cos ì  from when Gatoo has arrived.
All the adults have lost the hope.
For this…
… we have need of that bridge.
It will be a hope symbol…
… that it will serve to giving it it wants to fight…
… to people of this country
that submitted hour alive.
If only…
If we only finished the bridge…!
The city would return as it was a time…
… and cos ì  its inhabitants.
Sasuke-kun…
Naruto…
Cursed! Cursed!
Sasuke knows them more and more up!
Maledizione, a po' to the time is resuming to me.
Not, not!
If task to Sasuke I lose only the concentration.
Hey, hey…
Qual' is your secret?
Eh?
But not to say it to Sasuke, we go!
Ok?
It listens, "chakra" uses the spiritual energy…
… perci ò  you do not have to be
of nervous of impaziente.
Rilassati, concentrates your energy…
… and it focuses all the Chakra in your feet.
To focus! To focus!
Well, it is working!
Ok! Hour I can make it us!
Hey, Naruto!
Which devil you want!?
Not to break off when I concentrate myself!!!
I wanted…
I wanted to ask to you…
Which thing?
Strange that attacks button with me.
Before… before you have asked council Sakura, not?
What has said to you?
AH?
You I do not say.
AAAH, how nice!
E' for a long time…
… that we did not make one beautiful tavolata!
- Still!
If you must vomitare, you stop to eat!
Not! I must eat!
To cost to strain to me I must eat.
I must become stronger the first possible one.
(Not there is of need to arrive a lot.)
Uhm…
Why you hold one photo torn to the wall?
Inari-kun observed it continuously while we ate.
It seems that the ace of one person
it has been removed intentionally.
E' my husband.
E' the man who once it came
considered the hero of this city.
Inari, where you go?
Papà! I had said not to speak to you about he
to the presence of Inari!
That it is taken to Inari-kun?
Told to us cos' has not happened?
That man was the adoptive father of Inari.
But they were equally many joining,
just like father and son.
In that Inari period he was much happy one and sorridente.
For ò…
Inari changes ò…
… from the day of the incident of its father.
From that day, because of that tragedy…
… the word "courage" stopped to exist…
… for people of this island and Inari.
Which incident?
What succeeded to Inari-kun?
Before explaining that episode to you....
… I must tell you of the man who was…
… called Hero from the inhabitants of the country.
A hero?
He was to incirca the three years ago…
… when Inari knew this man.
Little!
Not!
Its name is * Shooting Star.
* Falling star
And from today the dog is mine!
It is not Shooting Star!
E' mine Little!
Ridammelo!
Little are my friend and not you giving ò  never!
Taci!
Little!!!
This why me you do not have intentional to give.
This stupid dog does not interest me more.
It leaves you to go it!
Cos' you have made!?
You want to kill Little!?
E' your precious dog, not?
Sbrigati and goes it to save.
What happens to you?
T' it does not import if Little die?
(Sure that m' it imports.)
(E' my only friend.)
(For ò…)
It watches! A not sà dog that neanche to swim!
(For ò!)
(Me dispiace Little.)
(But so' not to swim.)
Hey! If it is your dog you would have to be dived!
You have exaggerated Akane-kun.
If it did not know to swim?
You help me!
We go ourselves some!
For ò…
Then you want to save Inari?
(I do not want to die.)
(Someone me aids!)
P… Little!
Little!!!
It is not a lot important, for ò…
… in that moment Little impar ò  to swim.
Pochiii!!!
Hey! It is scappando!
We take it!
I do not succeed… in resp..irare…
I feel that…
Six waked up to you, boy?
I have given to those children one beautiful lesson.
You take! It eats!
An angel?
It has saved me, getlteman!
Before we eat…
… then of it we will speak.
And cos ì  has betrayed you also your dog!?
In my country, instead the dogs
many faithfuls are animals.
For ò  you you had to wait for, seen
that you have betrayed its confidence for first!
Cos ì  I was scared that
I did not succeed to move to me.
I wanted to save it, for ò…
… of it I did not have the courage.
Obviously.
Normal E' to your age to have fear.
For ò  it remembers to you…
… small…
What?
… that a man must living without regretted.
You must protect us ò  that it considers important…
… with both the arms.
It does not import how much hard one or sad it is…
… even if you had to die.
Its name was Kaiza…
… a fisherman who arriv ò
here chasing a dream.
After this, Kaiza and Inari remained joined very.
Perhaps because the true father of Inari
mor ì  before being able to know it…
It and Kaiza were inseparable,
truly like father and son.
To not he wanted a lot us because Kaiza became
a member of our family.
Moreover this city had need of he.
Kaiza-saint it is a disaster!
This rain has made to yield the dam!
The D Area stà for being overflowed!
What!
Papà!
Inari! You take to me one rope!
!
That disaster!
We must tie one rope to the dam
and to pull in order to close it!
Absurdity!
How we can tie one rope!?
Anyone morirebbe with that one current!
But at this rate the D Area will come destroyed!
What we make!
Making ò  I!
Not to make it!
This is too much, also for you!
Papà!
Not to worry to you…
Your papà is invincible.
Your papà loves the city where six been born.
You must protect us ò  that it considers important…
… with both the arms…
… also to cost of living!
Papà ce you can make it!!!
There is successful!
The rope has legacy!
Courage, we pull strong!
Force!
From then Kaiza hero was called
from all people of the city…
… and Inari was much proud one of its father.
Little after Gatoo arriv ò  in city.
And one night…
… I have felt that you want protect the city
with your arms, not?
It makes you to reflect it!
Force!
Listened!
This man was directing terroristic activities
against the Gatoo corporation!
Upsetting the order of this country!
Like punishment, he will be executed!
I hope that one what of the sort will not happen never more.
Papà!
Not, Inari!
Uccidetelo.
Papà…
PAPAAA'!!!
You said that you would have protect to me…
… and also people of this country.
With yours…
… arms!
You have mentito to me, papà!
From that day, Inari changes ò.
Like he also Tsunami, and all the population.
A hero!?
Stupid. The heroes do not exist!
What you make Naruto?
Scordati to continue the training.
In order today you have consumed too much Chakra.
If it exaggerates, collasserai.
Glielo dimostrer ò.
?
Which thing?
The dimostrer ò…
… that in this world…
… the heroes exist!
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
Uh? Who is this girl?
Me st ò  training in this moment!
We do not know when Zabuza will attack to us.
I understand that you interests
for that they seem stronger.
For this I want to become…
More and more strongly!
Dimostrer ò  to Inari that exists the heroes in this world!
In the next episode:
The decisive battle on the bridge!
The return of Zabuza.
To make ò  great things this time!!