sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni
jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
mayoinagarademo II
arukidashite
mou ikkai
NaruTeaM
It introduces
http://naruteamplus.altervista.org /
dareka not kitai ni zutto kotae
homerarerunoga suki dwarf desuka?
naritai jibun wo surikaetemo
egao wa itsudemo suteki desuka?
hajimaridake yume mild okiru
they are saki nara itsuka
jibun not ude de
souda daiji na mono wa itsumo
katachi not nai mono dake
you ni iretemo nakushitemo
kizukanumama
sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni
jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
mayoinagarademo II
arukidashite
mou ikkai
The vincitrice is… Temari.
They are tired.
That waste!
Because!
It was its occasion in order to become Chuunin!
It is made cos ì.
Indeed… I do not understand if it has been serious or less....
Neanch' I succeed to understand it…
But its intelligence and its strategy
they have exceeded the level of Genin.
If true mission with squares from four had been one…
It would have won once stopped the movements of Temari.
Creed that has gained the challenge, but lost the encounter.
E' a sin that cos ì  is svogliato…
However, it has not lost the head during the fight and…
it has not fallen in the panic.
This why it succeeds to maintain the calm
also in the more difficult situations…
why it knows to bottom its ability.
For a Chuunin these psychological bases
they are fundamental…
Shikamaru possesses all the qualities for being a leader.
If we had to judge like squad leader…
E' much more important protect just the group…
that to carry a.termine the mission.
Just.
The excuse "I have carried out the mission, but I have lost
all the my group "does not go well.
A.termine must know to estimate the risks of carrying
the mission and to think first of all to survive…
Otherwise one is not in a position to becoming Chuunin.
Under this point of view, Hyuuga and Naruto have failed.
Even if as Genin is Okay.
Task that Shikamaru has rinunciato to us too much soon.
What of tasks?
Be '…
they said that it has more possibility than Naruto.
Because it has been withdrawn!
That Stupid!
Truly they are incazzato!
I go to dargli one lesson!
Perhaps the person who will become Chuunin will be…
Stupid You!
Taci, super idiot.
Because six withdrawn to you!
We forget ourselves about this, okay?
But what you say!!
You could have won!
Taci. We go to enjoy the next encounter to us.
… E' Ridicule!
The Next encounter…
Sasuke!
Crash! The time of the dance of the leaf
and of sliding of the sand!
The next encounter is that one of the Uchiha finally!
Yeah, but who is this Gaara?
Of they are not sure…
But it will not be nothing in comparison to a Uchiha.
You have felt? The boy of the Uchiha will come disqualified!
You say seriously?
Yeah.
I have felt that it is remained hardly
hurt in training before the torneo.
Oh cabbage!
I have taken a day free in order to see this encounter!
It will be better than you come!
This encounter will come won from the Uchiha.
This is  that  that creeds.
I task that the boy of the sand will gain.
Of they are sure.
Not, in the world of the combats…
what  cannot be always foretold… will happen.
Hokage-sama, R-with regard to Uchiha Sasuke…
Still it has not arrived.
I have not just chosen…
I cannot make to attend beyond the spectators.
…  Others 10 minuteren.
We attend others 10 minuteren.
But this is…
The spectators have attended to along this encounter.
He would be cruel to cancel it.
We have already waited for a lot,
what will be never others 10 minuteren?
Hokage-sama…
Uchiha, what is that it does not go!
When inzierà the encounter? Force!
Kazekage, you have reason.
We will attend others 10 minuteren. It goes well?
It goes to say it to Genma.
Ok
The Uchiha must already have been disqualified.
I understand.
Others 10 minuteren, eh?
Sasuke-kun…
Hey, that one is…
You are…
Cabbage, What is making that idiot!
Still it has not arrived!
Sasuke-kun…
Perfavore.
Welcomes both.
Soon, You run within.
S ì!
Okay, we go, Lee!
Many encounter of the first one round are already finish to you.
It remains only the encounter of Uchiha Sasuke against Gaara.
Com' has gone the encounter between Naruto-kun and Neji?
E' be a lot interesting.
Hyuuga has lost.
Naruto-kun… has struck Neji?
Then it is cos ì.
Ce you have made it…
Naruto-kun.
Dev' to have been one exciting news for he.
When Uchiha comes outside!
Fairies to exit Uchiha!
Uchiha!
Hey, lacks little to the disqualification.
It is indeed in order to arrive?
It will arrive.
Of they are sure.
Eternal damnation, what devil is making Sasuke!
That it will be making the Uchiha!
It seems that the voices of a its accident were true.
If it loses for disqualification,   I will have gained the bet.
Others 30 second ones…
Sasuke-kun… you come I pray to you…
Sasuke… you move to arrive!
You will be in the troubles if it does not arrive!
The time is expired. Creed is the end.
The last encounter…
The time is expired, therefore…
You have seen? Arrived E'.
I make excuses myself for the delay.
Your name?
Uchiha Sasuke.
Sasuke-kun!
Ce has made it.
Lee-saint!
Diamine… It has caused a bag to us
of problems and it does not seem upsotten.
Always six in delay.
I had thought that you would not have come
why you had fear to fight against of me.
And who was what she said that would have come?
You have gained your first encounter?
Sure!
Cos ì  not to be excited, idiot.
Well, um…
Hard E' to say it after that we are it enters to you
in the arena with our super performance…
But Sasuke… has been disqualified?
It must have taken your ugly habit to arrive in delay.
Then it has been…
E' Ok.
The encounter of Sasuke has been postponed…
And it is just joint in time, therefore it has not been disqualified.
They are content to know it.
E' better than you do not lose against that boy!
Sure.
Anch' I want to fight against of you.
Sasuke!
I know.
Sasuke-kun!
Also after all those that it has made,
it is always crazy for Sasuke…
Poor Shikamaru.
Now they are not considered at all.
Task just not to be able to us to make null…
I want to see anch' this I meet.
Sakura, your group is fichissimo.
How never?
Why, per.primo.cosa, that Naruto has struck Hyuuga Neji.
And Sasuke-kun is one of the Uchiha clan.
And it seems that all have come here in order to see the encounter of Sasuke-kun.
Sasuke-kun is in order to strike itself with Gaara of the Sand
against which I have not been able to make null…
And Naruto-kun has defeated Neji, R-he who wanted to defeat…
Because…
Why they are cos ì…
…  mortified?
Lee…
He is in order to begin.
Gaara, you stop it to laugh and you come down in field.
Naruto, we go on.
Okay.
We use the scales in order to go up.
What?
Six angry anchor why I have thrown to you of under?
It is put badly…
It was from that I did not see Gaara cos ì.
Hey! Gaara!
You memories the mission…
Not to speak to Gaara now…
It would kill to you.
Just.
Hey, We go.
Hey, Sbrigati.
Us null gain not to go of race.
What is…
Tornei of cos ì  low level like the examination of Chuunin…
…  they are optimal for the bets.
Some Daimyo has come just with this attempt.
Therefore… You can lose the encounter?
Di' something, child.
Hai cos ì  fear to say something?
Aid…!
Stopped! Stopped!
If those two had not been '…
Probably it would have killed we.
I have not never seen to kill in that way without some hesitation.
Sasuke will have large problems with he.
Sasuke…
Finally it is begun…
daredatte wa surunda
hazukashii janai
kono muda ni shinaide
waratte to
sou ukana suikomi
hiroki ni kao wo age tobikomi
toki ame ga futtara hitoyasumi
ja u kaze fuku mama ni
takusan mattoteru koukai
kono muda ni shicha shounai
mune kunshou kizami koukai
shougai show
daredatte wa surunda
hazukashii janai
kono muda ni shinaide
waratte to
kanashimi kaze
tsuyoku
The next week, Naruto Mercoled ì  14  January…
There will be a special one of an hour that it will begin to the 7PM.
The man who  recalled  one storm!!
The Taijutsu di Sasuke Sopracciglione Style!
I was not for nothing in delay!
Definitive Movement - Chidori!!
We will show you these two episodes in an only time!
The secret movement of Sasuke will succeed in
to defeat the absolute defense of Gaara?
Naruto, an entire hour …
The special one on the Fury of Sasuke!
You lose it, and morirai.