Subbed by Kyubi
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
Iruka-sensei Good bye
Good bye.
Tried memorizzare the transformation technique that I have taught to you today.
And not forgotten to perceive your families of the ceremony of investitura of the Fifth Hokage.
It goes well
Konohamaru!
Which thing is, Iruka-sensei?
Eheh nothing.... Tomorrow.
S ì!  Good bye, Iruka-sensei.
Me it seems that that one of a time is returned.
Lee!
Vai to the rieducazione center?
S ì.
I hope that it res-establish to you in a hurry.
Thanks thousands.
To recover all the cells in once…
If this were for a single part, could find one solution,
but I cannot make it for all in once single…
In order to make it short, Konoha is in difficulty.
We must work hard in order to replace it in sixth.
Lee-saint, you would have to go also to find Tsunade-sama. He will cure you of sure!
He forgets the vocation about Ninja, you would have to try an other road.>.
Episode #100
The ties consecrate between a Master and its pupil to you
When a man loses its way of Ninja
Bunshin not Jutsu
Henge not Jutsu
Boy.
The concentration is a lot important for the training.
More you will train yourself, more you will become a great Ninja.
But who you are? You are cos ì  strange…
Child! You say cos ì  because six young person!
Later!
It was before the time that I saw Gai-sensei.
And…
Well, from this moment in then, you are of the Genin!
I would want to know your dreams, your plans.
I do not want to speak of.
I! I!
Even if I cannot use the Ninjutsu neither the Genjutsu,
I want to try that I can become a great Ninja!
E' which counts more for me!
That beautiful dream.
Tu! Which thing makes you to laugh!?
Not joke! Only using the Taijutsu,  I will try  that I can become a great Ninja!
Tu.... If you do not know to use neither the Ninjutsu neither the Genjutsu, you cannot become a Ninja.
The six only boy is not graduated to the academy having only used the Taijutsu?
Extraordinary what is not one.
It is  only an exception.
It is not necessarily true, if you have one great will.
If you will always try to train to you with yours avails again, you will become sure of large the Ninja.
But it must work hardly.
One great will?
All it is begun cos ì.
That  that has said to me has been  that  that it has made.
Six in delay! 17 minuteren and 32 second ones for the precision!
I do not have wants to fight today.
We have 48 victories everyone.
Who will gain this time will have won all.
Even if you had answered not, would not be changed nothing.
Stavolta is my turn in order to decide the rules of the combat, just?
A combat of Taijutsu, one run of 100 meters, a combat of sumo, or a challenge to who eats more?
Uh…
If you put it cos ì…
Then, what?
Janken.
[ Paper, Scissors, Pebble ]
Janken!? That you say…
They do not say that the fortune sorride to the audacious ones?
And for more it will try your glares. Task that is one good challenge.
Mmm but…
What? It has chosen this game because the others would have been too much difficult?
It would be said of .
I accept!  I will not lose.
If I lose,  I will go around  500 of Konoha walking on the hands!
Here an other stupid idea…
I promise!
You put it in yours objects to you.
Thoughts that can make it truly!? E' cos ì  ridicule. She seems a child…
Impossible! E' too much even for Gai-sensei!
It is not cos ì  impossible for an idiot!
Janken!
You were here then.>.
Gai-sensei…
Why you are here?
I know to you better than same you.
Yesterday six not gone to the rieducazione center… and not even today!
When they have become Genin, I have revealed you my dreams.
In this place.
Later on, Neji taken game of me.
But I was serious.
Even if I cannot use a Ninjutsu neither the Genjutsu,
I want to try that it can become a great Ninja!
E' the more important thing for me!
Then you have said to me.>.
"If trained with yours avails again itself you will become a great Ninja."
"But for this it must work hardly "
I was cos ì  content.
Henge!
When I was to the academy.>.
my companions and my sensei
they did not have confidence in me
They are felt to me refused.
For someone like me that he does not know to make nothing, it was obvious that…
there was… to work hard.
Only an upset worker  can  stick a genius. I have always guarded this phrase in head.
Sensei, you had said to me that I could become a genius also training to me with engagement.
That same day you had said to me that I had to believe in me in order to make it us.
There is a probability of 50% that the operation goes to good aim
But…
This time, even if I make of my best…
Even if creed in me.... will not change nothing!
Gai-sensei, you say something ve of it I pray!
You say to me,  I will become  like you, Gai-sensei?
Why they are the solo to suffer a lot!?
I will try  to us, even if I must die. I want protect my dreams!
Because it is my Ninja creed.
Which thing I must make!?
Hachi not Tonko, in order to exceed the limits of the body.  It is  a Kinjutsu?
You say something!
They are ready to run this risk. I want to learn this Kinjutsu!
I will make  all in order to lead my dream a.termine!
E'  that  that it more counts for me…
Only using the Taijutsu, you have covered one long road in order to become a great Ninja.
It was your objective and us six successful one alone.
It must be a indescrivibile pain to see that after all these efforts the destiny has tried to remove your dreams to you.
Any are its dreams, would make better to forget the vocation than Ninja.
Lee.
If you want to give a term to this suffering, you must face one challenge!
It is worth to say to have to forget my dreams?
If you abandon your dreams, of it you will suffer only more.
If it is not possible to cover the way of the Ninja, it does not have more sense.... seems stupid but it is cos ì.
Valid E' for you, but it is also for me.
Chip ax the operation, Lee!
How it goes? I speak about your study on regeneration.
The problem is the Chakra.
To arrange it with the cells, the skin, the organs, muscles. This truly is complicated.
To recover all at once is only much difficult one.
To recover in a blow?
You take game of me?
Not!
Creed in you.
I do not know because, but me memory of the time where you and Kakashi-sensei,
You have defied yourselves to Janken.
That day you said that the fortune was with you.
The operation…
That it survives or not.... To win or to lose…
Completely various E' from the Janken!
Memories what succeeded to you after, Lee?
500  turns, like promised.
Merda!
If I lose  I will go around  500 of Konoha walking on the hands!
I promise!
Thoughts that can make it truly!? E' cos ì  ridicule. She seems a child…
It is not nothing…
Which thing is, Lee?
Why the fairies? Kakashi-sensei if of frega.And nobody is watching.
If I have promised one what, even if I can seem to you infantile,
I maintain to cost of my life!
I promise!
Which thing?
Why before making any thing invented always these stupid rules?
It is  one beautiful question, Lee. a Six good observer.
Well. But not to say it to nobody.  It is  a secret.
Which thing?
It is  a type of training that leads the Victoria.
Car-objective is called!
Car-objective?
It listens…
When chip ax a challenge, must fix a objective in order to succeed to exceed it
As an example, behind the phrase "If I lose to the Janken,  I will go around  500", the objective is to increase my power
An able power to stick Kakashi making simply 500 turns.
Clearly.
Consequently, fixing my objective to
500  turns, I can be struck seriously to the Janken.
It is  the first advantage.
Then, if I lose, I go around 500,
therefore I train myself with assiduousness.
The combination of these two things gives "the extreme preparation to two levels "
I have understood!
Well, I continue.
I  will make also!
My objective will be…
Ehi. Ehi, Lee! Be reasonable, Lee.
If I cannot be maintained to your level…
Then  I will work  still harder!
If I take example from you and hard job, I could become a great Ninja.
Well. I go to add qualche.cosa to mine objects to you to catch up…
If you do not succeed to resist until the end with me,
I will dedicate  my life to your training.
If I dedicate my life to your training, you will be able to become a great Ninja!
You I promise.
It was happened cos ì.
That one was when you had taught the system to me of the cars objects to you…
You have always worked with engagement. The operation will succeed.
And a better future will carry you!
If per.disgrazia the operation will fail…
I  morirò  with you.
From when I know to you my objective has been
to make so that you become a great Ninja.
You I promise.
If we cannot more follow our way of Ninja.... patience.
It is worth for all and two.
Gai-sensei!
Well, we go, Lee!
S ì.
Tsunade-sama.
Beginning from today,  I will be  the carrying column of this village!
I am the Fifth Hokage!
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
Merda, dov' is!
Not to worry you. We must make the mission.
We will succeed.
Although it arrives.
We will remove its mask!
Next episode
I want to see it, I want to know it, I want to discover it!
The true ace of Kakashi