http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Hush, branco of stupiden!
They are the examiner of first part of the examination
of selection for Chunin
Morino Ibiki.
You three of the villagio of the Sound!
You do not believe of being able to you to involve
as it seems to you before the examination.
You want to be bocciati endured?
You excuse to us. Inasmuch as it is ours
first examination we are a po' excites to you.
I pick the occasion in order to specify
that combats are not allowed without
previo the consent of the examiner.
Even if the duel comes come to an agreement
it is not granted to kill the adversary.
The feccia that it does not follow mine
rules will come endured bocciato.
They are explained to me!?
This examination seems simple.
Hour we will begin with the first one
examination of selection for Chunin.
Delivered your question of registration,
then you take your number of place
and you are based the numeration second!
Dopodich we will deliver to you
the sheets with the questions.
Sheet
Questions
A written examination!
Already surrendered?
The most difficult first examination.
Uffa, is far away from all those that I know.
What I can make
Deprived of hope E'! Deprived of hope E'!
For Naruto it is worse the examination
that it could capitare to it.
Naruto-kun
Ah, you six Hinata!
But when
In mouth to the lupo.
Me of I was not shrewed
until that it has not spoken.
For this first examination there are
of the important rules a lot.
Not accetter   questions,
for which lend attention.
Rules?
And in more not chip ax questions!
Rule number one:
Everyone of you will leave with
a score of ten points.
This is a deductive test.
If mistaken a question
a point will be removed you.
If mistaken three questions
the score will come down to seven.
If mistake ten questions I take zero points.
Rule number two:
The promoted ones or bocciati will come decided in function
of the final score of every square.
Waited for a moment!
How it would be the score total of square?
Hush!!
Reason is one for all.
Been zitti and listened.
One reason for all?
If you have understood, we continue with the rules.
If an examining one will be strange to copy or to make to you
something of similar during the test
you will lose two points for
ciascuna of these actions.
In little words, there will be who
it will have to abandon knows it it
until that its test
it will not come characterized.
I have understood!
It has created other situation in order to embezzle points.
You know that who will copy dishonourably
it will make one ugly end.
You will be constantly under control.
You are all intenzionati to become of the Chunin.
If you are of the ninja, you behave yourselves from worthy ninja.
I must tranquilizzarmi!
! !
To Naruto part, I
and Sasuke-kun we can make it us.
Even if Naruto had to take
zero we will compensate it.
Moreover, if someone had
to take zero points
he will be bocciato with to its square.
COSAAA!
There are two persons whom they want to kill to me.
Naruto-kun
The last problem will be given to you
after 45 minuteren from the beginning of the test.
You have an hour for the examination.
BEGUN!!
We are truly in the troubles
Naruto I pray to you, avoids to take one zero!
I see badly
I hope that Naruto not
it has fallen in the panic.
To figure itself!
They are passed in many situations like this.
In these cases, I only must rilassarmi,
and to concentrate to me on the questions
and to resolve those most feasible ones.
We see the first problem is
a criptato text?
Following
Vediamo
the second question is
The B line
of the diagram it represents the maximum distance
percorribile from one shuriken launch from a ninja
situated on a high tree 7 meters.
To assume the characteristics of the ninja
considering the throw of the shuriken
and it calculates the maximum throw from earth.
To give of the explanation.
But this is a question that it demands
the elaboration of one uncertain condition
and the analysis of the energies.
Naruto pu   not to succeed to resolve it!
Sure the greater part
of the persons it will not know to resolve it.
Ok, we pass to the following question.
The other questions are equally difficult!
I have understood!
These questions are impossible
That disaster!
They are truly, but truly in the troubles.
If they came promoted approximately 10 squares on 51
it would be made of all in order conserving the points.
E' a system that it pushes to you to copy.
I hope that Sasuke-kun and Naruto
they are not put to copy.
It will go well.
Neanche Naruto is cos   stupid.
I trust myself he.
Calm one. With calm. With calm, and
I must copy without makes to discover me!
Not! NOT! I cannot!
I cannot make one rischiosa what cos  ?!
They seem to be most careful
it is like if they knew that we will copy sure.
Probable E' that takes
famous on those notebooks.
Someone must have been
been strange to copy.
Uncovered being to copy
it involves to lose two points.
To lose two points, eh?
Normally, it is come expelled if they are strange to you to copy.
You know that who will copy dishonourably
it will make one ugly end.
If you are of the ninja, then you behave yourselves
like a good ones ninja.
now I have been understood!
This is not only a test for
to estimate our acquaintances.
In truth it is
it is a test in order to estimate
ability to collect information
using the techniques
espionage officials.
The ninja they must know to anticipate the adversary.
Therefore the examiner means to spur to us to copy
as only a worthy one ninja would make.
Single E' cos   that the removal
of the points it has sense.
One is loss of single two points
for every intercepted attempt.
It comes put to the test the ability to collect
information eluding the control of the assistants
and of the person from which copy
and to obtain cos   the correct answer.
You must notice some, Naruto!
The examination if you do not make it!
Merda
If this examination
servants to determine the ability
to obtain information
she must it are to us someone in the class
that she knows the answers!
It seems that Gaara has begun
Account on you Karasu.
Evvai!
Bravo Akamaru!
Now the question number four.
To judge from the rhythm, the order
of writing and from the number of blows
Well, I have understood!
Well, dimmi all.
Eight.
Lee, if you have seen it makes me
sign with the coprifronte.
The time st flying!!
Maledizione, does not remain to me that to copy!
For , if they discover to me, I would put
in the troubles Sakura-chan and Sasuke.
For   if I take zero
Sakura-chan and Sasuke will come
bocciati however.
Naruto-kun
I make to see my task you.
What is saying?
Why it would make this for me?
it is even a trabocchetto!?
For  Hinata it is not the type of person
that it would make one what of the sort.
For
perhaps glielo Kiba has said
it makes me to fall in trap.
Hinata, you must dirmi one what.
Why you make to see your task me?
Why....
I
I do not want that you come endured bocciato.
As you know we nine we are the only esordienti,
and more ahead there will be other difficulties.
Then they are cos   the things!
I have doubted of you without reason.
However it is, is one great opportunity.
They are content that Hinata is
sitting propio to my flank.
What is why I was in order to turn itself!
What means?
You have mistaken five times.
Six bocciato.
Thing
You and your companions, outside from here!
Endured!
Number 23, bocciato.
Number 43 and 27, bocciati.
NOOO!!
Hey, than tests you have that
I have copied for five times?
Resolutions truly to control
all this people?
Listen to me.
We are Chunin chosen and trains to you
propio for this examination.
An elite pu   to say itself.
We do not lose neanche a your movement.
My force is the test.
Naruto-kun
Soon, it watches.
Hinata, you have not understood?
A large one ninja like me
it does not have need to copy.
Naruto-kun but
Moreover
helping me to copy you would put
in danger same you.
Naruto-kun
Dispiace, I did not have to make it me.
Not preoccuparti.
They are one stupid.
Why I have said to them cos ?
They are too much proud.
Byakugan!
Sharingan!
Copier   following its movements!
My hand is muovendo without indugio.
I have found that just one!
It seems that Sakura has ended.
I admit that the dimension of your forehead
and of your intelligence they are remarkable.
And for this you would have to be felt honored of being
the target of my tacnica.
Ninpou Shintenshin not Jutsu!
Ino must have used that technique.
Pu   not to contrast the technique of Ino.
Sakura, entrer   for a po' in your mind.
Hour, I must learn all fastly the answers
then I must pass to Shikamaru and to Chouji.
Number 59, bocciato.
Number 33 and 9, bocciati.
With this the bocciati groups are 13.
Number 41, bocciato.
Number 35 and 62, bocciati.
It is not true!
That child is making calmly
also with all this casino.
Impressive for a principiante.
The optical nerve is connected.
Opening of the third eye.
Maledizione, me has entered something in the eye.
Me forgiveness.
What you want?
I would have need to go to the bath.
The rules say that you must be
accompanied from one of we.
It goes well.
In spite of everything
these examiners are not a granch
Nobody is shrewed that
there is an examiner in more.
Not creeds, Karasu?
They are already passes 40 minuteren to you
me 20 remain some alone.
I must risk all
with the 10 question that will be given
only after 45 minuteren.
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
If I make it and the mistake, dovr   to remain in order always Genin?
(In truth? In truth? In truth)
If I do not make it, will suspend also my companions automatically?
(Impossible Impossible Impossible)
The rule without hope of the 10 question
(Bocciato Bocciato Bocciato)
I must choose between one or the other!!
(What I must make? What I must make? What I must make)
They are truly in the troubles!!
(Maledizione Maledizione Maledizione)
The next time:
To improvise!
The answer to the tenth question.