Subbed by Gatsu
Chekked by Kyubi
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
hikarabita kotoba or tsunaide
soredemo boku not shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dakenano
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete kimi to warau ima or ikirunoda
YEAH!
soredemo kono dekigotoga kimi wo kurushimeru darou
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
konomama dwaries mo nokorazu ni anatato wakachi audake
yagate bokurawa sorega subetedato kigatsuite
kanashimi ga hoho wo tsutatte namida not kawa ni narudake
yureru omoiwa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeaunoyo
Baby
Still it is not here? Still it has not arrived, Idate?
My Getlteman, R-with regard to the case that we have examined…
We have finally of the tests.
Oh? E' cos ì?
Well.
My Getlteman, something not và?
Not, it is not nothing.
To concentrate the Chakra…
We are knows to you…
Sasuke-kun, you are well?
Naruto, account on you…
Proteggi please Idate-saint.
Episode #106
Idate ce will make it!
Still a last effort!!
Your needles poison to you do not have some effect on me!
As you have dared to take it to you with Sasuke and Sakura-chan…
Not to worry to you, you will catch up them soon moltro.
You will not kill to me easy cos  ì!
Naruto…
What I must make…
The Rasengan  cannot  null against its sword.
It does not import! I must absolutely save them!
You want to still help them?
After a similar jump not creed that is still alive.
ZITTO!
Tajyuu Kage bunshin not jutsu!
Oh. Conti to escape confusing to me with this poor technique?
Well! I am not trying to escape!
Naruto, will not work!
This technique  cannot  null against this sword!
Useless E'!
Naruto!
How those losing the Uchiha, why Konoha is inhabited from idiots like you?
Zitto… I will save  them…
Creeds truly that they are still alive?
You would make scappare better.
It goes to hell…
To abandon my companions and to scappare via!
This is the answer to my tenth problem!
What you are blaterando?
Still…
You take this!
Imbecille…
Rasengan!
Naruto!
Still you have not understood it? You will not never strike to me.
Merda…
This is…
A leak made from Sasuke.
It goes well… If you headed at this leak…
I can make it us !
You want to be still struck? It abandons.
Zitto!
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
Sasuke… Not  lascerò  that the opportunity that has left Sasuke me comes wasted!
Naruto…
You are firm.
Sasuke! They are using of the "Mizu Bunshin "!
[ Cloni of water ]
I know!
You have confidence, Idate-saint, we it proteggeremo.
It knows… Sakura-saint!
It goes ahead…
We will catch up to you soon.
Sakura-chan !
I…
I dislike the persons who do not know when to let go.
This is the last one!
Still these trucchetti…
How!?
I have said to you that I dislike the persons who help an other,
Idate!
Your adversary is I!
Over of you!
Rasengan!
Like!
It cannot  be…
Naruto, ce you have made it!
Naruto, a six incredible boy.
It can  are given…
Sakura-chan?
Naruto!
Idate-saint!
Sakura-chan!
It is well....
Also Sasuke-kun stà well!
Hour I come to take to you! !
Idiot! He leaves to lose, thoughts to end the race!
OK…
But as we make to cross…
It watches to me!
It cuts the rope cos ì  we will arrive to the other side!
Understood!
I thought to be one person orribile…
But Jirocho head has believed in me.
I have confidence in you more than anyone other.
Life was before the time in me that someone has believed in me.
Here why I want to gain this race for the head.
But in truth, alone I cannot win.
For this many times are discouraged me…
Attention!
But that time that they wanted to kill to me, you have made of all in order saving to me.
Naruto, me dispiace. I had myself to be trusted you sin from the beginning.
About what it speaks?
Riparleremo some after to have gained the race.
You have reason.
Naruto.
Idate…
Hour, it makes it!
It goes well!
That beautiful the humor.
Naruto! Cos ì  we will crash on the wall!
The sò ! Us task I!
I will concentrate  my Chakra in my feet…
E' my last reservoir of Chakra!
Hour, we will salt with my Chakra!
! Ce you have made it! Naruto!
Hour you go towards the goal!
Sakura-chan!  I will come  to save to you later!
Well, we go, Idate!
Well!
It continues to I would run, Fukusuke!
Not to lower the guard until the end!
Zitto!  The sò!
Geez, you know it that I am running of the good humor.
I see, the Todoroki Shrine.
Head…
Merda!
Well, well.
Idate
Laggiù !
Idate of the Wasabi clan!
You run! You can still catch up it!
How!?
Idate!
Imbecille! What you make Fukusuke!? You run!
Merda…!
I will not lose…  I will not lose  for no reason!
I will not abandon,  I will continue  until the end!
E' one joke…  I will not allow  that it exceeds to me after that they have arrived end here!
Perfect!
Stà recovering!
Merda, this boy…
I will not lose!
Merda…
Idate!
Vai, Idate!
Head!
Force! Idate!
Ce I have made it…
Idate.
E' be one beautiful race.
Head!
You have made a good job.
Head… is spiacente.
Truly they are desolated.
Idiot! Why you are making excuses yourself?
You have won you know it ?
Not, you listen to me.
I want to be truly made excuses. You pardon to me!
I do not understand to you just. You a six truly strange boy!
Good job, Idate.
They are made an impression.
Hour, goes to receive the winner blessing.
It goes well!
Six fort, Idate!
A six imbecille!
You have rendered us two incapable ones of fornte to the head! Six ready one for the consequences!
Me dispiace…
The winner, Morino Idate of the Wasabi Family.
He… There is successful finally!
Hey, waited for a moment.
Eh? Kyuuroku.
During the race, Idate has been made to help from a Ninja.
E' against the rules.
How?
I have the tests.
Watched this photo.
The rule of the race says that it must be arrived to the goal with the own forces.
Therefore, Idate is disqualified.
The winner is Hikyakuya Fukusuke of the Wagarashi family.
But…
Waited for! This was…
Not there are excusing!
Jirocho, was a scomessa, is not cos ì?
They hate that the Wasabi family is announced publicly immediately!
Aspects a moment.
This rule does not exist. You do not say idiozie.
My Getlteman…
There is some reason for which you want that the Wagarashi family wins?
Not, absolutely…
Perhaps why if the Wagarashi family loses, you cannot make more one what like this.
Watched.
It Jokes! She withdraws to you from your position and becomes a monaco!
, Getlteman.
Wagarashi Kyuuroki.
Contacts have reported also of your bad ones you to me.
The punishment to give to the village of Degarashi will be heavy.
Therefore, from today the Wagarashi family will be announced publicly!
Understood…
, Getlteman…!
Today splendid day is one!
All it has been resolved.
Thanks for all the aid, Naruto.
Idate, is time of dirci goodbye.
They have come to take the wounded.
Ibiki-saint.
Bro!
Dov' is the wounded?
E' here.
Portatelo immediately on the boat.
Eeh…
Euh…
How?
Nothing…
Bro
It waits for, Bro
Who is?
The person who called me "Bro" is died three years ago.
Bro.
Hour, I know the answer of the tenth question.
I will not betray  of new my companions…
Hour, I can make confidence on the others.
Grown E'.
Goodbye, Idate. We will see again ourselves.
Good bye, to the next one!
, us rivederemo!
Also to she Head! Soon!
!
Goodbye !
Good bye !
E' indeed an interesting boy.
Task that the Fifth Hokage chosen for one the reason.
Naruto! Thanks!
Idate! The next time, I want to compete with you!
Sasuke-kun, you are badly?
Not…
They are content… Once it arrives you to the village your wounds will be recovered.
…
Then the voices were true.
The heir of the Uchiha clan is more the weak person than all.
They are not successful to strike it…
But he…
This Naruto…
goku tamani boku tamani
yume ni yabureru hito not kakera ga yama not youni mieru
kamisama ni hotokesama ni
sugari naiteru hito not kakera ga yama not youni mieru
dan dan dansu de randevu
hora shouri not po-zu from randaran
sheiku sheiku sheiku sagasoujanai
owaranai bay bays not rizumu de
yama not youni mieru
Waited for… Sasuke-kun and Naruto, what have you two?
Hé, we are in a hospital!
Sasuke-kun is the wounded, would not have to torment it Naruto!
Finitela with these dirty ones makes up!
Why? Why they must make this?
Following Episode
I want to fight to you
The final crash
Sasuke vs Naruto!