Subtitles By: BakaSan
Disqualified!? Danger! Ahead of Schedule!
Trouble in the Main Tournament!
Alright!
I'd never have thought that the fox-kid
would put up such a good fight.
He still has power to run around... man, he's a stamina freak.
I did it!
Naruto is getting stronger and stronger...
He is good, isn't he?
Yeah, he has a good sense.
And he's kinda cute.
I envy you...
Watching your fight makes me feel that I should
work harder, too. That's the amazing thing.
Ahhh... he won... I can't believe it.
I thought he was one of the uncool guys like me.
Uncool guys?
Everybody's cheering for him now
and he looks like a cool guy now.
I probably can't beat him... That's
seriously not good... I'm so depressed.
He channeled and used the Kyubi's
chakra without losing himself.
Yeah, most of Konoha here were surprised.
Naruto was able to control Kyubi's
chakra... since when did he learn that skill?
I'm the best!
Even a captured bird, as it tries to open
the cage with its beak, gets smarter.
It doesn't give up to fly free in the sky again.
This time, it's your loss.
Father...
Don't worry. There's no damage to your inner organs.
You seem too have used up almost all your chakra.
You're not the only one whose "special".
Why do you try so hard to go against your fate?
Because I was called a loser!
People who become Hokage are born with such a fate.
So what?!
Hyuga-sama.
Please leave us alone.
But...
It won't take long.
Yes.
What brought you here?
That day...
I came here to tell you the truth about that day.
That day?
Back then, I was planning to die.
What are you saying?
My father was killed as your double then.
The truth about that day is here.
It must be more excuses that the Souke made up.
You should be able to understand it now.
"To Neji"
This handwriting is my...
Neji, I have only a short time left.
I have something I want to tell you before then.
Something he wants to tell me?
The Shinobi-kashira of Kaminari who tried to abduct
Hinata-sama was killed by Hiashi-sama instead.
Because of the death of their Shinobi-kashira
the Kaminari demands were harsh.
They wouldn't even admit that they tried to abduct her.
There's nothing else we can do. If we
can save this village with only my life...
Wait Hiashi. Don't rush to that conclusion.
The blood-limit of the Hyuga is a
great last hand for this village.
It is the Souke's duty to protect it forever.
But, in the name of that duty, if this
village goes into such a hopeless war...
I know that. That's why...
There’s the Bunke for that reason.
We will give Hizashi's dead body as your double.
Hizashi has already agreed to it.
But what they want is the secret of this Byakugan.
If it's Hizashi, the secret will be sealed when he dies.
I don't believe the Kaminari will consent to...
That may be what they really want. But what the Kaminari
demanded was to hand over Hyuga Hiashi's dead body.
Since we will accept their demand and give them Hizashi's
body, which is identical to yours, they can't complain.
But...!
Hiashi, the time has come. Every ancestor of
the Hyuga Souke has protected the clan like this.
You have to have the mind to let go, even
if it's your sibling, or family member.
That's the Souke destiny. And this is the
fate of those who were born into the Hyuga.
Where's the usual
strong-willed Hiashi-sama?
This is totally different from the other important
things before. This can't be decided it so easily...
Hizashi... you...
Please have me go.
You have Neji... why do you choose to die for the Souke?
That's not true.
I have hated the Souke. To tell you the truth, I still hate it. That's
why I want to die to protect you as my brother, not as the Souke.
To do so is my first freedom that I can choose.
I have been showing only my ungraceful sides
to Neji. But I finally realized my own will.
Therefore, please tell Neji this...
I'm not going to die for the Souke.
But I choose to die by my own free will to protect
Neji... my brother... my family... and this Village.
You say its freedom to choose death with your own will?
Brother, I've always wanted to
go against the Hyuga's fate once.
I wanted to choose my own fate... That's all.
Overcome your fate, Neji. Your fate
is to be created by your own hands.
Father.
That is the truth.
I apologize.
Please raise your head.
Father... I still don't know whether a man's fate
is just to float on the fixed flow like the clouds.
Or if it can get into the flow that a man chooses to be on.
Either way, it may end up in the same place.
But when choosing the latter way to live,
people can work hard for the purpose of living.
And people who have it are the real strong ones.
I think I finally understood that in this battle.
Father, my purpose is only one thing...
I want to get stronger. Strong enough to lose to nobody.
That's what I think now.
Father, the birds fly’s well today... Fly as they feel well.
Noisy, isn't it?
Because that was a good battle.
That is true... but...
There’s no other match that is more
looked-forward to than the next match...
to the Shinobi-kashira and Daimyos
who will be requesting missions.
By the way, I didn't see him at the opening
ceremony. But he's already here, right?
We still can't find Sasuke.
There are also worries about Orochimaru.
Before people start to notice and
make a fit, we should disqualify him.
What're you guys doing? Start the next match already!
How long will you make us wait?!
It's going to be sunset soon!
What's going on with the next match? Did Sasuke come already?
Whats keeping him from coming? Is he not going to show up?
A wise man keeps away from danger. It may be a smart decision.
What are you guys talking about? He's definitely coming.
But what is he doing... you're gonna get disqualified soon.
There's no other choice.
Sasuke is disqualified.
Uchiha Sasuke is disqualified?
There's no other choice than that.
What are we going to do? If he
doesn't show up, our plan will be...
This isn't good.
Maybe then...
Where're you going, Gaara?
I'm going to verify my existence.
I wonder if Gaara actually killed him...
Sasuke, one more time.
What's up?
Releasing that much bad intention, you're
not hiding yourself at all.  Come on out.
So its you...
Hokage-dono, I want you to hold
on to disqualify Uchiha Sasuke.
You may be right, but any Shinobi who doesn't value time
can't become a Chunin, even if he's a very skilled one.
There's no reason for us to wait for him if he doesn't
have a very clear and understandable reason to be late.
I see... then there's enough of a reason.
Most of Shinobi-kashira and daimyos, including
myself, came here to see the next match.
I'm sure they will understand.
But...
After all, he's the survivor of the Uchiha. We, the Wind
country, would like to have our Gaara go against him.
Hokage sama.
There's no guarantee that Sasuke will come, but...
I understand.
I'll make an exception and hold this
match for later and wait for him.
Hokage-sama, are you really...
Tell the examiner.
But, it is really rare to hear you,
Kazekage-dono, to insist that much.
There's no other opponent than Uchiha to show
off my village's shinobi quality to the Daimyos.
It's a chance for us.
I understand.
Ladies and Gentleman.
One person for the next match still hasn't arrived yet.
Therefore we decided to postpone the
match, and start the match after that first.
What's he doing, Sasuke.
That's good. Sasuke-kun won't get disqualified.
Good.
Hey. That means my match is closer by one match.
Then, onto the next match. Kankuro
and Aburame Shino, come down here.
My match doesn't mean anything.
Besides, I don't want to show the mechanism I put
into my doll in front of the enemy before the plan...
Examiner, I forfeit.
What?
I forfeit. Continue onto the next match.
Due to Kankuro's forfeiture,
Aburame Shino wins without a fight.
You are?
It's my turn, right?
It seems you're eager to fight.
Alright. I'll start the next match.
Hey, the other one, come on down.
Hey, why the hell is she excited about the match by herself.
Plus, why is it always me getting the match plan changed?
Hey, Nara Shikamaru. I'm talking to you.
Shit... then I'm going to forfeit, too...
Alright, Shikamaru. Go for it!
Damn Naruto.
Go for it, Shikamaru!
It's a bit strange to see Shikamaru in the final round.
You're on fire, hot, excited! That's my teammate!
But he's looking up the sky and not concentrating.
What? It can be because he is so into the match!
Alright Shikamaru! Give the 16-combo and beat her up.
Next Episode
Clouds are good...
A Man With No Fighting Spirit
Ino, your cheer is scary.