Subtitles By: BakaSan
Jiraiya-sama...
I have faith in you.
Taught directly by the Pervert
Sennin It's the Summon-No-Jutsu!!
Not as I imagined...
Don't you ever sleep?
What do you want?
I thought I'd better take care of you here.
So I can possibly go against Sasuke-kun,
since I'm the odd one out in the first round.
I know your sand attacks...
I wonder if it's faster than my sound.
During the full moon...
During the night of the full moon,
I can feel the blood of "that" move.
What...?!
What are you?!
That's incredible.
Is that the real him?
But, is it ok?
He's from the Sound...
It's alright.
We were done with him a long time ago.
I thought he was a tool to...
test that Sasuke kid's ability.
Why is he meeting with the Sand?
No...
That isn't necessary anymore.
In fact...
I was already ordered to abduct Sasuke-kun.
But...
I failed to do it.
What?
Yes.
...somebody like you.
Do you want to try that somebody?
I see that you're a spoiled brat.
You shouldn't fuck around with adults.
Don't talk so big.
I've got an advantage in this situation.
They already know that I'm the spy of the Sound.
Then...
if they find out you're meeting with me secretly.
Everything, including the plan
to crush Konoha, will be in vain.
I heard that you're Orochimaru's right hand, but...
you're a fool to come to see me after you got caught.
Well, not really.
To be exact, it's not that they caught me.
It's me who revealed myself to them.
I wanted to know how much Konoha would react to that.
It is not too late to abduct Sasuke after seeing that.
If you guys fail, then we'll back out soon.
This is the plan that the Sound brought to us after all.
The Sand won't appear at the front until the last minute.
That's Kazekage's wishes.
What!
That's fine.
This is the execution strategy of the Sound.
And, please let them know about this plan, too.
Yes, I know that.
Then, I'm leaving now.
Our ally, the Sand is already connected to the Sound.
I need to tell this to Hokage-sama quickly.
Oh, and...
I'll take care of cleaning up.
No, I'll do it.
I should do a little work for our friends...
as the Sand are guests in the Wind country.
Besides there is only one rat.
It's easy.
Oh, It's Mr. Examiner.
What are you doing at a place like this alone?
There's no other choice but fighting you.
Konoha-ryu Mikazuki-no-Mai (Konoha
style Crescent Dance)
I can't pull it out.
This technique is the
Konoha-ryu Mikazuki-no-Mai?
It's impressive to be able to use it at that young age...
I can tell that this village has good ones, as I thought.
That was a great sword move.
But the truth is that the actual blade can be stopped.
However, no one can stop the blade of the Wind.
That's good. So good!
Hey.
This is paradise.
I said hey!
Won't you turn around and look at me already?
If you train me, I'll do you a lot of services.
P-L-E-A-S-E
Oh, you're finally out. I've been waiting for you.
Are you making fun of me?
You're doing the same to me, too.
Ah, I'm hungry.
Let's go back to hotel now.
Damnit.
Alright. I'll teach you the technique...
Do you really have the intention to do that?
Do you remember the chat about
two types of chakra from yesterday?
Our chat yesterday?
You were saying something like blue chakra and red chakra.
Yeah. And what about it?
You said you felt the red chakra
when a great power came out from you.
Yeah. I think it was something like that.
Then, channel that red chakra right now.
Ah... if you say so... Well, I'll give it a try.
How's it?
Nope. This isn't it. This is the regular chakra.
Man! You've got no talent.
Don't talk big! Besides I don't even
know what those two types of chakra are!
Shut up and continue.
"I don't even know", eh?
He doesn't realize yet that the red chakra is Kyubi's chakra.
Well, by summarizing what he says, being
at risk of his life or emotional rage...
...is the key to bring out the Kyubi's chakra.
Ah. No. No. I can only channel the usual chakra.
Hey, Ero Sennin. What's the relationship between
this red chakra and the technique you will teach me?
Listen, kid.
Your regular chakra isn't sufficient
at all for the technique I'll teach you.
That's why you need to be able to bring out and use the other chakra,
the huge one that is lying unused inside of you,  whenever you need.
But why do you know I have such chakra?
Oh, thank you for asking!
Beause... I'm a Sennin.
You're not answering my question!
Anyways, the special chakra that only
you have will be your greatest weapon.
My greatest weapon?
If you don't use it, you're wasting the treasure.
There's no need to do the same
training that everybody else does.
Everybody has things that they're good at and bad at.
You have your own style.
Trainings up till now were to hold, or
to keep releasing chakra at a fixed level.
In other words, it was a training for using chakra
with control so that you won't get tired out.
But you should learn the power rather than
control because you have great stamina.
With two types of chakra, you won't get easily tired
out... you should release as much chakra as possible,
and should train to be able to maximize
the amount of chakra that can be used.
There are techniques and skills
that can be learned only with it.
For example, what?
For example, the technique I'm going to teach you from now...
Kuchiyose-no-jutsu. (Summon-no-jutsu)
Kuchiyose?
That's right.
By making a contract with different
animals, with your blood beforehand,
you can bring them out anytime, and any place you
want with ninjutsu. It's a space-time ninjutsu.
Wow. That sounds great!
Teach me! Teach me now!
Before that, first...
You need to use up all your regular chakra.
Alright.
Leave it to me.
Oh, he can use Kage-bunshin.
I have a good idea to quickly use up all the regular chakra.
You've got a good number of replications.
Hey! We're gonna do the battle-royal.
The last one to survive is the strongest me.
We'll decide the me of me.
I see. That's a good idea from someone so stupid.
Alright. let's do it.
Well, this is an unromantic scene to watch.
Finally, the end is near.
Great.
I am the strongest me, as expected.
I see that you've finally used up most of your chakra.
I will finally teach you the technique now.
I've been waiting for this.
First, I'll  show you. Look carefully.
Kuchiyose-no-jutsu!
Cool!
Open that scroll.
That is the contract with toads for summoning, that
was handed down to me from generation to generation.
Write your name with your blood, and put blood finger prints
of all your fingers of one of your hands, underneath it.
Then, channel the chakra to where you want to summon,
and put down the hand you made the contract with.
In hand seal's it's boar, dog, hen, monkey, sheep.
U... Zu... Ma... Ki... Na... Ru.. To
Alright. It's done.
Your current condition makes the red chakra come out easier.
Try it once.
I'm already doing it!
boar, dog, hen, monkey, sheep
Ninpo
Kuchiyose-no-jutsu!
A tadpole?
He doesn't have any talent after all...
Hayate...
What happened?
Ino! I was going to see Sasuke at hospital alone
but why are you coming with me?!
Plus, what is that flower. Rose of Love? You got no sense.
I definetly choose this narcissus for my wish that
Sasuke get better very soon.
Next episode Painful Feeling A single flower with Wish
Alright! This will decide!
BakaSan: I was tired and really busy this week. I didn't do any second
pass for quality. Other versions using this will come out soon enough.