Subbed by Shinji 89
Checked by # [ Fabry ]
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not
fukinukeru Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda Yeah!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite
kanashimi mo hoho tsutatte
namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa
tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Merda.
Six sure good one.
You have broken the trees and attacked
with perfect tempismo.
You must have made much practical one.
Complicated song seems to be one.
You have understood that I succeeded in
to control them with my song.
Far from negligible for a bastard dirt like
you to pick the complexity of the melodia.
But it is impossible that you can
to understand it completely.
The art does not appeal to to me for nothing.
But, if it succeeds to control them with those flauto,
it must it are to us something in the song
that it controls their single actions.
It must it are to us some structure under.
Confido in my abilities of observation.
But stavolta the things seem to put themselves badly.
I do not know null on the manipulation
of the sound and its he aims weak people.
Episode #122
Fake!Shikamaru is entrusted to
resurrezione of the dead men.
Now, I will show  you  one my specialty, Tsubaki not never.
I will make   pieces!
You would not have to make promised that you cannot maintain.
Hush!
What ?
You I have said.
The boneses are dense as the steel.
It would be better if you tried than person
Eternal damnation!
Nobody is not never survivor
after to have felt this melodia.
Supreme Melodia n°9 - Lair of the demon
Music is changed!
They arrive!
What is those…
What ?
These things are…
It has understood the dangerousness of the ghosts
and it has been withdrawn endured.
It is not cos ì  badly.
But....
To hide is the thing better hour,
given the insufficient amount of I exploded to you
and smoke-producing that me is remained.
Those things white women…
Hanno divorato my spiritual energy.
Observing the passage of mine shuriken
I have noticed that nutrono of chakra.
They are composed from chakra
and spiritual energy,
They have need of stability, and they are
it starves you of psychical energy.
Continuing in this way not
I will more succeed  to paste the chakra.
They are truly dangerous.
It is similar to me.
One specialist in the use of the chakra.
Without doubt technical secret is one.
Therefore I do not have to go against those
transactions white men, but against who command them.>.
The simpler thing would be
to stop the sound of the flauto, but…
But in these conditions,
it is impossible to approach itself.
An other possibility is to capture them
using the Kagemane not jutsu.
But he is not simple why they continue
to attack in accidental way.
If of it you lacked one, me
they would attack and would be the end.
Its defense and its attack
they do not have points weak people.
It would be an optimal giocatrice of chess.
12 kunai remain me, 9 shuriken, 1 bomb
flash, 12 meters of cable and 1 I seal explosive.
Me it seems to play to shougi.
I have seeds them to you ?
Impossible.
Akamaru ?
You hold, you take these, Akamaru.
If it does not eat you cannot recover the forces.
All to place, Akamaru, we go!
We do not have to forget us about those here.
Tsubaki not Never
Not there is place in order to hide.
Ignoring their movements
that worm  cannot  escape.
I will find  and I will kill  it  to more soon!
Arrived E' the moment.
Ok, is all to place. I cannot
to make other that to attack it.
Nine attacks remain me.
The outcome of the crash depends on they.
One!
Too much simple! My ability in
to control them with the sound is imbattibile.
You will not succeed to strike to me,
any is your plan!
Two!
Those cursed bastard is scappato.
Dov' is ?
Three!
Low, eh ?
Four!
As it dares to make these stupiden giochetti!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Otto!
It is alone taking time.
What? one bomb flash ?
nine!
Merda!
It is using the light for
to extend its shadow!
Kagemane not Jutsu!
The Kagemane Jutsu has not succeeded!
Impossible!
How you have made to understand their movements?
Impossible E' that you can
to understand mine melodia!
Sin from the beginning, I have not only felt music.
there was qualcos' other beyond to the sound.
I have perceived from your commandos.
Your fingers!
Impossible…
Movements of those three…
Memorizzato the positions of the fingers
and it has read my movements !
Impossible E'!
In order to begin, you move the index
and the ring finger of the right hand.
Then with the mean and the mignolo of
left hand you play the melodia…
This serves to command the type to the center.
Then with the inch and the index of the right hand
together to the index and the mignolo of the left,
you make to deliver a blow.
Schivato Hai my attacks,
and while it watches to me to you,
I have observed the movements of your fingers.
I have observed their movements,
memorizzato and analyzed.
Impossible E'.
They are catches to you from my kagemane not jutsu.
The more interesting thing of the shougi is that
you can use to your piacimento the pawns
adversaries who you have captured.
And from hour, it will be like one left of shougi.
Hour that they are I to having the three pawns,
it touches me to put to you in difficulty.
It seems sure of same you.
Even if you it does not remain not even a kunai.
My only arm is the flauto.
I have said to you that nobody does not survive
after to have felt the sound of the flauto!
That emergency.>.
Kai!
That pain not to know to use the own pawns!
Now it is my turn!
What?
The Kagemane has had happened.
Six be you to dirmi that
I had to use those three in order to stop to you?
I have used them like decoy.
The first attack was a bluff.
While the second was a normal attack.
Tu!
I do not have other choice.
To use level 2 in a place like this.>.
A merda will render me, but I accept it.
E' an honor for like you.
What is… this ?
Even if you six much wide awake one,
from this moment it will not go
nuller second your plans.
What you are saying!
It is trying to break off the Kagemane
not jutsu with the single force bruta ?
And from where comes all this chakra?
Going ahead cos ì  the technique it will disappear.
As I thought…  I will have  to use that technique.
Ninpo: KageKubi Shibari not Jutsu
It is using the shadow in order to take to me.
Me it seems of to have been taken give of the true arms!
But, not you  lascerò.
Eternal damnation, than power race it has?
To this distance it strikes to me in force.
You take this!
Demonic Flauto, infinite Melodia!
It goes badly!
A genjutsu?
At what you are aiming?
My body does not move.
When step to level 2 this
flauto he is able to create illusions.
Probably this melodia is perfect
for lurido a rat of drain like you.
Why…
.... this firm illusion its preda and the alloy!
How it is being legacies  ?
And this was your last movement, eh ?
Ill-fatedly, it is one scacco matto.
Ugly bastard!
What?
That bastard, has used the shadow in order to break off the finger!
With the pain if he has gone some from the illusion
It has made feint of to have been caught in mine jutsu!
As I have said to you before, the first movement only serves in order to distract.
E' to hit after is logical.
And only the second round is various from the first one.
More the adversary approaches to more the technique of the shadow is effective.
They have been too much imprudent…
Oh not, not of all.
Your greater error has been when you have
saying that your only arm was the flauto.
It seems sure of same you.
Even if you it does not remain not even a kunai.
My only arm is the flauto.
I have said to you that nobody does not survive
after to have felt the sound of the flauto!
Not to say to me…
Exact.
The reason for which I have lacked to you with the kunai
it was why you collected it
and you came towards me.
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
bokura kara shaberi kaketure
meiwaku ni omou kara
sonna fuan wo kakaetie
yuuki wo dashite mitayo
umaku shaerinai bokuno
bukiyou na hanashi
kimi wa mimi wo sorasazuni
chanto kiite kuretayo
soredaked bokuwa ukarete shimaunosa
dakedo kimi wa boku nante
nantomo omottenai yone
setsunai yo
dakedo
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de!
hajimete kimi to shabereta
It cannot  be… I am dreamming?
Too much real E' for being a dream.
Arrogant ventilation…
the special coveralls that adapted to the body.
Not mentono these eyes, these hats, and these sopracciglia!
Tu!! what you make us here!
Next episode:
Here the green beast of Konoha!
E' as a storm in arrival!