Subtitles By: BakaSan
Hey, loser!
I will warn you about two things...
If you are a real ninja, stop the pathetic cheers for others.
and one more thing...
A loser is a loser, no matter what. You can never change!
You wanna try?
You!
I can feel the pain in your heart, Naruto-kun,
but the battle must be fought in a real match.
We will see if a loser can beat an elite with his
efforts... Im looking forward to the real final matches.
I promise you that...
...I will win no matter what!
Crash Gaara!! Youthfulness! Power! Explosion!
Hey, Choji. Youre in serious
trouble. Only strong guys are left.
That Sound Ninja seems to be the strongest in his team...
and I heard that Lee could match up with Sasuke.
Especially that Sand guy, his
type is usually the most dangerous.
I do not care... I will immediately forfeit then.
Oh I guess that means you dont
want the all-you-can-eat Korean BBQ.
Oh, no way...
If you get in danger, I will stop
your match like we did for Hinata.
You can eat Kalbi(korean beef) or
anything you want, and as much as you want.
Hey, dont tempt him with food.
Ah, by the way, you didnt go down there for Hinata...
WooooW! Yakiniku (Korean BBQ)! Lets
go eat Yakiniku! All-I-Can-Eat!!
This looks bad...
Because of the last match...
Hes starting to awaken...
the demon inside of him.
I want to know more about that Neji guy. I guess I have to...
Kankuro?
Im going to gather some information.
Hey!
What?
What are you doing there? Dont you need
to go back to where your comrades are?
It is none of your business!
Ohh.. I see.
Hyuga Neji seems he is still hiding his
real ability from what I saw in his battle.
What kind of guy is he?
I will beat him up!
Ah, no... Nobody is asking you that.
Also, you are not even in the same league.
You are a funny guy. I like you.
You are not funny. I dont like you!
Bastard! Im gonna kill you!
Well, we will continue the matches.
Alright! This must be your turn! Go for it, Lee!
NO!
I came this far. Id rather go last.
Lee-san, you are so childish.
Come down here already.
Wooooow!
Im saved!
Hey! Stop scaring us!
Gaara VS Rock Lee
You fell for it!
If I said I wanted to go last, then I know I wont.
Its like if I throw a rock at a pole
trying to hit it, I will miss it.
But if I throw the rock to miss it, then I will hit it.
I used principle!
Wow! Thats my student!
I never wanted to go last. You fell for it as I planned!
Who fell for it?
I will give you some nice advice.
It seems that no one else noticed
it yet, but his gourd is suspicious!!
Oh, I see.
Stop taking notes! You wont have time
to read it during a battle. Idiot!
I see.
They didnt notice it untill now?
I wonder if Lee-san is going to be alright.
Alright! Go for it, Lee!
It is my pleasure to fight against you this early.
I dont know what kind of fighting
style that bobbed hair guy has...
But he cannot win against Gaara. Never.
He sure did have the speed. But his kick wasnt that good.
No.
He is strong!
Please, dont rush.
Be careful, Lee.
Well then. The ninth match.
Begin!
Konoha Senpu (Leaf Wind)
Is that...?!
Sand?
What a strange technique.
He keeps sand in that gourd?
Thats it!
Is that all?
Sabaku Kyu (Desert Coffin)
Sabaku SouSou(Desert Graveyard)
That tragedy will happen here again.
A jutsu to control the sand... Thats a bit of trouble.
Well, I guess I will try!
The fast attacks from Lee-san cant even touch him.
What is going on here?
No physical attacks can touch him.
The sand will protect him as if it were
a shield regardless of Gaaras own control.
That is why there has been no one...
that could injure Gaara.
Shit! He didnt even move an inch.
Is that all?
Wont you let me have some more fun?
There is not enough BLOOD!
Why does Lee-san use only
Taijutsu? It is not good for a close match.
Hed better use Ninjutsu from a distance.
It is not that he does not use it.
He cannot use it.
Lee has almost no skills for Ninjutsu and Genjutsu.
Youre kidding?
When I first met him, he had no skills... no talent at all.
No way. I cant believe it.
It sure is rare to find a Ninja who
cannot use Ninjutsu and Genjutsu.
That is why Taijutu is the only
way for Lee to survive as a Ninja.
However, that is also why he can win!
Lee! Take them off!
But Gui-sensei! You told me that I can do so only
when I need to protect a lot of people precious to me.
Who cares! I will allow it now!
Is that...
Weights?
What an old style of training.
Oh, I see!
Useless.
Alright! I can move much easier now!
Just because he took a little weight off, doesnt
mean that he can catch up with sand of Gaara.
Isnt that a bit too much, Gui?
Go, Lee!
Roger!
Close!
Fast!
Incredible!
Since he cant use Ninjutsu or Genjutsu he
put all his time into mastering Taijutsu...
all his efforts were for Taijutsu, and he
has put everything hes got into Taijutsu.
Even if he cannot use any other
jutsu, he will not lose to anybody!
He is the Taijutsu specialist.
Unbelievable! Gaara was injured!
No way....
Thick-eyebrows is way faster than before!
Was he that strong before?
Youthful days are ...
Explosive!
Im over here!
Good!
I can feel it!
Amazing! He is so fast!
The sand cant keep up with that speed.
He landed his attack perfectly!
Amazing.
His attack is too fast.
My eyes cant even follow him.
This is bad.
Yup, this is bad. That black eyed dude got a heavy hit!
Thats not the type of bad Im talking about.
What is it? His face is falling off...
Hes got sand covering his entire body.
It seems that hes got no injuries!
What is that guy?
He was wearing the sand, just as I thought. But...
it has been a long time since I saw the face of Gaara.
I knew that he was getting a little bit
more unstable during this Chunin exam, but...
The other Gaara is now awakening...
Hey, what the heck is it? Did he use the sand to
protect himself from that attack by Thick-eyebrow?
Yeah. That is his Sand armor.
Armor?
In a normal situation, the sand
shield protects Gaara automatically.
Even if that fails, the sand armor will still protect him.
that is the Absolute defense of Gaara.
Is that? What can he do then? There are no weak points at all.
No, I would not say that. In reality,
the sand armor has a lot of weak points.
Because it is not automatic, he uses up a lot of
Chakra. Plus, the defense level is lower than the Sand shield.
Since the sand covers his body
closely, he also uses up his stamina.
It is a proof that he is at the
disadvantage, because he needs to use that.
That Lee guy is better than I thought.
But the result is obvious.
He can never beat Gaara.
Is that all?
What kind of protection does he have... Even though
I can move more quickly, my attacks do not get to him.
I have no other choice but to land a
powerful hit to get through his sand.
I must use the Renge (Lotus).
Prepare yourself.
With the Lotus of Lee that drops at high-speed,
the thin protection of the sand wont be a problem.
Come at me, already.
As you wish!
Not high enough!
Not yet!
What great continuous kicks!
Even the regular Lotus will do a lot of damage to his body.
Finish with this one, Lee!
Take this!
Omote Renge! (Front Lotus)
I did feel it!
Great!
It is over.
No way... you must be kidding me.
Yes! Lee san won!
Hey hey. Is he dead, isnt he?
What?
Hey, hey. What happen to you,
thick-eyebrow. You no longer show the power you had.
You will get beaten up if you stay like that!
What? The thick-eyebrow is smiling.
How can he stay relaxed like that even
though he is in this bad situation?
Next episode. Hot-blooded loser! Finally
blossom. Forbidden secret technique!
The look in the eyes of the thick-eyebrow changed!