http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
-  Tenten VS Temari  -
Encounter number five.
Tenten.
Temari.
A step ahead.
I feel myself to explode after
to have approval that encounter.
Also she…
… it comes from the country of the sand.
Tenten Force!
It will be an interesting encounter.
Begun!
Shikamaru astounds!?
The inflamed battle of the girls ninja!
Force! Tenten!
Vai with the force of the giovinezza! Tenten!
Tenten! We are with you!
You fight with all your forces!
Force!
Under with the tifo!
Sissignore!
Che casino makes sti two.
The distance that Tenten holds
from the enemy it is impressive.
It is not too much near and it is not too much far.
It can  distribute is attack that defended.
What happens?
You can begin.
You want to observe mine movements?
E' only a warning, but if attack in order before,
you will be defeat in a second.
You do not have the experience
in order to preview my attacks.
It abandons the idea that is better.
Facts under!
It seems much sure one of you.
Well,  I will not hesitate  to attack!
I have lacked!
It cannot  be!
You want to put to me to the test?
Or the fear has overwhelmed to you
and six resolution not to aim?
I thought that I would have amused myself more…
… but it seems that not I can
to wait for granchè from you.
Impossible!
The attack of Tenten has failed!
Impossible E'.
Tenten is in a position to hitting
a target one hundred times…
.. on hundreds tried to you.
It has not never mistaken a blow.
Exact.
It has not mistaken.
E' be obliged to make it.
As usual extension
a friendly attitude.
Superfluous.
He is not pleasant.
The country of the sand still wins.
Still we do not know it.
I know it.
Why? How you can say it?
It makes to understand me.
Idiot…
… it is too much boring startelo to explain.
If Shikamaru thinks it cos ì,
then it will end in this way.
These two I do not understand them.
I must be calm.
I do not have makes to provoke me.
One…
… two…
… and three.
If it avoids them, then I must make
so as to to prevent it to it.
It is measuring the distance between me and she.
The next one will be a determined attack.
I have understood!
The fan hides something.
E' that one.
It pecks this to you!
What!
My crews…
CHe trick hides the fan!
This…
… it is the first symbol…
… ce two are others.
When you see three symbols mean…
.. that you will be defeat!
Tenten!
You do not have to be to the game of the enemy!
It concentrates to you!
You must be concentrated!
I know, Lee.
I would have used in the crash
main and not in that preliminary matter…
… but I do not have other choice.
It wants gia to use?
Cos' has intention to make
with those two coils?
Useless E' that you us tests.
Soushouryu!!!
Evocation of the two dredges!!!
Even if the number increases,
it does not change nothing.
According to symbol!
I have not still ended!
I will succeed  to hit it!
Third symbol…
E' passing!
Dov' is!
They are here.
To the shoulders!
- Ninpou…
(Ninja Art…)
- Kamaitachi!
(Attack of the Wind)
Tenten!
That wind contains of the Chakra!
Tenten has fought well…
… but  it cannot  escape…
… to that tornado.
C-that cruelty…
Tenten…!
Painful.
Truly painful.
It has cancelled all the attacks with crews of Tenten.
Com' is possible!
But… who is that one?
Just as Shikamaru said,
the country of the sand has won.
Here why I said it.
Enough cos ì  little in order not to strike to us.
The country of sands…
.. it is demonstrated frightening.
The winner of the fifth encounter is. Temari!
Oh, not…!
Beautiful taken.
That devil you make!
E' this the way to behave itself
with an adversary whom it has given all!
Hush!
And door that good one to null via from here!
You are calm, Lee!
- Konoha Senpou!
(Wind of the leaf)
What!
Also you six late one… just as it seems.
As it dares!
You stop It, Lee!
Gai-sensei!
Temari…
… it returns endured here.
You have already won.
Not to be l ì  to lose time
with that wretch.
What!
You have already made enough, Lee.
Boys of the sand…
… I can inform you of one what?
This boy is strong.
You council to be attention.
That crazy to attack briga
with those of the sand.
I would not want to have null to that making to us.
Here there are the all ninja strongest.
Naruto, I recommend myself!
Not to lose against those ceffi!
Sakura-chan!
Sakura-chan, you are already well?
Not preoccuparti for me.
Preoccupati for you, rather!
di..di me?
They are not hurt.>.
An other thing.
That figure you would make us if you lose now!
And with that courage you would introduce yourself to Sasuke!
In effects.>.
Then…
I wanted ringraziare to you before in order.
"you cannot!!! Sakura-chan!!!"
"You six engaged cos ì  a lot
in order to arrive end here! "
"It will be a shame if you will lose against
that only obsessed matta from Sasuke! "
If it had not been for those tifo ridicule…
… I would even have lost easy against Ino.
It can  are given!
Bastard…!
From the!
Fast! Fast!
I want my turn!
To who it touches! To who it touches!
I feel that it will touch me!
-  Nara Shikamaru VS Kin Tsuchi  -
It touches me.
Shikamaru! Not to lose!
It demonstrates to us that a six man!
-  S ì,  s ì…
You defeat the adversary with one combo from 16 blows!
(Ino is resumption in a moment.)
-  Force! Shikamaru! Vinci!
Force! Vinci!
It manipulates the shadows.
You are careful to the parts not illuminated.
I will not fall  in one technical cos ì  ridicule.
Shikamaru! It makes it to see it!
Uffa…
That annoyance...... then…
… it does not go me to fight against one girl.
Then  I will make  to end the encounter in a flash.
Even if I have understood their force
during the Second Test…
… I do not know null R-with regard to its techniques.
Moreover it has seen my technique.  But  I…
Sixth encounter.
… I can only count on…
Shikamaru against Kin
Begun!
.. this!
Sai to use only that movement?
Zitta!
Ninpou… Kage Mane not Jutsu!
(Technical of the control of the shadow!)
One technical cos ì  not ago fear…
… if I follow the movements of your shadow!
Campanellini?
That stravista strategy…
Now you will launch one attacked spit with
campanellino and an other without, just?
I would have to react to the sound of the campanellino
and to schivare the spit…
.. but not to notice me of the other
that then it will hit to me…
… True?
Enough with chiacchere!
I must be careful does not make me
to hit from according to spit.
Knowing the trick enough to make attention.
What!
They give behind!
A thread?
To the shoulders!
Too much late!
Shikamaru!
It has taken in full load.
Not, it waits for.
It watches well.
Endured Ho..ho a hard blow.
Now it touches me!
You  I will not allow.
C-Che happens!
Who listens to the sound of the campanellini has this effect.
The vibrations of this special one campanellino
it acts directly from the eardrum to the brain.
Dopodichè will show you an illusion.
Useless E'.
You cannot cover the sound of the campanellino cos ì.
You cannot…
Eternal damnation, which is that true one?
You do not succeed to move to you, eh?
You do not succeed not to think where launch
your only hope, your shadow.
Now, I will make  you  to suffer slowly.
Eternal damnation, is underrating me…
Now,  I will launch  five.
The next time, seven.
I will continue  finchè you will not seem a porcospino.
That child bugiarda.
eh?
You had said that the encounter would be ended endured.
Already. You suffer cos ì  much from wanting
to alleviate the suffering more in a hurry.
Then, I will end  to you  with these.
E' the end!
co..cosa!
Mine. body…!
Finally it has succeeded to me
the technique of the control of the shadow.
What you are saying?
Not there is no trace of your shadow…
Not you of six shrewed anchor?
It is not possible!
S ì,  that it is possible, scemotta!
Or it thinks that a thread indeed to you
to this height it had a shadow!
I succeed to manipulate liberations my shadow.
I can lengthen and shorten.
Eternal damnation, the shadow is becoming more large.
This was not the shadow of the thread.>.
Already, I have lengthened and rendered my shadow thin
making it to seem that one of the thread…
.. until to you.
Now as you mean to defeat to me?
I and you make exactly
the same movements.
Hush…
… and it observes.
Cretino!
If me attacks with that one
also you will make yourself badly!
This I know it well
What you mean to make…
We will hit ourselves to vicissitude with the shuriken.
We will see who will resist more to along!
(It was alone bleffando…)
Sunk.
Even if we make the same movements…
.. if a six ninja you would have to fight…
… holding to mind the circumstances and
the configuration of the land.
The distance of every from the wall,
it was various.
I have used the shuriken only…
… in order it does not point out you the wall of behind.
The winner is Nara Shikamaru
Evvai! Shikamaru!
A six large one!
I will be  the next one! The next one! The next one!
E' always little striking, but I must
to admit that stavolta it has made a figurone.
Eternal damnation!
I lack alone.
We pass to the next encounter.
We are remained: that one of the sound…
I, Hinata, Naruto,
Choji, Neji, Lee…
.. and those tizio of the Sand.
That it is the only one that I do not want to meet…!
Excluded she, debuttanti of this year
they seem to know the fact.
-  Uzumaki Naruto VS Inuzuka Kiba  -
Evvai! Evvai! Evvai! Evvai!
Evviva finally!
Arrived E' my turn!
That fortune!
Against of he walk will be one, Akamaru!
If  I will not be  the next one…
… Sakura-saint ciglione will call me…
… and it will hate to me!
If  I will not be  next, the Sakura-saint one…
This boy, Lee…
… he is similar he from young person.
You make of your best, Naruto.
It leaves to make me!
Hour, Naruto…
… it demonstrates to me…
… how much six become strong.
Ce I will make  it!
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
Eternal damnation!
Kiba is making the gradasso
only why they have gone to us light with he.
Yours to bark it is boring!
You stop it of give airs to you
and it uses your dog or what you want!
I do not know that training race you have made.>.
.. but I am R-he who I will become Hokage!
You will be R-he who it will come defeated and cry!
In the next Episode:
Akamaru joins to the combat!
Who will be diseredato?