Grandel checking Kyubi
we to are fighting dreamers
takami or mazashite
fighting dreamers
narifuri kamawazu
shinjiruga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
bukkorose like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
kewashii not hito shura not michi naka not
chizu wo hirogete doko and iku
gokusaishoku not class ga sore wo
ubaitotte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro memi not hiraite
shikato ima wo mikiwamero "yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa
iza mirou!
we to are fighting dreamers
takami or mezashite
fighting dreamers
narifuri kamawazu
shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
bukkorose like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
bukkorose like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire! "bam!"
Well!
We go!
You stop to scream like of the children.
Eh? I have an ugly prefeeling.
M-but. they are only to the second phase of the training!
You said that the training was divided in three parts!
And I have only exceeded the first two!
We could end the third stage walking.
Truly!
A football?
You hold.
Che cos' is this?
A simple football…
Before the stage was to make to turn the chakra.
The second one was the power.
Finally, the third stage…
Eccola!
Episode #89
The Maledizione
Eccola.... But here that what?
It seems that I am holding simply a football…
It seems!
Just nothing does not happen.
Hour you monster the same thing in the left hand.
It watches that it happens in the football.
Wow…
The chakra it turns more and more quickly…
But perfect sphere holds the shape of one…
It would seem…
A small tornado, just?
The inside of the football in your right hand…
It is  the same thing of your left hand?
Exact.
Impressive…
The chakra it turns without…
to make to move the football.
It must have more power and speed
of when I made to explode the football.
It listens well, the third stage
it speeds up all  that  that you have learned.
In other words, you must increase
spin and the power of yours chakra…
And you must concentrates and to maintain
all within the football.
I have understood!
Therefore, I make to roteare the chakra
like for the previous exercise,
and I do not have to make to explode the football.
I see that beginnings to understand.
But to what serves me all this?
I will show  to you  why.
It watches carefully.
Once learned first and
second stage, the result is this.
Hour, when you succeed to dominate
this third stage…
The result is this!
If you can control this small tornado,
the power will not be dispersed.
More it will turn quickly, plus the power will increase.
And enormous damages can be caused.
Well, this is…
Perfect… I can make it!
OK… goes well…
Now!
It remains here…
I must hold it…
I must hold it!
Not rilasciarlo.
You must use the maximum of the spin
and of the power without to make to explode the football.
You are joking…
I cannot, I do not succeed in
to control all the my power
I am beginning to understand the third phase.
It is  of a completely different level!
You I had said.
It is  much difficult one,
technical Ninja of high level is one.
Much good, the explanation is ended.
We will train ourselves walking.
Ehi, ehi!
Because we must ourselves be sbrigare…
We have lost already enough time
in order it makes you to resume.
We do not know how much will remain in Tsunade city
Which thing? But! But!?
Neither if we will have to meet an old friend
in order to make four to chiacchere.
We go!
S ì…
E' from much time that… Orochimaru.
I have tried to you wherever.
Which thing you want from me?
You cannot have come quà in order to speak about the old times.
I have a small favor to ask to you.
Of you strike yourself irregular…
Its ace is pale…
It must be much exausting…
And these arms…
Tsunade-sama,
I suppose that already you have understood.
It finds qualcun' other to you. I do not practice to more the medicine.
This is not possible.
You have understood how much this wound is deep.
Nobody  can  recover it…
Except for the specialist doctor of the three Sannin Leggendari… Tsunade-sama.
You are the only one to being able to recover it.
This wound on your arms… is not one common wound.
It must be I seal secret
or one maledizione…
Which thing you have made in order to deserve it?
What I have made?
A small  gift is right that I have received when I have killed Sandaime
Six… truly…
Not to have this scared air.
Every thing is destined to collapse.
The same one is worth for the persons…
You would have to know it also.
He remembers, you have left to you to die the two persons who you loved more.
The two persons whom she loved more?
I see that…
you have in mind a cruel plan.
Exact…  It is  a orribile way to die.
Tu!!
Needles poison to you?
Fast E'!
You take this!
Lascerò  not to pass  to you!
You are Shizune calm!
This subordinate clause.... is strong.
Orochimaru.
Six not changed
You know to me… not to play with me.
Strongly…
Frightful E'.
Single it… must be.
Tsunade does not have truly no patience, knows…
Ehi Naruto, is not the moment to make the imbecille.
If not us sbrighiamo, it will still disappear, you know it not?
Ehi! Ero-Sennin!
This is the speech kind that a master holds its disciple
that ago of its best in order to improve?
It calm to you, of hour in then Tsunade is more important than you.
Which thing tells?
Ero-Sennin it has come on purpose in order to meet this Ninja woman,
Tsunade.
I ask who is.
I hope to find it soon.
We are not here in order to fight.
We have come to negotiate.
To negotiate?
S ì.
Not tried to take to me in turn!
Ve I have already said it, levatevi of I return.
We cannot.
Disappeared.
You are the only one that puo to recover the arms of Orochimaru-sama.
We are not saying that it will be an unilateral contract,
We make an agreement.
It would be better for you to disappear before that it has counted until 5.
Otherwise…
I will kill  to you.
You calm yourselves, ve I pray some. It will not be an ugly agreement.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
I can resuscitare your brother and the man who you loved.
With one technical prohibited that I have developed.
You have not still killed us.
That  means that we can make an agreement?
I know this woman.
Truly?
S ì.
It has said that it went to recover us ò  that it had lost qu ì.
It upsets some.... To be able.... I must push them to the maximum and must stop them.
Ehi child,
It would go you to play  a Pò?
It was here?
Ok… You choose two numbers, one equal and one uneven, the par is called
"cho", while that odd number is called "han ".
Zitto.
They are in full training. You stop to disturb to me.
But about that it speaks, this is a game.
Not to play with this football, plays with these.
Pff not! I do not have just the time to play with these dice.
Like six boring child!
Been zitto!
Then, where he is?
You will not free of charge have this news in a casino.
We play, if you win  I will speak, if you lose,
you will have to pay 1000 ryos to me.
Much good!
You choose: "cho" or "han."
Oh, therefore…
My age is an equal number, then…
Cho!
If it is "han"  I will win. Well, we see.
Oh not! Two and five make "han!"
Che cos' is this?
1000  ryos…
Beautiful tempismo, Naruto!
One would say that it has won.
Eternal damnation… I have still failed.
It remains to the inside…
Where  it can  be?
Maledizione, I am turning to empty…
Mmh… I?
One lotteria?
The adults, the children, all love the lotterie.
You will have soon turns out to you, then you want to try your fortune?
Six prettier when if full of moneies.
Impossible, only with a ticket of the lotteria…
Enough he is equipped for this kind of things.
To the contrary of the techniques. However....
Where puo to be Tsunade?
He would not have to be far.
Creed that  I will go  to watch lassù.
This city is constructed around to a castle…
Therefore we must go up…
Naruto, here!
You would not want to meet them of new… Tsunade?
Nawaki, Dan.
If  I will recover  your arms, what you will make?
I dislike mentirti, task that I will say   the truth to you.
Ehi, ehi… dov' is the castle?
Not there is…
I will obtain that  that I wish…
This time,  I will end  what I have begun, the destruction of Konoha.
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete
Listened now! Who is this Sennin?
Who is this Leggendario Ninja? And who is the specialist doctor?
This person is the new Hokage? You stop to say these things!
Speeches of Third and the Quarter in front of me…
It does not interest to me to know if she is the candidate for being Fifth....
I will beat!
Next Episode:
The temper is exploded!
Not you dimentich erò!