http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
Where
they are?
Who six you?
They are I from small?
!
Pap and mother did not have to die.
They were all assassinated
why I did not have enough force.
The clan was exterminated.
The definitive formation!
Ino - Shika - Chou!!!
Ino!
Why?
I do not want that you are the only one to make
beautiful figure in front of Sasuke-kun!
They kick up a row alone.
The bugs of Konoha
they are intromessi of new!
But what jumps to you in mind!
These tizi are too much dangerous!
E' a scocciatura, but goes made.
Hour that Ino has been made ahead
we men cannot at all scappare.
Excused if I am involved to you.
However we are one square
and we will share it together.
Well. He goes as he goes.
Not! I do not want to die!
He leaves the scarf me!
Taci! And you end it to churn to you!
If you want you of it you can go
ciccione.
That what has said!
They are not successful to feel well.
For Chouji that word is taboo.
If it repeats it of new
I have said that if you want you can hide
behind the trees
ciccione imbecille!
I am not ciccione!!!
They are only sturdy!!!!
It lives the sturdy boys!!!
(Oh wow)
Well! Understood that this is one war
between Konoha and the Sound, true!
Well, it has been scaldato.
Uffa. That annoyance!
The annoyance is only ours.
Merda! It has been ordered to kill
Sasuke before the aim of the examination.
Sasuke-kun
Sakura.
You take cure of those two.
The square of Ino will fight
with all its force!
Received!
Ino Formation!
Shika!
Chou!
Vai, Chouji!
OK!
Baika not Jutsu!
(Technical of the Expansion!)
And one combat style
body to body of Konaha
!
That technical ridicule!
Six solo a ciccione imbecille that it rolls.
Cutting Wave.
It cannot  be!
E' jumped in air!
With that spin the air pressure
of the cutting Wave it does not have effect.
If you used the supersonic waves
my boneses would be fallen apart
if you touched it directly.
Scordatelo!
Moreover you the six that most dangerous one.
Ninpou:
Kage Mane Jutsu!
* (Technical of the Control of the Shadow)
My body
Dosu! What you are making!
It must be the technique of the Tie of Shadow!
Ino, hour is your moment.
Ok! Shikamaru, I entrust you my body.
!
Ninpou:Shintenshin not Jutsu!
(Technical of the Spiritual Capovolgimento!)
Eccomi
Maledizione!
Kin!
What happens!
You are deals to you.
If you move, this morir Kin.
If you want to be withdrawn
left the coil and you go yourselves some from here.
I will free  when  I do not perceive
more yours chakra!
Why they are laughing
Chouji!
Not! Careful they want
Ino!
I have nausea
Che infami!
To hurt one your companion.
You have been imprudent.
Our scope is not one stupid coil
and neanche to pass to the examination respecting the rules.
What!
The objective is Sasuke-kun.
Oh
They are to the limit!
I see that your technique  cannot
to be used in order more than 5 minuteren.
It is not the technique of the Tie of Shadow
it is the technique of the Control of the Shadow.
And the technique of that girl
it seems that works threading
while in an other people's body.
To judge from the blood to the mouth,
it seems that killing Kin morirebbe also she.
You would kill a your companion?
If necessary we will make it.
E' the end.
Merda!
There were nearly. By now prendavate to us.
You have lowered the guard.
That pain.
Some simple ones ninja of the Sound
that they pose from vincitori fighting
against our esordienti.
What?
They are
of the square of Lee-saint.
Lee!
He seems that he is in the troubles.
They continue to exit like scarafaggi.
That boy from hats to caschetto
he is a our companion
How you have dared?
What its eyes are those!
E' like if it could see all with those!
If you want to continue to fight
we will participate with all our force.
What happens, Neji?
Che Chakra is never this?
If you have something in contrary
you come down instead of give airs to you.
Not!
Task ce will not be need.
If
you do not have the power
you cannot make null!
I was not strong and were all assassinated!
Not! You left them to die.
You left them to die.
If you only had the force!
Sasuke-kun! Six resumed to you!
That one is
Sasuke-kun!
Sakura!
Who has reduced to you
cos ?
The cursed brand has covered its body.
Sasuke-kun your body
Not to worry to you.
The important is that I feel to traboccare
of being able my body.
I am well.
E' be he to donate it to me.
Eh?
Finally I have understood it.
I am a vendicatore.
Also to obtain the power
I would entrust my body to the devil.
I have understood.
Just as I thought.
The bruise on the neck of which Sakura spoke,
it was the cursed brand.
But
that been strange that one stands in feet.
Sakura, dimmelo!
Who devil has hurt to you?
They have been I!
Ino!
You will get confused with the enemy if you remain cos !!
It returns in your body!
Chouji, you come here.
We go to hide to us.
Ok, ok!
To arrival!
Issolution!
Well, six returned.
Shikamaru
that it is happening?
As I make to know it!
Q that one is!
E' too much strongly!
We cannot compete!
Its Chakra
it is immense!
Dosu! It does not make you to scare from those moribondo!
Not, stopped Zaku!
You do not understand!
I will kill  them  all!!
I will end  in a moment!
Cutting Advanced Wave!
I have reduced to pieces!
To pieces who?
Zaku!
Che velocita.
Moreover, it has put in but also the others two.
Katon!
(Element of the Fire!)
Housenka!
(Fire of the Fenice!)
Not to mount the head to you!
The detention as I want!
What!
There were of the Shuriken in the fire!
Zaku! Under of you!
The chakra it is completely various from its.
E' truly sasuke-kun?
But what has happened to it?
It seems proud being of yours
arms!
Stopped!
Sasuke-kun, will come to try to me.
Six remained single you.
At least it tries makes me to amuse more!
It cannot  be true.
It cannot  be true!
The Sasuke-kun that I know!
FERMATIII!!!
Enough!
Please.
Stopped.
The cursed brand st disappearing.
They have been fortunate.
Sasuke-kun!
Six fort.
Sasuke-kun.
Hour we will not never succeed to strike to you.
Please it leaves us to go for hour.
This like riconoscenza.
We have many questions
and we must verify what we know.
In exchange I promise one what to you.
If we will have to fight a second one
time in this examination
we will not escape any we will hide.
It waits for!
Who Is Orochimaru?
Cos' has made Sasuke-kun?
Why to Sasuke-kun?
I do not know it.
We had only the order
to kill Sasuke-kun.
You ordered us to assassinate Sasuke-kun
and to instead you anticipated us.
Instead killing it you have left
the cursed brand.
What never will have in mind!?
Hey, been well?
E' one Ino annoyance.
But  occupied of Lee.
Sure!
Its Chakra is abnormal.
The force of the Uchiha clan
it is beyond my acquaintances.
Sakura-chan, watches to me!
Not to worry to you, you  protegger.
What we must make with he!
We wake up to soccer!
Can make it I?
What and succeeded to me
Sasuke-kun
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
What happens, Akamaru?
It waits for, Naruto.
It is being behaved in strange way.
What is starved?
Not creed propio.
What wants to make one walk?
I have understood, is trying some pole.
It has bitten to me!!!
In the next episode: Scared Akamaru!
The exceptional ability of Gaara.