NaruTeaM Presenta:
http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
Muori.
Cursed!!!
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
(Technical Advanced of the Multiplication of the Body)
Oooh, the advanced technique of the multiplication of the body…
… and cos ì  many cloni you have created.
You take this!
I knew that it was impossible.
Pu ò  not to strike itself like he!
We have only this way in order to defeat it!
Sasuke!
I have understood, Naruto!
Optimal idea!
From you me I did not wait for.
Fuuma Shuriken…
… the Shadow of the Wind!
The Shuriken does not work on me!
Capisco.
You have aimed at the true body…
… for ò…
… not of six to the height!
An other Shuriken hidden from the shadow of the first one!
E' the technique of * the Shadow Shuriken.
* Shuriken d' Ombra
E' too much close in order to avoid it!
For ò…
… he is not still sufficient.
It has avoided!
E' my moment!!!
Kakashi, C$r-he who uses the Sharingan.
Cursed Plump child!!!
Kakashi-sensei!
Naruto…
Your plan has been impressive.
Six improved a lot.
I have used the Advanced Multiplication of the Body…
… in order to hide the fact to me it are transformed
in a Shuriken and I have not made it in order to strike Zabuza.
I have left one of my copies
and Shuriken is transformed me in one.
Then my copy has launch to me, under shape of Shuriken,
towards Sasuke.
Sasuke!
Sasuke has become account that I was
I in the moment that it has seized to me…
… then it has overlapped me to its Shuriken…
… and it has used the technique of the Shadow Shuriken.
Fuuma Shuriken…
… the Shadow of the Wind!
They are hidden to me in the shadow of the true Shuriken,
and they are directed to me towards the true Zabuza…
Obviously I did not think to strike it cos ì…
… but it was enough to me only to melt
the incantesimo of the prison.
I knew of being able to avoid the water copy
and cos ì  it has gone all perfectly!
Only fortune.
Fortune?
For ò, to succeed to work in square in one similar situation…
… they could also die.
I have lost the patience
and I have melted the water prison.
Not! You have not melted it, but…
… it has been cancelled.
I perceive to you that the same technique
it does not work on me two times.
What now you will make?
Sakura, we do not lower the guard.
Sharingan!
Suiton Suiryuudan not Jutsu!!
(Technical of I dredge aquatic)
All those positions in cos ì  little time…
… and to moreover it has copied them perfectly.
But cos' it is? Also this is one technical ninja?
Something does not go… What is happening!
One supposes that the Sharingan is an ability with which
memorizzi the techniques from the contrary, until copying it…
… for ò…
Suiton Suiryuudan not Jutsu!!
… it has used the technique in the same moment.
For case he…
(Cursed Bastard…!)
Stà muovendo in the same way!
And in perfect way!
What stà happening, Sasuke-kun?
It is copying perfectly…
… all mine movements.
What! Law pure my thoughts!
Bastard… has indeed…
One disgustoso, true look?
You do not make other that to copy. And one copy…
… pu ò  not to strike it originates it them!
Clown!
To close you ò  that one cursed boccaccia!
Not six other that one copy!
But that one…!
… they are I!
Not pu ò  being.
It is using one technical illusory?
Suito Daibakufu not Jutsu!!
(Technical of the aquatic outbreak)
What!
Impossible!!!
They are I that I have begun the technique, for ò…!
… they are not successful to stargli behind!
This is fine yours.
But why?
You can see the future?
…
… and you morirai.
Dead E' truly…
In effects it is died.
Many thanks.
For a long time I waited for the propitious moment in order to kill Zabuza.
That mask indicates…
… that you must be ninja a hunter
of the village of the fog.
You are a lot very informed.
Ninja a hunter?
You do not know neanche who is a hunter?
You must have learned it to the academy.
The hunters…
… esiliati are those who kill the ninja, like Zabuza…
… that for some reason it has been put against its village.
They make in order protect the secrets of just the village.
Enough simple E'.
You would have to study more.
Exact, they are a member of the unit ninja that it chases the esiliati ones.
From the height and the voice would not have to be
larger than Naruto and the others…
… nevertheless she is already ninja a hunter.
He is not sure a normal boy.
Who you creeds of being!!
Who six!
It calm Naruto to you, is not an enemy.
St ò  not saying this.
For ò…!
Zabuza… one cos ì  strongly like Zabuza…
… it has been killed.
For ò  it has been killed cos ì  easy…
… from a boy not much various one from me!
We have made ourselves…
… the figure of the deficient ones!
I cannot accept it!!!
I understand that you cannot believe to us.
For ò…
… also this is the truth.
In the world, there are also children smaller than you…
… that they are also more forts than me.
For the moment your battle ends here.
I must go to arrange the corpse.
E' a full body of secrets.
If you excuse to me.
Disappeared E'!
Not here…
Why it has succeeded this!?
To what…
… we are you use!?
Naruto…
Maledizione! Maledizione! Maledizione!
Maledizione!!!
They succeed things of the sort when one is of the ninja
If it does not appeal to to you, arranges it the next time.
However our mission still is not ended.
We must escort Tazuna-saint to house its.
Me dispiace for all, children.
You will be able yourselves to be rested all to house mine!
Courage, on with the moral and we go.
BUT…
What happens?
Kakashi-sensei…
Kakashi-sensei!!!
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain…
… never coming down.
Break into the contents…
… never falling down.
My knee is still shaking…
… like the was twelve…
Sneaking out of the classroom…
… by the back door.
To man railed at twice me though…
… but didn' t the beloveds.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don' t try to live I know wise.
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears…
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end.
Don' t try to live I know wise.
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears…
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end.
Don' t try to live I know wise.
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears…
What we must make? What we must make?
The Kakashi master is svenuto…
And bulli de the Gatoh chissa if they continue to try to us!
Task that ce we must cavare alone!
I do not know if this training will make us to become stronger, but…
It is being made interesting!
Finally, I am becoming stronger!
NEl next episode, the forest of the Chakra.
Avr ò  a part a lot important this time!