http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
Why six returned?
Although it is from that we do not look at ourselves
six a lot bearing away.
Six returned in order to assassinate Hokage-sama?
Not, not.>.
I do not have men for that one still enough.
I thought to recruit of someone
in this village.
I have already donated to a boy
I seal equal yours, you know?
There is a boy who I want.
Egoist, like always.
That morir boy.
Vero!
The possibilities to survive are 1 on 10
but as you it could make it us.
It must appeal to this boy indeed to you!
Six gelosa?
Ce you still have it with me why
I have taken advantage of to you and abandoned?
With the exception of you,
it seems skillful indeed.
Of other part he has inherited
the blood of the Uchiha clan.
And it is also much beautiful one.
Perfect for being my successor.
If that sopravviver boy
we will see some of the beautiful ones.
I recommend myself, not to suspend the examination.
There are also three members of my village.
I want just to enjoy it.
Know that if someone will intralcer to me
it will be the end of the village of Konoha.
We have lost average day
to try food and water.
Many squares now are resting.
E' the moment to attack.
We begin the recognition of the area
and it is that we will find or less
of the other squares
we will return here.
You have understood?
Okay.
Roger!
Of agreement
We go!
Platonic Sopracciglione:
You  protegger  until death!!
I cannot now addormentarmi.
I must proteggerli both.
I have slept indeed well!
Naruto!
Sasuke-kun!
Six taken cure to you of we.
Thanks, Sakura-chan!
Thanks to you, now I am well!
E' be an honor.
The prede they would have to always make
of their best for scappare
when the predator chases to them.
I do not succeed to speak!
An incubus
E' already mattino?
It cannot  be
One scoiattolo?
Diamine! That fright.
Nothing does not escape it!
It is shrewed of the cartabomba on the scoiattolo?
Not! Not creed.
What you would want to say?
Probably we will know it when
we will arrive near.
From
we go.
Of agreement!
There are twenty leaves.
If  I will succeed  to take them all
before that they fall to earth
Sakura innamorer of me!
And if
instead me of scapper also one only
mine it will be a love not corresponded.
In more
"Sopracciglione!"
it will always call to me in order in that way!
One, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
nine, [ ] eighteen
dician....
nine
Still one!
But that one....
As soon as in time.
This is one bomb paper
that it explodes with a timer.
Who has made one orribile what cos  ?
You do not hide! You come outside!
And also we are hidden in time!
Boys ci we are made to discover from the mistaken person.
The strategy "caviamocela hiding there" is failed!
We pass to plan two!
What? We must make it indeed?
Why, you have some problem?
It would have to work!
But still....
But it watches! I would not have never believed to meet
here the genius of the slid year, Hyuga Neji.
I can have an autograph?
Ah, you are boys....
Here made, it will remain hit from my fascination!
I have always wished to intercross yours sguardo
Disappeared.
Why they have not succeeded in sedurlo!
This makes me to incazzare! eternal damnation!
You say to me, the fact you aims me the fist against
it means that you want to defy to me?
Sure N not that not
Well, then goodbye!
To obtain the coil from codardi like you
it would make me to become the zimbello of the village.
Sure!
Scappano like rats!
As I thought
a boy as it would have taken to us
the single coil if we had provoked it.
Perfect, now we try a rammoliti team of!
Not there are squares more insufficient than we.
You have made the guard all the night?
Calm, it is not more necessary.
Sasuke Alarm clock!
We want to fight against of he!
These boys!
But what been saying!
Qual' is your scope?
I know that you are to the dependencies of Orochimaru!
Cos' is this strange brand
on the neck of Sasuke-kun?
You are that gliel' you have made
and now you want to fight it?
I ask what is planning that man.
But  after what we have felt
we cannot leave to go it.
I make outside this girl
and I make also that Sasuke outside.
He waits for, Zaku!
Huh? And why?
Not six for nothing good
Rivangata earth of recent
and of various color.
And then this type of grass
it does not grow on this land.
The traps do not have sense
if they are succeeded to see.
Pft, stupid.
Therefore those kunai served in order to remove
the scoiattolo from the trap.
We kill it.
A log!?
An other trap over?
Oh not!
Sure Beh
Frankly you do not have no talent.
As you it would have to be engaged more!
konoha sempu!
It is....
Then also you
you would have to be engaged more!
Who six you?
The fantastic green fury of Konoha
Rock Lee!
You make what here us?
I
I always join when it finds to you in the troubles.
Instead it has been alone thanks to you.
Now, you go.
But now, they are a your enemy.
You I have already said.
I you  protegger  until death.
We exit entirety!
Proteggero you to cost of my life!
Thanks.
! Fact! Fact!
I have made blow, Gai-sensei!
Oh of agreement.
Zaku, you can have Sasuke.
I  will kill  they.
Sakura is not in condition for fighting.
That sopracciglione is an expert in taijutsu.
It will be a lot amusing.
There is something behind your attacks, true?
I will not put myself  to schivarli.
I have already seen your attacks before.
This boy
he is truly strong.
Three against one are hard.
I will have  to risk
and to make using them outside all my forces.
No square does not find itself
that she seems to our capacity.
As I have already said
the only group more weak person
of we it is that one of Naruto.
Idiot! But what you go raving?
Why?
Naruto and Sakura, of sure are of losing
but with they there is the super Sasuke-kun genius!
I would not know.
In the true and own combats
also that genius is not a granch.
What?
Okay, okay. Me spiace to have to you offeso.
Cazz.....che breach of scato them.
One gets angry as soon as a po' speaks badly about Sasuke.
Not there is way that Sasuke-kun can lose!
Naturally for Sakura it is an other speech!
Sasuke has been put to carpet!
And Sakura is fighting.
What
Lee is in delay.
That strange. E' a type much punctual one.
It will not have for met case of the enemies?
And if for case!
Task is improbable.
We go to try Lee.
Of agreement.
! To the end there is I have made it!
You are calm! Lee, not to celebrate too much!
Lee is only the able one of padroneggiare
this technique.
Yahoo!
Hey Lee
There is I have made it! There is I have made it!
Lee!
Evvai! !
Hey!
It lend attention to what I must dirti!
What is?
This technique of the loto
it will be one technical forbidden of hour in then.
What you want to say?
This technique subjects to
great effort your muscular fibers.
Practically it is one technical kills.
Normally the human being uses alone 20%
of the force that really possesses.
If it used 100% of its force
the muscles would be destroyed alone.
For this the used power
it comes limited from the brain.
But  this technique eliminates through
chakra the limits you set up from the brain
cos   you can execute the taijitsu
to high speed.
In practical it is one technical dangerous that it is based
on I use of all the force available.
Therefore it uses this technique
to one single condition.
Which condition?
It listens carefully.
You will be able to use it when
Gai-sensei
I am in order to use those jutsu
inasmuch as now
it is the moment protect who I love!
E' scomparso!
We have not still ended!
Cos   will not be able to proteggersi!
E' in the troubles!
You take this!
* Omote Renge
(Frontal Loto)
That strange feeling.
But it thinks
ce I have made it hardly in time.
Impossible!
That technical terrifying.
Of risento equally the effects.
Now it is my turn.
Maledizione! It is put badly.
My body is still
Lee-saint!
Your movements are to high speed
but we exceed them with the speed of sound.
I will show  you  a limit that your engagement
he will not be able to never make you to exceed.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII