Here Sasuke, is in the B point.
Here Sakura, has arrived in point C.
Here Naruto, in position in the point To.
Six too much slow one, Naruto!
Well, group 7…
Eh!
The objective moves.
Well, it is l ì.
Distance from the objective?
5 meters!
They are ready in order to enter in action.
Also I.
Ok…
Gone!
Taken!
It has a tape on the skillful ear?
E' our objective, Tora? (tiger)
E' without doubt the target.
Ok!
"Operation Tora recovery, the mascotte smarrita" completed.
Not there is no mission
more exciting that we can make!
Important Mission! Towards the Country of the Waves!
Oh, mine adored Tora-chan.
I was a lot preoccupied for you!
Moglie of the Sr. Fudal of the Country of the Fire.
Madam Shijimi & Tora.
Hi hi! Cos ì  learns, gattaccio!
Now I understand because it escaped…
Well!
The next mission of group 7 of Kakashi is…
… to cure the child of Yojyu-sama… (old test)
… to help it in the purchases until the near city…
… and to help it to collect potatoes.
NOT!!!
Not thanks! Now enough!
I want to make missions impegnative!
They give qualcos' other to us!
It has not twisted…
Che rompiscato them!
I previewed that it would be complained.
Stupid! Six solo a novellino!
All how many must inziare with simple missions,
in order to acquire experience!
For ò.>.! For ò.>.!
… lately you have assigned only painful missions to us!
Stà a po' zitto.
Naruto!
It seems that it is necessary that what explains you is the missions.
It listens! Every day many demands to the village arrive.
From that one of baby-sitter to that one of assassin.
There is an immense assortment of missions
that they come classified with the degrees…
… To B C & D, second of the difficulties.
In the village the ninja they come subdivided
to second of their abilities…
leaving from me and arriving to Jonin, Chunin and Genin.
Advanced we distribute the missions
to the ninja that they have the abilities adapted.
And if door to good aim the mission,
we embed the compensation from the customer
You are Genin from little, for this the missions…
… of D rank they are adapted you.
… and inasmuch as yesterday I have eaten the tonkotsu ramen,
today taking ò  of miso… (zuppa of pig)
He listens to me!!!
Me… me dispiace!
It always makes me foretells, old.
But I am not more the dispettoso child who tasks!
Uhm…!!
To take ? one  to me beautiful curried.
He watches as the child has grown
that he could only express itself to jokes.
He goes well!
Ah?
Inasmuch as you insist…
… compirete one mission of degree C.
One mission of protection of one sure person.
Indeed!
Who is? Who is?
Of a Daimyo! Or of one prince!
Not to churn to you…
… now you I introduce.
Entrances for courtesy…
What? They are only mocciosi!
Ehi! I say you, dwarf with the face from dumb…
… a six truly ninja?
And who would be the dwarf with the face from dumb?
I kill to you!!!
You would want to kill the getlteman
what you must protect? Stupid!
They are the great constructor of bridges, Tazuna.
You will make me from guard risking yours
life until not completer ò  the bridge of my country!
Aaaaahh!!!
Departure!
Pu ò  to know because it churns you a lot?
Because they are not never exited from the village.
Ehi! Six sure one that there is gives
to trust itself this child!
I do not preoccupy myself, you accompagner  ? also…
… that they are a Jonin.
we figure ourselves if this rincretinito…
but we figure ourselves if this rincretinito…!!
Peggior the customer… that schifo!
Now I make to see it…
Old Ehi, you would not have to underrate a ninja!
It watches that I am a large one!
They are a ninja best
and a day verr ò  name Hokage!
My name is Uzumaki Naruto!
You would better make to remember it!
The Hokage is the better one ninja of the village?
Not creed that as you it can inhale a lot.
Taci! I am ready to whichever hard work in order to become it!
When he will happen, also you will be
forced to recognize my bravura!
It not to never make ò , moccioso.
Neanche when you are Hokage.
I kill to you!
And you stop it, dumb!
Not and not!
It leaves it to me until when it is not one sogliola!
Ehi, Tazuna-Saint…
What is?
It is original of the Country of the Waves, true?
S ì, and with this?
Kakashi-sensei, is ninja in that country?
Not, not there are ninja, but in kind in the other countries s ì.
The other states even have various culture and customs…
… but they comprise a village ninja.
The villages of the ninja are represented you of the military power…
… of the country to which they belong....
… and they consequently serve also to discourage
the adjacent countries from eventual aggressions.
The villages ninja, for ò, are not
directly host controls to you from the country…
… and they boast therefore an independent government.
The island of the Country of the Waves and other small be insulari, do not have a threat directed from other countries.
Perci ò  does not have need of the villages ninja.
Between several the villages ninja those
of the Leaf, Fog, Cloud, Sand and Cliff…
… they are largest and powerful that together
they take the name of "Five Great Lands of the ninja".
Country of the Fire: Secret village of Konoha.
Country of the Water: Secret village of the Fog.
Country of the Beam: Secret village of Cloud.
Country of the Wind: Secret village of the Sand.
Country of the Earth: Secret village of the Cliff.
In these countries the best one ninja only comes name "Kage".
Hokage, Mizukage, Raikage, Kazekage and Tsuchikage,
that is the five Kage…
… they are the ninja that the others ninja of the world reign on all.
Wow! Hokage-sama is indeed unparalleled!
That calm vecchietto would be cos ì  strong?
Me it does not seem true!
He must be a bale… s ì, a bale!
Ehi!
You doubted all of Hokage-sama, true?
But not to worry to you. We will not have ourselves to be defended
from others ninja in one mission of level C.
Little evil. I was preoccupied from a possible one
crash with of the ninja foreign.
But và! Ah Ah Ah!
Ah!
Thing…!
Outside the first one!
Here the second…
It is not detached!
Incredible!
Are… it is arriving!
I must make it us…
I must make it us!
Been behind getlteman!
Ehi!
Kakashi-sensei!
Alive E'!
That exhibitionist!
Therefore, what…
Kakashi-sensei has used the Technique of the Substitution.
Naruto, scusami if I have not helped you endured.
You six hurt for guilt mine.
I did not think that you bloccassi for cos ì  little.
I have escaped…
Tu Sasuke six state Bravo.
Sakura, also you.
I… they are not successful to make nothing…
… instead Sasuke has not had fear…
… although it was its first true crash.
It has not changed expression and not
it is not soiled the dressed ones. Indeed, it has also saved me.
Ehi!
You are well…
… fifone?
Sasuke!!!
Naruto!
There is of the poison on their claws.
You must be become disinfected to more soon.
That?
It must open the wound
and to remove the poisoned blood.
Not to move to you too much, otherwise
you will put in circulation the poison.
, on purpose Tazuna-saint…
Cos…
… What is?
I must speak a moment to you.
I presume that they are Chunin of the Village of the Fog…
Famous Sono ninja because they continue
to fight in whichever situation.
For they it does not count the number of the victims.
How you have made to preview our attack?
In one beautiful day like this…
… when it is from days that piove,
not there are puddles.
Why you have made to fight the children if you knew it?
If you had it intentional, I would have eliminates them to you in a moment…
… for ò....
… I had need of knowing…
… who was the objective of the enemy.
What you want to say?
In practical, if the target…
… you were…
… or one of we ninja.
Tazuna-sama, you have not said to us null
on the fact to be taken of sight they give of the ninja.
The content of the demand was simply
the protection from bandit and pregifts…
… but cos ì  this becomes one mission of advanced level.
You have asked to us for proteggervi until when
the bridge would not have been completed....
… but if the enemies are of the ninja, without doubt
the mission would go placed to the expensive B level.
Your behavior will have of the reasons,
for ò  you put to us in difficulty if mentite in the demand.
Now we are completely outside mission.
We are not still ready for this assignment.
Lasciamo to lose!
We have also need of the anesthesia in order to open
the wound of Naruto and to remove the poison.
We will have to return to the village and to consult a doctor.
A pie after the other.
We return to the village and medichiamo Naruto.
Because there is all this difference!
Because always I create problems!
Maledizione!
Naruto, than what you are making!
I am becoming more and more strong…
… I have completed one mission behind the other
and I train myself alone in the techniques.
I swear that not to make me ò  never more to help!
I swear that not me spaventer ò  or scapper ò  more!
And I swear that not sar ò  inferior to Sasuke!
I swear on the pain that I have to the left hand!
With this kunai protegger ò  the old one!
The continuous mission!
Naruto, goes well to remove the poisoned blood, but…
… if it continues cos ì  morirai dissanguato.
It will be better than firm the blood fastly.
NOOO! NOT! NOT! NOT!
NOOO! NOT! I cannot die cos ì!
They give the hand to me.
It helps me!
Naruto! A six self-destructionist!
E' masochismo yours!
The wound is already healing.
Sai.. I… I…
Uhm?
… to survive ò?
You have a too much serious face.
You will see that all good will go.
E' just the power of the Vixen to nine tails.
You have failed!
I have spold understanding them in order to engage to you,
because I have felt that you were ninja valid!
It complains to you too much.
The next time you ammazzer ò  I,
with mine mannaia.
Six sure one to make it us?
Also it has assumed a ninja of a sure level!
In more, after the attack of the Siblings Devil,
they will be all in guard.
For who you have taken to me?
I am Zabuza Momochi, called…
… the Demon of the Fog!