http://naruteamplus.alterista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Siii! Also in the mission
today sar   I dredge!
The examination from Chuunin!
Good Sakura-chaaan day!
Uffa of new!
From when they are returns to you from the country of the Waves
these two are a po' strange.
I feel myself to uneasiness
You come Kakashi-sensei soon!
Cursed!
Good day boys!
Sapete today is lost to me for road.
Hey, hey, Kakashi-sensei!
We of group seven lately
we have only easy missions!
Not more stimulant is something.
Much more exciting one!?
One hotter mission
where it can express my ardor.
my passion!?
S , s , s  I have understood what you want to say.
In all the missions ago always beautiful figure
and all the space removes me.
But it will not succeed more
Rompiscatole
Today I would want propio
MPF! Six propio one ball to the foot.
dirgli one what of the sort!!!
Hey Naruto, what you are making?
We leave!
Siii!!!
Seccato to me! It plants urlare!
I cannot lose against Sasuke.
Ehy, you
Eh?
IH, mrs....
I have torn all the erbaccia.
Eh?
What happens?
These are not erbacce
Eh?
This is the garden that I was cultivating!
Ahia!!!
That someone me aids!
Stupid
Hey, from this part.
- Field of Traps -
Not to enter.
We go, you hold it
Bha, stupid.
It has intentional he to take the dog more large.
Asp waits for, waits for
This is the field of the traps!
This happens why it exaggerates.
Six propio one ball to the foot.
Sasukeee!!!
If still churns you I give you
the grace blow!
Lately the spirit
of square he is dissolving himself.
They are of agreement!
And what it is compromising the job
of square six you Sasuke!
Circles always to put to you in extension!
That one six you, cretino.
If you do not want it are to me inferior
enough that it becomes more strongly than me.
It seems that they go less of agreement than before.
Maledizione, than nervous.
Outside from the village there are
tantissimi ninja more forts than me
and I am here to lose time
with missions ridicules!
Well!
In order today we have ended.
Now I must deliver the relationship
of this mission.
Then me I go some.
Eeeh!
Sasuke-kun, aspettaaa!
You feel why
we do not go
to deepen entirety
the square job?
Six equal one to Naruto.
- Equal to Naruto -
If you have time to lose with me why
you do not go to exercise to you in some technique!
For sincere being, your abilities are
inferiors to those of Naruto.
- Inferior to Naruto -
It has reason.
In whichever mission
they are that one that contributes little.
Sakura-chan!
It leaves to lose Sasuke and we train ourselves
we two entirety!
The master is disappeared.
He has intentional to leave us single?
Would want to pass for one cliff!?
One cliff squared with two holes cos ?
Truly impossible E'!
I had not mistaken to judge to you!
Merits indeed of being mine avail again.
Hey
We have used too much powder.
With the femminilit of one woman
the girl of the group ninja senior, Moegi.
The factorial decomposition fascinates me.
Udooon.
The brilliant one ninja
number one of the village
Konohamaru!
We three form the army of Konohamaru!
Just as I imagined.
Konohamaru & company.
Eh?
Why you have
those glance at them?
In homage to your old one look.
Oooh
What means Oooh?
Lately your reactions
they are a po' cold.
Then?
What you want?
You see that coldness.
Head
Now six free one?
Not, hour I go to train to me!
What!? You had said that today
it plays to make the ninja to you with we!
Truly?
If game with they
dovr   stargli behind all the day.
That sense has that a true one
ninja you play to make the ninja?
What is?
And I would be inferior here to this?
When me gurda in those
way me renders nervous.
Head, who is this girl?
He is watching like
if he wanted to kill it.
Six best about that I thought
Ah?
It is
your girl?
A six child many perspicacityes.
BUT NOOO!!!
Head!
Why you have made it!
Oh not head!
Its wrist its wrist
Six one racchia!
Six one witch!
You are Konohamaru-kun well?
That pain
That one racchiona from the gigantic forehead.
But second you is truly one female?
You have made me badly.
Well!
Me of it I occupy.
Naruto succeeds to go
of agreement with its companions?
Beh enough.
Lately they have been a lot engaged
and they are not successful anchor to see it.
They are a po' preoccupied
Iruka-sensei, like sapete
Naruto is in square with Sasuke Uchiha
and with he bisticcia a po'
because it sees it as it avails again
but like result its
abilities are improving.
A lot that sooner or later will catch up to you.
Of they are content.
Of what draft?
Tsk propio hour?
This here
Konohamaru!
You have made me badly, moccioso.
You stop it.
Otherwise after you will feel to them.
Me dispiace, mine has been guilt
But who is these?
Hey ciccione, leaves endured it!
These are of the Genin di Konoha.
It would not be badly to amuse to us
before that it arrives the rompiscato one them.
Leave me!
You have much energy, moccioso.
Bastard!!!
And hour what has happened?
That weak people
this Genin di Konoha.
They are of the aliens
but why they are here?
Konohamaru!
Konohamaru-chan!
Konohamaru-kun!
Ehy! If not the soft ones
you you will see with me, idiot!
Six you idiot it!
What provokes it to make!?
They give to me on the nerves.
I hatred the children....
and you six too much presuntuoso end
for being smaller than me.
I want to kill to you.
I me of it wash the hands.
That type
it is dangerous.
After this marmocchio
me occuper   of the other dwarf.
Detention!
You it seems the way to involve to you
in a foreign village?
Sasuke-kun!!!
That pretty boy.
Head!
An other hateful child.
Sparisci.
A six myth!!!
Naruto, than figuraccia!
Stupid, one cos   also I
I can strike it when I want.
Tsk!
Cursed Sasuke!!!
Why ficchi always, always, the nose!?
Hey, child, you come down from l .
The wide awake children like you
they are those that hatred more.
Ehy! You want to use Karasu?
You stop It, Kankuro.
You will ruin the reputation of our village.
G Gaara
Quand' is
..che me it has been approached
Silent E' like Kakashi.
I have re-united to you here for a reason.
Inasmuch as you are here, creed that already you know it.
E' already arrived the moment?
Those of the other countries are
already be it informs to you, true?
I have seen them in turn for the village.
When it would be exactly?
Between one week.
Cos   soon?
Ve I communicate it officially.
Between seven days from today
the examination of selection of Chunin will have beginning.
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
Finally!
Finally! Finally!
My dream to become Hokage st approaching itself.
Sure E' that not to lose .
The tasks also you, Konohamaru?
From where these types come?
What I want to make
Seizing Moegi?
It waits for! Not to scappare!
The next nose-dive:
Identification! The apparition of formidable enemies!
Avr   a part a lot important also this time!!