http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
Ce I do not make it more.
Sakura-chan!
For how much we have walked?
The tower still does not seem to approach itself!
E' like if it remained of forehead to we
Strange E'
Obvious.
It seems that someone
warm acceptance has prepared us one.
Watched l !
But that one is
What is happening?
It cannot  be!!
Genjutsu!
(illusory Art!)
It would seem.
We have fallen ourselves like of the polli.
Too much it engages to you to attend to the ambushes
we have continued to turn
around to the same place.
They are observing.
Probably
They try to tire to us most possible
in order to attack when we are to the extreme.
Therefore we are making the game of the enemy.
Sure
They will attack to us soon.
Eccoli here.
A lot is being made interesting.
The Combat of the Cloni!
I am the protagonist!
Which thing is happening?
They are many.
And they are all Bushin (cloni)
Like a rat in trap.
We will see!!!
Oh, is more weak people of the previewed one.
Very made, Naruto!
Who who is in truth!
That he happens!
I will discover  their secret.
Sharingan!
Naruto!
Sasuke!
Sasuke-kun!
That it is happening!
My body!
You are well?
Without doubt they are real.
They are not illusions.
If Kabuto-saint it is remained hurt means
that in truth they are Kage Bushin (Cloni d' Ombra)?
But
The Kage Bushin, when they endure
damages, would have to disappear.
But they not, are really of the illusions?
What diamine are!?
Eternal damnation!
Useless E'!
Stopped!
Illusions are alone
E' a Genjutsu of the enemy.
But.>.
The wound of Kabuto-saint is real.
Not, Sasuke-kun has reason.
The enemy is hidden sure from some part
He attacks to us sincronizzando
with the movements of the illusions.
Cos   makes us to believe that they are
the illusions to attack to us.
Then  I will find  the bastard
that nozzle the kunai secretly
And I will step on  it  to it must!
It waits for, Naruto-kun.
In this moment, the source
of the launch of the kunai it is indefinite,
We do not know the exact position of the enemy.
You understand?
This is their strategy.
According to my experience, who is inferior in the Taijutsu
(Fight body to body) attacks in this way.
The enemy will not reveal itself until when
we will not be more in a position to moving to us.
You listen to me well.
In order now
We can only schivare the attacks.
Then
If this is their plan
Interesting
but how much will last!
The night is long.
It never does not end!!!
You take this!
Stopped, Naruto-kun.
Not to waste Chakra.
E' useless to attack them.
If free me of the illusions in one single time
The enemy will not be able to attack until when not
they will return to their normal state.
Otherwise it would reveal its position.
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
(Technical of the Clone d' Ombra)
Kage Bunshin?
I have not still ended!!!
Sasuke-kun, what we can make?
That idiot
We must fight also!
But
,  the situation  cannot control alone.
We go, Sakura!
Eh!
I have not still ended
The sky is schiarendo.
E' the moment to hunt.
Mubi, you can stop hour.
We have fiaccato their minds.
Now
Their body lacks us.
That fortune
Tu!
You six which have hurt to me
to the left shoulder, true?
We meet ourselves finally.
You have wasted your time.
That fortune
hour  I will be able  to be revenged.
You have wasted your time!
That fortune
Finally  I will be able  to be revenged.
Like a rat in trap.
Well succeeded E', Naruto.
What has made
It cannot  be
When they have!
Stupiden!
To the fine ones you have shown yourselves, cursed.
What!
Those boy has
It is not possible!
I have used the Kage Bunshin
in order to prepare the trucchetto.
They are successful to replace
all the elements of the square.
Not hardly Naruto has created our copies,
we three are hidden.
Cos   a master of Genjutsu has been tricked.
Naruto!
Naruto, you have consumed much Chakra.
I  will make I remain.
I will not allow that it takes to you
all the merits after this hard work.
E' truly "that" Naruto!
From when
he has become cos   strong?
That boy
he can himself  be still moved after all this.
Naruto
That incredible amount of Chakra.
Endured after the Kage Bunshin not Jutsu,
it has transformed three cloni in our copies.
After all this  it can  still move!
Moreover we are to the fifth day.
If it obtained the mastery
of its Chakra, it would become
monstrous strongly.
Very made.
But we are not still defeats.
Not there is more time.
Now we will show you our Ninjutsu!
(Technical Ninja)
Ninpou: Oboro Bunshin not Jutsu!
(Ninja Art: Technique of the Clone di Nebbia)
The Kage Bunshin
Not, normal retorts are alone.
But they must have in mind some type of tactics.
It makes attention!
If they are only of the copies, solo one is real.
I will hit  them  all until sending
to the carpet that true one.
Idiot, is only one waste of energies.
You I have already said
not intrometterti!
Naruto, is impossible!
Imprudent
When I try to use the Sharingan,
I feel one driven in to the neck.
What is using too much Chakra?
Eternal damnation
Accidents, copy was one.
Also this
Also this!
Naruto-kun, stopped!
What is all is made?
Of new a Genjutsu?
This is
those that me remains
of my Chakra!
Sharingan!
Sasuke-kun!
It is being increased of new
You do not have more to use the Sharingan!
Not to lower the guard!
Kabuto-saint!
Maledizione!!!
Stopped, Naruto!
It does not import how much you insist
it originates it them is not between the copies!
Then from where is attacking the enemy?
If they are of the normal copies,
they would not have to succeed to attack!
If we knew it, we would not have to strain a lot.
This is the plan of the enemy.
I cannot use the Kage Bunshin are sfinito!
It seems has arrived to its limit.
That fortune.
I have understood!
Those true ones have hidden under earth and attack
camouflaging itself between the shadows of the cloni.
Kabuto-saint!
Not to lower the just guard?
Naruto-kun Thanks.
You have saved to me.
Six great state, Naruto.
How you six fact that one?
Six hurt?
It seems a large brand.
It is not null.
I have found!
It watches!
E' a Coil of the Sky!
Huge.
This tizio
he is not  that  that seems.
You are!
Late arrivals Kabuto.
They are ended a po' in the troubles.
Me dispiace.
But, thanks to you
we have both coils!
Not.
E' be thanks to your hard job.
Especially your last movement
he has been incredible, Naruto-kun.
We will enter from this door
Good fortune to all.
!
Com' has gone?
Well, better of the previewed one.
I have collected all the regarding data According to Examination.
They served, true?
Then
that of tasks of he?
It seems is just to heart
Orochimaru-sama.
I wanted your opinion
in how much spy of the Village of the Sound.
My opinion does not have some importance
You are
that you decide all.
I appreciate your shrewdness very.
Good job.
Not there is nobody.
Sakura, hour I am well.
Ah..si
Maledizione
That-sfor-you-na!
Hey!
Hey! Which thing we would have to make?
It watches that one!
If you do not possess the Sky
I do not understand nothing to us
If you do not possess the Sky,
it earns acquaintance and you be prepared.
If you do not possess the Earth,
you run for the fields and finds the force.
If you open the Sky and the Earth,
the dangerous way becomes sure.
This is the secret of "something" or "someone "
(Sakura does not succeed to understand)
It will be able to guide to you in your way.
Which thing means?
In that point it seems that one lacks word.
Sure one refers to the coils.
Creed that is saying to open
the coils of the Sky and the Earth.
Then we open them.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
Che diamine!
It seems that those strongest ones are remained all
Hinata, Kiba, Shikamaru
All the esordienti of Konoha are here!
And also the square of Lee!
Frastornato Sono.
Oh I am well what it will become Hokage.
I must demonstrate to these zucconi
the difference between me and they!
Next episode:
According to Examination, Completed!