http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
I  will be to end to you fastly.
I will not make  you  not to move!
The initiative is equivalent to the Victoria!
Wow! Incredible!
You have seen its body!
With the Chakra I can be disarticulated
and to control to piacimento my body.
With its Chakra?
I can tighten until breaking to you boneses to you.
I will continue  to tighten until your yield.
I do not know that type of tool uses
but immobilized as six do not have importance.
I can break the bone to you of the neck.
You surrender in a hurry.
Scordatelo.
You want to die?
Stupid.
According to me you will be to die.
He has broken the bone of the neck.
What!
That idiot.
Accidents to you. Stupid.
They are innervosito to me and I have broken it.
What!
Now it is my turn.
What.>.
E' a burattino!
E' that one the true body!
E' a marionettista
With the chakra
the burattino controls.
m..mi....
If you sbriciolo the boneses you will become
still more snodato.
Little evil.
I was in order to commit the error
to interrupt the crash.
From the moment that the adversary
he cannot  fight
the winner is Kankurou.
Two against one are scorretto.
But it is valid?
Kakashi-sensei?
Not there is nothing of scorretto.
That one is a burattino.
E' the Technique of the Marionettista.
The burattino controls like
an arm using the chakra.
Exactly like the Shuriken.
They are the all best ones to use the Chakra.
And I that I thought to be
to a good level.
Crash between you avail again!
The Hearts of the Girls do not joke
Ino
You have Sakura fear?
They have had to medicare also Sasuke-kun.
But  he if it is cavata it with little wounds
but I do not succeed to imagine what
it will happen when it will touch you.
You would better make to withdraw hour.
Useless E' against of me.
It goes well.
I can make here of my best also!
To withdraw itself?
And who of it has intention?
I do not see the hour that it touches me.
It burns!
Facts under, eternal damnation!
We will go ahead with the fourth crash.
Accidents! Accidents!
They are all strange ones here!
You feel who speaks.
True E'!
Sakura chan, also you....
Ehi
It is not the moment to joke.
Haruno Sakura
VS
Yamanaka Ino
I would not have never thought, Sakura,
of having to you to face.
Perdipi cos   soon
Even if it does not seem, Ino was more ahead
regarding the other feminine esordienti.
Now it must see if it will succeed
to giving all if same against Sakura.
Just they two had themselves to be met?
Che casino.
Ino if the caver one?
We will be to see.
What you will make, Ino?
Sakura-chan! Force!
Not to lose!
Begun!
Just as I thought.
Sakura-chan is in advantage!
Stupid.
What you have said?
If six stupid then you are not sleeping.
That you have det....
After all they are * Kunoichi.
* (ninja females)
Their physical power
he is inferior to the norm.
It is not why they are females.
It does not give the maximum why they are friends.
The being woman enters not there in battle.
Friends....
HOUR!
Beyond that the own disciplines of a ninja
the Kunoichi must learn to bottom
the Fine Arts and the culture
why during the spionistica activity
in enemy territory if it is not acted
like a normal woman, it is come discovered.
The lesson today will be on the Ikebana.
You collect the flowers that preferred.
S !
Ino-chan! It waits for!
How much six awkward one!
They are not much good one in these things.
And you, Ino-chan?
Not six worthy one of the Sakura name.
(Sakura=Fiore of ciliegio)
There are of the rules for
the disposition of the flowers.
When you have chosen
that flower to use like departure point,
of it you add others in order to exalt it.
Moreover the flowers do not have to be supported between they.
It could be type
As an example
Those are the Cosmee.
If you decide that a Cosmea will be
the "main flower "
the eupatario that you have collected
it will be only of contour.
The Cosmea is considered the flower
beautifulr of the autumn
cos   like the flowers of ciliegio
they are for the spring.
Its name indicates also "HARMONY "
why it is well with all the autumnal grass.
Me it is well
like if pits one Cosmea?
They are pretty?
S..Si
Why me it does not seem convinced?
It today seems that ours ninja from the frontona
it is being amused.
Cos' is this new habit is made beautiful?
Not to mount the head, you have understood to you?
Ami-chan!
Oh me spiace a lot!
Six cos   it deprives of curves that
I have exchanged to you for a vase.
Ino!
The Acconito is a flower used from the ninja.
It does not have much poison but being toxic
it convene to you sputar it to more soon.
In the roots the poison is only present.
Incredible Ino-chan six.
Sai a bag of things and six also pretty one
Without to count that six good one
nel' use of the Shuriken
and in the Jutsu ninja.
I instead
Sakura?
If you six one Cosmea, Ino-chan.>.
I am one Aquatic Hemp.
But that you are saying!
Bh.>.
You a not six neanche flower,
six solo a bocciolo.
Eh you have reason.
It arrives you to this point
I do not have neanche to fight
with you for Sasuke-kun!
What?
Tu and Sasuke-kun you would not never go of agreement
and I am also more fort than You.
He would not watch to you not even!
Sakura!
You know with who you are speaking?
Sakura, child piagnona!
It seems, seems!
Sakura has exaggerated.
The look of Ino puts fear.
You are mistaking.
What?
Sakura is not type to boast itself of its force
and to hurt someone without reason.
It does not want that Ino is indulgente.
They are a bocciolo, eh.>.?
Ino-chan
Things are?
Why
you have given to me
this tape?
Why
.. I have thought that it would be
peccatto if you did not bloom.
A flower does not have no sense
if it does not bloom.
A flower that even
Cosmea will become still beautifulr than one.
Thanks
Ino-chan.
Sakura, we collect the flowers!
S..S .
Cos' you have, Sakura?
Not, null. Something has gone me
in the eye when they have fallen.
How much six awkward one!
Ino
always they have gone ahead
on the tracks of your words.
I thought would have been beautiful
if it had been true
that I could bloom in a beautiful flower.
I wanted
to be like You
I have continued following to you
like point of reference.
E' thanks to you that they are hour here.
And it is for this, Ino
.... that I want to fight seriously.
It would not have sense
if now you did not engage to you indeed!
Why Sakura-chan has
Mmmmm
Why those two are scaldando a lot?
One does not notice that also he
it makes the same thing with Sasuke?
You avail again are legacies
from strange relationships.
Hello
Mine it avails again of youth, Kakashi.
That strange reaction is dumb.
It will make me to become crazy.
I am
in the same group of Sasuke-kun.
Why me the rinfacci?
Ino, you  I will not be  more inferior in null.
Anch' I Sakura
you  I will not be  from less.
The tape?
I give back this tape to you.
You I have given that tape!
And then the coprifronte it goes put on the forehead.
I will not be  more the child who runs after to You.
I will put  on the forehead when I have  to you
exceeded in ability like ninja.
Good idea.
Then anch' I
.. I will make  the same one.
I have understood
Sakura.
Well
We use fully
our force and we fight
loyal!
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII