Subbed by Shinji 89
Thanks to God you are well, Sasuke.
Also Naruto stà well.
The voices were true.
Outside from the Uchiha clan
the only one sopravvisuto is one smidollato
Sasuke, you must be starved.
There is something that you want to eat ?
I can go to buy something…
I want to fight against of te!L' last crash!
Sasuke vs. Naruto
If I must be honest with you, I do not know what me of it I must make of these
From when the examination has been interrupted
Some persons think that nobody must pass
but to how much she seems is someone that and has made it there.
However, I have felt good things on you from the third Hokage.
I have felt comments also from the others
chuunin.
All the inspectors, the lord
and the examiners are of agreement.
but from this moment not there are more problems.
From this moment, mostraci your abilities
and not vergognarti of Konoha.
Congratulations!
From this day you will be chuunin!
Benchè you do not want to make nothing, you seem much serious one.
He is not from you.
Not to laugh.
However, we must celebrate the promotion to chunnin
of Shikamaru.
Itadakimasu!
Chouji! Not to take the meat before having taken the bread.
Ma..E' one waste.
We have an abundance of meat.
It watches ahead and it eats!
Ok!
Hour, you not me interests.
E' Naruto your obbiettivo.
It watches that you will end of new in hospital, Chouji.
You do not succeed to chew with calm tasting the sapori ?
Calm.
I  sò  to taste the food even if eat of haste.
Chouji!lascia the last piece of meat!
The last mouthful…
E' the great end to savour at all costs.
This last piece…
not  the lascierò  to nobody.
Scemo!Come you can of the sort give you of airs for one what!
And for that six taken in turn from all
only six a cicc -
Ino!
That one is one prohibited word.
And you choji it remembers to you that a meal is not a battle.
You take it with more calm…
six impossible one.
One greedy,
one rozza,
and one svogliato…
I wonder if these boys starrano in near future well
In particular....
Chouji.
You only engage to you in eating.
You would have to train a Pò  more  to you.
Chouji, six cos ì  fortunate.
With your character, it never does not preoccupy you of how much eats.
I am to diet I cannot imagine how much I am hard.
Why six to diet ?
The girls want to appear R-al.meglio
in front of the person that they love.
But.>.
She is not said that that person
piacciano the lean girls.
Mpf!
The boys in kind prefer those that they are not cicc -
that is the girls snelle.
And the same one is worth for gentil the sex.
You would have lend more attention to your line
cos ì  you do not have possibility with the women!
It has not understood null that one.
It is not true that to the boys piacciono always the tipe lean.
The majority peferisce those a tantino in meat.
And it is cos ì  also for the girls.
If ino rather than to put itself to diet it took  a Pò
of weight… they would make the double quantity them of the thread
A six amusing boy.
And six also inteligente one.
The sò.
Comparing to you to Sasuke and Nenji,
you will be always the best one.
I have not never made this kind of reasoning.
I am I.
Bè… You the six only one to to have been promoted to chunin.
But, perhaps if I and you defied yourself would gain you.
or not ?
Probably even if pits be you my adversary
I would have withdrawn myself.
Ma..prima the master has said that I do not make other that to eat,
and that  stò  not improving.
I have said to you that I am I.
and therefore you six you.
it is stupid to compare itself to the others.
Not to too much make case to   that Asuma says.
You would have living with spensieratezza and with
nature
We look at ourselves.
I must return to casa.Mio father to comnciato to
to speak me about pallose things
like handing on one to me new technique.
Shikamaru!
mmh?
They give to us within with the training.
A six propio Choji friend.
Hey, Sakura-Chan!
Naruto!
Gone to the village of the leaf.
Joined E' the propitious moment.
I have seen.
You have thought to us well.
Si.Sono prepared for the operation,
I want to recover to more soon.
Lee…
?
What is ?
On you lascerai to lose your dream
you will not risk to die
Why you insist in wanting to become
a ninja ?
I want to show to all
that I
I can be an optimal one ninja
If it has not happened.>.
morirai.
But.>.
E' one promised.
This why I have a dream.
Why you want to become Hokage?
They are not like you, I I want to become Hokage!
Why to become Hokage is my dream!
There are many interesting boys in this village.
saturabi, six state a perfect Hokage, after all.
The operation will carry out this afternoon.
You keep yourself ready.
We go, Lee!
Apples were alone.
You see ?
Huh?
Had the knife ?
It was not in front of you ?
Sasuke must have moved it.
Huh?
U
U-zu
U-zu-but
U-zu-but-ki!
Naruto nisen renden!
(2000  attack continue)
Enough!
Kuchiyose not jutsu!
Sakura is…
the person who I want protect!
Aspetta!Alzati!
Sasuke.>.
they have been saved once again from you ?
Not…
Naruto has saved you.>.
Your weakness…
it derives from the inadequacy…
of your hatred.
Sasuke eccoti your apple.
What ?
Sasuke ?
What has happened ?
What you have to watch to me cos ì ?
Hei, Naruto.>.
What is ?
You fight against of me.
What ?
Tsunade has said that you must rest.
About what you are speaking ?
Not importa!Combatti against of me!
Sasuke
Tasks to have to me saved ?
Not null me frega of the 5 hokage
Deovevi not to put to you in means.
What ?
You have not said that you want to strike to me ?
It makes it.
I have you have too much fear ?
Sa-Sasuke!
What happens ?
Naruto d ì  something!
It does not have sense, why ?
I pick the occasion!
Also I wanted to fight against of you!
smettetela all and two.
You follow to me.
Cosè this feeling ?
Me the stomach is tightened.
I want to fight against of you.
Stò  exciting  to me.
What finds us of amusing ?
Not there is null of amusing
I laugh why they are content…
Inasmuch as finally
I will be able  to strike to you.
To take Naruto!
E' the supreme order given to us from dawn,
our organization.
Failing like you ?
But that scemenze you go saying ?
they are not more…
failing of weight to all.
In this moment I do not try no interest
in yours it confronts.
Why.>.
Pazzo!
Fast we begin!
It is not from you to scaldarsi a lot.
Of always calm usual six.
it is not that now you have fear ?
Facts under force!
Before you put the coprifonte, I waited for to you.
It does not serve to me.
You put it!
You will not succeed makes me not even
a scratch on the forehead!
It is not for this!
The coprifonte it symbolizes the fact that we will fight at par
… according to the code ninja of the leaf.
Then I had reason to say that you six mounted the head.
Creeds indeed that I and you are to the same level !
That the task!
I never have not felt inferior you.
I do not want to listen to your sciochezze.
Why you six remained weak person!
ahead piccolino made under!
NARUTOOO!
SASUKEEE!!
You stop it to make casino!
Naruto…
You take cure of same!
Tajuu!Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
U
U-zu
U-zu-but
U-zu-but-Ki!
Naruto Rendan!
The position of the tiger!
KAton!Tecnica of the supreme fire ball!
Naruto!
Che cos' is.>.
merda.>.
Chidori!
Enough…
I will win!
Some cos ì  it are not convinced!
Smettetela!
Enough!
Next episode: The sound never seen.