Subtitles By: BakaSan
As a start, rough up the medium kid to wake him up.
Then the jutsu will end.
How're we gonna wake him up?
Just give one blow to that kid.
But, I'm not good at Henge.
What?
So, you become my will and do the hand seal.
It's a Combination Henge.
One with fangs and nails, you got it?
Let's go!
Henge!
Exceeding the Limit!
~ Light and Shadow ~
A fox?
Here!
What kind of battle are they doing!
I can't say I'm safe here either.
Shit.
His power is getting stronger.
Oyabin! We got to wake him up soon!
I know that!
Let's do this!
Die!
Here I come!
Alright! Now!
Wake the fuck up!
Bastard!
Good. It hasn't been long since
the medium kid went into sleep.
In his current condition, that one blow is enough.
God Damn it! I just came out!
His Jutsu was disengaged?
I'm still being pushed even after
releasing the Tanuki Neiri. (Fake Sleep)
He released my Jutsu?
Sabaku Kyu (Sand Coffin)
Dad!
Yup!
This is the tongue of Oyabin!
Don't mess with me!
How much power does this guy have?
This isn't good. Both Naruto and I have
already used up our chakra completely.
You are going to be killed by me.
My existence won't be erased!
Konoha Senpu!
Not only the Sound, but this many Jounin
of the Sand came... Who'd imagine this?
Well, logically that isn't out of the ordinary...
This is a war.
This is long.
It's very rare that a shinobi keeps battling
against a shinobi for this extended period.
What on the earth is going on inside?
My arms are still held.
I can't do any Jutsu.
Won't you let me go already?
I won't let this village get involved
in your wild ambition any more.
My ambition won't stop.
And you're going to die here.
You still say that, even aged, you have power
to save this village as the Third Hokage?
Do you understand the current situation?
Not only my own subordinates but also those from
the Hidden Sand are coming into this village.
You and Shinobi of Konoha will all
die, including the women and children.
The Konoha Kuzushi (Konoha Crash) succeeds here!
The inside is empty.
Nobody's there.
Strange...
Yes.
We came into the center of the Konoha village
but why haven't we had much of resistance?
Because...
Also, why have we not seen even one woman or child.
What's wrong, Konohamaru chan?
Gotta use the restroom.
Me, too.
It's an emergency situation now! It'll be
serious trouble if we are found by the enemies!
Go back to the room and be quiet!
That's not it... I need to pee.
Hold it!
I don't think I can hold it any longer.
Alright, then... I'll go with you to.
It's gonna leak! leak! leak!
That is the...
Finally, eh?
I'll definitely avenge you...
Gekkou Hayate.
That's the sign. Let's go.
Yes.
You don't understand, Orochimaru.
Don't underestimate the Shinobi of this village!
Are you alright?
Yes.
Are they the last ones?
Yup. The evacuation is complete.
What do you mean?
The Konoha village has a plan in case
we get a surprise attack from an enemy.
The first stage is to eliminate the surprise attack units.
If elimination was not possible, then
immediately move onto the second stage.
In other words, the evacuation of all civilians.
We evacuate the women and children to
refuge areas all around the village.
Once it's completed we start the third stage.
The third stage?
To eliminate the enemy with what all that this village has!
That means...
The counter attacks begin now!
I won't let you go even one step further beyond here!
You've got to rescue Sakura with everything you have.
I'll protect Sakura-chan no matter what!
You're going to be killed by me.
My existence won't be erased.
I've got my back to the wall. I have
to stop this monster Tanuki soon.
Please.
Just a little bit is fine...
for me.
Give me your chakra!
What're you doing? The enemy is only one person!
Hyuga is the strongest in Konoha. Remember that!
My body can't...
move!
Is this the first time for you to experience the  secret
of Konoha, Kageshibari no Jutsu? (Bind with Shadow)
If that's the case, take this one also.
The  secret of Konoha, Kage Kubi Shibari
no Jutsu. (Tie the Neck with Shadow)
Baika no Jutsu (Multi size)
Shin Ran Shin no Jutsu (Spirit and Body Switch)
What?
My body moves against my will!
Stop it! Stop it!
This reminds me the old times.
Yup.
It's the reunion of the Ino-Shika-Cho trio
Kuromaru, you ready?!
Yup!
The Shinobi of Konoha will fight, risking
their lives, to protect this village.
The real power in this world is not through archiving all Ninjutsu.
The poison in my body is...
Don't move, Shino. I put my bugs into you.
They're removing the poison from your body.
Father...
I believe I taught you once that...
...when you protect your precious people,
the real power of Shinobi will appear.
I will protect everybody!
Ready? Stupid Tanuki!
Die!
God Damn it!
Did he win?
Just a head bang...
Though his fighting style isn't smart at all,
I'm surprised that he pulled more
chakra when he's at his limit.
I've never seen such a clumsy Ninja, but he's the
first kid in long time to be the out of this world.
It's too bad that I can't see this
till the end, but I'm also at my limit.
Gamakichi, we're going home now.
Alright, dad.
Even I'm empty now.
You, too, right?
Let's make this the end for us...
I guess I don't have enough power
to pull your entire soul out...
But your ambition ends here, too.
Not yet!
My ambition won't stop yet!
I'll give you the punishment that suits you.
You are addicted and extremely proud of Jutsu..
...so I'll take all your Jutsu with me.
What did you say?
You don't say...
Stop it!
Fuuin! (Seal)
My arms!
You won't be able use both of your arms anymore.
Since you can't use your arms, you can't form hand seals.
You no longer have any Ninjutsu.
Your Konoha Kuzushi (Konoha Crash) fails here.
You, old man!
Give me my arms back!
How foolish of you, Orochimaru.
I'm regret that we can't go together, but, my foolish subordinate...
I'll see you in other world later.
How dare you... you dying old man... Taking my Jutsu!
Fire will be aflame where the leaves dance.
The shadow of the fire will light the village and...
... the leaves will sprout once again.
The Third...
The will you were talking about...
...seems to be carried over by...
... the small Shinobis of Konoha.
Nest Episode
The Third, Forever......!!