Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
Orochimaru's Shadow
No way... What happened
to Iruka Sensei?
Iruka's scent ends right here...
In any case,
all we can do is search for him.
Damn it. Where's Iruka Sensei?!
Iruka Sensei!
What a relief!
You're safe!
Somehow...
Damn... that Mizuki...
Iruka Sensei...
That injury...
Huh, this injury is nothing...
Iruka Sensei!
I'm all right...
I just had a little rush of pain...
Somebody's approaching!
What a relief
the wound's not deep.
Yes...
The atmosphere feels kind of heavy...
Hmm... There must be something
between those two...
Well, what I think is...
What's up with the paw pad?
Idiot! Look carefully!
The little finger, the little finger!
Little finger? Huh?!
Iruka Sensei's?
Well, my intuition tells me
that it's positive...
Naruto, what are you two
talking about?
Uh, nothing!
Huh? Let me make an introduction.
This is Tsubaki...
Mizuki's fiance.
Fiance? Mizuki's?
Ah, it's negative...
What's up with that reaction?!
Mizuki has caused problems
for you again...
I sincerely apologize for that.
So you know about
Mizuki's prison break...?
Yes...
He came by my house once...
I became aware of that immediately
and tried to stop him.
But ultimately the result
was that I allowed him to go...
It really couldn't be helped
in light of the situation...
No. I should have tried
even harder to stop him.
But I...
Iruka, Naruto, I beg you!
Please take me with you!
Tsubaki...
I understand that I'm making
an impossible request!
But I want to stop him,
no matter what!
Iruka Sensei!
Tsubaki, I understand how you feel.
In that case...
I'm sorry, but I cannot allow that.
But why?
Why can't she?!
Naruto, we must hurry up
and search for Mizuki!
If she's with us,
she'll interfere with our mission!
But... But!
Iruka... If that's the case,
I think I'll be of service to you.
I have an idea of
where he might be heading!
Is that true, Tsubaki?!
There's probably no mistake...
But...
I beg you!
I think it's certain
that he'll use various tricks to camouflage
his tracks as he flees...
If we spend time on that...
it will all be too late!
Please take me with you!
Regarding the matter of Nara No. 23...
Huh, what was the result?
The Ninja Herb: Creeping Saxifrage...
Huh?! Who are you!
Dragon, Rooster, Dog...
The lookouts have been taken down!
It's an intruder!
What?!
The Nara Clan's research lab
was attacked?!
Yes... I just received a dispatch
from the Nara Clan...
According to the dispatch,
the insurgent's physical characteristics
match those of Mizuki.
Mizuki's...?
Yes!
What is that Naruto doing?
But it's something to have come up
with the idea of the Nara Clan's institute...
Notwithstanding the abundance of
narcotic substances that are stored there,
due to its remote mountain location,
security is comparatively lax.
And what substances were stolen?
Well... Because of their thorough control
of the substances,
they were able to determine immediately
which substances were taken...
So the description matched
after all, huh...
But even if a mere Chunin were
to remove those narcotic substances
what would he be able
to do with them?
Oh... Thank you. You may go now...
Yes ma'am!
In any case,
I can't take any chances...
There's nothing I can do if
I don't know what his objective is.
If I can't discern that from
the actual materials...
there may still be some means...
Perhaps the proportions
of the formula,
or possibly the order
in which they're blended...
There's no mistake that
it's this direction, right?
Yes... Please continue to
proceed just like this.
Tsubaki, you said
"It will all be too late."
But do you know what
his objective is?
Probably... Although maybe not totally.
Tsubaki, please tell us!
In the past, he told me...
"I will get my hands on Orochimaru's power
and go to where Orochimaru is."
What was that?!
The reason he stole
the Scroll of Sealing
was simply because
he had chosen it as a hospitality gift...
Tsubaki... You knew that?
I didn't convey it to the village...
Just removing the Scroll of Sealing
is a serious felony...
And moreover, I was scared for
what'd happen
if his real objective
had come to light...
I believed that he would
mend his ways.
In that case you cannot avoid
retribution either.
I am prepared for it.
I thought it was strange...
If you knew where Mizuki was going,
you should have pursued him alone
in the first place.
But you...
I may not be able to stop him alone...
I want to stop him at any cost...
I don't want him to commit
any more crimes.
Unbelievable!
That Orochimaru...
So this was his plan!
However, could an ordinary Ninja
really manage to do this...?
It's something only within
the realm of an ex. Perienced
artisan's technique...
I'm busy!
I have a progress report on
the inmate prison break incident!
All right... Enter!
Yes, ma'am!
We have just finished
recapturing all inmates
with the exception of three -
Mizuki, Fujin and Raijin.
Good work...
We are now continuing to investigate
the other three...
But, the last inmate we captured said
something that concerned me...
Something that concerned you?
Yes... He apparently saw the three of
them fleeing together...
Fujin and Raijin were fleeing
with Mizuki?!
Damn it!
Lady Tsunade?
I'm going out!
Where are you going?
There's no need for you to come...
If what he said is true,
the guys I sent out won't be able
to deal with the situation alone...
Hey, Shikamaru...
If things continue like this...
we'll be in trouble!
We're already in trouble...
Shikamaru... All the Chakra is...
I know that...
I've thought of several methods,
but if I let go of these guys we are
gonna find ourselves in trouble...
You insolent jerk!
Having said that,
I can't take them down simply
by catching them,
so that's why I'm doing this...
I won't let you leave here alive!
These guys have monstrous stamina...
And what's more,
although their bodies
look like rubber at first glance,
with that much muscle strength
their instantaneous reflex. Es
are probably quite something too...
In other words,
you're saying that this is
the only possible method...
Let's do our best, everyone!
Sorry about this...
What do you think, Mizuki?
It's no good...
It's unfortunate but, he can no longer...
I see...
All right! Let's withdraw!
Hurry up!
Yeah...
It's unfortunate but...
guys who are of no use
on the battleground
only become a ball and chain...
Even though it's just a minor injury,
you won't be able to move
from this place, can you?
Who's that?!
Oh no! Is it Genjutsu Paralysis?!
I saw that...
No way... This can't be, you're...
Orochimaru?!
You are correct...
This can't be...
Why are you here?
Your whereabouts are supposed
to be unknown!
It doesn't matter why...
More importantly,
I witnessed something
very interesting earlier on...
You took the life of
an injured comrade, didn't you?
You saw that...?
That piqued my interest...
That's not a sight one sees
very often among the Leaf Shinobi
who devote their entire time
to playing house in the village...
So what are you trying to say?!
I didn't do anything wrong!
I had no choice but to do what I did!
You're a short tempered child,
aren't you...?
I'm not reproaching you.
You were just carrying out your mission.
That's right...
But... Is there anybody in
the Leaf V illage who acknowledges you?
What did you just do?!
What in the world is this...?
This is my present to you...
Go visit that place if you feel like it.
Here it is...
Looks like there hasn't been
a trespasser here before me...
The eighth one on the right...
What's happening?
What is that power of
Orochimaru's anyway?
I don't know either.
And I don't know when
he encountered Orochimaru either...
But I'm positive that the answer to
those questions is waiting just up ahead!
That Scroll of Sealing incident...
You must be angry about it,
aren't you, Naruto?
I don't care about that in
the least anymore...
Because I repaid my debt to that
jerk Mizuki right there and then.
But...
But?
If that guy is still connected
to Orochimaru,
I need to ask him about something!
Because there's someone
I need to find at any cost!
Sasuke...!
It's up there...
All right!
That's everything...
With this all...
This will...
This will make me perfect!
This place is...
That guy has done something...
That smell gives me the shivers...
Smell?
I was wondering who that was...
You guys are really persistent,
aren't you?
Well, this is very convenient.
Because I was intending to take
you guys down anyway.
Mizuki...
You jerk!
Mizuki... Your ambitions end here!
Impudent as always, huh...
However, you're too late!
Just like you always are...
What is that?
Beautiful, don't you think?
Damn it!
You guys... should feel honored
to be my first prey...
What?!
That's... almost like...
But that's they way it is,
isn't it, Naruto... ?
It's true, you were actually special.
But...
Then that's...
Orochimaru's power!
Mizuki...
Crappy news pass us by
And you become speechless
My voice is way too soft
So you don't answer
You're crying Crying alone
What can I do? I'm crying too
"Let my lonely scream ring out
through the night"
I'll thrash this confused era
with my speed Yeah
And I'll thrash this confused night
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar
and my speed Yeah
This sinking world and its evil bastards,
I'll kick their butt Yeah
That's what you meant by
the "invincible body?
No matter how much strength
you gain,
the kind of strength dependant
on drugs can never be a true strength!
Hah! Just like Iruka Sensei says!
Orochimaru's Drug?
I'll crush that kind of nonsense,
so be prepared!
Next episode: "A Clash of Fate:
You Can't Bring Me Down!"