Subbed by Kyubi
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not fukinukeru
Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda YEAH!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite kanashimi mo
hoho tsutatte namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Baby
That dark sky. Storm is arriving one.
Eh?
Idate.
Episode #104
A storm is get loosed on the island of Nagi
You run Idate, you run!
Aoi, Bastard!
Not scappi?
Scappare is your specialty, not?
You are zitto!
They are not like you!
You mistakes. I and you are equal.
He does not trust you the aliens. You betray them.
You have betrayed your brother. and abandoned your village.
Six one orribile and egoist person.
You while still alive do not have reason to be.
You die!
Sakura-chan, as it goes?
It is  a scratch, nothing of serious.
Instead…
Those ninja of the Rain…
they are not worth nothing.
It is not this. If they were following Idate-saint…
Idate is in danger!?
It is  about that we are speaking!
Naruto, is not the moment to make the buffone.
Not!
Quà Sono!
Naruto!
That fortune.
In the water, we are invincible.
They are one annoyance.>.
Finally they have fallen in trap.
Misu bunshin not jutsu
Sakura-chan!
Kage bunshin not jutsu
Che imbecille.
To that they serve of the Kage bunshin in this situation ?
In these deep waters, you do not have no hope against ours cloni of water.
Even if tests to make something,
I know who I am that true one
Which thing is making?
Impossible!
Good idea! The chakra it provokes upsets some!
Bravo Naruto!
It is  first part of the Rasengan training!
Sakura-chan!
Sakura-chan, you hold hard!
Not to abandon to us, Sakura-chan!
Sakura-chan?
You resist! Sakura-chan!
This is…
The last hope.>.
Sasuke-kun?
It would appeal to to me that Sasuke-kun revived to me…
With a mouth mouth…
....  Sakura-chan.
Which thing you wanted to make? Idiot!
Sasuke-kun?
We do not have time in order to rest to us. We must find Idate and escort it.>.
It waits for, Sasuke-kun.
You do not leave me here.>.
In this moment,
Fukusuke is in order to catch up the stage of the Tempio di Modoroki.
You do not have more no possibility than to catch up it.
You will not be more able than to run, and not to raise to you.
When the pain propagherà in your body,
You will have caught up an other stage.>.
that Hell is called!
Which thing tasks to make with your stupid knife?
Not to touch it!
It seems that you do not know more from where you come.
You cannot only run…
with this fierezza.. he is unforgivable.
I…
You pardon to me…
Head…
I will not be able  to honor my promise.
Idate!
You…
That rain!
Then the six leader of the Rain?
If you have them defeats, is only because you were more than they.>.
You are only of the Genin, your level is not that one of Konoha.
He is  orribile.
You are only of the Genin, like you will make to stop to me?
You close the spout!
Over!
It is  all what sapete to make here?
You would have to follow the same road of Idate.
E' the moment to send you to the other world.
Useless to waste other chakra.
Sakura-chan!
These needles…
It is  my poisoned rain.
Any is the resistance of your body, after some minuteren will be fatal.
Not to underrate us…
Fukusuke has caught up the Tempio di Modoroki.
It would be piaciuto to see to me to you to die. For of the Genin like you, to die cos ì  it is an honor.>.
The Wagarashi clan will still win?
Could not happen a miracle?
By now it is only a memory when Jirochou controlled the city.
They are truly tired.
You are best, the Fukusuke-saint one.
If continued cos ì,  the head of the Wagarashi will be content!
Not to speak cos ì  in front of me. For who you take to me?
Which thing?
It has been already decided that  I will win. You leave to make one pause me.
Cursed, not to remove to you.
Hour enough!
Brother, does not have accadergli null!
Sai what would make the Head us?
I know.
Not to forget it.
Merda! This boy…
Naruto, Sasuke-kun.
This is…
Sakura-chan, this is…
When I have left Konoha,
Tsunade-sama has given this to me.
You take these. They are sure that of it you will have need.
The Old One?
With this, it will resume acquaintance soon.
Sasuke-kun and Naruto, prendetene one.
If the lasciamo here, its body will be exposed to the cold.
We must put it from an other part.
Brother!
It watches! They have finally become a Ninja!
I understand.
They have been the best one.
Beginning from now,
I will always train myself , and I  will make  of the missions, and  will become  to all Chuunin speed!
After  I will be  Jonin!  I will become  like you, brother!
And all will call me "Idate-sama!"
Brother?
It listens well, Idate.
There are of the more important things that the force and the infuence.
More important?
Until you will not have comprised it,
You will not be able to realize your dreams.
It is being resumed!
You are well?
Dov' is? Aoi?
It is  disappeared. Aoi? E' cos ì  that this ninja of the Rain is called?
Idate-saint, you know it?
It was my sensei when I lived to Konoha.
Tu.... to Konoha?
Aoi has betrayed Konoha and has become a Jonin of the Village of the Rain.
Che cos' has happened?
You would not have to move. You must still rest a po '.
Your hands are well?
Your hand.... you have held it the entire time!.
To be arrives end here to you…
it is not served to nothing!
You are losing heart yourself too much soon.
Six state truly a Ninja di Konoha?
I have forgotten all about Konoha, from when I have abandoned the village.
Abandoned?
I have failed to the Chuunin examination.
And I had taken it badly.
There were nearly, Idate.
Not to be sad.
Other ways exist in order to become Chuunin, without to pass from the examination.
Truly.
S ì,  truly.
Enough to make what I say to you.
S ì!
Aoi-sensei.
Idate.
Aoi-sensei!
I have carried, as you have said to me.
They are the used Parchment and the Katana from According to Hokage.
The sword of Raijin.
[ Raijin is the God of the light ]
Beautiful job, Idate.
And with this,  I will become  Chuunin?
S ì,  you will become it.
To the Village of the Rain.
You and I will disappear from Konoha…
And we will carry with we our acquaintances.
Impossible…
They know that you have stolen the treasure of the Village.
You will not be able more living calm.
You have embedded to me!?
In order to survive in this world, us  it cannot  be trusted the others.
Not to forget it.
Now, than what you will make, Idate?
Any thing you had to choose, you would be announced publicly from Konoha.
Your reputation will be muddy, in order always.
After, they are returned to the village.
But I more did not succeed to do good the things
But Jirochou Head believes in me.
Even if I have not made nothing for he,
The Head has always had confidence in me!
But… io.>.
This boy…
He is  similar to me.
Nobody will recognize someone like you!
You die Naruto!
Naruto! It lowers to you!
They are truly.... a bond to null!
Because…
Because we are similar.
We have lived the same situation.
I only make of the stupidaggini, and I am incapable to end any thing.
Siccome has said Aoi to it, I…
I do not have the right of living!
Idiot!
There is at least a person whom he believes in you!
Is not true, Naruto?
You truly only feel yourself, is not true?
You must have suffered a lot, is not true?
One person!, better than nothing not?
The race still is not ended.
We must arrive until the end!
But…
It raises to you!
Naruto,  cannot. Its body is always…
If it  cannot  run, I  will carry  it on the race shoulders!
Probably our adversary has already caught up the Tempio di Modoroki.
Not to let go!
Naruto!
Sasuke-kun…
It leaves to make it.
Jirochou Head waits for, not?
Yours pulls outside all grinta!
Head, you are sure that those mascalzone is not escaped?
It will come.
Creed in he!
If you fail hour, you will be losing for the rest of your life!
There e' someone that believes in you and that it waits for to you…
It is  the faster boat.
Thanks!
It is  mine it must.
The appuntiti objects are not made in order to hurt the persons.
You make to see to all your determination!
Naruto!
Portami!
S ì!  Us task I!
Get out sumimasen
boku tamani boku tamani
yume ni afureru hito not kakeraga
yama not yoni mieru
kami sama ni hotoke sama ni
tsutae naiteru hito not kakeraga
yama not yoni mieru
dan dan dan sura nanderu
borushoi it did not place ni narandara
shake shake shake sagaso janainowa
bye bye bye not let' s of
yama not yoni mieru
Ehi, you! You would better make to plant it!
It speaks like if you knew all! Six annoying one!
We go, Idate. The Head waits for you to the stage.
M' he does not import that Aoi is a Jounin or cos' other!
I will take  to soccer in the culo and we will gain the race!
Next Episode
Just in time!
The noise of the thunders, one violent crash.