Subtitles By: BakaSan
It was worth it teaching you Genjutsu during the
survival exam to decide whether you guys become Genin.
You have the talent for Genjutsu, as I thought.
Release the Genjutsu and wake Naruto and Shikamaru up.
I'm sure Naruto will be happy.
It's the first mission after a long time.
A mission?
Take it with care.
It's another A-rank mission like the Wave country mission.
I was waiting for it! It's an A-rank Mission!!
Sensei! What're we going to do with
an A-rank mission in this situation?
Sasuke is chasing Gaara of the Sand and his company.
Sakura, you will track down Sasuke after
releasing the Genjutsu on Naruto and Shikamaru.
It does worry me... that strange chakra.
But, if that's the case, I should
wake Ino and Choji, and go with more...
There are probably a large number of Shinobi's
from the Sand and Sound in this village already...
Moving around with more people than the basic four-person unit
will loose speediness and make it harder to  hide from enemies.
You learned that in the patrol-training
from the Academy, didn't you?
That's right. So, four people
means you are coming with us, too?
No, I can't leave here.
Kuchiyose-no-Jutsu
From here, Pakkun will track down Sasuke by his scent.
If I'm understanding you correctly...
the last one is this doggy?
Hey, little girl. Don't call me a cute doggy.
I didn't say "cute"...
Alright, Sakura. Release the Genjutsu on Naruto and Shikamaru.
Yes.
Kai! (Release)
Huh...? What's up, Sakura chan?
Get down!
We'll talk later. Just stay down.
Shikamaru... from the beginning you...
Ouch!
You also were able to do Genjutsu-gaeshi
(counter-Genjutsu)! Why were you pretending to be sleeping!?
I don't want to be involved. I
refuse to. Who cares about Sasuke.
Ouch!
What's going on?
Behind you!
Fast!
Not just fast.
Now, I'll tell you the mission. As soon
as you hear it, leave from that hole.
Go after Sasuke and join him to stop him.
And until further order, stay at a safe place.
What happened to Sasuke?
I'll explain as we go.
We're leaving!
Damn it... why me?
Hey kid...
If this mission is succeeds, I'll let you
touch my footpad as reward. So, don't complain.
What?
See? It's Puri-Puri (soft but tense).
Puri puri...
No. It's more like... PURI PURI!!
Anyway's, let's go.
Is it alright with just those four?
They have Pakkun with them, so it'll be alright for now.
As long as they don't get in too deep.
I can fight with you again...
This Kekkai can only be broke from within...
If Hokage-sama could beat one of those
four, then we can join him to fight.
Hey, it's going to start soon.
Create Kekkai inside, too.
Alright.
I see it's not so easy to get out from here.
You're saying something that you don't even think... It's
worse for you to have somebody coming in to pull your leg.
Ninpo-Kawara-Shuriken
It isn't enough...
Senei-Jashu
Just with this level of attack... don't
want to get older, do we, Sarutobi sensei...
Kawarimi...
Doton
Doryu-taiga (Earth Mud-River)
Your level is only this much?
I won't let you...!
Doton Doryu-dan (Earth
Mud-Cannon)
Karyu-dan (Fire Cannon)
Combining Doton and Katon... That's the Hokage-sama!
Stop your stupid pretend playing, Orochimaru.
After all it's you...
But I am underestimated, I see. You thought
you could kill me with such level of Jutsu?
You're without charm, just like before.
Well, don't say that. It's said that a student who demands more
of your attention is more adoreble isn't it? Sarutobi-sensei?
Self Study
It's strange. All classes of the Academy
are told to do self-study... Plus that smoke.
It's the direction of the exam arena.
Isn't it noisy to the East?
I wonder if something happened.
It really is strange.
But, I don't like it when they tell us to do
self-study all of the sudden. It's been a while.
Yeah. Iruka sensei isn't late... Right, Konohamaru-kun?
What is this?
My mom just bought this for me recently!
You can borrow my color pencil.
What're you saying! This color is a new color
out this spring! Man... what should I do?
That is...
I wonder if Naruto-kun and
others went to stop Sasuke-kun.
Those kids did? Well, no matter how
many Genins make moves, it's nothing...
Is this the data of that kid?
You worry too much.
You're wrong.
They'll take your feet, if you are careless.
Teacher's room
I heard the information that there're a
number of units in the village already.
I think we should take the students to a safe place quickly.
Right. Plus, without making the students panic.
Then, tell them that this is an emergency
practice, and quickly take them to...
Won't we stop playing around now? Since
this is not a class of the Academy.
You're right.
I see you were expecting to die.
I won't go easy just because you're old.
That's my wish. Depending on your Jutsu performance,
you may need to go back to the Academy again.
Don't disappoint so much.
Amazing! What chakra...
Yeah. It's like the air is pressing down on my entire body.
Shuriken Kagebunshin no jutsu
Kuchiyose Edo Tensei (Summoning the Dead)
That jutsu is...
One.
Using Kuchiyose as shield... and those dead people are...
Two
I have to stop the third one no matter what...
Three
I couldn't bring the thrid one, I see. Well, it's ok.
I was able to prevent the third one,
but... it's going to be very hard from now.
Of all, he brought those two people.
No way. Those two people are....
Those two people?
Well, what're you going to do, Sarutobi Sensei? No...
the Third Hokage sama.
Everybody, move quickly.
Man, today isn't a good day... my favorite
color pencil didn't need to break like that.
An emergency practice... I prefer self-studying.
Konohamaru-chan has been quiet... what's wrong with him?
yeah.
After all classes do the self-studing, now all classes do
an emergency practice together... It truly is too strange.
Ok. Stop walking and get in line.
Iruka-sensi's face... there must be something.
and
Everybody listen. Do not leave here by yourself.
I've been thinking about it... that rainbow.
Hey Old man. There's a strange rainbow over there.
It's a rare rainbow.
Do you like rainbows, Konohamaru?
Yup. And I've never seen such beautiful rainbow before.
I see, I see. But Konohamaru.
What?
It's been said that a rainbow is a symbol
of snakes, and sign of bad things to happen.
For such a beautiful thing? It must be a lie.
I see... I see...
A symbol of a snake... what's going on now?
Long time no see, Saru.
Oh, it's you. You've aged, Sarutobi.
Who imagined I would meet you two brothers again in this way.
I regret it.
This isn't good.
That Kuchiyose....
Who are those people anyway?
Be prepared, Shodai-sama (The First)
and Nidaime-sama (The Second)
That's right. The one with black hair is
the First, and the white hair is The Second.
Both were praised as the best Shinobi, and together
they are the Hokage-sama's who founded Konoha.
Edo Tensei... this the young man who summoned
us with the forbidden jutsu, is he? Such a man.
That means we have to fight against you, Sarutobi.
Let's stop the old man's reunion
chat, and let's started it already.
It's war in any days.
You like it, don't you?
You're playing with dead people. It
won't be good to play around with time.
I see. That's what was going on.
Sasuke hurried too much.
And why do I need to be here? Super troublesome.
No choice. It was Kakashi sensei's order.
This way!
That kid, huh?
Let's go!
Damn it. It's too eary to be chased.
We will all die if we Genins are caught by them.
Then, should we beat them up by waiting and hiding?
I thought of it, but it won't work.
Then what should we do?
Whatever you say, there's only one way we can take.
Next Episode Number 1 Running-away Style
It's troublesome but I've got to do it!!
It isn't my character, but I guess I've got to do it.