An Assassin in the Moonlight
This guy..
Sasuke-kun..
We were a bit too late it seems..
They are..
Sa.. Sakura-chan..
You two..
Th.. this is..
He must've fought out of control..
..like that time.
Sasuke-kun!
But Kakashi-sensei said the mark was taken care of..
Who is that..
Sakura-chan..
Sakura-chan!
What is it!?
Who.. who the hell is that?
Although his figure has been transformed..
..he's the one named Gaara.
Having this body possessed by the incarnation of sand..
..I came into this world stealing life away from a woman I would've called my mother.
I am a born monster.
So.. that thing is it?
He.. attacked Sasuke-kun..
Hey Missy!
I feel that I should tell you I'm not a battle-type.
I can tell!
Anyway, we have to somehow lose them..
..and take Sasuke-kun to Kakashi-sensei as soon as possible.
You..
Sasuke-kun..
Well, your limit is at two shots..
it seems..
There would be no third one..
Never forget that.
When you try to strain the activation of a jutsu not only will the jutsu fail..
but you also lose all remaining chakra..
..and your life in the worst-case scenario.
Even if you survive..
You will face difficulties no matter what.
Especially because you have..
..a curse seal?
If you give in to hatred and depend on the power of the curse seal..
..that'll be it for your strength growth.
In that case, you can never defeat Itachi.
I have to control this..
Sasuke-kun!
I see..
You..
you're the one I failed to kill that time.
I fight for my sake only and I live to love no one but myself.
As long as mankind exists for me to kill..
my existence will never end..
You guys!
Get away!
Die! Uchiha Sasuke!
Sakura-chan!
She held her ground against Gaara even in his current state..
Damn it!
Dammit..
What are we supposed to do!?
Anyone but him..
Come on, let me feel it..
Why?
Gaara-sama, please calm down!
It's no use..
The sand gets in the way..
Gaara-sama..
Yashamaru..
As a member of your medical team at Kazekage-sama's command, my duty is to protect you from any harm..
Please do not try to do such a thing..
..although the sand will protect you anyway.
Yashamaru, I'm sorry.
Oh this..
Don't worry about it.
Do injuries..
..hurt?
Well, a little..
But it's nothing serious.
Hey, Yashamaru..
Yes?
What is pain?
I've.. never been injured so..
I wonder what it's like..
How should I put it?
Afflictive.. or dreadful..
like when you're beaten or cut..
your body's in an unbearable condition in which you feel that you're unable to stay in your usual self..
I can't explain it very well but.. I think I can say that it's unpleasant..
Yashamaru..
Yes?
Then..
Yashamaru, do you..
..hate me?
In life there are times people hurt and get hurt by others..
But it's not that easy to dislike someone from such an experience.
Thank you, Yashamaru.
I think I understand what pain is..
Is that so..
Does that mean I am injured..
..just like everyone else?
Then I always.. feel pain..
Although it doesn't bleed..
this part hurts so much..
Bodies bleed upon physical injuries and they may look quite hurtful..
But eventually the pain will wear off as time passes..
..and they can heal faster with medical aids.
What's more serious are emotional scars..
They are the hardest to heal..
Emotional scars?
Physical and emotional scars are a bit different..
Unlike physical ones, there's no ointment available for emotional ones.. and pain may never go away.
There is only one thing that can stop such heartache.
However, as inconvenient as it may seem this cure can only be given by people other than yourself.
What? What is it?
The only thing to stop heartache..
is..
..love
Love?
Yes.
H.. how can I receive that?
What should I do to get rid of the pain?
Gaara-sama, you are already receiving it..
Love is.. care and devotion you feel for the precious ones around you..
Like the feeling Sister had for you..
I believe she loved you so very much.
The Sand Shuukaku is primarily a living spirit specialized in attacks.
It's automatic perfect defense is a proof of maternal affection..
Your mother's will remained in the sand to protect you.
Sister..
even after death..
you wanted to be there for Gaara-sama..
Yashamaru..
What is it?
About today, thank you..
..for stopping me.
You're very welcome.
After all Gaara-sama, you're my precious one around me.
Can you..
..feel my pain?
It tastes like metal..
Finishing Kick!
Konoha Whirlwind!
Kakashi.. how many did you beat?
Twenty-two.
Looks like I win again.
That was my 23rd.
Yeah, yeah.. that's great.
That attitude of yours is hip!
That makes you a worthy rival of mine.
Let's go!
Right!
Hey, Yashamaru..
I have a favor to ask..
What is it?
I want some ointments.
I'm sorry about earlier..
it must've hurt..
Please, use this ointment..
Go away, you monster..
Watch it, you brat..
You.. You are..
It's..
Go away, monster!
those eyes again..
You.. You are..
Why..
Why!?
H.. hey..
What!
- What happened!?
It.. it's Gaara!
- H.. Hey!
This guy's dead..
Father..
I knew it..
It doesn't go well at all..
How come..
..only I am such a monster?
What.. exactly am I?
There is one thing that can stop such heartache.
It's love.
Yashamaru..
What..
Why?
Why me?
Only me!
..Who?
..Why?
Impressive..
Gaara-sama..
Yashamaru..
Those eyes again..
What's the matter?
Weren't you going to retreat?
Sasuke-kun..
Naruto..
These guys..
What do they mean to you?
They..
..they are my friends!
Leave them alone, or else!
I'll kick your ass!
Now what?
Aren't you going to kick my ass?
Bring it on.
Damn you!
#Yomp@Rizon
yomp1.cjb.net
#Anime-XP@Rizon
Ani-XP.com
I understand his power.
To him, I may only be a frivolous coward..
But what.. what is this feeling that's gushing out of me?
I don't know.. I don't know, but I..
..don't want to lose to this guy even if I die!
Next - Light and Darkness
The Name Gaara