http://naruteamplus.alterista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Eternal damnation! From where it attacks!
It is using the Bunshin?
Dov' is
it originates it them!
E' useless to try to follow to me with the eyes
you will not succeed to take to me.
kage bunshin not jutsu!
Not to make it!
This is a technique
of transfer in which only
I am reflected in the mirrors.
Regarding my speed,
he is like if you were firm.
As I thought!
E' one specialty
innata!
Innata specialty?
E' like my Sharingan.
Then....
. Neanche I can copy those jutsu
and neanche to neutralize it.
Maledizione
And then!
I cannot be stopped here.
I have a dream to realize!
In my village all
they will recognize my force.
Diventer   Hokage!
Dream
Lotter   for me, my dream.
You will fight for yours
I pray you not to serbare rancor.
I want protect
one important person to me.
For he job.
For he I fight.
And for he realizzer   its desires.
This is my dream.
For this I would become a ninja
and to kill to you.
The battle with zero of visibility.
The destruction of the Sharingan.
Sasuke-kun! Naruto!
You cannot lose against that boy!
Not, Sakura!!
Not to urge them.
Eh?
Even if there was a way
in order to defeat that technique
they cannot compete with that boy.
What you would want to say?
They still do not have the force to submit
the own feelings
and to kill one person.
That boy knows the pain of being a ninja
to the contrary of Sasuke and Naruto.
Exactly.
The true ones ninja do not grow
in pacific villages like yours.
They do not have the possibility
to try the experience
fundamental of a ninja: Having to kill.
Then....
Then
Sensei, what we can make!
If I go to help Naruto and Sasuke
the Sig. Tazuna will be in danger
Even if I try with the Kage Bushin
it will be limited to stop them with its Mizu Bunshin.
I would only waste of the chakra
And then
Me dispiace, but
I am in order to place fine to this
crash immediately.
Sharingan?
Still the Sharingan?
E' the only trick that you know?
Sensei!
You will call also "trick"
but you still have fear
of the Sharingan, true Zabuza?
Ninja not an extension to the same adversary
the technical usual in order more than once.
You would have yourself to be felt honored.
The six only person who
she has seen two times
and not third time will be one.
Even if to lose
you would not succeed to win against Haku.
Neanche kakashi-sensei pu   to strike it!
But that boy is cos   strong!
Sin from when he was young
I have taught all the types to it
of skills from combat.
I have instilled
all my techniques
and the others have learned to them alone.
The result:
although it met great adversities
it succeeded to exceed them
without heart or fear for the dead women.
It is one machine from combat
known like Ninja.
Moreover on the jutsu they are
advanced even to mine.
Its innata specialty
it renders frightfully strongly.
Port one quality instrument
not like the refuse that turns to you around!
Not to surrender to me   to the first failure!
Us riprover   still and still!
Kage Bunshin not jutsu!
Not to make it.
But that it happens?
Not still, but
beginning to catch a glimpse its movements!
Once again!
Kage bunshin not jutsu!
You do not succeed to understand that it is useless?
Even if I see it
I do not succeed to go to its speed.
The water comes swept via
but if use something of various of the water
It goes well!
To make   cos !
Your square of route to me will not strike Haku.
Haku is better the combatant one never seen.
Not more boring is null than a presuntuoso speech.
Then, we begin!
It waits for a moment.
As you have said
to make   an other speech presuntuoso.
In our first combat
I was not embedding blows like an idiot.
Ended E'.
Was Haku hidden in the forest
that it examined the combat.
Haku is indeed much able one.
After to have seen a jutsu,
also only once....
it succeeds to find a way in order to defeat it.
Hour ricambier   the phrase
that you have said time to me ago.
"to say to You   that"
" the same movement does not work
on me two times."
It is not perhaps cos ?
Ninpou:
Hidden mist not jutsu.
But that what
Cos' is the this most driven in fog?
The visibility is practically zero!
Sensei.
Sakura! You are near Tazuna!
Just one.
I must have confidence in Sasuke,
Naruto and in Kakashi-sensei!
I have my job to carry out!
Oh, Sakura!
Tazuna-saint!
Not allontanatevi from me!
, I know it.
I have understood, Zabusa.
All it will end soon.
Kage Bunshin not jutsu!
Not soft never!
What!
Fire element jutsu?
You have lost too much time!
Well, slowly I am succeeding to follow it.
This fog is too much driven in end.
Neanche Zabusa would have to be
in a position to seeing to us through.
Impressive that you are successful
to bloccarli, Kakashi of the Sharingan.
Its eyes are sluices
But
the next time that you will see to me will end all.
You depend too much on your Sharingan.
What?
It speaks like if you knew all
But you
you succeed
to preview the future?
.
And you morirai.
But the forecast has been revealed wrong.
Kakashi.
You do not preview the future
neither you read my thoughts.
The Sharingan
it is a simple trick that allows you
to make to believe it the adversaries.
Who uses the Sharingan
he arranges the clairvoyance
with one ipnotica ability.
Arranging these two ability, copies the movements
of the body, the thoughts and finally the techniques
involving to you like if you saw the future.
With the clairvoyance it copies the movements.
When six assured to you of my insecurity
scruti my mind for intuire my thoughts.
And it is cos   that you read the thoughts to me.
Once confused, you will know what to say
"All the one which you make it is copiarmi."
you immedesimi in me and after....
"you cannot strike to me, bastard of one monkey! "
"to close You   that one cursed boccaccia."
When my tension is to the maximum
"That one"
it takes advantage of a skillful trick
"They are I!! "
through the genjutsu ipnotico
you induce to me to use the movement that you want you.
To the fine ones you limit to you to copy to me.
Here as you have copied mine jutsu.
"Suito Daibakufu not Jutsu!! "
"Impossible"
Therefore, the solution is simple.
With this fog
you will not succeed to see to me with your clairvoyance.
Eternal damnation!
E' difficult to defend itself with this fog!
I hold the eyes sluices
cos   in the crashs he draws near to you
potr   not to remain ipnotizzato.
But as you will fight?
Also you will not see to us.
You have perhaps forgotten?
I am the genius of the silent homicide
and I eliminate the enemies only picking up the sounds.
My movements
Not
impossible!
Eternal damnation! We were cos   near....
Naruto, is makes it to continue?
Sure, I am very well!
Tired E'.
I cannot.blame it.
Kage Bunshin not jutsu
it consumes a bag of chakra
but it is thanks to he if I have found
a way in order to contrast it.
It is not possible
Coincidence must by force be one.
Naruto, Vai!
You exit and attacks from the outside!
To succeed to us !
It will not be able to never happen.
I not to lose !
Now!
Katon Goukakyuu not Jutsu!
Eternal damnation!
It went well.
An other time.
I have understood!
Its will have a limit chakra
inasmuch as he is slowing down.
The things will not go as you would want.
Comincer   with you!
Sasuke!!
Eternal damnation
It was from much time that I did not fight
in one unfavorable situation cos  ?.
Also they are preoccupied for Sasuke and Naruto.
I must rilassarmi....
Pensare....
What will make hour?
Oh not!
Too much slow!!
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.