Subbed by Gandelr
Chekked by Kyubi
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers
takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers
narifuri kamawazu
shinjiru ga mamani
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
kewashi not hito shura not michi naka not
chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
gokusai shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro memi not hiraite
shikato ima wo mikiwamero "yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa
iza mairou!
we to are fighting dreamers
takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers
narifuri kamawazu
shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire! "bam!"
Episode #90
The outbreak of the temper
That what.... Che cos' is happened?
You help us!
Ehi Getlteman, you stop a moment.
Che cos' is happened exactly?
E' better than scappate. There is a laggiù monster.
A monster?
Which monster?
It is  an enormous snake! It has destroyed the castle in a moment!
Ehi! Of that dimensions are this snake?
Anch' I have seen it, once in my village, I have been attacked from an enormous snake.
We must sbrigarci Naruto.
It is  sure the same snake that you have seen.
Gone to destroy Konoha!?
Qual' is your answer?
Tsunade-sama!
You do not have to listen to them!
Your brother and your fiancèe would not want one similar what.
Their will.... And more important, Tsunade-sama,
Your will, you have forgotten your dream?
I comprise to you.
It is  the truth, even if are cos ì…
You open the eyes!
It is zitta Shizune!
Not there is need of give to me one answer immediately.
But we would want between one week to it.
For more, we have need than to make of the sacrifices for this "Kinjutsu ".
Prepared two bodies.
Tsunade-sama, we make it now.
If we remain entirety, we can strike them!
Tsunade-sama…
It is  true that they are weakened.
But…
I know the point weak person of Tsunade.
It is  true that Sannin is one of the 3.
It is informed…
I see that still it is not recovered…
You have fear of the blood.
Ematofobia?
We go ourselves some to more soon, Kabuto.
Tsunade,
Aspect one answer.
We are arrives to you too much late.
It has been the snake?
We go, Naruto!
Tsunade not is more.
Firm a moment "we do not go ourselves qui", "we go them "…
Welcome!
Getlteman! An other!
Tsunade-sama, been drinking too much.
Tsunade-sama…
It is not from no part.
You did not stop to say "is here" "is laggiù."
All  that  is not served to nothing…
We go to eat here.
But it is a bar!
And then?
Ve I have already said it, I do not want drink are only a child!
Idiot, I have not said to you that it was only gone to drink.
The children must to only drink the aperitifs you.
-  Welcome
It is not obligatory to eat here.
Why not a restaurant of ramen?
Six stupid?  He is  in this kind of places that collect news.
Tsunade!
Jiraiya!?
Which you make thing here us?
I have found again to you finally! They are tired.
This woman is Tsunade?
She has 50 years truly? Impossible.
To see the Three Sannin in one day…
Here, Good appetite.
I must say that…
Today I have met persons who have remembered me my past…
Orochimaru, is not true?
Che cos' is happened?
Nothing of special, we play.
This is a "Kunoichi" that recovers the wounds…
[ Donna Ninja ]
What is true?
And you, than what you want from me?
You I say frankly.
Tsunade, the High Council has to you chosen for being the Fifth Hokage.
Getlteman, "nikujaga" please.
[ Meat with potatoes ]
Fifth Hokage?
Che cos' is happened?
On purpose of the Third party…
The Third party?
Then it is true.
It has been Orochimaru, not?
Me it has said.
Orochimaru?
Orochimaru, has killed the Third party? Who is this Orochimaru?
Like me, Sannin is one of the Three.
Why the Three Sannin are of the Ninja di Konoha? Why?
Who is this child?
Uzumaki Naruto.
This child is.... Kyuubi?
Waited for a minute!
I have not ended to speak!
Who is this Orochimaru that has killed the Third party?
Eh?  Sannin  is one of the Three!
Then because you, Ero-sennin, have left it to make?
And because this would have to become the Fifth Hokage?
Naruto, is zitto.
But…
Enough.
As I said to you,
The High Council has to you chosen for being the Fifth Hokage, Tsunade.
Your answer?
You will accept?
I can resuscitare your brother and your fiancèe.
The next time, I would destroy Konoha completely.
Then?
Tsunade.
Tsunade-sama…
I do not understand more nothing.
It is  impossible.
Refusal.
Me memory of this answer.
A day, I had asked to you to exit, and you answered to me as you have made now.
But that told?
You have said Ero-Sennin.
We must bring back it to the village so that it can cure Sasuke and Kakashi-sensei.
And because it must become Hokage? And for more it refuses!
Tsunade-sama.... Impossible E' that you accept the proposal of Orochimaru…
Not innervosirti, Tsunade is the only one to being able to become Hokage.
A lot in the wars has helped us.
Nobody  can  rival with she in the cure techniques.
She is not more the small girl than Shodaime.
If account of its abilities is kept, is adapted to become the Fifth Hokage.
If it becomes Hokage, will have to return to the village.
Then, it will be able to recover them.
Is  one decision taken from the High Council of Konoha.
The Genin as you they cannot be rebelled to their word.
Jiraiya.
It is not like the last one.
It speaks badly, it is stupid and it does not have head on the shoulders.
Which thing?
It is  hard for all, when it is compared to us to the Quarter.
This Ninja was ovunque the best one.
The mastery of the techniques, intelligence, always worked.
In short, he is a little ordinary man.
But the Quarter is died a lot quickly.
For the village.... it has sacrificed its life.
The life is not like the money.
The imbecilli they could only put propia the life
cos ì  easy in game.
It has said that they are stupid?
My grandfather and also the Second.
They have made all for the peace.
But in effects they have sacrificed their life only for a dream.
Six changed, Tsunade.
I do not know  that  that tasks, but to insult them…
Even if  that  is not looked at, has 50 years.
The time changes to us.
Sarutobi-sensei is equal, the old ones that hopes of living…
It is  normal school that dies.
The title it of Hokage, is alone merda. Only the imbecilli they want it.
Species of…
You leave me!
Detention, six in a bar.
You leave me!!
Tsunade-sama.
Even if a six woman, you do not have the right
ridicolizzare "old" and the Quarter.
I will hit  you  with all my forces!
You have the courage to say this in front of me.
I waited for to you outside, marmocchio!
Tsunade-sama!
You do not have the air to comprise that they are one of the Three Sannin.
I will not use  all my force against a genin.
Which thing!?
It is  your limit of time?
I will not use  other that.
A finger.
A finger will be enough to me against of you.
Tsunade-sama…
Force…
You come, small!
Not to take game to you of me!
Merda!
Tsunade-sama!
It has hit to me with a finger.... Maledizione.
Impressive!
Ehi child!
You I want to ask one before what that you lose acquaintance.
Because…
You rage yourself so much for being a Hokage?
They are not like you.
I want the title it of Hokage absolutely.
To become Hokage…
To become Hokage is my dream!
This child…
Which thing? I must risk hour.
I still do not know it to padroneggiare well, but I must make it.
Concentration!
It is not possible!
This technique!
You take this!
The Believe your promised, it' s to hard to give me courage.
All with my feelings, the precious Time secing you.
Tachidematta kade ni
Osu and mukau kaze we kanjiteta
Machi not akani hoshikuzu I changed ni
Futari tsutsumu kedo
Sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru kara
Warau kimi ga ichiban mabushiku mieru go
Yume wa ryuusei of yo ni
Ome agari of niji of yo ni
Kagero Kono ni hikari we tsurete kuru
Mayei tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu of kotae ni naru yo
Gomakashitari shinai you chikau yo
All with my feelings, the precious Time sesing you.
We have made much time ago, drink entirety, Tsunade.
I did not have wants to see to you.
Not to say this. Six become still beautifulr than before.
Six not changed.
It leaves me dirti one what, the six solo that I did not want to meet.
More they are not interested, you you have in effects 50 years.
You have said qualche.cosa?
Not nothing, I was thinking next to the old times.
The next episode:
The inheritance of Shodaime