E' in delay!
Naruto, you are a po' firm!
Because between all the Sensei,
only ours it is cos ì  in delay!
All the other groups if they have gone some give
some teaching part with their new one…
… and also Iruka-sensei if n' it has gone.
It is not important!
Naruto! And now that you are arranging?
The guilt is its that is in delay!
Argh! It will be guilt yours if you put to us in the troubles.
I adore these types of jokes!
Figuararsi if a Jonin falls in one
trap from two moneies like that one.
! Naruto is too much stupid!
There is falled! There is falled eccome!
Sensei, us excuses.
I have tried to stop Naruto, but…
Ok! Ok!
But it is truly a Jonin?
That to say?
The first impression that you have made me…
… it is PESSIMA!
The test!
Practice of survival!
Vediamo… S ì, in order to begin said
that everyone of you would have to be introduced.
To introduce itself?
And what we would have to say?
Oh be', what it appeals to to you, what hated,
your dreams in the drawer…
… things cos ì, insomma!
Ehi, ehi!
Then, than you say some to introduce to you
you for first, Sensei?
I?
Be', I call Hatake Kakashi…
I do not have no intention of dirvi
what appeals to to me and what does not appeal to to me.
Dreams in the drawer? Be', even if ve you said them....
And in order to end… I have various interests!
In practical it has only said its name to us.
…
It touches you.
Parts you!
I call Uzumaki Naruto!
It appeals to the ramen to me…
… and it still appeals to more the ramen to me
that it offers Iruka-sensei to me to the Ichiraku!
Us ò  that hatred three minuteren are those
in which aspect that the ramen is ready.
Mine hobby it is to make jokes and to eat tazzoni of ramen!
And my dream…
… is to exceed in ability all the Hokage…
… and to make to understand to all people
of the village how much I am worth!
True E'… has grown just well.
Well, the next one.
I am Haruno Sakura!
What is one that it appeals to to me…
… indeed, one person…
… ahem.. then I do not know if dirvi
my dream in the drawer… beh…
My dreams are…
And that what hatreds?
Then?
NARUTO!
The girls of its age more are interested
to the love that to the training.
We go with the last one!
I call Uchiha Sasuke.
Hatred a bag of things
and me of it it does not appeal to nobody in particular.
I do not want to speak about my dreams…
… but I have an ambition…
… that I do not mean to call dream.
To bring back to the antichi makes my Clan you…
… and to kill who I know!
He will not speak at all about me!
Sasuke-kun is indeed fantastic!
As I thought…
Well, you three have of the personalities
a lot different. You appeal to to me.
From tomorrow you assegner ò  a task!
Getlteman! Which task draft!
In order to begin, one what to only make between of we.
What? What? What? What Coooosa…!
A survival practice.
A survival practice?
Why like mission us from a practice?
Of those of it we have made a bag school!
Not draft of one simple practice.
That… which type of practice is?
Ehi, what is of cos ì  amusing Sensei?
, it is not only that… they are sure that
if ve you said it you would scare.
Uhm?
Of the ventisette that they have been graduated
only nine will be able to become Genin.
The remaining eighteen will have to return to the academy.
This practice is a examination of income with
a rate advanced failure to 66%.
Approval? There are terrorizza you!
But it is absurd! With all the hard work
that we have made…
… then to that what is served the diploma examination!
Be', that one…
… it only served to establish who had
the characteristics in order to become Genin.
Cooosa!
However tomorrow, after the practice,
to establish ò  who to promote or to bocciare.
Portatevi the equipment ninja,
the encounter will be to the 5 of morning!
Not to make me ò  to bocciare! Also to cost
to fill up of botte Kakashi-sensei.
Mostrer ò  to all my force!
With the cabbage that to make me ò  to bocciare!
If not superer ò  the test,
dovr ò  to separate to me from Sasuke-kun!
This will be a love test!
E' all, finished reunion.
Oh, I forgot…
… not fairies breakfast…
… otherwise vomiterete all!
Buongiorno…
Buongiorno boys!
Six in ritardooo!
A black cat has crossed me the road, percui…
We begin endured…
I have put the alarm clock to the 12.
!!
There are two door-bells. Your task
it will be to steal them to me within that hour.
Who not will be successful, will jump the lunch…
… legacy to a log will come and me it will be
to watch while I eat.
E' for that he has said to us…
..di not to make breakfast…
A moment!
Why is alone two door-bells?
Exact! By force one of you
legacy to the log will end.
Moreover who will not take it will fail
the mission and will come bocciato…
… and it will have to return to the academy!
It could be one single… or all and three!
Used also yours shuriken…
… also because if you will not mean it
you will not exceed never this examination.
But Sensei… is dangerous!
True E'! Six cos ì  imbranato that
you do not know not to schivare cancel!
In the society…
… those most insufficient ones can turn out
of intralcio for the others.
For this the boy with the qualit ò
more insufficient he would go ignored.
After this speech we can
to give marks them of beginning…
The boy with the more insufficient qualities!
Not to churn to you.
I have not still given the way!
Incredible! I have not seen it to move.
Then the force of a Jonin is this!
Be', to at least has come wants mean it you.
I do not know because but begun to appeal to to me.
We can begin.
, then ready…
… VIA!
Which thing you want to know?
They are sure that you have not offered a tea to me
only for drink in company.
That type of university professor is…
… the Jonin of the group of Naruto?
Kakashi?
It preoccupies to you?
I have I feel some voices… not much good ones to my opinion.
Che cos' is?
E' the list of turns out you of the Genin
of which up to now Kakashi has been taken care.
I want to see!
But what…!
One of the fundamental abilities to ninja dev' a being
knowing itself to hide camouflaging the own presence.
Well, by now they will be all hiding.
Ah?
I defy you to a clean and directed duel!
Che cretino!
It knows to me that you have something outside place.
The only thing outside place is your hats absurd!
Hour you insegner ò  the first foundation
of the combats of a ninja.
That is the martial limbs!
For martial limbs the Kumite agrees,
that is the fight to hands knots…
Nevertheless… it wants to use an arm!
What takes to you? Ahead, made under.
S ì, but that you make us with that book?
That I make us?
I read. E' that by now the argument has taken to me.
But you do not make case us.
Even if I read, to you does not have to import.
HOUR I FILL UP YOU OF BLOWS!
Merda..! Flying soccer!!
What!!
Scemotto, a ninja does not have to offer
its back in continuation.
It is not possible! It has the hands…
… in the position of the tiger!
It wants to use one technical similar against Naruto?
It will not make it indeed?
That one is a sign of fire.
Then that teaching
it is not limited to schivare the blows.
Naruto! Scappa immediately or morirai!
Eh?
Too much late.
The leggendario secret blow
of the Village of the Leaf!
PAIN MILLENARIOOO!
Oh… it was not one technical magical
but simply clistere devastating.
Then of cretini ce they are two.
Vediamo…
However he is indeed strong.
And now that it is made?
Eternal damnation! If it thinks that it ends here…
But… but it is not possible!
Indeed hard E' to the contrary of the voices that turn!
Perhaps the tests of Kakashi are a po' difficult.
S ì, for ò…
… its percentage of promotions…
..E' ZERO!
Its examinations…
… they make always one massacre.
Then that you make?
If you do not take a door-bell
within noon, you will jump the lunch.
I have understood!
You have said of wanting to exceed the Hokage,
but me it does not seem a lot in shape.
I know! I know! It watches that I can fight
also to fast!
I, instead am to diet, and yesterday evening.
… I have not touched food. That hunger that I have!
First they have been only a po' imprudent.
Eternal damnation…! With the empty stomach
I feel myself without energies…
But those costs that costs,
I must take that door-bell.
In a way or the other…
… I must fargli recognize…
… my force…
… and to become a ninja!
Ah Ah Ah! This is my special Technique
Advanced of the Multiplication of the Body!
Is others seven Naruto?
What! They are not real illusions but bodies!
All real ones!
The Advanced Technique of the Multiplication…
You will not put neanche a finger on Iruka-sensei…
… or to kill to you ò!
Why not us tests, cursed demon!
The Multiplication of the Body!
E' one technical complex that concurs
to create various physical copies of if same…
… it is the prohibited technique of the forbidden parchment
with which Naruto it has struck Mizuki.
Considered your force,
you will be able to maintain it single for a minute.
Six pompous ciarliero and. In practical, Naruto…
… you cannot still win to me with that technique.
What! From the shoulders!
Ehi Kakashi-sensei, we had not said that
a ninja it does not have is made to pick to the shoulders!
After to have executed the technique they are exited
secretly from the river and they have arrived give to you behind.
And approval the mega to clistere before,
now to take ?  the satisfaction to me…
Naruto! Then you the cables!
That type… indeed a beautiful diversivo.
… to give back a blow to you!
What?
Naruto has been hit…
… alone?
Ouch!!!
You…
I bet that six you Kakashi-sensei!
You have taken my aspect, true?
I could say the same one of you!
I, instead, say that six you!
You stinks of old like the sensei!
But which it smells, deficient!
Felt a po'…
… we try to melt the technique…
… cos ì  we will remain in two
and we will understand who is the sensei.
Cretino! You could not think to us before!
It watches that you six me, deficient!
Well!
Naruto… that figuraccia.
Stupid. The sensei have used
the technique of the substitution.
E' one technical that consists in replacing itself
fastly with an animal or an object…
… giving cos ì  to our adversary the illusion
to have to us hit in order then to take advantage of of the disattenzione.
First Kakashi had been seized from Naruto…
… and quickly it has been exchanged
with one of the Alter Ego of Naruto…
… taking advantage of its same attack.
A door-bell!
It must essergli fallen…
… in the confusion before.
It was clearly that trap was one…
Sure that that Jonin is indeed Bravo.
It does not lower the guard not even for a moment
while it is to the taken ones with Naruto.
The door-bell!
You must use of the techniques using the head…
… otherwise he will be your adversary to use of you.
And then, scemotto…
… it makes me the favor not falling
in obvious traps cos  ?.
The ninja they must anticipate the adversary!
I know anch' ' ste things!
Instead he is because you do not know to them that you I say.
Understood?
The movements are mistake to you for via of your impulsività.
Arrived E' my opportunity.
Finally it is uncovered!
Just six…
Waaah! You have centered!
Sasuke, wretch! You have exaggerated!