Exceeding the Limit...
Sasuke's Decision!!
Over there, eh?
Over here!
Damn..
I'll return them to you!
It was a clone..
Curse you..
Uchiha.. Sasuke!
Why are you hesitating?
Why do you..
..run away!?
Here!
Pass it!
Shoot!
What do we do?
We haven't mastered Wall Climbing no Jutsu yet..
Y.. you are..
Here..
Gaara..
It's Gaara of the Sand..
Run for it!
Wait!
Don't leave me alone!
Help!
I..
don't want to be alone..
anymore..
No!
Gaara-sama, please calm yourself!
Yashamaru..
I won't let you..
I won't let you run from me!
Uchiha Sasuke!
Damn it..
What's that incredible power?
Are you afraid of me?
It's too much..
Uchiha..
..Sasuke!
Afraid of my existence!
Don't forget..
You're my prey..
Hold it!
Why..
What is it you want from me?
Your eyes tell me that you know what true loneliness is..
Furthermore..
You also know that such solitude is the worst possible pain in the world..
I've told you..
You have the same eyes as I do..
The eyes, filled with hatred and death, that long for strength..
Just like mine..
Your eyes tell me how badly you wish to kill the one who put you through the hell called loneliness..
Yes, that look..
Alright, timeout..
Gaara, is it?
I don't care what you think you know about Sasuke..
You shouldn't talk as if you can see Sasuke's inner self.
What were you trying to accomplish, coming all the way out here before your match?
Fighting is all about..
putting the lives of others and your own on the line..
To fight to the death..
Only then can the victor be assured of the meaning of his existence..
So you're saying you want a deathmatch instead of a tournament, is that it?
Uchiha..
You must be wishing for the same thing..
deep down inside..
You wish to determine if you deserve to live..
You wonder if you're really strong enough..
Stronger than the one you are dying to kill..
What's the matter..
Uchiha Sasuke!
Are you afraid of me?
Has your fear overtaken the hatred, the killing urge?
Is your reason for existence as puny as that?
Fight with me..
..and confirm it.
Verify your value..
your existence..
Feel it!
If you crave for an answer..
..come!
It was intentional..
only I was left alive..
But for what reason?
No..
I know why..
He let me live so that he doesn't have to feel guilty about killing the entire clan..
My brother Itachi chose me to be the avenger..
That's why he chose me!
Let me have some fun..
Uchiha Sasuke!
I'll finish this now!
End your suffering by dying quickly..
..you old man.
I told you already..
..you're going to die too.
You..
Get your hands off me!
I won't! No matter what..
Not until I pull out your soul completely!
At this rate..
Gaara!
I felt it.
I see!
..so that's what it was!
Impossible..
He countered the transformed Gaara?
The reason I'm so excited..
I just got the answer.
It's this pain..
Defeating a man strong enough to hurt me and utterly destroying him..
..that's what gives me an even greater sense of existence!
He wounded the invincible Gaara..
Not once but twice..
He's.. a monster..
No..
The real monster is..
After all, Gaara has only transformed his right arm so far..
More! I want more!
What?
What the hell is he!?
He keeps changing shape..
He's faster than before!
Dodging his attacks would be impossible if I wasn't reading his movements..
I would have been long gone without these eyes..
But..
Chidori isn't an option..
Fire Element - Blazing Fireball no Jutsu!
Seems like fire is useless against sand..
Besides, a jutsu of that level isn't..
Die!
Chidori is the only way after all..
Well, your limit is at two shots..
it seems..
Damn..
At your present chakra level, that's the most amount of times you can use Chidori a day..
In any case..
this is a jutsu that can't be used in a real fight unless you have the sharingan as well..
However, using the sharingan and the other jutsu at the same time is..
just the same as consuming all your chakra by detonating it inside your body..
Still, you're rather impressive, as I expected..
Even when I use Chidori, or Lightning Edge as it's otherwise known..
after four times in a single day I use up all my chakra..
If I attempt for a third one.. what would happen?
There would be no third one..
Never forget that.
When you try to strain the activation of a jutsu..
not only will the jutsu fail..
but you also lose all remaining chakra..
..and your life in the worst-case scenario.
Even if you survive, you'll still be in a tight spot no matter what..
especially if you have..
What's wrong?
Is this all your existence means to you?
Let me make it clear..
You..
..are weak!
You're too soft..
Your hatred isn't strong enough.
The power of hate is the power to kill..
The power to kill, is the power of vengeance!
Your hatred is weaker than mine!
Shut up..
Do you understand what that means?
Shut up!
It means..
..you're weaker than me!
Itachi chose me as an avenger..
..in order to have him killed.
I am an avenger!
The curse seal again..
Damn it..
Can't move..
Sasuke-kun!
#Yomp@Rizon
yomp1.cjb.net
#Anime-XP@Rizon
Ani-XP.com
Hey, Yashamaru..
..what is pain?
I've never been injured so..
I wonder what it's like..
Maybe I'm wounded..
Although it doesn't bleed..
..my heart hurts so much
It's suffocating..
..and somehow it's very painful.
Next - An Assassin in the Moonlight