! ! From it releases!
It goes well.
But after not complaining to you.
Ok, cheese!
I am Konohamaru!
Ninja Registry
Official number 102607
Date of birth 10/10, age 12, Balance
I was always indeciso on rests…
Thoughts that in order to obtain those
result I have put us three hours very!
, but, but…!
How to say?
It has those I do not know that of artistic that…
RIFALLA!
By no means!!!
Rifalla!
Not to say cos ì!
Transformation!
Please, Hokage-sama…
Sexy, true Jutsu…
That technical devastating that you have.
In any case…
… that fine it has made yours coprifronte?
I want to conserve until the encounter.
Cos ì  will be like new.
However it is…
… the indentità paper ninja is an important document…
… secret that only belongs to the village.
But what would be this face!
Be'!
To me nobody has never said these rules to them.
Old!! You fight against of me!
Sar ò  I the fifth Hokage, Konohamaru-sama!!
Owwwww!!!
But it never does not end…
Who has put the trap!
Been well, signorino!
… and for recorded, I inform to You that
not there is some trap!
Oh… that one is…
the demon from the nine tails.
Like hatred that losing insopportabile!
I have understood! Six you that me
you have played that ugly shooting!
But six dumb one!
Six simply inciampato alone!
Naruto! It leaves it immediately!
That boy is the grandson of the member of parliament Third Hokage!
When they discover that they are the grandson
of the Hokage they lower all the crest.
Tsk! E' you serve them also he,
exactly like the master quattrocchi.
Something does not go?
It tries to beat to me if you have the liver!
Now that you know that I am the grandson
of the third party…
And you know that me of frega of who six grandson!
Stupid!!!
This boy.
C… What!!
That annoyance…
You listen to me, she is the grandson of the third Hokage.
Until it will come beaten, will not attract
the attention of the persons.
It will not obtain nothing of good from this.
I, its chosen master, Ebisu,
I know us ò  that it is better for she.
It wants to become the fifth Hokage, just?
If she will learn the ninjutsu from me,
to become Hokage will be simple.
S ì! To learn from me is the better one scorciatoia
in order to become a Hokage.
It comprises this, signorino?
It has not listened to me!
If it has gone some after Naruto.
What! You say indeed!
Signorino!!!
Goodness knows as it will have made to become cos ì.>.?
Twentieth attack to surprise was its, today!
The fact preoccupies me that is with to Naruto.
We hope you do not make yourself to contagiare from its scemenze.
You stop it to follow to me! That devil you want!
Six rincretinito to you…
Impressive, six successful one to see to me here behind.
The gossips on you are true.
Ehi! You lascer ò  to be my master!!
What?
In exchange, insegnami the Technique of the Erotismo
that it has defeated my grandfather!
Not to think to us not even.
Not dirmi this, Main!
Master!
Master! Master! Master!!
uff…
it goes well…
Now it listens to me carefully…
For having one good mastery of the ninjitsu,
you must have a good control of the "Chatra".
Cha-tora?
(cat)
S ì, Chatra!
Perhaps master, you want to say "Chakra"?
Sta' zitto! The ninja with talent they say cos ì!
Oh, then will be cos ì!
Phew… fortune that is an idiot.
It listens, the Chakra is…
In little words it is the energy that is used
when the Jutsu (technical is used).
That is in order to execute the techniques of the ninja it must miscelare the chakra,
that is the energy of the body collection from the same cells
and the spiritual energy, than is acquired with the experience.
Then with the just imposition of the hands, the jutsu active.
… if the laws from one parchment!
, it seems well that you something know.
But in order to use the jutsu well, you must…
I must…
To work hard and with intensity.
To work hard and with intensity?
, I have intention to teach to you from endured,
therefore it is better than it prepares to you!
To the orders, Master!
Ok, before for ò  test to transform to you.
What?
I want to see the level of your qualities ninja.
But in what I must myself be transformed?
mmmhh…
Ok, we begin with becoming that girl.
C$r-nessun.problema!
Transformation.
Then? I am similar?
good… mmmhh… dressed and the stoffa they are similar
That what you say!
You listen to me, signorino,
when it is transformed in me,
circles make me more snella.
You. terrible…
Why they are the only one that has taken a fist?
- Bookcase -
Ok! Now we will study in library!
S ì, Master!
I have already said to you not to leaf through without permission
in this store, Naruto!
- Baths publics of the village -
This is the last thing!
We enter and we give ourselves to make!
Master goes well!
Transformation! 		Transformation!
Naruto, still you!!!
But because always and only to me?
Me dispiace…
E' because I am the grandson of the third Hokage
Not preoccuparti.
eh?
Hour you would have to be ready for
to execute the Technique of the Erotismo.
Us servants now single a little practical.
Commandos Main!
Ok, remembers "Bon, Kyuu, Bon to you"! It makes it now!!
(Abundant Breast - Tight Life - Beautiful Culetto)
It goes well, master!!
Transformation!
Then as I seem you?
Noooooo!!! Mistaken! More snella.
S ì  Master!
Now as it goes?
Not, not the much beautifulst one!
Ok, Master! Ehi, than it says some of this?
Damned Naruto,
what you have intention to make with the signorino?
That boy where he will be!
I am the better master whom he has educated
many future candidates to the title it of Hokage.
Estirper ò  all the virus that they infect my students!
Dimmi… why you hold us cos ì  a lot to strike your grandfather?
My grandfather me chiam ò…
"Konohamaru".
I have the same name of the village.
(Konoha = leaf)
even if all know this name…
nobody has never called me cos ì.
When they see to me or they call to me…
all the one which they see she is the grandson of the third Hokage.
Nobody knows to me for what I am worth.
They are I stew of this.
Here because…
Idiot, who would want to know a plump child like you?
eh?
To take the name of Hokage is not cos ì  easy.
What!
It is not cos ì  easy.
Hokage, Hokage.. if you want cos ì  a lot this name, then.
Then what!
Before you will have to strike to me!
Hokage Member of parliament,
I was trying.
Six you Iruka?
Naruto has delivered its identity card ninja?
S ì…
I have made one lecture yesterday
to a plate of ramen,
… but it continued to repeat that it would have become one
large ninja and that all to the village would have appreciated it
and they would have recognized its value…
Naruto cultivates a dream difficult to come true itself.
Eh?
As very you know the only ones to knowing that Naruto
it is the incarnation of the vixen to nine tails,
they are the adults who 12 years ago
they fought that demon.
From then, in order protect that secret I have assigned strict
punishments to anyone smashed the rule of Hush.
In this way the new generation is some to the dark one…
..e ?  it would have had to us to help Naruto.
The fourth Hokage exhorted people
to consider Naruto like a hero.
This was its desire,
but he for ì  in imposing I seal.
Hero?
The fourth Hokage sigill ò  the demon
in the navel of a baby.
For the salvation of the village,
Naruto divenne container of that demon.
But nobody consider ò  Naruto like salvatore.
Indeed, the persons identified in he
the demon vixen from the nine tails.
Silently they have transmitted to the own sons…
… their attitude of hostility towards of he.
Iruka, you know it…
What?
That when the men despise one person…
… their eyes make colds and pungenti like the ice.
I have finds to you to you!
Demon vixen…
Still those hostile eyes.
Cursed!
Force signorino! We return to house.
NOT! I to defeat ò  my grandfather and conquister ò
the title it of Hokage! And making ò  now!
Not to intralciare to me!
A Hokage must be Bravo in all the abilities ninja.
(Sincerity, Humanity, Gentility,
Wisdom, Loyalty, Precaution, Justice)
It must moreover padroneggiare more than 1000 techniques.
Transformation!
You take this! Sexy not Jutsu!
(Technical of the Erotismo)
Uhm? It does not work!
That technical gross it is never that one!
I am a gentiluomo!
Artifice cos ì  schifosamente sconcio
it will not never have effect on me!
Signorino! To be with those cretino the only thing that
you will learn will be like becoming stupid!
To follow my indications is the way more express
in order to deserve the name of Hokage!
Force, to house!
Not!
Kage Bunshin Not Justu!!!
(Technical Advanced of the Multiplication of the Body)
Wow… he is incredible!!!
Ridicule!
For your information they are
teaching of high degree…
they are a very various adversary from Mizuki.
Master…
Transformation!
Ebisu-sama!
This the chiamer ò…
Harem not Jutsu!
(Technical of HAREM -:D LOL)
It has combianto the Kage Bunshin with the Sexy not Jutsu!
It has created an other technique without sense.
Even if perhaps against of me it would be lethal.
Perhaps…
Eternal damnation!
They are not neanche successful to strike my master quattrocchi!
I want that people you respect to me endured!
Because I do not succeed to us!
At all it is cos ì  easy.
Eh?
Because it means to become a Hokage,
the ninja better of the village.
Here about what you are speaking.
With many deprivations…
… I was often single…
and to the end I have obtained
respect of one single person…
… and in order to succeed I have made one hard work to us of the devil.
It wants determination to us…
Determination?
In order to obtain the respect of all and to be Hokage…
I assure to you that scorciatoie do not exist!
If you to become Hokage…
… before you will have to strike to me!
MPF! But that beautiful it foretells you have made me!
Not to consider more your disciple me!
From now in then…
… we will be we avail again!
Me dispiace, our roads are divided.
but…
… a day us contenderemo the title it of Hokage…
It continues to train you of hour in then,
Konohamaru.
The road in order to become a true one ninja…
… as soon as it is begun.