Subbed by # [ Fabry ]
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not
fukinukeru Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda Yeah!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite
kanashimi mo hoho tsutatte
namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa
tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Yahoo!
I have taken!
Eternal damnation…
But like possible?
I would have had to hurt it seriously
but on he it has not worked
and those its attack…
Akamaru, listens to me.
We will use the Gatsuuga in order to stop it.
Hour!
Gatsuuga!
Kuchiyose not jutsu!
It does not go well.
I will play  for you a funeral song
This tizio… who is?
What?
Two against two. Perfect E'.
Is not true, Sakon?
If the Four are employing cos ì  a lot
they must it are imbattuti
in of the enemies forts like they
or they are losing time uselessly
Probably to slow down them it is Jiroubou,
that one always starved.
or Kidoumaru, that it always loses
time to giocherellare
But most intelligent, Sakon,
it is also most problematic, right?
It will not be calmed finchè will not have
killed all its adversaries
even if he had the possibility to continue.
He believes of being the best one in absolute
only why he is more strongly of the group
Strangely,
also Tayuya is not type to surrender.
But from when we have sent He,
nothing has been left the case.
Kimimaro.
It will be gotten rid easy of
all  that  that does not serve me more
Lascerò  not to carry  to you via Sasuke!
To how much it seems is much
trash here around
But to the very fine…
it also remains always trash…
in attended of being jetty via.
You are zitto!
You come.
I destroy to you!
This would be the funeral song?
It is controlling them with the melodia of its flauto!
Merda…
I am going away too much from she.
What I make? What I make hour?
It does not go at all well!
Akamaru!
Ooops, qunidi is that one l ì  the true one?
Tarenken!
You hold!
We are siamesi siblings
Of usual my Ukon brother rests within me
… but to times in battle
it comes outside for give to me one hand.
Therefore is this its innata ability?
Ukon  can  extend arms and legs
from every part of my body
and it is in degree is to attack
that to defend
Just cos ì!
Tarenkyaku!
Three soccer at the same time
they make, true badly?
Well, the next one sar -
We do not have time to lose, Sakon.
We will defeat in a moment.
USA level 2
It goes well, goes well.
Mine fratellone he is impaziente
That hat mass behind
its head was not feint.>.
Once appeared the other boy
its chakra is increased ten times.
E' a battle without hope.
That day…
How it would appeal to to you, brother?
In small pezzetti.
Well, the moment has arrived of
to show your determination.
I will take care myself  once of you for all.
Very said!
But this is worth also for you!
Tzk, is being gotten annoyed.
But I am beginning to understand
as they move.
…  the problem is that they are too much far.
Merda…
this is all which
we are resolutions to make.
What?
You say that it is the case to make it?
Not, we cannot Akamaru.
To make it here, without nobody of ours
companions, would be too much dangerous!
You would have to know it, not?
If we used that technique, we would have cos ì
little chakra from not being able to us more to move.
If we had to fail, moriremo invano.
Akamaru…
In order it makes me to bite from you…
I must have been pessimo landladies.>.
I have understood Akamaru.
I will make  as you have said.
E' our only occasion!
Garouga!
Akamaru, hour!
What?
Not to mistake, Akamaru.
Fagli to see on what there are trains to you!
Dynamic marking!
As it dares to make one schifosa what cos  ì!
With this, we have ended the preparation
Inuzuka Ryuu Jinjuu Combi Henge!
Soutourou!
Finally something of interesting,
even if stupid beast is only one
What will succeed to make?
You take this!
It salted?
Sakon that you make! To your right!
Merda!
Garouga!
Heh, than of tasks of this?
The spin of the Garouga is such that
our field of vision is practically zero.
Even if we do not succeed to touch to you
you come equally cut.
If a directed attack arrives you,
you end in pieces.
Six pushed to you too much beyond.
Huge.
I was just thinking about
to divide to us in order to fight.
But c-that.>.?
They are uniforms!
True E' that if we had been hit
we would have been hurt seriously
But the true show begins hour!
Eternal damnation…
, I know it, Akamaru.
We can use the Garouga
only an other time.
The next one will be the last one.
And we can kill them both!
Garouga!
We cannot hide!
You I have said, we we do not use the eyes!
Why via scoviamo through
your odore and we attack that one!
Alpha!
Beta!
Kuchiyose!
Rashoumon!
That it forces…
They are resolutions to damage the Rashoumon,
the absolute defense of Orochimaru-sama.
But…
Arrived E' the end!
Akamaru!
Akamaru, you have …
… tried to cover to me!
Merda!
It has made of new!
Argh! My eyes!
Eternal damnation!
Merda!
This is not simple urine.
E' a powerful acid.
The eyes are burning me!
Dov' has gone the other?
Hey…
It tries to me to you?
Me of it I occupy. You go
to wash the eyes to you in the river.
This is my special ability.
Neanche with yours fiuto and your brain
you will be in a position to defeating to me!
Against my abilities not there is escape.
Sai that the flow of chakra
it encircles every single organ?
E' closely legacy
to the organs and the epiteliali cells.
In these cells the proteins reside all
that they are taken care to manage
the cycle of life and dead women.
And when within in level 2
they are in a position to using the chakra for
to divide and to reconstruct these proteins.
In poor words,
I can divide in pieces my body,
and to enter in that one of
adversaries in order then to reconstruct to me.
Akamaru…
Me dispiace, Akamaru…
Soon we will be of new together.
Every time, in whichever place,
always we have been!
Yeah! Beautiful job, Akamaru.
Fortunately those that have fallen in
trap had the parchment of the Earth
At this rate we will be first!
Akamaru without warning has been scared.
It succeeds to perceive the chakra of the enemies.
But this is before the time
that I see it cos ì  scared.
Those boys who are
fighting laggiù…
… they are not at all normal.
Seventh encounter.
Uzumaki Naruto vs. Inuzuka Kiba
Hey! That doggie does not have to immischiarsi!
It would be only of impiccio during the crash!
That stupid…
Also Akamaru must fight…
Well,
Akamaru, we go!
You take this!
Successful E' to find it!
Naruto.
Hour  I will resume  Akamaru.
M-but that…!
You have given what to it?
Its hair has become red!
Here why Akamaru is called
(Aka=rosso)
We go Akamaru!
Juujin Ninpo!
Juujin bunshin!
Hour!
Shikyaku not jutsu!
I am arriving.
Juujin taijutsu ogi!
Gatsuuga!
Akamaru!
You take the pill of the soldier.
it uses the Gijyu Ninpo!
Gatsuuga!
But stavolta.. they are forced to surrender to me…
My cells are rambling
free in your body
and I can make in way to hold isolated yours.
We are in one be of fusion.
We are sharing the same body.
You have said to share?
Exactly.
I can use with you one dead women
brutal, that it consists
in tearing to you from the body
all the cells that belong to you,
I have understood…
In such case…
What will happen making cos ì?
The suicide!
That stupid…
We moriremo together.
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
bokura kara shaberi kaketure
meiwaku ni omou kara
sonna fuan wo kakaetie
yuuki wo dashite mitayo
umaku shaerinai bokuno
bukiyou na hanashi
kimi wa mimi wo sorasazuni
chanto kiite kuretayo
soredaked bokuwa ukarete shimaunosa
dakedo kimi wa boku nante
nantomo omottenai yone
setsunai yo
dakedo
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de!
hajimete kimi to shabereta
What has this boy?
One innata defense?
Merda! I have not never seen or
felt to speak about one technical similar!
Nonstante is fighting with all my forces
my attacks not
they make not even a scratch!
Also with like you, it does not import to me.
I will make   pieces!
Next episode!
Everyone in just the combat.