http://naruteamplus.alterista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Naruto and the others are already fighting!
Also we
One called instrument Shinobi
Getlteman!
Mr. Giichi!
You open!
You come to the bridge with me!
This time if we go all together
we will defeat the men of Gatoo!
Inari
I have stopped to fight.
Also your father
the called man hero
not there is more.
If we will fight
we will cause many victims.
We do not want more to lose our beloveds.
Nobody wants to make more things
which it could repent.
Sure one.
Also I do not want more possession regretted!
And he is for that we must fight!
A true man must living without regretted.
I want my mother, my grandfather well,
and also to you Mr. Giichi....
and anyone of this city!
Now I know that....
simply complaining itself
pu   not protect nobody.
Now I have understood it!
Inari sta becoming an admirable boy.
You want indeed to leave it to go alone?
You open!
I pray to you you fight to my flank!
I pray to you you listen to me!
But because....
Perche nobody opens the door?
"Six fort"
(Naruto! )
Zabuza, six arrived too much far away.
Your ambitions were too much large.
You have failed the attempt to assassinate
the Mizukage and the coup d'tat.
You have abandoned county and six
become a ninja without rules.
In little time your reputation has arrived
to the village of the leaf.
You had need of money for yours vendetta
and for scappare from ninja the pursuers.
Probably the reason is this for
which six joined to you to Gatoo.
Zabuza...... six convinced that I am survival
only thanks to the Sharingan?
Hour you mostrer   one mine
technique and not one copy.
Lightning Edge!
(What! )
In the hand such amount of chakra has one
that it is even succeeded to see it.
You six too much dangerous one.
Tazuna, the man that you wanted to kill
it is the courage of this country
the bridge that it is constructing is the hope.
With your ambition you want to sacrifice
too many persons.
This is not from a ninja.
Not me of frega nothing.
I have always fought for my dream
and always making !
You I repeat.
Hm?
Rassegnati!
In your future there is the dead women.
Naruto-kun
I pray to you you kill to me!
Now sbrigati!
Why it continues to hesitate?
They are not of agreement!
To be strong is only the your reason of life?
You could makes you to appreciate for qualcos' other....
not necessarily for your force.
The day that I have met to you in the forest
I thought that I and you resembled yourself.
You would have to succeed to comprise to me.
Me spiace that you must soil the hands.
Sure that this....
That this is the only way?
S
If you had met to you in others
circumstances we will be able to become friends.
(I pray to You, realizes your dreams)
Also Sasuke also he had its dreams!
Thanks. you will become strong indeed.
The superdriven in fog is beginning to diradarsi.
There are two persons l !
It seems are being watched to vicissitude.
I do not succeed to see well....
Qual' is Master Kakashi?
Oh! One is muovendo!
Scusami, Naruto-kun.
I cannot still die!
(arrived E' indeed the end? )
Cos' has happened?
Zabuza-saint one....
My future is the dead women?
Six mistaken to you of new Kakashi.
It is not possible, you will not go alone to the bridge!!
I have tried in all the city,
but nobody is intentional to come.
I have not chosen.
But
It waits for!
Six anchor a child!
Sar   still a child, but
I know what wants to say to fight.
Because they are son of my Father!
(Beloved)
He waits for Inari!!
(But, dov' he has gone? )
Hey, the fog is beginning
slowly to diradarsi.
But what!
What is happening laggi?
But that one is not the masked child?
One is intromesso in order protect Zabuza.
This boy  already died....
Optimal job, Haku.
Kakashi-sensei!
(It has intention to cut to us to all and two!? )
Of sure it has been an optimal instrument!
In the dead women it even has to me
offered this possibility!
"Haku, unfortunately"
" stanotte account to abandon the county."
"But a day torner   sure"
" in order to take of the possession."
"For this I do not have need
of consolation or encouragement."
"That one of which I have need truly is"
"I know It."
"you do not preoccupy yourselves."
"I am one your arm, Zabusa-saint."
"You hold me to your flank
and you use to me as wished."
"Six Bravo boy."
Bastard!
Six successful one to move to you because Haku is dead.
Unforgivable!
Naruto! It remains l !
This is my crash!
Naruto?
Naruto! You are well!
(Sakura-chan....)
How it is Sasuke-kun?
Naruto! Dov' Is Sasuke-kun?
Sakura....
Kakashi!
Not there is time for distrarsi!
I come with you.
Cos   not disubbidirai to the orders of your master.
Thanks
Sasuke....
Six cold....
This is not more an illusion.
Not to withhold to you because there are I.
In these situations you can cry how much you want.
I have always taken 100 to the examinations
academics of the ninja.
I knew beyond 100 Ninja rules.
In class I have always given the just answer.
A day, me present   this question....
"To write the 25 doctrine"
As always I gave the answer....
"a ninja it does not have to express
the own feelings
in no circumstance ".
"a ninja it must give priority"
to the mission and not to show
never just the pain."
(Therefore this is the life of the ninja.)
(E' one life too much hard end)
Sasuke-kun....
(Because)
(Because I do not succeed to hit it? )
Eternal damnation!
You cannot defeat to me in the conditions
in which it finds to you now.
What!
Not you of six shrewed one?
What is the true force.
But what is happening?
This is a goodbye, Demon!
Hour you cannot use both the arms.
You cannot not assume
the positions for the techniques.
You it has played just well Zabuza.
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear