Subtitles By: BakaSan
It is definently your fate to lose against me.
Nobody knows that until the fight is over!
I don't know how much you've suffered by having
your father killed in the past, but...
It’s a huge mistake to believe that
fate's been already decided because of that.
You're hopeless.
Examiner... it's over.
Loser.
Deep Power of a Loser!
Don't run away.
I won't run away... I won't bend my words...
That's my Nindo.
I won't bend my words...
That's my Nindo, too.
Phrases I've heard before.
I won't lose against a guy like you... who's
always running away from your fate or whatever.
Don't preach like you know everything, kid!
Everybody is born with a fate that can't be refused.
Neji, stay alive. You're the one whose got the
most of Hyuga's ability in the entire clan.
I wish I could've had you born into Souke.
A guy like you won’t ever understand what its like to have
a seal that you can never get rid of your entire life!
Yeah, I do.
And then... so what?
You...
Don't act cool. You're not the only one who is "special".
Hinata, too, has been suffering like you've been.
She's been struggling to change herself, who's
not accepted even though she's Souke.
That's why she fought against
you even when she coughed up blood.
You're the same, too.
Even though this is an exam, you're the Bunke that's
supposed to protect the Souke yet you did that to Hinata.
You, too, were trying so hard to go against your fate!
The liveliness came back to Hinata's face.
He sure is ANBU.
It's alright now. She just needs to rest.
Your 64 tenketsu (chakra holes) are closed already.
How are you going to fight? In that condition you
won't be able to channel chakra for a while.
After all, you share the same fate with Hinata-sama
Shut up! You judge everything with your
Byakugan and talk like you know everything.
Then... let me see if what you're saying is right.
Yeah. I'll prove that by beating you no matter what.
Shit...shit. Although I said so, I can't feel chakra at all.
It's like the time when I used up
all my chakra during the training.
You have two types of chakra.
You need to pull the large chakra that's inside
of you, and channel to use it whenever you need it.
That's right. Kyubi's chakra... I need to...
Shit fox... Give me your power!
The talk ends here. Examiner, I'm going to go at him with
the intent to kill. If you want to stop me, do as you wish.
Man...
I told you it's useless.
This time... I can not lose.
I'll win no matter what.
That's useless. All your tenketsu are
belong to us. I pressed all your tenketsu.
Definitely...
Oh yeah. Make sure to come see me beating up Neji.
A loser can beat up an elite with
hard work... It may be me going against him.
If it is you, Naruto-kun, no hard feelings.
Why are you trying so hard to go against your fate?
Because I was called a Loser!
No way. Chakra is flowing out... What's going on?
What on earth is he?
What is he?
No way... this chakra is...
This can't be...
No way... his tenketsu were pressed.
This chakra... it's no mistake... it's Kyubi's...
Since when did he learn he can use Kyubi's chakra?
I'm coming.
It's wrapping around him.
What is that? Is that chakra?
Incredible power... I can feel it more than in the training.
Kaiten!
What?
His speed increased. What's going on anyway?
You have confidence in close battle, don't you?
You become Hokage, eh? I guess you're not at that level.
Only handful of Shinobi will be
chosen to be Hokage. Look at reality.
Those who become Hokage are born with such a fate. It's
not something you can be because you want, but it's fate.
Everybody is different from each other. There's no
other way than to live in the flow that can't be changed.
I don't know if it's Hyuga's hateful fate or what, but...
If you say you can't, then you don't
need to do anything anymore!
Damn it... I need to start Kaiten!
Once I become Hokage,
I'll change Hyuga for you.
What a chakra. That kid released some
insane power... At this rate, the Hyuga kid may...
Hey, which one is Naruto?
I can't even tell which is which!
Neji's Kaiten is a technique to recoil the
opponent's chakra by spinning his body.
It seems that Naruto-kun got more damage
because he went straight to Neji.
There's no Genin who can win against Neji.
But Naruto-kun, you're incredible...
being able to push Neji this far.
Loser... Sorry to say but this is the reality.
This truly says...
I can’t move my body...
Leaving a Kagebunshin on the hole, and finding the way to win.
Even being beat up, he believed that
he could win and thought of the next move.
The power to believe in yourself
will become the power to change your fate...
This kid understands that...and it comes natural to him.
In that situation, you quickly did the Kagebunshin...
it is your favorite Ninjutsu. It was my carelessness.
I failed the graduation exam of the Academy three times.
With my bad luck, the Ninjutsu for the
exam was always the one I was worst at...
Bunshin-no-jutsu
was my worst skill.
Don't whine about fate or how you
can't change fate and all that stupid stuff.
You're not a loser unlike me.
Winner, Uzumaki Naruto