http://naruteamplus.altervista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Hey, you
Introduce to you.
They are not obliged to answer to you.
What?
That pretty!
Cos   these are the students
"predelights" of Kakashi and Gai.
For the moment they have passed the test
of delivery of the registration question.
Also for we examiners
this year will be a lot amusing.
Well! Sasuke-kun! Naruto! We go!
Not to pull to me.
Sasuke....
Uchiha Sasuke-kun
Interests you that boy?
Lee, we go.
What you are making?
You begin to go.
There is something that I want to control.
What will be?
What you want that it knows some?
You from the oblique look, it waits for a moment!
What you want?
I propose you one challenge!
Energy 120%!
One new and hard challenge!
You want to fight here and now?
S .
I am Rock Lee.
Before asking the name
to someone it must introduce itself
true, Uchiha Sasuke-kun?
Then you know to me.
I want to fight with you!
I want to test my techniques on an adversary
worthy like the heir of the more brilliant clan ninja.
And then
Sakura-saint one
Love!
Hatred that eyelash!!
Its pettinature are orribile,
and also those sopracciglia!
Too much grotesque E'!
A six angel!
Impressive!
Therefore of you still want?
This was the last one
Hey, six crazy one launch things of the sort!
I have risked the life in order to avoid it!
You would not have to be cos   negative!
Damned! Always and only Sasuke-chan!
Me challenges also knowing the Uchiha....
frankly, a six incoscente.
You will discover to your expenses what
it wants to say this name, ciglione!
Combatti.
They are fortunate to find me of forehead
the number one of the recruits.
Tester   my potentialities, Gai-sensei!
It waits for!
Me occuper   I of the ciglione.
But you....
Give five minuteren to me!
I do not want to fight against of you
but against a Uchiha.
Damned! You have broken all to me
with this history of Sasuke!
You take this!
* Konoha sempuu!
(vortex of the leaf)
As I thought is much fort!
You announcement
that you are not in a position to starmi behind
why they are
genin the more fort
of the village of Konoha.
It has stopped my soccer
This chakra comes from its arms?
It seems amusing.
I want to try to us.
Better than not Sasuke-kun.
Within the three we must carry the registration
and it lacks less than half hour.
Not preoccuparti.
Five minuteren are enough to me.
Eccolo!
It pardons To Me, Gai-sensei
But I must smash the rule
and to use that technique!
Konoha sempuu!
(vortex of the leaf)
Accidents, I must avoid it!
What!
Sasuke-kun!
COs' is succeso?
Sasuke was clearly in defense.
It has eluded my guard!
It will have used ninjitsu or the genjutsu?
As imamginavo it is still in feet.
Well! Now it is my turn
in order to make a little exercise.
Facts under.
But that one is
..lo Sharingan!
From when it you possess Sasuke-kun?
Why just in its eyes?
And ce it even has it in both!
It would be that one the sharingan?
Sasuke-kun is just incredible!
If this and the same technique of Kakashi-sensei
it will be able to preview the movements of the ciglione!
Genjustu or ninjutsu that it is
draft always of a trick
and I to discover it !
It seems that Sasuke-kun
he becomes more and more strong.
The Uchiha clan is formidable!
Sure
Sasuke-kun will defeat that boy!
The sharingan
The sharingan it has not worked!
Impossible! It means that
Gia'.
My techniques are not based ne'
on the ninjutsu and neanche on the genjutsu!
S Sasuke!
Gia'!
My techniques are simply
taijutsu, Sasuke-kun.
* (combat body to body)
You can also not believe to us
but these are my bases.
TU!
The sharingan pu   to reveal the abilities of
genjutsu, taijutsu and ninjutsu.
To ninjutsu and genjutsu the servants to paste
the chakra through the position of the hands.
this facilitates to you
the advance of the movements
but the taijutsu small difference has one.
What you want to say?
Even if with the Sharingan
advance payments mine movimeti
your body is not cos
fast to favour it.
Therefore even if you understand what to make
but you cannot move equally
quickly, it is all useless.
You know?
The strong persons divide themselves in two species.
The geniuses and the untiring ones.
Yours sharingan it derives from the blood
exceptional of the Uchiha clan.
I instead am a stubborn one who
he is strained to perfect the taijutsu.
Dimostrer   that mine taijutsu
pu   to defeat your Sharingan.
Stopped!
As it has made!
Now prover   "that technique"
You will understand that the engagement exceeds the genius.
What thinks to make?
I have won!
As it has made!
Now prover   "that technique"
You will understand that the engagement exceeds the genius.
What will have in mind?
I have won!
But this!
Now enough, Lee!
That he happens!
Sasuke-kun!
Sasuke has been defeated?
Cos' is succeso while I was svenuto?
It goes all good, Sasuke-kun!
Upset E'.
It is not successful not even to falling correctly!
You were watching?
Lee! That technique I had forbidden it!
But that one is one turtle?
Me excuses! The technique
Quel' to be is reproaching it!
That turtle even is
the sensei of ciglione!
But
In truth I did not have intention
to use the secret technique
It must be the sensei.
Hey, hey!
What?
That one
is one turtle, just?
It is not obvious!
But But!
One turtle pu   to be a master ninja!
But that I know some!
* Baka!
(* STUPID)
Creeds that pack-saddles one similar justification!
Sai what wants well to say for a ninja
to make to discover the own technique.
S !
Eternal damnation! I have lost against
that type bizzarro.
Six ready one to receive one punishment?
Sure one.
Then to make   to come Gai-sensei!
Accidents! You are just of the children!
Ack! E' become orrendo like that boy!
Yo Lee.
Super eyelash folte. Super pettinatura to bowl
Those incredible eyes.
I have not never seen sopracciglia of the sort!
Ehi! Not insulted Gai-sensei!!
You are zitto!
Strange as you are
ours is one reaction than more normal!
But what I have made you
Ehi Lee, enough!
S !
Cretino!
Lee, you six you six
Sensei!
Lee!
Sensei! I I
It makes nothing Lee. Not to say nuller!
Sensei!
Lee!
And I would have lost against that type?
S ! This is the giovinezza!
Sensei!!
You not creeds that are
a beautiful relationship between the two?
Idiot! That type of tie
it is too much dangerous!
Not preoccuparti Lee.
When he is himself young mistakes itself.
I had forgotten.
It is too much good, sensei!
Now, we go towards the sunset,
going around 500 of field in order to train to us!
S ! Sensei!
We go!
S !
You stop yourselves! We must still speak!
How you will make with the examination of the Chunin?
You will not arrive in time!
Oh gia
Lee, your punishment in order to have fought
trying to use the forbidden technique he is
of having to take place to the examination for Chunin.
.
The gioventu he calls to us!
We go to go around 500!
!
Idiots
Ehi ehi! Who devil is that turtle?
These would be the boys of Kakashi.
Yaa! Not to watch to us in that strange way!
Boys! How it is Kakashi-sensei?
You know Kakashi?
To know it?
Thoughts that people call to us
"Gli Eternal you avail again".
What?
What you want to insinuate?
Gai Sensei not mind never
E' all ok.
The facts sometimes are worth more of the words.
We are to 50 victories and 49 defeats for me.
This man
As you have made
I am more strongly than Kakashi.
N not. us creed
E' faster than Kakashi.
E' a monster!
You have felt? Gai-sensei is strongest!
Eternal damnation
Excused the disturbance that has caused Lee.
I ask forgiveness also from part mine.
I swear on this beautiful face.
Advanced to Kakashi?
I do not want to believe to us but
this man is not mentendo.
You boys and Lee must
to go soon in class.
Those!
Good fortune Lee for after!
Thanks!
Sasuke-kun! There is an other thing that I must dirti.
To say the true one, they have come
in order to test my abilities.
Before I have said one lie.
Probably the Genin more strongly
of Konoha it is in my group.
They have entered in the group in order to defeat it
and my true objective is he.
You prepare yourselves for the examination!
Sasuke-kun
the Uchiha clan is not successful
it is made to be worth today!
Naruto!!
Vedrai
that the next time striking .
Sure, even if hour has stracciato to you.
Naruto! It plants!
Also you have seen its hand, true?
Ciglione is trained tantissimo
every day.
Also more than we
and the point is only this.
Sasuke-kun
Interesting.
It begins to appeal to this to me
examination of selection of the Chunin.
Already!
We go?
Naruto, Sakura!
S !!
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.