http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
I will show  you  a limit that your engagement
it will not be able to never make you to exceed.
The invicibile formation!
Ino-shika-cho!
Your movements are to high speed
but we exceed them with the speed of sound.
Lee-saint!
The left ear
Use a small trick.
Enough not to schivare
my attacks.
Cos' you have made!
I use I play.
Even if you have schivato the blow
the sound has hit you.
The sound?
You know cos' you are the sound, not?
Vibrations.
Exactly.
To feel a sound means
that the eardrum is recependo
the vibrations of the air.
The human eardrum is broken off
when the sound exceeds the 150 Mhz.
Moreover, more in depth of the eardrum it exists
an inner membrane that if it comes damaged
all the your body loses the equilibrium.
For a po' you will not be able to move perfectly.
The simple one taijitsu does not work against of we.
However six state Bravo.
You have forced to me to show mine jutsu.
E' already something.
I succeed to produce supersonic waves
and to vary the pressure of the air.
I even succeed to crack one cliff
Omote Renge!
and to modify the air to the ground
in order to create a pillow.
Our techniques are very various
from your moved ridicules.
Eternal damnation!
Lee
You will be able to use this single movement
when you must protect who loves.
Protect who I love?
But  the six best state to learn it!
Very made, Lee.
Eternal damnation
Well.
Next the six
you!
It arrives!
Lee-saint!
Konoha Senpuu!
The blow before has made effect.
You have been strange to me
but in this your attack
you have lost your speed.
This arm
it amplifies to the maximum the acute sounds
that they are accumulateed to the inside.
Lee-saint!
The sound propaga
in the direction of the arm
but towards the target
established through the chakra.
Lee-saint!
E' the hour of the grace blow.
You  I will not allow.
Oh Sciocca
Hey! Scappiamo!
Those three are indeed dangerous!
It seems that Naruto and Sasuke have been puttinges KO.
Also Lee has been defeated
and Sakura is remained single.
What you want to make Ino?
In that sense?
Sakura is in danger. T' it does not import?
You were not many friends?
Hey
What is Sakura?
Perche six become cos   serious?
E' that
Ino-chan
Then? Ahead dimmi.
I have felt that also to you it appeals to Sasuke-kun.
Then, of hour in then we will be you avail again.
Why?
Why comes me in mind that time?
Hey!
Ino!
What we make?
I have understood but what we can make?
We cannot simply jump outside!
If I exit hour
I will only embed .
I can anch'
The pressure of the air
it has rejected my Shuriken!
But it watches that beautiful hats cure to you.
Instead curing hats to you, it trains to you!
A ninja it does not have to be sensuale.
Zaku!
You kill that Sasuke in front of this ninja.
Ah, optimal idea!
Hey, Hey
You  I will not allow!
Not to move to you!!
Sakura-chan!
I not....
I will be  never indeed strong.
They are
once again
.... a useless weight.
Always protect from someone.
I cannot accept it!
I thought to make it us.
At least this time
I had protect the persons to me beloveds.
Then....
we begin!
Hey! Also Sasuke and Naruto are in the troubles!
What I can make?
Useless!
You cannot makes me null with those kunai.
Cos' you have understood?
What !?
I always have
thought to be an optimal one ninja.
I have always asserted that it appealed to Sasuke-kun to me.
Sgrido always Naruto with superiority air.
But I
I was always behind of they.
It is behind
You are down!
Now
We can begin!
This is the only way in order to defeat it!
Sasuke!
" Now! "
They have always fought for proteggermi.
Lee-saint.
You have said that I appealed to to you
You  protegger  until death!
Omote Renge
Being to me neighbor, you have risked your life.
I feel to have learned something from you.
Sakura-chan!
Sakura-saint!
Mmm!
I want to become like you boys!
This time
I  will be
that
there will be .
Sakura!
Sakura
Kin! You kill it!
That position I know it.
Kawarimi not jutsu!
E' to right.
Foolish E' cos  ?
It underrates me using jutsu cos   elementary.
Kin, removes to you!
Useless E'!
Atmospheric pressure 100%!
Supersonic wave 0%!
All here!
Zankuuha!
Not six much fool then.
Up!
Useless E' that us new evidences,
a lot is useless!
You enough this !?
Dov' is the next one?
What diavo!
This time
it has not used the Kawarimi?
Mollami!
Sakura
They always take to you in turn
for your forehead, Huh?
Who six
I call Yamanaka Ino, and you?
I
Sakura.
I do not succeed to feel to you!
Dillo more strongly!
Sakura Haruno.
In effects
you have the high forehead.
E' for that you cover yourself
the face with hats
like a ghost?
Sakura, just?
.
It returns here of new tomorrow.
I will make  you  give!
It leaves stronza me!
Sakura Approval?
Cos   six prettier!
That tape now is yours.
Gr..Grazie.
But
But why?
My forehead
They take to you in turn
just perche tests to hide it.
Inasmuch as you have a beautiful ace you would have
to be surer than same you.
Ino-chan
Oh, Hey Ino-chan!
Who is that girl?
Sakura is called.
It greets, Sakura.
It appeal to to know to you.
Listened to all!
I have found someone that it appeals to to me!
Who tasks are?
Ahead, diccelo!
I pray, not to say Sasuke-kun to you!
How you have understood it?
But about that it speaks?
Sasuke-kun is one of the more popular boys!
Truly?
Therefore I have many you avail again, just?
What I would have to make?
Ino! Lately Sakura
you it does not seem gladder?
It is only churned in order attract attention.
Ino-chan! I have uncovered that to Sasuke-kun
piacciono the girls with long hats.
Girls with long hats
Sakura
Ino-chan, I have felt to say that
also to you it appeals to Sasuke-kun.
Therefore of hour in then we will be you avail again.
Your hats are become to you long indeed
Ino.
Why?
Why six due to capitare
in the same square of Sasuke-kun?
Ino, I not
you  I will be  more inferior to null.
Anch' I Sakura
you  I will not be  less.
Sakura!
I I.>.
You grow!
It does not go well for nothing
Hey, Ino?
I must protect the boys.
Mocciosa!
They are dulls other idiots to you.
Ino!
Sakura
I had promised to you that
you I would not have been from less.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu