Subbed by Kyubi
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
Episode #98
It forgets the vocation about Ninja!
A council of Tsunade
Vai Akamaru! Aerial Marchiatura of the territory!
You make a triple hole the next time.
Not to lack the target!
Is  this would be one walk?
Not, this is…
I cannot be concentrated in my collection.
S ì  but hour is beautiful to be able to make all and three what we love.
Hinata, you would have to make qualche.cosa also you.
You have reason.>.
Then because?
You have already found?
S ì…
Watched this design and you say to me qual' is the faster road in order to catch up the objective
Begun!
Listened to all.
the course is ended.
Fantastic!
But you must equally resolve the problem!
E' a fortune that the lesson of Taijutsu is ended!
But…
It is  already the fifth time that it succeeds.
An advantage for we is not sure…
You do not have preoccuparti! Ehi, Konohamaru-chan?
Konohamaru-chan?
Konohamaru-kun!
Which thing fairies of documents of the Grandfather?
Ah six you…
They are the documents of the Grandfather!
Where them capacities!?
Euh… these?
Since they did not come more uses you we were carrying them from an other part.
They do not come more uses you…
What you believe to make carrying via the transactions of the Grandfather!?
To the Godaime they would not serve…
[ Godaime = 5° Hokage ]
the Godaime?
S ì,
The Fifth Hokage has been chosen…
We can sleep calm dreams now.
Here why we carry via these papers
How the Fifth Hokage!? E' too much soon!
E' always be my grandfather!
Ah.... is cos ì  soft…
ch.ch… Which thing us fairies here!?
It rather touches me to ask it to you!
Ero-Gaki Small!
[ pervertito Child ]
You repeat what you have said!
Ah s ì?
You want to still feel it?
And
I was
It distributes
E-ro-ga-ki!
Grrr! Not to call to me cos ì!
Tsunade-sama!
They are waiting for, we must go.
S ì,  arrival.
Fa' more attention, Child.
For it appeal to, you are more comprehensive.
They are I that I am from comprising.
S ì  s ì…
They are not at all one child!
Who is this that…
Eternal damnation…
Naruto nii-chan!
Konohamaru?
E' from much time!
S ì!  But is something more important, has seen one woman with a large breast?
One woman who.>.?
If I have seen it?
But who is!?
What has happened!?
Ah! It must run in hospital!
To the hospital?
This woman is a Specialist Doctor.
We have as soon as brought back the Hokage here, and already she disappears.>.
Hokage?
The Fifth Hokage.
For God, it is in its interest to make its job very, or will have of the troubles.
Minds.
I do not believe to you! You are mentendo!
Why?
To the two.
In the beam of 50 meters… seven birds.
Tenten?
Neji!
Tsunade-sama is returned!
That true one! We go to see it!
It does not interest to me.
Ce n' was eight!
Listened to Tsunade, we must prepare the ceremony of investitura of the Fifth Hokage
The village must begin the prepared ones to you.
One Ceremony of investitura?
Che sciocchezza…
Tsunade!
S ì  s ì,  I have comprised.
It is  a duty of the Hokage.
Genma.
Aoba.
It announces it to the village and fairies to you to come the Daiymo.
We go to celebrate the advent of the Fifth Hokage.
S ì!
Stupid Grandfather!
Why six died?
Godaime…
What has all?
I have wants to rest, to make a good warm bath and drink to me of the sakè.
Tsunade-sama!
Waited for a minute!
E' hour that you put yourselves to make something!
, but what ?
Ve I have already said it! To recover Kakashi-sensei, Sasuke and the Sopracciglione!
Ah is true…
Eh? Six you Naruto?
Eh, Shikamaru?
Which thing here you make?
Which thing you make you here us?
I do not know it, but my father has asked to me to accompany it
What happens ?
How much time, Tsunade-sama.
Oh, the small of the Nara family.
You can take cure of the red deers?
They can be had of excellent medicinal ones.
S ì  if it wants.
Ehi Naruto…
She is  who is this woman who da' many airs?
It is  the new Hokage.
It has the young air but in effects it is one old of 50 years.
Gone! More is looked at to us late.
Well.
Well, we head to the hospital.
Later Shikamaru. I will show  you  my technical new, is fantastic!
Therefore is it the Godaime?
Ehi Shikamaru.
It is beautifulst and more strongly between the women.
In effects she is the woman of the leggendari Sannin.
A Hokage woman?
Not me piacciono the women.
They are egoist borings and.
They have always the pretty air but I never do not succeed to preview their reactions.
And for more they try always than to command the boys…
In order to end, they are borings.
Shikamaru.
If not there were women, not there would be neanche men.
A man is not nothing without one woman to its flank.
The woman more boring e' that one that is tender with the man whom it loves.
But that she says.? It makes yourself to always sgridare from the mother.
You will understand when you will be larger.
Oups, we must sbrigarci
They are in delay, your mother sgriderà to us.
Sbrigati, Shikamaru.
There are men who make themselves to command like he …
Buongiorno!
You are…
It is  cos ì  beautiful.
Sakura-chan! Sakura-chan! You do not have more preoccuparti!
I have brought back the best one!
Sasuke will be better now.
Naruto.
These flowers are freschi…
It comes every day?
Gai-sensei has spoken to me about she.
Saved Sasuke-kun, I pray to you.
Sure, it leaves to make me.
Sasuke!
Sasuke-kun!
Sasuke, you…
Even if it does not seem, Naruto is an sensitive boy.
Here, here.
That disappointment…
You have been defeated from two persons only!?
I believed you were a genius.
You excuse to me…
Very well, Kakashi-sensei is recovered!
We go from the Sopracciglione!
Sbrigatevi I pray to you! Gone to see Lee!
Lee!
Tsunade-sama is here!
Then this is your pupil?
S ì  is my better pupil!
I see…
Naruto!
Not tasks that are better not to lose time here?
Ah s ì!  I forgot, I had promised to Iruka-sensei to go to see it.
Vai then!
S ì!  I leave you. You take care yourselves of he!
S ì.
Ehi, Naruto!
You are in delay, Iruka-sensei!
Scusami, from the arrival of the Godaime I have much to make.
He is not serious.
And here to you!
Good appetite!
Naruto.
Six grown much from the period in which you wanted mine wrap of Ninja.
True, not found?
This wraps that you have given to me goes to me to wonder is not true?
But that you say.>.?
You have still much road to make.>.
You must be engaged hardly!
Sai Naruto…
The times are hard to Konoha.
From the dead women of the Sandaime and other Ninja of talent…
Our force practically has been halved
But we have the duty to continue to complete our missions.
Why? Since our forces are reduced, we cannot simply refuse the missions?
Not to say it not even!
If we refuse the proposals, the other countries will know that we have weakened ourselves.
Kakashi-sensei that is hurt even must engage a lot equally
I have understood, the situation is delicate.
Ehi! It watches that also not esonerato you six!
Even if you have saved Tsunade-sama you must acquit also you of the missions.
Sure! But before I must fill up the stomach.
Ahah.. Hour I recognize to you.
Fa' of your best!
Still one!
Ehi! Ehi! two!?
Spiacente Sono…
But you must forget the vocation about Ninja.
Tsunade-sama not jokes!
There are of boneses fragments in the sensitive points of the spinal marrow.
Probably your body sopporterebbe an other mission
But, you can recover it the same one?
Even if I make it…
Lee not to listen to it! It is not the true Tsunade!
Henge not Jutsu must be one. Who devil you are!?
Not there is no means?
They are the only one to being able to realize this operation.
Not to only it will want much time us, but there will be also…
Of the risks a lot elevates to you.
Of the risks?
There e' 50% of the possibilities that it goes to good aim
But if you had to fail
Moriresti!
Gai-sensei!
I will not only abandon  for this!
Gai-sensei! Cos' is this schifo!?
My  special prescription of restructuring littles ball is one!
If it eats 100, perhaps your guariranno wounds!
I understand, what it wants to say is that if I do not eat 100, my wounds not guariranno never.
I did not want to say 100 in a blow…
It forgets the vocation about Ninja, you would have to try an other life.
Lee…
If you had known it, I would not have asked to you for parlargli.
This is not…
I understand your pain.
But it is best to be honest with he.
It is  better for he to stop itself now.
To wait for…
It would only carry to the end…
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
You exit here from Konohamaru!
Traitor dirty Vattene!
Che cos' you have said!? Then  I will use  the strong ways!
Next episode
C$r-he who had inherited the will of the Fire…