Subtitles By: BakaSan
Release the Genjutsu and wake Naruto and Shikamaru up.
It's the first mission after a long time.
A mission?
Take it with care.
It's another A-rank mission like the Wave country mission.
Ouch!
You also were able to do counter-Genjutsu!
Why were you pretending to be sleeping!?
Go after Sasuke and join him to stop him...
and until further orders, stay at a safe place.
What happened to Sasuke?
I'll explain as we go.
We're leaving!
I see. That's what was going on. Sasuke rushed in.
Why was I selected for this? This is way too much trouble!
You have no choice! It was Kakashi-sensei's order!
This way.
How soon can we reach him?
I don't know. He's moving at very high speed also.
Shit!
Damn it!
No. 1 guy to run away Troublesome, but I have to do it!!
Hey you guys. Pick up the pace more.
What's up?
You found Sasuke?
No. Two small units, eight people are coming from behind.
No, wait... one more person. Nine are chasing us.
No way! Already? This isn't funny.
It seems that they haven't figured
exactly where we are, but...
we've got no choice but give them the slip.
Hey! What're you going to do by stopping?!
Shut up and follow me!
Backup by using your own footprints. This will make
it look like the footsteps all of the sudden disappear.
But even if we do this, they'll figure it out eventually.
It will earn us some time at least. That's enough.
It looks like the impatientness has risen within
the chasers. It will cloud their sight for chasing,
and if they lose signs of us, then that will be good for us.
Hurry Up!
We don't have time.
I know that!
This is not good. They're shortening the distance
between us, even though they're cautious about an ambush.
Shit. I'd bet all of them are Chunin or above
level. If they catch us, we'll be annihilated.
Annihilated!
Then... then should we ambush them?
Ambush? That's a good idea.
It's true that we're at an advantage to ambush. Even since
the enemy has double the number, if we catch them off guard...
It still won't work. They're subordinates
of Orochimaru, who once was a Konoha shinobi.
In the worse case, there may also be Jounin's with them.
I thought we could do it, but I guess not.
Hold on a sec. Why? The enemy's level isn't
that much of the factor for an ambush, is it?
Hey, what're you saying?
You guys don't understand it at all.
Listen. It's true that an ambush is a very advantageous
basic tactic, but there're two neccessary conditions.
What are those neccessary conditions?
One... move without making any sounds,
and find the pursuers before being found.
Two... Get in the position, and conceal yourself quickly, where
you can catch the chaser off guard and give the sure damage.
Only when those two conditions are
met, the ambush becomes effective.
Meeting the first condition won't be that hard
since we have the Nin-Ken's (Ninja dog) nose.
And the second condition... it seems
that we have the advantage with the
knowledge of the geography of this
village because this is our village. BUT
Orochimaru has been here before. This won't
work against the subordinates of Orochimaru.
So, what do you mean?
I'm sure that the chasers were taught about the geography of
this village, and should've had mock trainings for this battle.
Also, I'd bet they're all the Ninjas with chasing skills.
I see... They know our hands.
Well, even then, an ambush is still effective.
But there's too many unknown factors.
Our enemies are special units that are formed
for this operation. But what we have is...
An idiot, ...
A Kunoich (female ninja) without any notable skills, ...
one dog, ...
and me, who is number one in evasive attitude.
Stragegy is to analyze the situation
throughly and to come up with the best plan.
So, there's only one thing we can do in this situation.
One thing?
A feint operation pretenting to be an ambush.
One will stay behind and make it
look like an ambush to delay them.
In other words, a decoy.
That's right.  If one of us can delay them, they
won't be able to find the other three any more.
Well, we can give chasers the slip, but
the one who is the decoy will probably...
die.
So, who'll do it?
The dog is needed to chase Sasuke. That means...
I understood. I...
I guess it'll be me.
Why you?
It's better than being annihilated.
Also, you need one who can be a good
decoy and also has possibility to survive.
It's only me in us.
Kagemane-no-jutsu is originally for detaining.
Well, I'll catch up with you later, so go already.
I'll leave it to you, Shikamaru.
Is Shikamaru a person as dependable as this?
Be careful, Shikamaru.
No matter how hard you try to erase your signs...
it's still fully exposed.
Hey, the enemies are getting closer.
What?
Is that guy actually delaying them?
and me, who is number one in evasive attitude.
Maybe Shikamaru...
Don't worry about Shikamaru.
Did he possibly run away?
I said it's ok.
What?
He's got a bad mouth and is always lazy,
but he isn't the type who'd betray us.
He rarely say he'll do something voluntarily, but
he'll do it if he says he will. That's for sure.
I want to believe. I want to believe, but...
We'll increase the speed...
I somehow managed to run away.
The distance between footsteps is irregular.
Their anxiety must be making them tired.
Sorry. I thought I was always ready to run away, but...
I guess my character changed a bit this time.
It's true that I'm tired, but those footsteps are different.
By the way, this is the real body of those dog footsteps.
Man, it's just a little kid.
We all got caught by this kid...
So this is the Kageshibari-no-jutsu
of Konoha that I heard of?
That's the old way of calling this.
Time's have changed. This is
called Kagemane these day, old men.
As I thought... that match wasn't good.
I used too much chakra. I won't
be able to hold this so long...
One.
Two.
Three, Four.
Five, Six, Seven.
Eight... Eight people.
Eight people... wait... no, one
more. Nine people are chasing us.
As I thought, the nineth one's role
is to protect them from an ambush.
Moving behind keeping a certain
distance, to respond to enemy's attack.
Well, now it'll be found out where
the last one is hiding by this...
So... over there.
Shit. My shadow won't reach. I don't have
any more stamina to allocate to chakra.
It's useless. We know your technique.
Is this it?
I see that's your limit now. This so-called
Kagemane will be released soon. Be prepared!
I was going to be a decent ninja, earn a decent salary,
marry a decent women who is neither beautiful nor ugly,
and have two decent children. The first
one would be a girl and the next be a boy.
After the daughter got married and the
son becomes independent, I would retire...
as a Ninja and spend all day playing
Shogi and Go, and enjoy the retired life.
And finally die before the wife, due
to old age. That's the life I wanted.
I did extraordinary thing, outside of
my style. I wanted to stay ordinary.
I sure did a troublesome thing.
The chasers' movement has stopped.
Alright! The decoy was successful!
Shikamaru did it.
I'm sorry for doubting you even a little.
Good... Wait for me, Sasuke.
Shikamaru... Be sure to survive
and come and catch up with us!
As you said, it seems this is my limit.
Hey, come out now.
and cut this guy's head off on the way down.
I finally caught up with you.
Asuma... why?
You did good, Shikamaru.
It wasn't my character after all.
You retire here for now.
Hurry up!
What a persistent guy.
The number of chasers has increased... two, no three people.
Kankuro, we're increasing the pace.
Right!
I won't let you run away!
Don't do a rash thing, Sasuke.
Shall we get started now?
What on the earth is going on anyway?
Why is Hokage fighting against Orochimaru?
Why is Sasuke chasing the black-eye dude?
I was told to stop Sasuke... I have no idea what's going on!
Anyway's, I have no choice but to just chase him.
Wait up, Sasuke!
Next Episode:
Nothing at the same level even now and then!
A fight at the level of Hokage
What is going on with this village anyway?!