Subbed by Gandelr
Chekked by Cardboard
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
Of thermal sources?
, there is a laggiù thermal center
The thermal sources of Hira-Sato…
They remove the hard work and they render the skin soft
Hey, I thought that we would have gone straight to house
Naruto has reason. To the village it serves immediate aid
We do not have time to lose
If we delay days one or two he will not be serious!
The place is famous for the girls,
and the baths are mixed
Hey! Ero-Senin!
To times us it must be rested
We go takes a bath us
But you have said the contrary just hour!
Determined E'. We go.
E' it, not is doubts
We have found finally.
Episode #97
The Spring of Naruto
, service for four persons and a pig!
You are the welcomes!
They would have to be mixed baths…
but they are alone with he…
Che sfigato
Well hour, we go to play to the Pachinko.
[ Pachinko: Slot-machine that somiglia to the pinball machine ]
We have much time before the supper
You did not want to go to sources?
There are the idiots here hour
Well, we go!
I me of it go hour
I… did not wait for that the girls arrive
Oh.... I understand…
Hour you come, you come girls please!
Welcomes!
Refreshed Ahh that!
Eh?
C-c' has been a ladro!!
The necklace that has given Tsunade to me is disappeared!
Dov' is?
Where  it can  be?
"If rivolete your necklace, you give again the moneies to us.
We will wait for close to the three trees on the hill behind the inn.
Akagi Family "?
Moneies?
About that they speak?
Some girl has arrived
Only that…
they are a branco of monkeys!
I would want to take a bath with of the persons
Ehi! They are here!
Escapes! Akagi!
Which thing you want child?
I must dirvi one what!
I have not never asked you on loan for the money!
Therefore you give again my necklace to me!
"My necklace "!?
You want to say that this is yours?
You give again it to me!
It waits for!!!
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu
To the attack!!
You take this!
They have arrived of the persons
But…
They are all men!
[ Expression used from the sumo ]
Doshikai!
I would want to take a bath with of the women…
The old one must you of the money?
also known like the eternal one losing
It has lost to the game all the moneies that we have lend to them
As you can see we have also one changes them
Ehi! Cos ì  a lot!!!
They are Feels, and he Bunzo.
Our getlteman has ordered to us to recover the money 3 fà years.
We have left mountains of Akagi with the promise
not to return without the money
We have followed the traces ovunque
but it has been hard, it arrived and it left unexpectedly
But finally, we have had information that were in zone
Cos ì  we have waited for close to the main road
Then you have seen to us to arrive with Tsunade the old one
But because you have perquisito my room?
One says that it cannot be dealt with the losing leggendaria
We have thought that if we had gone directly from she,
it would not have paid to us.
It is  true that it is tirchia.
We have thought that it would have paid if we had had
the more important thing of its life, the necklace
It does not interest to me! You have perquisito my room!
We did not think that the necklace had changed owner
Euh.... you could try to ask them to pay to us?
Eh?
E' one demanded difficult.>.
You of supplico! If we do not have the money, we cannot return to house
Mia moglie and my sons are waiting for to me!
Naruto you supplichiamo!
Finally it has ended
That misfortune…
Eternal damnation, is empty!
Well, we stop to play to the Pachinko and go to the terme
Shizune!
?
We have left the ag the hotel, true?
Which thing!?
You will not want that it goes to take it…
Our savings are all
I cannot placare mine ira finchè I do not win
Not to discuss here and portala!
!
Oh, six you!?
Oh, you six.>.
The women have arrived
But…
I prefer young people and I live to us!
Here here
Thanks
You are a friend of Tsunade-sama?
S ì.
There is a message for she.
One letter?
From part of who?
Tsunade-sama!
Tsunade-samaa!
Eh?
Tsunade-sama!
If n' it has gone.
It listens, Tonton… finds Tsunade-sama
You have understood?
What? You cannot? Why!?
I understand.
The vapor of sources prevents it to use its correctly fiuto.
Then we will try it on foot!
Tsunade-sama!
Tsunade-sama…
Where you are?
There is a problem!
Tsunade-sama!
What I must make?
Uzumaki Naruto is in our hands
If you want it safe and sound, paid your debit!
We will wait for to you close to the three trees on the hill. Akagi Family.
That to make…? We must save Naruto-kun!
And for more, if the debits of Tsunade-sama were discoveries,
it could have problems to become the Fifth Hokage
We must take care of!
Of agreement, Tonton?
I ask myself if he will work.
Not to worry to you!
He arrives!
Tsunade the Old one!
Stopped!
Sai who we are, true?
Served the Akagi clan, is not cos ì?
In this case, it is useless to say other.
You render the money us that you have asked to us on loan!
Otherwise…
Morirà!
You save to me!
It does not interest to me what you will make it…
Which thing!?
Then.... For the money…
Why it has gone cos ì…
I want beautiful girls! Hour is only a large one casino!
I must resist…
You have felt to me?
It does not interest to me what you will make it.
You old witch!
This is  that  that I would have said until little ago
But now that they are Hokage, I have need of a servitore small.
I cannot leave it to die in front of my eyes
Uhh Tsunade the Old one
This is all  that  that I have hour
Prendeteli!
Fatemi to control
I cannot knit the debit, but those are enough for the interests, just?
They were is made!!!
You do not want to pay the debit?
It does not regard to you.
But these persons will not be able to return in their village! They do not make pain you?
Tu! It is not possible!
Then, we must take the moneies with the force!
They were cloni of Naruto?
I understand, Naruto-kun has formed an alliance with the Akagi family
If it is cos ì,  than intentions they will have?
I did not expect that it would have paid without to fight,
but me I did not wait for cos ì  treacherous
What now we make?
The old one has one large ag.
They are sure that it is full of money.
We will take the ag, does not import like
Merda! it is drinking of the sakè while it knows that they have been kidnapped!
That one must be the ag
How we will make to take it?
Left to make me!
Tsunade-sama, you are returned!
Ah, here the ag!
He is  imprudent to leave it here, I go to put it to the sure one.
Soon
You have seen? Eccola!.
Very made!
Ah! The Old One!
Merda…
If you the six Hokage…
If the six Hokage, satisfied your debit!
The Hokage is R-he who protegge all, right?
These poveretti cannot return from their beloveds…
Naruto-saint…
Or perhaps… Does not interest you  that  that it happens elsewhere?
I will not accept  one person cos ì  like Hokage!
Now!
You take!
Force, Force! You run!
It is catching up!
I hope functions
Ce you have made it!
Tonton!?
Naruto!
Motivating force the ag! Otherwise…
Dammela, soon!!
If the Old one hits to you you are died!!
Scansatevi! Scansatevi!
It is  a emergency!
Via!
Ehi! Not disturbed passing!!
You not to chase to us!!!
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
Kage bunshin not Jutsu!
But that devil…
Naruto-kun, we count on you…
If they discover what it contains the ag, we are in the troubles
Hour memory, is passed much time
Laughed them to when I was young.
Hour we drink a toast
You excuse to me, getlteman
That there is? I have a host
Bhe…
You take this!
A clone.
Still a clone?
An other
Qual' is that true one?
Dov' is…
Dov' is the last one?
Laggiù!
Stopped!
Naruto-saint!
It prepares you for the defeat!
Merda! It leaves me!
You are calm!
Ce we have made it!
The money!
! There are resolutions!
Of it changes them!?
It is not money?
It is not possible.
That been making here?
Eh? There are two Old ones!?
Why you are in means to this finimondo?
You would make better to having one good excuse, Shizune!
Blank, Tsunade-sama…
Tu!
Served the Akagi clan, is not true?
Mr. Jirocho!
Who?
You do not know it!?
He is  the head of this province, large the Jirocho-saint one!
He is  an old friend.
I have met here.
You are Bunzo and Senta, true?
Much good, I have qualche.cosa from dirvi.
Cooosa?
You are here for my debits with the Akagi, true?
I have them reimburses a year makes to you.
Truly?
I have paid the slid year when we were in the pressed ones of the Akagi, not memories?
They are desolated…
Ehi!
S ì!
I have one letter of the Akagi clan
I will read  what it regards to you
Senta and Bunzo, the debit has been reimbursed, returned to the village.
Akagi Shuugo
You see?
Which thing?
All I am casino for nothing
Thanks infinitely!
We can return to our village
You are prudent
Also Naruto-saint you!
Be prudent!
Why pressed you a lot to recover the ag if not there were money within?
Why if you had seen changes them to them and uncovered our huge debits
The title it of Fifth Hokage di Tsunade-sama would have been in danger.
It preoccupies to you too much
To have debits it does not prevent to become Hokage
Then you will reimburse all your debits.
Not there is no reason to preoccuparsi.
We do not have preoccuparci of the Akagi family
Calm, calm
Which thing? We have forgotten qualche.cosa?
Eccole finally…
I can enjoy a mixed bath.>.
the wait is been worth the pain…
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
Next episode
All in order to become Hokage!