http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
Fuuja Houin!
(Suppressor of the Evil!)
It seems sfinito!
Now you succeed also to use seals.
Six improved, Kakashi.
You six
It is passed some of time, Kakashi-kun.
Orochimaru.
-  CRITICAL SITUATION  -
Kakashi against Orochimaru.
Spiacente Sono
but six you not to interest to me.
Instead I want the boy behind of you.
Why Sasuke?
You six lucky person.
You have already obtained  that  that it wishes to you.
Time makes did not have it true?
I am speaking about
Sharingan to your left eye.
Anch' I want it.
I want the power of the Uchiha clan.
Ahead, it raises to you.
P-Perch !
Cimici ?
They exit from its body
through the skin.
_ E' rivoltante !
Which kind of trick is never this?
These "boys" call cimici Kikai.
They attack in swarms the prede
divorando their Chakra.
If you come attacked from an elevated number cos
of bugs you will not be able more to make the ninja.
You council of withdraws to you
if you do not want that  that  happens.
If you will attack to me with your left arm
you will be vulnerable to the bugs.
Viceversa if you will hit the bugs,
I  will be to attack to you.
In any case you do not have via of escape.
You wanted to hide your blow to me
secret until the end.
Hey! Stopped !
Bastard of a ladro !
Someone the firm ones !
Merda!
Stupid plump child.
That useless loss of time.
Six promising.
It appealed to the expression little ago to me.
If you come with me,
you will be able to become still more fort.
You follow to me.
If you come with me,
you will be able to become still more fort.
you will become still more fort.
You fight for me
and I
you  I will render  more powerful still.
You correspond to my expectations.
I cannot
They are strong
It seems to go much fierce one
of your arms.
Detention !
STOPPED ! !
I cannot
to comnettere other errors.
Not
to underrate me!
You wanted to hide to me
.. your secret blow until the end?
True?
You wanted to hide to me
your secret blow until the end?
True ?
What !
It succeeds to use also the skillful arm?
That one dramatized was only in order to make to think
that it could not use the skillful arm.
Arduous movement, Zaku.
Qual' is your scope?
The village of the sound is been born from little
and it is MY village.
Task that you have understood?
That stupid ambition.
Like you mistakes
But in order to realize I have it need of arms
and legs that follow my orders.
You take this !
Also Sasuke one of these pawns?
Sure that not.
Sasuke-kun, is the king.
Those that hour are supporting the examination
sacrificabili pedestrians are alone.
My arms !
What !
When I have said to you to withdraw to you
for emergency I have ordered to the bugs
to block with their body
those annoying air holes.
This is my secret movement.
You are zitto !
Not to dare
to make an other step
towards Sasuke!
Even if six one of those three ninja
hour they are in degree at least to hinder to you!
What finds us of amusing ?
All this that you are making does not have sense.
What !
Those I seal is useless.
You know.
It ambisce only to the power,
he does not import how much can be malvagio.
It has this predisposition.
It is a vendicatore.
You want to take advantage of this situation.
but Sasuke does not want
Sooner or later it will come to try to me.
It will come to try the power.
While you want to kill to me ?
It tries to us if
of six in degree.
To sacrifice my life in order to kill it ?
Perhaps they are driven crazy ?
It cannot  continue.
The encounter is finished.
The winner is Aburame Shino.
Neji, but
as it has made ?
Byakugan!
That boy
I believed that he had evoked the cimici
but it raises the cimici to the inside of the body.
Com' is possible ?
It makes part of the clan of the breeders
of bugs of Konoha.
I have felt some to speak.
E' a clan that renders the own bodies
of the nests for bugs.
They come uses you
in order to fight.
The bugs with the mind command
and these fight for they.
In exchange they allow the bugs
to nourish itself of their Chakra.
Cos   he
he is the successor of that clan.
I will revenge  your defeat, Zaku.
Why the arms of Zaku are exploded?
That such Shino
it has filled up of cimici the holes
of the arms without it is made to notice.
If he in those conditions
it had executed the Zankuuha.
The accumulated energy, not finding vent,
it would have been condensed in a point.
The arms of Zaku were like containers,
that it saturates they are exploded.
Hour they are unusable.
I and Zaku were joined only
from the mission that we shared.
Ciononostante
I will revenge  it.
I am myself innervosendo.
What?
Shino !
Six indeed cos   strongly?
I
I did not think was able a lot.
Shino-kun, optimal job.
Largest !
Thanks.
I waited for me a lot also from you.
Damned! One still gives airs from
great head!
Well, they said to begin
with the next encounter.
Kakashi-sensei.
Hey.
Like "hey "!
Sasuke-kun
Sasuke-kun is well?
S ,  hour is resting
in infermieria.
Even if escorted from the ANBU.
TSURUGI MISUMI
VS
KANKUROU
Finally it touches me.
Kankurou
Not to underrate your adversaries.
Idiot.
E' he.
Various from Yoroi I will not underrate  you
only why a six child.
You warning.
In order to strike to you
me enough a single blow.
Therefore it withdraws to you!
We will be to see.
I  will be to end to you fastly!
Well
you can begin the third party encounter.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
OF KIKOEMASUKAA
They have arrived until here believing in your words,
trying to be like you,
And hoping that your words came true.
But now
I want to strike giving the best to you.
They are not more that one that tasks than to know.
It would not have sense
if now you did not engage to you truly.
-  NEXT EPISODE  -
-  CRASH BETWEEN YOU AVAIL AGAIN  -
Challenge between women to the maximum power.
It will be a loyal and cleaned up combat!