Subbed by Gandelr
Chekked by Kyubi
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers
takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers
narifuri kamawazu
shinjiru ga mamani
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
kewashi not hito shura not michi naka not
chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
gokusai shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro memi not hiraite
shikato ima wo mikiwamero "yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa
iza mairou!
we to are fighting dreamers
takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers
narifuri kamawazu
shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire!
right to here! right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan laughing
right to here! right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire! "bam!"
Impossible…
I would not have never thought that he could use the technique of the Quarter.
However, it is not successful anchor to learn it.
This technique is an imitation.
Tsunade has still that monstrous force.
Me memory still the time in which it had launch to me to a hundred of meters with a fist.
But, the technique of Naruto was not enough strong.
Tutto OK?
Jiraya! six you that you have taught the Rasengan to it?
Rasengan?
After all, they are teaching its.
Only You and the Quarter can use this technique.
Insegnargli one technical that will not be in degree to learn. You chiamaresti teaching itself?
You are joking.
Here because this child says sciochezze on as he she wants to become Hokage.
They are not sciochezze.
Idiot! you a six idiot!
I can dominate this tecnina in three days!
You say, child.
A man must respect the given word.
I will respect  the given word.
This is my creed ninja.
Well, then we make a bet.
A bet?
I will give  one  week to you.
If you succeed to dominate this technique, I  will recognize  that you can become Hokage…
And I will give  this  necklace to you.
Tsunade-sama! that one is important…
That necklace does not serve me worthless.
Not to say cos ì,  Naruto.>.
That one is an only necklace that could buy approximately three mountains if you would sell it.
It belonged to Primo Hokage.
Wow…
Task that  I will accept.
I can say that piacciono the moneies…
OK, but if you do not succeed to dominate to the technique in one week…
You lose. And I  will take  to all your moneies.
Ah! Gama-chan! When you have it…
Tsunade-sama, because? This necklace is…
Like if it could make it us. We go via, Shizune.
It has not never bet that necklace…
If I do not have one endured answer, not ago nothing.
But it would appeal to to us to have it within one week.
Episode #91
The inheritance of Primo Hokage
The necklace that calls the dead women
Who is to this hour of night?
OK, OK, arrival.
Scusami if you disturbance to this hour. Naruto-kun, I must speak to you.
I want to remain calm this evening, I must train to me tomorrow.
Me dispiace, but I do not want that there is a misunderstanding with Tsunade-sama.
And also.... He has purpose of that necklace!
That old one, has given to me of the crazy one.
Tsunade-sama is not the person kind who creeds!
Not to speak like if you knew all of she!
Scusami if I have screaied…
Before, it was not cos ì.
It was a great person who loved its village.
But then  she changed…
from that day.
That day?
What happened that day?
It is  the day where it has lost
The Dream, the Love, and the Hope.
The only thing that remains it of its past, is that necklace
For Tsunade-sama, this necklace is more important of its life.
It is not qualche.cosa that  can  be bet cos ì.
I do not know what dirti.
Who  is she has defied to me.
That one not one normal necklace that a person as you it would have to carry.
If someone beyond to Tsunade-sama tries to carry it…
This person will be condemned…
To die.
Nawaki, congratulations for yours twelfth birthday.
Hour they are not more a child, I do not have need more than gifts.
What you are saying? You six anchor a child.
Soon, you open your gift. They are sure that it will appeal to to you, Nawaki.
Sorellina, this is......
, this is the necklace of Primo Hokage, our grandfather.
I want to you well, Sorellina!
I have thought that it would be better than costudisca you.
You wanted from much time, true, Nawaki?
You guard it preciously.
P roteggerò  not only this necklace…
but also this village that is the treasure of the grandfather.
I must proteggerlo.
Nawaki…
I am the grandson of the first Hokage that has founded the village of Konoha.
You feel it!
A man must respect the given word…
S ì,  I want to become like my grandfather, and a day  I will receive  the title it of Hokage!
Why to become Hokage is my dream.
You remove the coprifronte, Nawaki.>.
you move, you remove it. I have an other gift.
E' a portafortuna in order to realize your dreams.
E' better than does not watch the body.
It leaves it. Even if it watches will not be able to recognize its brother.
Enough, Orochimaru!
After all, we are in war hour....
All the Ninja make the same end… not are doctors on the battlefields.
But the children are too much unconscious.
Especially the day after that they have received a gift.
Proteggerò  not only this necklace…
but also this village that is the treasure of the grandfather.
I must proteggerlo!
Then, in order to facilitate the happened one of the mission,
The small squares of four will have to strike themselves in enemy territory.
If a specialist doctor is assigned to the square,
The rate resolution and the probability of survival will increase…
Consequently, task that now, the more important task…
It is  to carry of the Ninja medical to a high level…
and to promote the development of medical techniques.
That  that you have said is right, but currently we are in war.
To train these specialist doctors will make us to lose the time, and for more it is not much realistic one.
The enemy will not be to wait for to us.
What says, old matto!?
In this case, it does not import the time that we will employ ourselves…
I am of I come to an agreement with she.
We do not want to waste the life of the Ninja, than they are sacrifices to you.
We would have to act already from now,
Scusami…
Thanks in order before.
What you said was right.
Um....
E' late. You want that it accompanies to you?
How? If it does not disturb to you? Where dresses?
From the other part of the city.
It leaves to lose.
Not preoccuparti. I want to speak with you.
I often passed from this road in order to go to take my sister to the academy.
He passes to you?
Oh, she is died a fà year when Konoha was attacked.
It is like me…
Tomorrow, our mission will carry to us close to opposing front line.
To fight makes us to only lose the persons to we more beloveds.
It is not the job of a Ninja.
Because we live in a world of Ninja, where the dead women attend to us…
I want to sacrifice itself in order to make that all she ends.
I love this village and all people.
Here because I want proteggerli.
When my sister mor ì,  that feeling has helped me.
This is because I want to become Hokage.
For the emergency of all.
To become Hokage is my dream.
Dan…
I want that… You chip axes this.
You resume yourself, Dan!
Tsunade, I do not want to die…
I have still many things to make…
Not to speak, Dan!
Its broken kidney and…
Also Tsunade, a Sannin,  cannot  make it us…
I cannot die here…
He will not happen. I have stopped the hemorrhage.
All good will go!
Tutto OK, hour. Soon you will be well, Dan!
I see…
They are content…
Dan! You resume yourself, Dan!
Eternal damnation, stopped!!
Stopped! Stopped!
stopped, Stopped, Stopped, Stopped…
Stopped! By now it is died.
You have understood, hour, Naruto-kun?
After that day, Tsunade-sama has not been never more the same one.
Naruto-kun?
I go to train to me.
Oh, you are drinking!
Welcome!
What makes us here?
Not to say cos ì,  six cos ì  cold.
Jiraiya-sama…
Shizune, scusami, but you can leave us alone?
E' from much time that I do not drink with she.
Getlteman, of the sakè! And also of the ravanelli.
S ì,  endured!
Please cure of she is taken, Jiraiya-sama.
There are the ravanelli.
Oh, seems good.
I did not think that you would have guarded cos ì  preciously this necklace.
I was convinced that you had lost it in some bet.
This is a memory, just?
It annoys to you?
Which thing?
Naruto.
Not of all.
But a six too much hard adult.
In a week, it is practically impossible to dominate that technique.
I would not call it a bet.
Why six frustrated?
I am not frustrated.
You have met true Orochimaru?
It can  be seen from the face of Shizune.
But I do not know that type of proposal has made you.
Not to take one hurried decision.
And then, what is one that I must dirti.
Old the proteggevano Hokage Konoha and the life of the persons…
In order to guard the things and the village com' they were. This was their dream.
Poor their life in game for this dream.
With this I do not want to say that you did not comprise old the Hokage.
But know that if you betray the village of Konoha,
Then, in that moment.... I will kill  to you!
It does not interest to me.
Only the murders do not feel nothing when their neighbors die.
Six various one.
Nobody has taken cure of the village like has made you.
Also this time.>.
You stop makes me foretells!
Because…
You have carried this child here?
To become Hokage is my dream.
The somiglia it is not true? It has more or less the same age.
And with this.
To become Hokage is my dream.
You stà exiting too much blood… You want to perhaps die?
Nawaki, you a six Genin, therefore if six on a battlefield, you must escape.
A man  cannot  escape!!
This dream, and this enthusiasm, also…
I do not succeed to make it us…
Merda,  I will recommence  tomorrow…
That badly of head.
To cause its, I have passed one ugly night.
Naruto…
One would say that it is not returned to house yesterday.
It can  be that.... Imprudent.
Which thing you would say of an agreement?
I can resuscitare your brother and your fiancèe…
Thanks to one technical prohibited that I have developed.
You would not want to see them of new, Tsunade?
If I recover your arms,
Which thing you count to make?
This time,  I will end  what I have begun, the destruction of Konoha!
It does not listen to you!
Their dreams.... And your dreams…
You have forgotten your dreams?
I must dirti one what, Tsunade.
Tsunade, the High Council has to you chosen for being the Fifth Hokage.
The Believe your promised, it' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kado ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aru ka
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
yume it has ryuusei not you ni
ameagari of niji of you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoui tsudzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naru yo
gomakashitari shinai to chikau yo
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
Today, it is the day of the challenge!
I have not ended the training, but  I will head  all at this blow!
Next episode:
S ì  or not
The answer of Tsunade