Guideline 9 AM
Today it is a special day
Itadakimasu
(typical phrase that is said before eating)
You avail again! Sasuke and Sakura
You fight against of me!
What you are making, Konohamaru?
Inpressionate, Naruto.
I did not expect nothing from you less.
I have not made null.
You fight to me, with all your techniques!
Me dispiace but I have the guideline stamani.
Guideline?
Inasmuch as from today they are a ninja!
- guerriero Spirit -
Sakura, not six ready anchor?
I was just in order to exit!
Conscience of Sakura
Eternal damnation, you end it to deal like one child to me!
They are not more one student of the academy.
Hour they are one ninja of the Villagio of the Leaf,
Haruno Sakura!
I am exiting!
Buongiorno Sakura
Buongiorno… Ino.
Who would have never said that also you would have been given a degree to?
What it has happened before today does not have
more importance.
From now in then we are of the true ones ninja.
Not to lose more  ? against than you… Ino.
Uh?
Ehi, than devil six come to make?
This guideline is only for who has been promoted.
Ehi! Ehi!
You do not see this coprifronte?
From today they are also I a ninja!
You say what to me?
Me it is not well?
Therefore… Naruto-kun… it has been graduated…
Goal!
I have won of new, Sakura.
But about what you are speaking!
My foot was a centimeter more ahead!
Eh! Six blind person or other?
E' Sakura-chan!
Sakura-chan is watching to me.
Ehi, Sakura!
Buongiorno, Sakura-chan!
Rises from the feet!
Buongiorno, Sasuke-kun.
I can be based close to you?
Ehi! Me sieder ò  I close to Sasuke-kun!
Is not who before arrives, better lodges?
I have entered in class before you!
I!
And I then?
I was before!
I want myself to be seated close to Sasuke-kun!
(Annoying…)
Cos ì  is he?
This year has been the recruit to miglire, Uchiha Sasuke.
Exactly.
The last one of the Uchiha clan.
(Uzumaki Naruto, eh)
Naruto! You stop to fix Sasuke in that way!
Sakura-chan…
I always feel "Sasuke here… Sasuke of "
What has of particular this type?
Sasuke-kun, you take it to soccer!
S ì! S ì!
Wow! Indeed!
Oh, scusami…
Damned!
The first kiss of Sasuke-kun had to be mine!
Naruto, I kill to you!
My mouth marcendo!!
Uhm? E' guilt mine?
What? I perceive I mean omicida…
Naruto… six…
An incident! E' be only an incident!
Insopportabile!
That Naruto… always in means to the troubles.
This happy day marks
your promotion to ninja complete.
For ò  you remember yourselves that you are still of the Genin.
(ninja novice)
The difficult part comes just hour!
You will form groups with others two companions…
in more you it will follow master Jonin. (ninja expert)
Squares of three persons?
I would want to know who will be with Sasuke-kun.
Who pu ò  to know it!
Eternal damnation!
Star ò  I in square with he!
One square of three…
they will intralceranno to me and enough…
The ideal would be to be with Sakura-chan…
… and anyone other except Sasuke.
The groups have been decided from teaching we…
… so as to to balance the abilities to everyone.
Next one… Group 7…
Uzumaki Naruto.
Haruno Sakura.
Evviva!
(Because with Naruto..)
and Uchiha Sasuke.
Evvai!!!
Because with Sasuke…
Therefore, they are not in square with Naruto…
Now Group 8. Hyuga Hinata.
Uh… S ì!
Inuzuka Kiba.
Aburame Shino.
As it can happen!
Group 9
S ì!
(it appeals to to Me to win)
Why to you girls appeal to so much that type?
How, you do not see, Shikamaru?
They are not one girl.
Here because she does not depopulate between the girls.
I hope not to make square with you.
Group 10....
Yamanaka Ino.
Nara Shikamaru.
It seems we are ended in the same square… Ino.
and Akimichi Choji.
(to act cruelly also with a ciccione)
Then these are the squares!
Iruka-sensei!
Because one student model like me
it must end in the same group with those fiasco?
Sasuke has been graduated with best ballots between you 27…
… while you Naruto, six state worse!
You are ended entirety in order to balance the group. Understood?
Therefore it tries too much starmi between the feet… not losing.
Aaaaargh
As you have called to me!
You want to fight… losing?
You stop it to call to me cos ì!
You end It Naruto!
Then boys… this afternoon
we will introduce you your Jonin sensei. (masters jonin)
Until that moment you are free!
Sasuke-kun!
Where it will have gone?
Inasmuch as we are in the same square
that you say some to eat with me?
Sakura-chan!
Inasmuch as we are in the same square
that you say some to eat with me?
Why I would have to eat with you?
But we are in the same square…
Six annoying!
Sasuke-kun, where six?
Eternal damnation! It is not amusing.
Even if they are successful to end in square with Sakura-chan,
why it continues to deal to me badly?
I must escogitare something…
Ecco!
You listen to me! Hour that you are in my same square
you will have to follow my orders.
s ì, s ì.
Any reasoning with Ino
loss of time is one.
We exit and we go to eat something!
uff…
Naruto!
Uh!
six you, true, Naruto!
You stop it to resist!
Naruto, you making ò  to pay six you make of
badly to Sasuke-kun!
What will have happened?
Eh, idiot.
Cos ì… Naruto has failed.
Natural one… How pu ò  Naruto to compete with Sasuke?
Not there is need of being impazienti.
We will make square for a bag of time.
But…
With the fascination not to only succeed ò  never to conquer it.
They are flat as one table…
The only thing that I have of special is my enormous forehead.
As I can make for…
What! Impossible!
Sasuke-kun is fixing to me!
And for more in intense way cos  ?…!
That beautiful spaziosa forehead that you have.
It comes to me wants to kiss it.
Made E' on purpose.?
That foolish.
They are not more a child whom it believes to fables.
What will not never succeed one of the sort.
That beautiful spaziosa forehead that you have…
Eh!
It comes to me wants to kiss it.
EVVAI!
The fable… has become truth!
… or at least cos ì  creed that Naruto would say.
Sakura, I would want makes a question you.
Eh?
What tasks of…
… Naruto?
It makes always the part of who wants
to intralciare history of other people's love…
… and it is amused to see that I make myself in four for you.
Naruto does not understand null of me.
Indeed insopportabile E'!
To me it interests alone…
… to be appreciated from you!
To be appreciated… solo from Sasuke?
In order to appeal to I would make to you of all.
Because I love to you!
Maledizione! Those cretino…
That it has in mind to make taking
my sembianze with the Bunshin Not Justu?
(technical of the transformation)
They are serious.
Now finally I have understood…
… because it appeals to Sakura-chan to me…
Just hour me had to come a diarrhoea attack!
That it takes to you!
I return endured…
Who would have never said it that Sasuke-kun is a timidone..?
He wants to us a little preparation.
Uuuhh!!
That risk!
For the pain I was in order to lose
the control of the Bunshin Not Justu!
Because my stomach betrays to me
in an important moment cos  ?!
Annoying, eh?
Me it has said of new…
They are only transformed in order to discover to me
the true feelings of Sakura…
It waits for a moment! I could also make to think
to Sakura that Sasuke is unpleasant…
Uffa Sasuke-kun! Six indeed timid one!
Hour you feel yourself ready? I am most ready!
Ehi, Sasuke-kun!
Dov' Is Naruto?
Not to change speech....
… that you it imports some of Naruto?
It always attacks briga with you.
Perhaps because nobody has educated it as it must.
It has not never had the parents.
Pu ò  to make all the whims that it wants!
If I involved to me like he, I would come sgridata from mine!
Made happy he! It does not have nobody that says what to make to it.
E' for that he is cos ì  egoist.
The solitudine…
Uh?
… it is a pain that it does not have null to that to see
with the being sgridati from the parents.
But that it takes you the unexpected one…
Six… insopportabile!!!
Alleluja! Finally the diarrhoea has been calmed.
Goodness knows if Sakura-chan me is still waiting for.
Aaah!
Co.... You make what here us?
Ropo Untying Justu is not one technical elementary.
(to melt the nodes)
What you wanted to make transforming to you in me?
I have made because it seemed amusing!
Of new the Kage Bunshin…
I am in order to defeat to you…
… and you will admit that I…
… they are more strongly than you!
Six ended, Sasuke!
Not! Of new…
Bath!
Before I! Not! Before I!
Invalidity…
Annoying, eh…
Therefore also Naruto will have been felt cos ì…
Of hour in then… prover ò  dealing it with more care.
Maledizione. Avr ò  eaten something of expired…
Naruto?
Sorridere, sorridere..
We return in class, Naruto!
Sakura-chan…
It wants to fregare to me?
Sasuke has been transformed in Sakura in order to be revenged…
Tasks to trick to me, true Sasuke! But it will not work!
Ow, ow, ow…
What happens to me?
Naruto Stupid!
Cos ì  this is the house of Naruto..?
Your square will have also Sasuke of the Uchiha clan.
I augur you good fortune.
These latte…
… it is expired from a piece.
Who has it drunk will have large pains to the stomach.
I do not envy it of sure.
That devil is!!