Connecting old words
that have been used up
I just want to convey
my simple thoughts
That day's faint wind blows away
at the castle ruins of yesterday
I'll laugh with you
and live for the moment
Still that incident
will continue to trouble you, right?
That's why it must be good bye
Leaving nothing behind,
let us share what is left
In time, we'll realize
that it was everything
And sadness will touch our cheeks,
creating a river of tears
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex
and melting away
That form...?!
So that's the extent of
the rumored "Absolute Defense?"
How disappointing.
I see... You were wearing sand, eh?
Your opponent's not just him!
I'm here, too!
Th That attack just now...
It would've been dangerous
had I not been protected by sand.
M My body is still...
I'll just be a hindrance like this.
Annoying sand...
You're first, Gaara.
He yanked out his spinal column?!
Vengeful Strike.
The Bracken Dance
Dance of the Clematis Flower.
Vine!
Flower!
A bone of the strongest calcification...
It will pierce you,
sand defense and all...
No time...huh?
Ultimate Defense: Shukaku's Shield!
Kabuto...
How much longer will
Kimimaro hold out for?
I think he should still
be okay for a while...
I did all I could with the treatment...
But there's not nearly enough
information about his body.
I think it'd be quite different
if we had something
like the medical history
and treatment data of his clan.
What came out after looking into it
was the bloody history of how
the Kaguya Clan became just him...
Fools who provoked the great land of
the Village Hidden in the Mist into battle
with just their clan
and were annihilated.
The Kaguya Clan was
a foolish clan that liked battle.
The battlefield was the only place
where they could be at peace.
But it was long ago when
a simple minded group
that only enjoyed slaughter
was acceptable...
The times are different now.
Doing something like fighting
only with power
against a governed organization
like the Mist...
can only be called an act of fools
rushing towards death.
And then you saved only he
who was the youngest
and the most exceptional
among the Kaguya Clan...
That kid possessed the power that
would be feared even by the fighting clan.
So it seems he was kept
in prison the whole time.
It would've been a waste to let him... die.
Who wouldn't want
that rare Kekkei Genkai?
He possesses a strong
and firm bone structure
and a defensive power to
repel all kinds of physical attacks.
And if turned to offense...
the bones become
a most powerful weapon.
It's because I've fought him once
that I understand this.
That sand shield is
an absolute defense, no less.
And that unusual form...
It'll be okay.
There's no way it'll be broken!
It's hard...
I gathered minerals with
great hardness from the ground,
applied pressure with Chakra
and mixed them into the sand.
You... that unusual Jutsu...
It's the Kekkei Genkai, right?
The Kaguya Clan...
The ability which now
only I possess.
The last one of the clan, eh?
Then it'll die out here today.
Indeed, that might happen.
Due to sickness,
my body will not last so long...
But, the clan will not die out.
Besides I'm not alone.
This is the "Earth" Curse Mark...
With this...
I can become a part of you,
Lord Orochimaru.
Let's get everything, Kimimaro.
And let's see the truth of
this world together.
Yes.
You're my "Vessel of Dreams."
I'm counting on you.
They are presents from me.
I hope you like them.
Would you rather... die or obey?
Obey...
You will!
Is this the best a team
of four can do?
I'll ask just once more...
Which would you rather choose?
Very well...
As of now, we're the Sound Ninja Five.
Not alone, you said?
That's right...
As an existence shouldering
one part of Lord Orochimaru's ambition...
I will remain inside
Lord Orochimaru's soul...
for all eternity.
Orochimaru's brainwashing, huh...?
You're a pitiful guy.
I used my big moves too much.
I don't have much Chakra.
This is the last of it.
What an amount of Chakra...
You are something...
I'll sink and confine you
200 meters into the ground.
By the pressure of the sand
stuck to your body,
you'll soon be unable to move,
not even a finger...
You did it...!
This time for sure you did it.
Dance...
Bracken Dance!
It is annoying...
It feels like a long time
when waiting eagerly for
something you want.
Kabuto...
Stop talking like
you're humoring a child!
I'm sorry...
But you should know
this the most, Lord Orochimaru.
Nobody can beat Kimimaro,
no matter what hindrance
should appear.
Thanks for saving me...
Being able to do something like this;
very impressive.
All I did was ride the sand
I'm always controlling.
You just have to know how you use it.
Lord Orochimaru...
I'm sorry, Lord Orochimaru...
At last... The destruction of
the Leaf will begin...
Third Hokage...
I'll teach you a thing or two.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's the matter, Kimimaro?
No... It's nothing.
Even the Kazekage of
the Hidden Sand Village
is no match against us.
Of course...
Kimimaro, it's thanks to you...
Kimimaro!
Kimimaro, so you can't go on, huh?
I'm sorry, Lord Orochimaru.
If I can't be of use...
then there's no significance
to my living.
How is your condition, Kimimaro?
The "Destruction of the Leaf"
resulted in an unfortunate near miss.
But the Sound Ninja Four
have gone to pick up a new vessel...
Lord Orochimaru's new
"Vessel of Dreams."
Orochimaru's brainwashing, huh...?
You're a pitiful guy...
You're wrong... Far from it!
There's no significance to living...
But...you might be able to discover
something interesting
by continuing to live...
Like how you discovered that flower...
Like how I discovered you.
This is the "Earth" Curse Mark!
With this... I can become
a part of you, Lord Orochimaru.
Let's get everything, Kimimaro...
And let's see the truth of
this world together.
I'm going to discover
the truth of this world!
With Lord Orochimaru!
He was a persistent guy,
but this is the end.
He won't ever come out again.
R-Right...
I can't go on...
We're getting off...
It's not brainwashing!
That person...
Lord Orochimaru understands me!
What do you guys know?!
He's dead...
Could it be? Has Kimimaro...?
The likes of Kimimaro makes
no difference now...
Sasuke... I can hardly wait for him.
He'll come here even by himself...
I would have been totally hammered.
That's not the case.
My sensei said it often...
Luck is also a part of strength.
That backseat driver?
He's not a backseat driver!
It's because...
I wasn't good enough at that time!
I'm grateful for you saving me.
But please don't talk like that
about my sensei!
You, too...?
When you feel that
the honor of someone you revere
has been hurt,
you yourself are hurt badly
and become enraged.
The more important the person
you revere is to you,
the greater the feeling...
The clan won't die out...
I'm not alone.
I will remain inside
Lord Orochimaru's soul for all eternity.
That person,
Lord Orochimaru, understands me!
What do you guys know?!
Fighting for the sake of someone
important to you...
He was also the same
as Naruto Uzumaki...
But... the person who is important
to oneself
might not always be "virtuous"
I wonder...
There's no way someone evil
can be thought of as an important person.
No. Even if you know they're evil...
People can't defeat solitude...
Sasuke!
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
Would you think it was
a bother if I approached you?
Despite my doubts,
I worked up my courage
My clumsy attempts with words
You listened without turning away
No wonder I get carried away by you
But you don't feel anything for me, do you?
I feel so sad
But...
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
You gotta be kidding me!
What do you mean
"for achieving your goal"?!
Orochimaru wants you
only as a "vessel"!
There's no way
I can let you go to him!
This is no joke!
If you insist on going,
I have to take you back by force!
Next episode: "A Cry on Deaf Ears"