Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
Blaze Away, Byakugan!
This is My Ninja Way!!
Kiba!
Naruto!
This isn't good.
Oh my, what's wrong?
So you'll just stay there
and become larvae food?
Queen Bee...
That kind of stuff shouldn't
be effective, should it?!
Chakra...!
Byakugan!
It's no good... There's no way
I can make it in time!
Naruto...
I don't know when to give up!
That's right...
I know that Naruto would never give up,
no matter what the situation is!
Hey, did you catch them?
What a foolish group!
They made this creature mad...
And they all got bound in wax!
Bees make wax...
You're an insect handler
and you don't know that?
He's right!
C'mon, are you really an insect handler?
What about the Bikochu?
Nothing.
We did an all out mobilization
and searched,
but we haven't found it.
Aren't these guys carrying it?
That's unthinkable.
So that means...
So we're going to have to
ask one of these guys, after all.
Who's gonna talk?!
We can tell you.
Shino!
However...
It's in exchange for Hinata.
That's stupid, isn't it? To bargain...
Do you not understand your position?
You guys definitely will not
find the Bikochu.
And you're pressed for time.
You are the ones... who will regret it.
What should we do?
If things stay like this,
the Bikochu won't be of any help
even if it hatches.
In that case, our mission is also...
But...
If we can get rid of even one
of the Aburame family...
Hinata...
Are you worried?
Of course!
She's strong.
Huh?
Much more... than you think.
I concede. We have a deal.
First of all, we need our friend.
What happened?
The brat... isn't here.
The wax she was trapped in isn't there...
She may have been swept out
to the waterfall.
Jibachi!
It can't be helped! I warned her not
to make a bad move or she'd die.
You!
What did you do to Hinata?!
What happened to Hinata! Hey!
Shut up, kid.
The kid's probably in
the depths of hell about now.
Damn you!
Aha, the girl's your girlfriend?
You...! I absolutely will not forgive you!
You're kidding me.
What can you do looking like that?
Without Hinata you'll never get
your hands on the Bikochu either.
You are right...
That girl's death was not part
of the plan,
but in the end, it's a good thing.
Because... we'll take your lives in return.
From the very beginning, people from
the Village Hidden in the Leaves and
from my own Village Hidden in the Stones
have been sworn enemies.
It's natural that we kill
each other, isn't it?
What're ya gonna do, little guy?
Die like this?
Or if you tell me where the Bikochu is,
I could save you for now.
- All right.
- Don't you dare tell them!
Those jerks,
I'm going to blow them away!
Shut up, brat!
- Jibachi?
- Hey!
Shut up, I've got to kill him!
It's a Paper Bomb!
You're...!
Y You're...!
...still alive!
That was really close.
But I didn't give up, just like Naruto...
Did she escape from the wax?
It can't be!
These are not ordinary kids.
Leave it to me!
Hinata!
I've never used that in an actual fight...
But I have to do it here, now!
Bee Bombs Jutsu!
1000 Bee Stingers Jutsu!
Bee Swarm Jutsu!
Naruto...
Naruto... Watch me.
Protective 8 Trigrams 64 palms!
- What?!
You're kidding, right?
That Hinata can do
such an amazing Jutsu?
The Hinata that you know, Naruto,
is from when?
What do you mean?
You've learned new Jutsu
since the Chunin Ninja Exam, haven't you?
Hinata has been steadily developing, too.
She always has been concerned...
Take aim.
That's nice, the three of you,
all have something you're good at
and something you like.
Hinata, you should find something, too...
You're right.
By the way, what is it?
You had some business with me,
didn't you?
Yeah...
I want you to join me
in my training.
Hinata was fretting over
what she could do...
What she should do...
Hinata!
Hey, I don't think that we should...
No... Don't go easy on me!
If you're doing it for me...
Do it seriously!
I've got it!
During the harsh training,
Hinata discovered her own styles...
and her own special Jutsu.
That's the result of her training.
Huh? You, why!?
I'll tell you something...
Angering the Queen Bee,
getting encased in wax,
it was all part of the strategy.
With our Chakra being sucked
and being immobilized,
it was the only way to protect ourselves
from the larvae...
And, do you think I was doing nothing
while I was captured?
I was ordering my bugs.
The wax we're wrapped in is very weak.
Shino!
Because of her hard training,
Hinata's Chakra control
has dramatically improved.
That Jutsu is what she developed
from the training...
Protective 8 trigrams 64 palms!
Hinata's already flexible body combined
with fine-tuned Chakra control
could completely defend
an attack from every direction...
Truly, it's an ultimate defense Jutsu.
Yet it's different from
Neji's 8 Trigrams Palms Rotation.
It's Hinata's own Jutsu...
She finally worked that out on her own.
She probably did it because she wanted
to be acknowledged by her father.
To be acknowledged by everyone...
And to be acknowledged by you.
Our Jutsu isn't effective at all?!
What the hell is going on?
What a girl!
Hey, what happened to those guys?!
When did they?!
Summoning Jutsu!
Blow them away!
Hinata!
Shino!
Believe... in her.
Make the Chakra...
sharper, stronger...
bigger, more flexible...
more...more...more...
more...more...more...more!
Hinata!
Naruto...
Hinata, that's an awesome Jutsu!
You're really awesome!
Naruto!
Let's hurry. It'll be dawn soon.
- Okay!
- Yeah!
Oh, it's becoming a pupa already?
If we make it smell Sasuke's scent
at the moment it hatches,
the mission is complete.
Right!
Sasuke... Wait for me!
No way!
Inside the tree, huh.
If it was there,
the bees should have found it...
You can still move?
This insect cage was coated
with secret Aburame family insect repellent.
Wh What?
The bees won't come close
because of the repellent.
As long as you're using bees to search...
you definitely won't find it.
I expected as much.
I think as long as your clan exists...
my clan maybe destined to
be ruined some day.
But!
I absolutely will not let you
succeed at your mission!
Even if it kills me, that Bikochu...
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
This is our hope...
in order to get our friend back!
I won't let you do that!
Shut up!
Rasengan!
Hey, look...
The pupa is hatching!
Okay!
Huh? It's gone!
You had it'til just a minute ago!
Hey, search for it, hurry!
R-Right...
Byakugan!
Naruto! Over there.
You blew it away the instant you set off
the Rasengan!
Hurry!
I know!
C'mon, c'mon.
It's going to hatch!
We did it! Hurry, make it sniff this...
Wh Why...?!
That thing just now doesn't count!
C'mon, sniff Sasuke's smell!
It's all over now.
Huh?
Hey! Stop! Wait!
So you failed because you farted!
Take responsibility!
What are you saying that for?!
Well then...
That's... the Bikochu, isn't it?
Naruto... I found you!
C'mon, forgive me already, Sakura!
No! I absolutely will not forgive you!
- Sakura, you look so scary!
- Come back here!
So the mission failed...
It seems that they succeeded
at protecting the Bikochu,
but failed at getting it to smell
the scent of Sasuke Uchiha.
I see... Hinata must be depressed.
This strategy was her idea, wasn't it?
Well... Looks like that's not the case.
Hinata... I heard that your mission failed.
Yes. It didn't work at all.
I have to train more and more...
and work harder next time!
I I see... Good luck.
More...
More!
Crappy news pass us by
And you become speechless
My voice is way too soft
So you don't answer
You're crying Crying alone
What can I do? I'm crying too
"Let my lonely scream ring out
through the night"
I'll thrash this confused era
with my speed Yeah
And I'll thrash this confused night
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar
and my speed Yeah
This sinking world and its evil bastards,
I'll kick their butt Yeah
What! Why do I have to go on
such an easy mission?!
Don't complain! You're the one
who picked up this mission's client!
That's no reason!
After all, I'm busy with a lot stuff!
That's enough,
or I'll send you back to the Academy!
That's not fair...
No arguments!
Neji, Tenten, Lee, Naruto!
The four of you,
I'm delivering your new mission.
Next episode:
"Funeral March for the Living