Subtitles By: BakaSan
Shit!
Damn it... At this rate this will be really bad.
No matter what...
No matter what I'll save all of them!
Light and Darkness
The Name Gaara
You fight for others?
That's why you guys stay that level.
You don't need a reason for fighting.
Only a winner can experience the value of existence.
Forget about your worthless friends and
just fight only for your own existence.
Worthless...
friends...
Those who bring in worthless emotions should die.
You... I won't let you keep talking like that...
I'm going to defeat you no matter what!
You guys don't know what real strength is...
Shut up!
Why? Tell me why?
Why are you... Why?
Why?
Love is a pure heart because you want to
help those precious people close to you.
Just like my big sister.
You are a precious person who's close to me.
You always... always... me... why?
It was an order.
I was asked to kill you...
by your father, Kazekage-sama.
By my father...?
Why does my father want me...?
You were born with the Shukaku of Sand as an experiment.
But you are unable to take control of the sand
that contains the living spirit of Shukaku and...
will be too dangerous for the village itself in future.
Before that becomes a reality...
Then, you had no choice because of my father's order...
No, that's not true.
It's true that I was ordered by Kazekage-sama...
But if I wanted to I could've refused that order.
Gaara-sama, in the deepest bottom of my heart, I've probably been...
...cursing you.
You were born by taking the life from my sister that I loved.
I've tried so hard trying to love you as a keepsake of my sister.
But I couldn't.
She didn't want to give birth to you.
She became a victim for this village and died cursing this village.
From then, I believe I got a wound of the heart that never healed.
Unlike the wound of the body, it doesn't have medical
cream to help it heal. Also, it may never heal.
A wound of the heart?
Your name is what my sister gave you.
This boy's name is Gaara.
Shura loves himself...
(Gaara = The god of war who loves himself)
So love only yourself...
And fight only for yourself.
You will continue existing if you do so.
Those were her wishes.
But she didn't name you this because she was worried or loved you.
The reason why she wished you to keep
existing and named you this name is...
...to let her deep grudge to this
village exist and always remain.
To make it known to the world that...
...you were not loved.
"Explosion note"
This is the end.  Please die.
I think my sister loved you.
Love?
The sand protecting you automatically is the love of your mother.
I think mother's will is in that sand.
It's Love.
Love only yourself.
And fight only for yourself.
That's what Gaara means... me.
I finally understand.
I'm alone.
I'll never believe anybody anymore
I will love no one.
I'm alone.
That's right. I'm all alone.
What's wrong? Come already!
You don't mind having your "precious friends" suffering?
Shit!
This is not like the usual Naruto. Did
something happened between those two?
Somehow... somehow I have to rescue Sakura-chan.
But how?
Yep, that's right. In this case,
though I'll use up lots of chakra...
I've got to summon Gamaoyabin!
Kuchiyose no Jutsu!
What? It's just a kid.
If you've got some business with
me then give me some snacks...
...or else I won't play with you.
I've got to say that I hate you so-called frogs!
What? Don't underestimate us Amphibians!
It's not time to play around you little one.
Damn it. Why? I trained so hard.
I don't have any other way...
I have to save everybody!
"everybody", you say? Don't make me laugh.
I fight only for myself.
He's transforming again.
If you don't defeat me the sand
on this girl won't get released.
On top of that, the sand will get tighter as
time passes and it eventually will kill this girl.
He's getting close to the final form.
He hasn't started that jutsu yet,
but at this rate even I will be...
Those eyes...
Sand Shuriken!
You are weak.
Shut up!
Any way’s, what is that?
You're so stubborn, Sarutobi Sensei.
It doesn't move.
You two should be dead already.
You still don't understand it, Orochimaru?
The Konoha village is my house.
And I told you that I'm the pillar of this house.
That's why I told you that I'll break that pillar!
As long as the people in Konoha fight for their precious
friends, this pillar won't get broken by somebody like you!
Is that so?
Don't underestimate Hokage.
No way. Where have you... your chakra should be drained by now.
Chakra and Ninjutsu are not everything of power.
What sad eyes...
Eyes that shows the deep solitude.
This guy is a monster.
The same as me.
I hated everybody.
I didn't know who I was, why I was hated so much, or why I existed.
In other words, you are the nine tailed demon fox
that killed Iruka's parents and destroyed this village.
You have been fooled by everybody in this village all along.
After I learned that there's the Kyubi inside me,
people in this village seemed colder to me than before.
Really, it was very painful.
But...
Naruto, do you want to go to eat Ramen?
Yes! I'll get extra Chasu today!
You useless idiot. If you want to
win against me then train harder.
Shut up. I won't lose to you!
Hey Naruto. What did Sasuke-kun say about me?
Nothing much.
Hey, don't you want to know what I think of...?
Naruto, you're gonna die for sure if
you keep eating only Ramen and Shiruko.
As a Ninja you need to eat more vegetables.
I brought these for you.
I don't like vegetables.
I had people who recognized me.
That's why I wasn't concerned about the demon fox
inside me or people in the village treating me coldly.
I'm not alone anymore.
I never imagined that it would
bring me this much joy and happiness.
I really... really thought it's great.
I felt that it's ok for me to be here and I'm existing and... I felt at ease.
That's why I feel so desperate when I think of the past.
That pain is no joke.
It's a dark hell.
If I were still alone...
That's why I understood.
Then, for what do I exist and live...
I concluded like this...
I exist to kill every existence but me.
I don't know what happened to him.
But he's been all alone and has kept suffering...
Never feeling at ease, and even now he can trust only  himself.
He's struggling in hell even now.
That's right. To him, I'm somebody that is...
...a weakling living in no-worries world.
Is it really possible to win against such a guy?
What's wrong? Are you afraid of me?
Fight for the others or fight only for yourself...
Just love yourself and do it.
Fight only for yourself!
That's the definition of the strongest person.
Fight with me. Where's your
spirit you had a few moments ago?
Show me your power. I'll crush that power.
What's up? If you don't fight with me I'll kill this girl.
Shit!
Taju Kagebunshin no Jutsu
(extra-multiple Kagebunshin)
Fuuton Mugen Sajin Daitoppa
(Wind element Limitless Sand Dust Great Wind Wave)
That's not good. That was a bad hit.
I'm going to play around without killing you for now.
I'm looking forward to see when you
run away leaving your friends behind.
But what is this?
Not yet.
What is this feeling?
Sand Shuriken!
Damn it!
God damn it!
He...
What is this feeling welling up?
For some reason, only to this guy...
You...
I don't want to lose even if I die!
Hey hey hey! Listen up! If you're not close to the TV...
...come closer and check this out!
There are many Genins in Konoha...
but I'm the only one who'll be the next Hokage!
I turn the worst situation into the my chance...
Henge! Kuchiyose! Kagebunshin!
...to double the return of blows!
As the most unpredictable Ninja in the world...
now is the start of Uzumaki Naruto Ninpocho!
(Uzumaki Naruto's book of Ninjutsu)
Next episode
Explosion!
This is the Naruto Ninpocho!!