Subtitles By: BakaSan
Hey... closet-pervert?
Special Secret Konoha Taijutsu Technique
Senen Goroshi (one thousand years of pain)
He's completely out. He's so weak after all.
What the hell is that big frog?!
Who are you anyway's?!
Thank you for asking!
I'm the spirit master of the Toad from Myouboku-mountain!
It's me whom called Gama-Sennin!
Hey, stop for a second! Pervert-Sennin Appears!
Sennin?
That's right!
Hey, hey!
Ero-Sennin! (pervert-Sennin)
What're you gonna do for me now?!
He was gonna be my trainer, but you made him like this!
'cause he disturbed me from gathering some material.
Gathering materials?
I'm a writer.
I write novels...
like this one!
Icha Icha Paradise!
That's....!
Huh? Have you heard of this?
I've became a bit famous...
That's an indecent novel!
Besides, that wasn't "gathering material".
You were just peeping in the women's bath!
Noooo!!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
They heard us peeping!
You're a pervert!
Dumbass! I'm not a pervert!
I was getting some inspiration for better novels by peeping.
Liar! I don't need to hear anymore excuses.
Anyway's... What're you gonna do about my training?!
Your training?
Are you talking about that
walking-on-the-water practice?
Huh... You know it?
Well then... take responsiblity and train me!
It's none of my business.
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait Ero-Senin!
You have to train me!
Shut up!
I hate people who don't know how
to talk to others respectfully!
Plus... I'm not into guys.
well, well...
Your book "Icha Icha paradise" was very exciting...
...and cool. It was really interesting!
Don't lie! The book isn't sold to people under 18 years old.
Ahh.. that's just what I've heard about the book.
It's useless trying to flatter me like that.
I'm a Sennin.
I'm not that stupid to be convinced by a little kid like you.
Hey! Wait a second!
Later, kid!
Amazing! He's a pervert but still so cool!
Hey! Ero-Sennin!
Where did he go?
What are you doing to me?! You perverted old man!
I'm sorry, little lady.
But those are very nice boing-boing's.
Pervert!
Ouch...
It's so shameful for a grown-up man to be like that.
He might not be as great as I thought...
...but I haven't got anybody else.
Oh well...
The women in this village are strong-minded, as usual.
But that's the good part.
As usual? Have you been here before?
You!
And you have been peeping all the time!
You're a Ero-Sennin!
Stop saying Ero (Pervert) with such a loud voice!
Be quiet!
The hit you knocked out the
closet-pervert with was a pure fluke.
Anyway's, you have to take
responsibility for ruining my training!
You're such a noisy kid!
Be quiet inside of here for a while!
Hey... let me out!
I want to meet a girl with a nice...
...body that makes my heart pitter-patter.
This is for what you've done to me!
Kawarimi-no-Jutsu (Body Swapping)
That old man isn't a regular guy as I thought.
That little kid... it's a million years too early...
...for him to come against me!
I doesn't seem that way...
I see you have some potential.
That means you're gonna train me, right?
Give and Take!
If you do me my favor, then I might do you you a favor...
That is I guess so... maybe thats how it works.
So, which is it?
I need a well-ripened fruit like this...
...and this... and like this.
If you bring me that...
...then I'll oversee your training.
Really?
This Toad-Sennin never lies!
Alright! Wait here.
A plan is just a plan...
It's not a... for sure thing.
Excuse me!
Ladies!
Mr. you're so funny.
Well, this is a real true story.
And then?
Ero-Sennin!
He called him Ero-Sennin.
Dumbass!
Who's a Ero-Sennin?!
I brought you what you wanted as promised.
The well-ripened fruit!
Stupid!Stupid!Stupid!
That's not it!
It looks so delicious!
Well, don't hesitate and eat them.
No!
Where did those ladies go?
I'm stuffed.
The ladies...
I can't be mistaken.
That person is...
Oh well...
I wasted my time so unproductively.
Hey, where're you going?
What about my training?! MY TRAINING!
Who cares!
My hard work's all wasted because of you!
What hard work?!
I don't have time to waste here either.
I will train myself a lot and...
I will be stronger than everybody and...
I will pass the Chunin exam and finally...
I will surpass the Hokage!
That's none of my concern.
You always get in my way!
I don't even like you!
For me to write a great novel...
young girls like the ones I had here...
are neccessary and required!
Oh, I see.
So, I need to bring you some young girls?
Alright.
Henge! (Transform)
What the...?
I feel embarassed if you stare at me like that.
What a beautiful girl!
I like you now!
You passed! [Full points!]
What an idiot.
You're dead-on my type of girl!
What is the name of this Jutsu?
I named this
Sexy-no-Jutsu.
Oh, such a wonderful idea!
You're a genius!
I think all the adults are so weak to this jutsu.
Then, you're gonna train me, right?
Yes... but there's one condition...
A condition?
What is it?
Always stay in that form in front of me.
Hey!
You're just a pervert after all! Ero-Sennin!
No, that's not true!
I'm not just a pervert!
What? Don't play innocent!
I am a super pervert!
Shit...
He took a defiant attitude.
Well, everything up to now was just a joke.
I'll train you from now.
Is that the truth?
This Sennin doesn't lie.
Now kid, continue the training you were doing before.
Alright.
Alright...
Shit
Not good at all.
Quiet!
Wearing clothes is useless!
Hey! Channel your Chakra again.
Huh? Again?
Shut up. Hurry up and do it again!
You...!
You look a bit sexy in those shorts.
Don't disturb me when I'm concentrating my mind!
Oh, sorry, sorry. Please continue.
He disturbed my rhythm...
I see...
this is the seal of Kyubi.
It's doubly sealed by two Shishou-Fuin. (Four symbol seal)
That's the Hakke-Fuin style. (Eight Trigram seal)
It's done to make it possible that Kyubi's chakra...
which leaks between those two Shishou-Fuin...
return into this kid's chakra.
Fourth Hokage...
It's to protect this boy, I see.
But since then...
it has been stopped by Gogyo-Fuin. (Five element seal)
By putting an odd-numbered seal...
on top of the even-numbered seals!
The chakra of this boy and Kyubi mix together...
out of order and has been unstable.
This is why he can't channel chakra well...
It's ticklish!
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I guess somebody else did it...
The style is rough.
I guess it was most likely done by Orochi-maru.
Water, Metal, Earth, Fire, Wood (five elements)
Kid, raise your arms.
What?
Just do it. Banzai!
He sure does make a lot of orders!
Gogyo-Kaiin! (Five Element opening seal)
What did you do to me?
Well, I just pressed some body points to make you relax.
Just try walking on the water again.
Dammit...
I don't know why but I can do it well now!
I am amazing!
I guess it's about time for me to teach...
him how to control Kyubi's chakra.
Alright, kid. Come over here.
Huh?
I'll teach you a great technique from now.
What? What?
A great technique?
Is it a special technique?
Before I teach you the technique...
I have something that I want you to really understand.
You may have not noticed yet...
but you have two types of chakra.
Two kinds?
Have you ever felt a special chakra before?
Special...?
Since you mentioned it...
I think I remember that I gained a ton of power...
with chakra coming out all of the sudden.
But I don't remember that time very much.
I see.
But, I remember it was different feeling...
than the chakra I normally channel.
If I put colors on them...
usually it is blue, but the other one is something like red.
I see.
Ok. Today's training is over.
Already?
What happened to that "great" technique?!
I can still train!
Impatience is forbidden for training.
Let's get in the hot spring...
Not FALL into it.
This warms me up.
The one drink after training is irreplaceable.
Hey, Ero-sennin.
What is the great technique?
You'll find it out tomorrow.
Heh! Stingy!
If he stays longer in the hot water, he'll be a boiled frog.
Sorry, Ebisu...
that I took your student from you.
No. But I was surprised.
The Hokage-sama has ordered to look...
for you but hasn't been able to find you at all.
Who would've guessed that you're in this village?
The Hokage-sama will be happy to hear that.
Did you already tell the Third Hokage about me?
No, not yet.
I see. It's better not to.
So, it's about Orochimaru.
No. I'm afraid that's not it.
What?
I just stopped by here to get some material for my novels.
I'm not the type to put my nose into others problems.
What are you saying?!
I believe you already knew about this!
In order to stop Orochimaru, one of the legendary Three
Ninjas, we need the power of another one of the Three Ninjas... you...
Jiraiya-sama!
First, write my name with my blood on this contract.
Then blood-finger-print-seal of all my fingers on one hand.
Then, channel chakra....
In (Hand seal) is Ino, Ee, Tori, Saru,
Hitsuji! (Boar, Dog, Hen, Monkey, Sheep)
Finally, place my hand that made
the contract on where I want to summon!
How about this?
Next Episode Transmitted directly from
Pervert-Senin It's the summon no jutsu!!
What the hell is this?!