I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long way to go
on that road.
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star lit sky with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that...
What were you gazing at?
Kakashi Sensei...
The mission in the Land of Birds
is over...
That is enough.
But, then what about Naruto?
As the leader,
I am responsible for all of this.
Sacrifice is an unavoidable part
of Shinobi missions...
Now...
Let's go back to our village!
Do you think they're really going back
to their village, Nagare?
Perhaps...
But I'm concerned about that masked guy
who joined up with them later...
Shall I follow him, Hokushin?
No, I'll do that.
You give the report.
All right...
The Death of Naruto
How did things turn out?
The two as well as the one
who joined up with them later...
seem to have crossed the border
and are heading for the Village Hidden in Leaves.
I see.
And it seems Lord Sagi
took care
of the one who infiltrated the residence
of the feudal lord.
Very nice indeed.
What're they doing there
for the past hour...?
P-Persimmon!
Wh-What the...?
- Ouch...
- That hurts...
It couldn't be!
Substitution Jutsu!
Since when...?
They tricked me!
Those Leaf Shinobi...
Lord Komei... Come out.
Land of Birds Tactician Komei.
You have abused the key position
in this land of tactician
and committed the crime
of assassinating
the previous feudal lord Lord Owashi
and his child Lady Toki.
And you also ordered a subordinate
to run wild as the ghost
called the Cursed Warrior,
disturbed the public, you undermined
the government of the land,
endangered Lord Sagi's position
of feudal lord
and attempted to attain
the position himself,
an unforgivable crime of treason!
Therefore, you are ordered
to perform seppuku!
I see... That explains it.
You ensnared me,
didn't you, Moso?!
You're disgraceful, Komei!
If you're a warrior, kill yourself like one!
Assist him with the seppuku
at once!
- Yes, my lord!
Is this it now...?
Wh What?!
Hidden Mist Jutsu?
No! This is...
It does not matter! Kill him!
Yes, my lord!
Begging your pardon,
I shall assist!
Who are you?!
Wh What is this?
What's going on?!
- The Cursed Warrior!
- It's the Cursed Warrior...
That's the Cursed Warrior?!
Yes!
After him! Don't let him get away!
- Right!
You guys go after him as is...!
I've got something
I want to look into,
so I'll be going on ahead!
- Roger!
I knew it!
You two were conspirators, right?!
Hold it!
You're the guys from
the other night...
I've witnessed the true identity
of the ghost.
Who's there?
Hey hey, Komei.
You're the one responsible for
controlling the Cursed Warrior, right?
I was also attempting
to investigate
the true identity of
the Cursed Warrior that day...
I was almost sure it couldn't
be anyone but that person...
What a pain! I'll expose
the true identity here.
Don't bother...
Kakashi Sensei.
Where were you until now?
I'll explain later.
Go on ahead!
Hurry! You're going with them.
But...
Let's go, T enten!
Wait, Neji!
Come on out...
You were following me
the whole time, right?
If that's your intention...
Summoning Jutsu!
What is it, Kakashi?
Smoke out the Ninja hiding
on the temple grounds...
Consider it done.
Hey! You there...
Hide and seek is over.
Come on out now!
I can't fool a dog's nose,
as would be expected...
You finally grace me with
your presence, huh?
Why is there a hole...
in a place like this?
I have heard the feudal lord built
secret passages such as this
all over the land in order to look in
on the lives of the general public...
The feudal lord?!
Then that Cursed Warrior
has something to do
with the feudal lord?
At the very least,
it seems he's not a ghost.
When the time comes,
I'm sure he will reveal
his true identity from his end.
Isn't it common sense for
hired Ninja
to return quietly to their village
after completing a mission?
It's different in the case
of the premise of the commissioned
mission breaking down.
There were too many
suspicious points in this mission.
You're sticking your nose too far
into the business of another land.
Here you could've returned safely
to your land
if you hadn't secretively
sniffed around like a dog.
Excuse me for being a dog!
Universal Assimilation Jutsu!
Prepare yourself!
What?!
What is this guy?!
Has he introduced properties
of stone into his body?
Since you've learned of part
of this land's secrets,
I can't let you live!
He seems to be a somewhat
troublesome opponent.
Yeah. That's good enough, Pakkun.
I'll be okay by myself from here on.
I see... See you later!
Assimilation: Rock Tank.
I'll crush you!
A Shadow Clone...?!
This is as far as it goes...
It can't be...
A Paper Bomb?!
Now... That should be enough, right?
Huh?
Yeah... We should be okay
having come this far.
Th That voice...?!
N -Naruto...!
I knew it.
The true identity of the Cursed Warrior
wasn't Lord Sagi?
Your...
Your true identity is...
Lord Sagi?! It is you, Lord Sagi?
From the way he was standing still,
I thought for sure it was Lord Sagi.
There's a profound reason for this...
What're you doing, Tenten?!
Then tell me sooner!
It seems you also knew
it was Naruto, Neji.
Yeah... Ages ago.
Jeez, you two!
I was really worried!
There was a surveillance Shinobi
following us the whole time, right?
Neji, Tenten...
Don't look back.
We're being followed!
We're going back to
the Land of Birds.
Just do as I say... Got it?!
Y Yes!
Understood...
But didn't we shake the pursuer
with Substitution?
Yes... Once...
However...
when we chased the Cursed Warrior
from the execution grounds...
a different Shinobi followed us.
Jeez... Am I the only one
who didn't know?
It was a waste to worry!
Then you,
in the place of Lord Sagi...?
Yeah...
I see... So Lord Sagi is safe!
You okay, mister?!
I'm sorry...
That Moso acted rashly,
forcing me to make
a false confession.
Man, you've been beaten up good...
Well, we'll tell you about
the developments inside.
Sagi is waiting!
Assimilation: Rock Shower!
We're Wandering Shinobi...
We make do without having a village
by going around to every village,
stealing Jutsu and
devising new Ninjutsu.
For example,
a Jutsu like this one, too...
S Say what?
Sharingan!
Assimilation: Sand Coffin!
He's using the same Jutsu
as Gaara!
Assimilation: Sand Funeral!
Sagi!
How's Chishima doing...?
He's okay...
There's no threat to his life.
He's resting and receiving treatment
in the treatment room
of my residence.
That's good...
Did something happen to Chishima?
Who...? Who hurt him?!
K omei... I'm sorry for
the misunderstanding!
My lord, I don't deserve
those magnanimous words!
Although he had suffered injuries,
Chishima came to tell me.
At that time...
I must not let you live as is
now that you have learned
of everything!
As the thief who snuck into
the residence of the feudal lord,
your fate is the death sentence!
No way...!
L-Lord Sagi...
Chishima?!
Bro!
Shuriken wounds...?
Go to the residence doctor!
Lord Sagi...
Please listen...
Lord Moso, no,
Moso has betrayed you...
What?
Moso was the one
who killed your father, Lord Owashi,
and Lady Toki!
And Moso had his own Ninja henchmen
use the guardsmen shuriken
to falsely accuse Lord K omei...
I'm sure Lord Komei learned
of Moso's scheme and...
Hang in there, Chishima!
Lord Sagi, please...
Stop Lord Komei's execution.
We have to go save him quickly!
I must not stop the execution!
Wh Why is that?!
I won't be able to have my revenge
if Moso realizes that
I have learned the truth...
Are you saying it doesn't matter
who is sacrificed
if it's for the sake of your revenge?!
Then what would you do?
Komei is being kept under strict watch
by powerful soldiers.
We would have no chance
of winning
if theywe were to cause
a rebellion there...
Then I'll go!
I will save Komei on my own!
You don't have a problem
with that, do you?
Lord Sagi...
Do as you like...
And so I disguised myself
as the Cursed Warrior.
I played the part of Cursed Warrior
and attempted to look for
the assassination culprit...
But against my intentions...
Instead of finding
the true culprit...
K omei... I was used as a tool
to incriminate you.
I thought the Cursed Warrior
I encountered in my bedroom
was you, Lord Sagi...
And so I headed for
the abandoned temple
where the Cursed Warrior
once vanished.
There I encountered
the Cursed Warrior, but...
That Cursed Warrior wasn't me.
Perhaps it was a fake
that Moso devised.
That's it, believe it!
All of it was that old man Moso's trap!
That Moso!
Did he think to first dispose
of me
and then eventually attempt to rule
the Land of Birds
by doing away with Lord Sagi?
That guy acting like a good guy!
I'll grab him up and kick his butt!
Naruto, was it?
You did good work.
However...
I will take care of things
from here on!
Well... But...
I will even the score by myself.
As long as the score isn't settled...
the clock inside my heart...
will remain stopped in the past!
So many things happen
on this endless road, huh?
Although you're strong willed,
your voice wavered on the phone today
What dreams did you chase to get here?
Even I have times when
I just don't understand, baby
When you're sad, I'll be close to you
Even on nights when we're apart,
I'll be close to you
What do you mean you will
even the score on your own?!
What good can you do
going by yourself?!
Even you did avengerthem,
the dead won't come back!
Do you still insist on having revenget?!
Would that make you
feel better?!
Would that really make
your father and sister happy?!
Next time: "When Time Stands Still"