Subbed by
Shinji 89
Byakugan!
Taken!
Optimal!
I will bring back  Sasuke to the village!
Naruto me dispiace,
but I will introduce   my technical new here.
Also mine!
Not churned to you.
We will only approach ourselves the target after that we will have prepared
my strategy.
It seems that they are not still shrewed of we.
Eh?Sasuke not is?
It seems that it is found to the inside of the barrel.
Eh?
I believed that there were of the snakes,
but to how much it seems are only of the bugs.
Aspetta!Aspetta!
We have not come in order to fight!
We have come here in order to only negotiate.
And then this thing is!
What you would want to make with that smoke-producing ?
You will not succeed in scappare from me!
This nearly invisibile thread is still finer and
strongly of a steel cable and it is impossible to see.
I can easy occupy me of you.
Merda.
It has placed on purpose two you spin various…
Why in truth triple trap was one.
Accidents.
I would not have never imagined that there was someone
with these powers.
I  will be I make you fuo -
What happens?
Optimal Kiba and Shikamaru!
The control of the shadow is successful!
But  as you see, this type of power exists also.
Thanks for being fall to you in our strategy.
You have frigates to us.
But ill-fatedly,
abilities of this kind exist also.
And '?
Art of the earth!
Cliff prison!
Dispute between the critical membri?Momento for the group of Shikamaru.
Maledizione.
This is…
We are in the prison of those boys.
Us task I to they.
I want to still recover  a Pò  of energies.
As you want, when you have ended to eat you catch up them to us.
Fast.
Ehi fatemi to exit!
Maledizione!
Six too much noisy one, Naruto!
From what I see, seems that is only a normal wall.
E' their technique.
Strategy is sure one.
I of it do not know nothing, but
but he seems that we will have ourselves to be rested for little.
E' dangerous to move, but also what you have said to make is dangerous.
Armor-piercing attack!
Regeneration is one…
I have seen.
It lets out us!
It seems that simple earth wall is not one.
Byakungan!
What !
That there is ?
Accidents.>.
They are sucking the Chakra.
Task that us they do not want to only lock up here.
I did not expect that they tried to suck the chakra.
You stop it to speak and portaci outside here!
I have eaten enough chakra.
Thanks for dull it.
What happens?
I feel that my force has been sucked.
Shikamaru, we must make something.
I did not imagine that we would have been captured all
before discovering their characteristics.
Moreover, sluices here within.>.
Maledizione!
We do not have alternatives.
Before exausting all mine chakra  bucherò  this wall!
Akamaru!
Here the war tonic.
Akamaru, uses human the magical art!
And I  will use  the wild magical art!
Zanne armor-piercing!
Perfect, Kiba continues!
Not there are points.
Eternal damnation is regenerated.
The same one is worth for the ground.
In these conditions we will not last not even 10 minuteren.
We will end the chakra and we will be destroys to you!
In this place it comes sucked the chakra.
In this state  I will not never succeed  to use one technical difficult
like the rasengan that it demands an extreme control of the chakra.
Hei!Ascolta!
I want to speak with your head!
We will not chase more Sasuke.
Therefore I ask you lets out us!
Shikamaru what you are saying?
Litigated Cos' è?Avete?
Interesting.
But you are my food.
I cannot lets out you.
Enough that free one single person.
She leaves to go me.
This combat…
it has stew to me.
Shikamaru but you know what you are saying!
Zitto, Kiba.
Urli too much.
What you are saying!
Conflicts in the group?
You the six group leader and put yourself to pray for your same life!
When a person approaches itself the dead women
extension its true personality.
An idiot as you she does not have the right makes itself loaded with the other people's screw.
Six solo losing.
I will say  to you  for last the more important thing.
You would want to abandon Sasuke and to sell your companions?
The chuunin of the village of the leaf they are all cos ì ?
Sasuke is a ninja of the leaf like we. E' a our companion.
And for that ce we will put it all in order to save it.
E' this the creed of the leaf.
The types as you they just deserve to die.
I will not let out  you .
I trusted myself te!Mi I have disappointed!
We go outside that you less!
It is not succeeded to exit dumb!
E' for that it it is supplicando!
What you have said ?
E' the truth, idiot!
You have said idiot of new!
Been all  a Pò  zitti!
Chouji?
And hour as you will astound to us ?
And now what tasks to make.
You the moment to put itself seems this to eat!
When Choji is angry is put to eat furiously.
Here an other incapable one.
Then the advanced technique of the multiplication remains us only!
Not to make it.
The wall is covered of the chakra of the adversary.
Even if you succeeded to break off it  a Pò, would return endured
to its shape it originates them.
Therefore we have need of a powerful martial art to the point to perforate it
in a single blow.
Choji it only possesses a more powerful martial art of mine.
… but it watches…
Maledizione what we can make ?
Neji, with the chakra remained you could observe the wall
behind of you and that one behind Choji?
It goes well.
Shikamaru, you are zitto!
Naruto!Non you have still understood!
It tries to remember what Shikamaru has said when has re-united to us!
Although it is svogliato of nature, to this point I cannot more say that
I do not have any wants…
Inasmuch as they are responsible of your screw.
Chouji,
from now it tries not to speak to high voice.
Kiba,
you can hit the wall that is between Neji and Chouji?
I do not know what is happening,
but  I will create  of new chaos!
Armor-piercing attack!
For how much casino you can create you will be always useless.
I understand.>.
Neji, tries to hit it with a kunai.
Chouji, six ready one?
OK
When you want!
Optimal, we begin ?
Hei what happens ?
As I have said before, walls of this cell are covered
of chakra.
But, Shikamaru has intuito that, also in one sturdy wall cos  ì,
there is a zone in which the layer of chakra he is thin.
And as you make to understand one of the sort what ?
It tries to remember…
Shikamaru if n' it is shrewed when Kiba and Akamaru have hit
the part…
… why there were of the points that richiudevano more slowly respect to others.
Therefore,
Where the repair happens more slowly is less chakra.
Moreover conversing with the enemy to the outside it is successful
to verify its position…
.. inasmuch as the farther wall from the adversary.>.
e' what it contains little chakra.
It wanted the confirmation of its position.
Just ?
But sure…
in order to trick an adversary it before must trick the companions.
The plan was this that hid behind the conversation
before
Therefore Choji had intuito the strategy…
… and it has been put to eat to squall in order to contain the chakra.
These two…
It was only in order to show that this not
it was an accidental attack.
It depends all on you, Chouji!
Technique of the expansion.
Ok!Andiamo!
It projects them human sweeping.
What !
Chouji, you six…
the maximum!
Boku Tamani, Boku Tamani
Hito Yume ni afureru not kakeraga
Yama not yonimieru
kamisama nihotoke samani
Hito Tsutae naiteru not karekaga
Yama not yonimieru
Nandero Dan dan dan sura
Borushoino placed ninarandara
Shake shake shake sagaso janainowa
bye bye bye not let' s of
Yama not yonimieru
I will make  a pact with he!
Chouji, not to say it to me…
Just, I have a secret.>.
But this is
Not there is a lot tempo!Shikamaru, you take all and we go!
Prossimamente:Potere massimo!Brucia Chouji!