Subtitles By: BakaSan
I...
to become Hokage...
can't lose here.
You will be Hokage even though you're weaker then me?
I will become Hokage for you!
Transform!
No way... it can't be true!
You can't even do the transform
after three years in the academy!
You guys... just wait.
I will become a real Hokage someday!
No way! You become the Hokage?!
You don't truly believe you can become Hokage do you?
Don't talk so big!
You are wrong Kiba-kun.
If you fight with me for the Hokage name...
...you will be a loser!
Hinata's Red Face! Spectators Surprised by Naruto's Final Hand
You're annoying saying the same thing over and over again.
That's fine... I will make you unable
to stand up. Let's go Akamaru!
I don't get beat by the same hand twice.
Take this!
Shit!
Even though I've seen this
attack before I can't keep dodging it.
What should I do? What should I do!
You look like your about to lose.
This is easy. Even if there are
3 or 4 of you I can still beat you!
You never stop talking! I'm going to finish
you next attack. Let's go Akamaru!
Shit! I need to counter-attack somehow!
Even if counter-attack, I need to
get to Kiba. But which one is which one?
What are you going to do Naruto?
Naruto-Kun!
ahh! I get it!
Transform!
I got you!
Ahh, I see.
Look closer.
Good! Good idea Naruto!
Naruto-Kun!
So if you transform into Kiba the real Kiba
won't know the difference between Naruto & Akamaru.
So he can't attack without thinking.
But Naruto-kun can attack either one!
Naruto stopped Kiba's attack. Good thinking.
Ahh I see...
...but, I will tell you one thing. I was
surprised but your transformation doesn't work on me.
Just because...
... I can smell.
Don't under-estimate our sense of smell Naruto!
Kiba can make his sense of smell 10,000 times stronger
by gathering his chakura into his nose.
Of course he can tell people apart by smell.
I win!
What?!
What's going on? Kiba's nose couldn't tell which was Naruto?
Shit! What's going on here?!
So this one is Naruto!
What?!
That's a pranksters idea.
He was fooled.
Naruto! Amazing!
The Naruto who transformed into Kiba was attacked
by the real Kiba because of the smell.
But Naruto transformed into Akamaru quickly
instead of returning to his real form.
It looked like Akamaru was beaten and his transformation ended.
Was Naruto that smart?
It that so?
Use your jutsu's after you think.
Otherwise it will be used against you, stupid ass!
Hehe, that's exactly what I told him before.
It's a waste of time arguing with him.
Don't fight at Naruto's pace. Calm down.
Calm down!
In fact he can't catch up with my speed. I'm at the advantage.
If I look closely at Naruto's movement, I can
get behind him for sure with Shikyaku-no-jutsu.
There's no need to worry... if I
calm down, I can win this match for sure.
I can see the enemy has already calmed down...
so, what're you going to do, Naruto?
Huh... so you're finally in mood for real fight, Kiba?
Well then...I will finish this with my super new technique!
So, you're finally in mood for a real fight, Kiba?
Then, I will finish this with my super new technique!
What?
A new technique?
When did you develop that?
Still hiding your new technique!  Amazing!!
A new technique?  That must be a bluff!
Try it on, if you think it's a bluff!
Damn it... this is same as before...
Don't get caught in his pace... Calm down!
Here I come!
Don't know what kind of technique it is...
I won't let you use it!!!
Now!
Giju-ninpo
Shikyaku-no-jutsu! (4-legs no jutsu)
Fast!
What are you stopping for?!
Naruto!
Hmm... I knew he's just at that level.
Stand up! Naruto!
Shit... there's no time to channel my Chakura!
Hey, what're you doing, Naruto!
Faaaast!
Impossible... there's no time to do it.
Too much difference in their skills...
I guess it's not possible for Naruto...
Shit...
Take this!
What?
This...
I will become Hokage...
I can't lose here like this!
Shut up! You can't even catch up with my speed at all!
It's like this when I fight with my real power!
Now you understand! To a great man like me, you're are just...
What?
I...
won't lose... Never!
Naruto is going all the way...
If I was Kiba, I'd get annoyed already
I don't care who wins anymore...
I just want them to finish up already
Naruto-kun... Do your best!
Naruto! Finish up with your new technique or whatever!
Naruto-kun! Do your best!
I have to stop Kiba's movement somehow...
Huh! Your attack doesn't mean shit to me!
I recognize only your spirit to fight
He's weak now... I'll finish with the next attack
I will show my new technique no matter what!
I won't let you!
You're slow!
Take this!
Oops?!
The fast movement and strong sense of smell...
Giju-ninpo became the opponent's best hand
Right now, Kiba's sense of smell is
10,000 time stronger than normal
Well... that fart must be an
accident. But that's the most unpredictable Ninja.
Naruto! It's the chance to finish now!
Oh man... I clinched too much!
But! It's time to show off my new technique!
Shadow-Replication no jutsu!
Alright! I'll give you back the pain you gave me at once!
U!
Zu! Ma! Ki!
Naruto Rendan!
A new technique, eh?
He saw the Sasuke's technique earlier...
Shishi-Rendan!
And... the name is also a complete copy.
The winner is... Uzumaki Naruto
Yeeees! Good! Alright!
THAT Naruto beat Kiba!
This is a big surprise.
I've been ... surely... getting stronger!
Hehehe... Easy! Easy!
Wha... what should I do? what should I do?
Huh? Oh Hinata? Did you say something?
What's this?
It's a cream medicine.
Why for me?
Just take it... Naruto
Thank you! You're a good person, Hinata!
Kiba. Don't be ashamed... This
kid was a really strong opponent.