Subbed by Gandelr
Chekked by Kyubi
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
Not rimangio never my words!
This is my Ninja creed.
And if you die.... your dreams moriranno with you!
Not firm! It moves to you from them. You escape!
As I have promised to the age of our bet…
I will earn  this necklace.
I…
Not  morirò  before becoming Hokage!
tsk.. You will not go from no part!
Vai!
Not.... Impossible!
Episode #95
Godaime Hokage
One life sacrificed to the combat!
Rasengan
This is…
Naruto.... has made it…
This Ragazzo-Volpe, has learned that technique?
Incredible…
Just incredible!
In a week it is only successful to learn…
The Rasengan!
You, after to have embedded this technique…
Before that the ball of Chakra caught up my stomach, I had begun
to accumulate the chakra in the abdomen.
E' for that Orochimaru-sama has to me chosen,
Not only for my performances, or the level of my techniques, but for my ability to regeneration.
I can replace the old cells and replace them with of the new.
However, I have nearly exausted my Chakra.
This technique,
It seems to be the winning paper of Naruto-kun.
Che cos' is …
Impossible.... I have regenerated my cells…
but the damages are however serious…
I do not have more much Chakra…
Of you strike yourself irregular!
Merda, the muscles are tear to you!
How it has made?
In that moment?
Sezionato muscles around
to the heart before the impact with the Rasengan
Not to shake!
Ehi Gamakichi-niichan.
We will have truly of the food?
That boy has the air of being died.
Taci! You cannot remain calm!?
Morirà Naruto-kun.
The organ that transforms the chakra of Kyubi in energy…
The heart…
I have stopped the circolatorio system of the Chakra…
I have used my last forces…
in order to prevent that it was regenerated.
Not there is no means....  It cannot  be recovered.
Also for you…
You are zitto!
I will kill  you  more late.
It does not breathe more…
Merda.
Merda!
Merda!!
The dusk…
The buio.
Why stà becoming gloomy all? Why is disappearing my power in the dusk?
Because…
Che cos' is…
Not to die.
Not to die!
The bet…
I have earned…
Impossible!
Poichè you say that your dream is to become Hokage…
A last time…
Once again…
I want to believe in you.
That child me seems put badly.
Tsunade is a specialist doctor.
Naruto will be well, not is from preoccuparsi.
It is not what I wanted to say.
That what imports…
E' time to end.
You do not have time to lose.
I did not expect that he became cos ì  strong…
If Akatsuki put the hands on that boy,
it could become a problem…
This wants to say that if I must kill it,
I must make now!
Merda!
It wants to hit it!
Tsunade, I did not have intention to hit to you.
But to leave this boy while still alive is one bad idea.
It could cause me of the troubles.
Not to interfere.
This boy…
Proteggero this boy!
Why a Sannin like you that it shakes
alla.vista of the blood…
it tries protect a simple one genin to the price of the life?
In order protect Konoha.... our village !
In order protect Konoha?
Why… Why… a boy a day will become Hokage.
Those inept ones.>.
In any case, to become Hokage, is one stronzata!
The imbecilli they only wish it.
To be Hokage, is one Stronzata.
The imbecilli they only wish it!
Their desires, are also yours, Tsunade-sama…
Your dreams, you have forgets them to you!
Old the proteggevano Hokage Konoha and the life of its inhabitants.
They put their life in game for this dream.
Even if you a six female, do not have the right to insult "old" and the Yondaime.
I will hit  you  with all my forces!
Beginning from now, also I…
I will put  my life in game!
Six you want to risk the life for this child....
then merits to die!
Tsunade-sama!!
I must make in time…
After that fatal blow, as  it can  still move!?
You want still protect this boy?
You I have as soon as said!
Beginning from now…
I put in game my life!
Then you end to crack!
Beautiful words, however still shake.
You do not succeed neanche to stop yours fobia.
I do not understand why you want protect this boy,
Because you strike yourself for Konoha…
Impossible!
It does not shake more!?
It has been stopped!
This is because now…
They are the Fifth Hokage di Konoha!
Qual' is this seals?
Tsunade-sama has sormontato its fobia? But this is…
Which thing you count to make, now?
I have hurt to you and you have lost much blood,
you will not be able to fight with me in this state.
Waited for a moment!
I  will recover them your wounds!
You do not open I seal, ve I pray some!
I pray to you, freed I do not seal!
Liberation of Sigillo!
Ninpou, Souzou Saisei
[ Regeneration ]
Which technique is this?
They are not the solo to have developed of the technical new…
Qual' is exactly this technique?
Well…
I have passed much time to store my Chakra.
I have used one great amount of chakra in order stimulating my cells…
and to increase to their speed of regeneration and division.
My muscular woven organs are able to reconstruct all and.
This is not only one guarigione, but one regeneration.
That  never means that in a combat  not  morirò.
But the time number that the cells can be regenerated is limited.
Who uses this technique abbrevia its life!
Tsunade-sama!
This gesture…
Orochimaru-sama!
I hope to make it us!
Sbrigati!
Ino
Inu
Saru
Tauruses
Hitsuji
Kuchiyose not Jutsu
Episode #96
A Combat to Three
Ah, papà!
It is put badly!
Ehi, Gamatatsu! We go ourselves some!
Eh? Why?
Not to make questions, you go via!
Manda and Orochimaru, Katsuyu and Tsunade…
an encounter like the old times.
You want to make one reunion with old friends, Jiraiya?
Idiot! E' from much time that not you invocavo, it avoids to joke?
I had thought to carry a.termine a our small transaction.
Orochimaru, today you will be defeated.
Ehi Orochimaru.
Not invocarmi for much annoying situzaioni.
Therefore, you want that it eats to you?
Not speeches cos ì,  Manda-sama.
Ringrazieremo to you later....
To who creeds to speak?
Not to speak to me like if you knew to me, small parasite!
Ehi, Orochimaru.
For the sacrifice, you will have to prepare a hundred of bodies.
Even if it is its servitore, "Sends" will betray to us
not as soon as it will have uncovered that Orochimaru not
it can  use its Jutsu.
In this situation.>.
to invocare Manda is extremely rischioso!
Katsuyu, you lead this boy from Shizune.
S ì,  I have understood.
Perfect! Also I…
Shizune-sama, I pray to take you to you cure of this boy.
Naruto-kun…
Also, this place will become a terrible battlefield.
You move yourselves more far away possible.
E' which wants Tsunade-sama.
Tsunade-sama…
Plants it, Wants that it reduces to you to pieces?
Just when I had need of a new pocketbook in snakeskin.
Orochimaru! You have made too much badly.
We are not more similar.
Companions?
It does not make me to laugh.
The legenda of the three Sannin will end today!
Zesshi Nensan!
[ acid Jet ]
and you!
Katsuyu!
Tsunade-sama!
Merda!
It arrives!
I have seen!
Tsunade, remains in disparte!
Bunta! of the oil!
OK!
Katon, Gamayuu Endan
[ fire Element: Braciere to the oil of Rospo ]
ce we have made it?
Creed.
Not, this is…
One skin! It has changed skin!
Bunta, is under!
Which thing?
Stopped!
As I thought, to strike itself against two Sannin at the same time is revealed difficult.
Tsunade!
I will strangle  to you, cos ì  we make it ended…
My Chakra…
If it continues…
Even if you have said that not morirai never in a combat,
If I strangle to you, morirai, Tsunade.
How much time I can restistere…
This is a bet.
Much good!  It is  time to make ended it!
Impossible!
You take this!
This is the end!
Merda!
E' this that Tsunade-sama....!
One would say that it has caught up its limits.
My God!
Always beautiful E' to hit it…
It is  all that one here of which six able one.
You are zitto!
I cannot be stopped!
I must continue it to hit it.
E' mine the life that I have put in game in this combat!
Orochimaru-sama!
Not scappera!
It remains with me until the end!
Spece of…
I must hit it still and still…
Che cos' is this strange feeling?
Finally with this…
This is the end!
It has given off all this power with only a blow.
The combat is ended…
S ì…
Orochimaru-sama!
As dared to humiliate to me in this way.
I would have eaten to you gladly, but…
With my bucata mouth, I cannot swallow nothing.
Me you will pay to our next encounter!
Tsunade, I do not have more need than you,
poichè other means remain me…
in order to recover my arms.
Cos ì  I will come  to destroy Konoha definitively.
I would want see again to you in that occasion, companions mine.
Tsunade, Jiraiya.
This ace…
Able E' of impossessarsi of the body of an other?
That  explains because it does not seem to try the effects of the aging.
They are the incarnation of immortality.
I am indestructible!
We will see again ourselves soon.
Waited for!
I have one fracture to the ribs and the leg.
I begin to feel the symptoms of my technique.
My body, I cannot more…
Tsunade, six never be one good giocatrice.
To become Hokage is my dream!
I will give  one  week to you. If you will be able to dominate it…
I will recognize  that you can become Hokage,
and I will give  this  necklace to you.
Not there is problem!
If I have three days,  I will be able  to dominate it!
A man  cannot  return on its word.
I am the grandson of the first Hokage,
R-he who has founded the village of Konoha.
A man  cannot  return on its word.
Here! Like my grandfather, a day  I will be  Hokage.>.
Why to become Hokage is mo the dream!
I love this village and its inhabitants.
It is  for that I want proteggerli.
I live for proteggerli.
Why to become Hokage is mo the dream.
I want that you chip axes this.
I feel the secondary effects…
Tsunade-sama…
Therefore you say…
And then? Meeting my aspect with  a rest  Pò.
We go to rest to us in city, and not hardly Naruto
it will have resumed acquaintance we will return to Konoha.
Tsunade…
Beginning from now, they are not more Tsunade, I I am…
Godaime Hokage-sama!?
(Fifth Hokage)
Then the old Tsunade beginning from
now it will be the fifth Hokage?
How? You do not have the air of one happy, Naruto.
Evidently! Compared to the old Sandaime, she…
It violent, egocentrica, is vitiated and idiot.
Task that you have the head from an other part.
Then, Tsunade-sama, you want to order qualche.cosa…
And then, after all it has 50 traveste years and from young woman…
E' a good for a Hokage  can  mentire to all in this way?
You have ended, moccioso!
Eh well, recommences…
Whether you like it or not, I have become Godaime Hokage.
I do not have need to strike to me seriamnete against a child like you.
A finger will be sufficient.
This is not because they are a child who must make fun of itself of me!
Sai, a day  I will be  Hokage!
Eccomi!
Not once again?
Good person becomes one!
And excellent Hokage.
S ì!
Then, we return to the Village.
He! But I have not still eaten nothing!
You stop to laugh!
Nawaki, Dan…
I have found a boy with your same dreams…
And it is here!
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
Yume wa ryuusei of yo ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
Yahoo! It is  the spring!
Ero-Sennin it has cut its hats and the Old one has left is not known where!
It is  well to rest itself of the times.... Who has perquisito my room?
I do not know who has been, but  I will find  the guilty and gliela  I will make  to pay!
Next episode:
The Spring of Naruto
The next Naruto week will be transmitted to the 19:27.