Subbed by Kyubi
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
Ehi, you do not want to see it?
Seriously.
About what it speaks?
Of what creeds that speak?
The face of Kakashi!
you are joking?
Not… It does not interest to me.
The mission has been concluded today. I return to house.
Indeed?
It would have been cos ì  amusing…
And if it has the mouth to shape of Tarako?
[ Tarako: cod eggs ]
* Mouth… *
* like the Tarako… *
Eheh.. an other pochino.>.
Or perhaps of beaver…
beaver
* beaver *
Episode #101
The true ace of Kakashi!
I want to see it, I want to see it!
Strange  what is one.>.
I pray.
that you want to be with me.>.
It is in order to snow?
Happening!
I must wait for one to me similar what …
I pray.
You ask me to come for being able to be with me
It is in order to snow.... Not!
but …
Happening!
or something of the sort.>.?
I pray.
You ask me to come for being able to be with me
It is in order to snow.... Not!
Must explode qualcos' other? Not creed.
Happening!
or. one what cosi ?
Or you hide me qualche.cosa?
Of… of.... Of that what speeches?
It is  ours it must occupy you to us, Kakashi-sensei!
To. All-all-allora…
Eaten, eaten!
It goes well.
Then I cannot refuse this meal.
I pray.
The pig is our specialty.
I do not see the hour to taste this pranzetto.
Sasuke-kun!
Ino, ugly stronza!
-  not to push! I do not see nothing!
I have eaten indeed well. It was delicious.
That fast!
There is something that does not go?
Uhm.... Nothing…
He is  truly incredible!
Mmmm, in such case, I  to us  will think!
But that you count to make?
In this case…
I  to us  will think!
I am asking like you will make to you, idiot!
You have a plan, Sakura-chan?
Then…
We must pedinarlo. E' the only way. Sooner or later it will remove the mask!
Like six intelligent Sasuke-kun! The six best one!
But if he is a deficient one.>.!
Which thing you have said?
N-nn.. nothing
But that ago Kakashi-sensei!?
You are zitto, incosciente.
We have been discoveries!
Naruto, a six idiot! If it has seen to us, is for guilt yours!
Mine is not guilt!
The film!?
I must buy endured a ticket!!
It is  disappeared!
We follow it.
S ì!
Dov' is!?
Merda, is disappeared.
From where it is passed?
Which thing fairies?
It has qualche.cosa to that to see with me?
Not…
Ehi, because we are made to discover?
It can  be because we were too much numerous.
If one hides to us correctly, imports how many little we are.
You have forgotten your training, Sakura-chan?
Better if you are zitto!
To follow it would be a good training.
We go now. we divide ourselves.
S ì, you have reason. Lasciamo Naruto to go for first.
Eh?
Here that Junko said…
"I am in order to lose your traces."
It is scappato to me.
As usual, vigliacco.
That idiot race.>.
Bastard…
But that ago Kakashi-sensei? E' l ì  from cos ì  a lot.>.
It is not possible!
Sasuke-kun! Then?
E' scappato to me.
We go!
The mission today is to work in one small farm.
The mission is not for nothing amusing.
I will make  all those that I can
In order to see the face of Kakashi-sensei!
Which thing is? You have a less enthusiastic air of the usual.
They are much enthusiastic one!
Much good.
I have found to you finally…
Hatake Kakashi!
Kakashi…
In our according to encounter,  I will have  my rivincita one.
Brother, which rivincita?
Idiot, already six forgotten to you?
I will not never forget  it .... was the spring of 3 years ago
Iaaaaaaaa!
You must not have fear!
Our brother wants to only speak with you.
Brother?
I love to you. You want to marry to me?
Brother, six cos ì  beautiful!
Not…
Not to have fear.
You tighten to me between your arms tenderly and…
Not.
All good.
It would not be said, but they are rich!
I have said to you not!
Which thing?
Me refusals…
I have said noo!
A lot for this romantico moment is engaged me…
When I do not want I do not want!
Why not left it to be?
ta-dan
It watches, this girl to not wants you.
Any thing you make, you will make yourself to reject.
Six much brave one!
You are defying?
We are the 3 frightening siblings Moya!
The siblings Moya? Never felt to speak about you.
Never felt to speak about we!?
As it dares to take game to you of we!
Infame! Who six!?
They are not known, but.... I call Hatake Kakashi.
That stupid name!
Ehi, Infame!
You of it you will repent!
You have interfered with with one love history!
Of love?
You are seccanti, sapete ?
Ok boys, we go!
S ì!
To the attack!! To the attack!!
Please, someone us aids! You help us!
Waited for! You help us!
You bringing back to the village.
You help us! Ehi! You do not go yourselves any, you do not leave us here!?
S ì,  Was happened just cos ì.
It is not beautiful to speak of inasmuch as we have been humiliates to you!
Then, this is the rivincita one that we wait for from 3 years?
During these 3 years, six trained to you in order to become stronger. You will crush this parasite!
It will be a beautiful combat!
Imbecille! Who would make one similar what?
If  I will be able  to make it, I will make  it  furtively, in the shadow, and with astuteness.
Secretly!
Welcome!
Impressive!
It seems cos ì  good!
They are delicious.
Pure fairies with calm.
Kakashi, eats, is happy, today morirai.>.
I have put in the food one powder that da' an interminable sob.
Your sob will not be stopped, and you will not be able to breathe more correctly. Then morirai.
This is the dead women who are up to you.
Which thing does not go? You have not touched yours cotolette.
Nothing. Also you would have to eat, Kakashi-sensei.
He does not go to me, are full…
He does not go well. In this case,  I will make  of all for togliergli the mask!
Aaah, is slipping to me!
Which thing you have made!?
They are mortified. E' be an incident.
It has not been an incident!
All that good food…
Unjust E' cos  ì…
Ehi, than what we make hour?
You are calm. I have a plan.
A plan?
I have understood.... you have had truly one good idea, Sasuke.
Of habit the persons remove the mask here.
Sure, they are a Ninja of talent.
Kakashi, morirai here.
It is  one of my inventions.
There is a needle poisoned with a pozione that provokes uncontrollable risata.
To die to laugh…
She will be your dead women.>.
Uff.. I wanted to see it also.
But it is a public bath…
I want to see!
Kakashi-sensei! Not six ready anchor?
S ì,  arrival.
I must see it!
Laggiù!
Perfect.
I do not see nothing!
Eccomi…
You excuse me for the delay.
Why it is ended cos ì…!
Hour!
Eh? That there is?
Vabbè, I am based.
That what is that one…
I ask what has happened.... I want to know!
Maledizione! Next to that what thought Kakashi-sensei?
Maledizione, than loss of time!
Our uniforms!
Returned when you want!
-  Thanks for all.
Merda…
I have not ended with you, Hatake Kakashi!
We have been fortunate in order to have of the dresses of reciprocation.
They are of agreement with you.
But I ask who has taken them.
Well fairies the one which you must make, and it does good it you.
Gone!
Ehi, I cannot still wait for I am becoming crazy.
I am in order to catch up the limit.
Sasuke-kun, honestly, also I…
In this case, it is our last possibility!
Our last possibility?
But this …
You have not understood? They are of the estates from Ninja!
Where you have found to them?
Not not not.... not fairies attention to the details.
What you count to make?
To remove its mask, with the force!
Kakashi, eh…
Brother! Laggiù!
Ehi! Hatake Kakashi!
Eh? Which thing you want from me?
Of that what speeches? We are only of the Ninja ordinary…
It is not that we want to see what you hide under the mask…
Idiot! Better if he does not speak!
This is…
Brother! There are other persons who want to be revenged with Kakashi!
It is  our occasion!
Much good, we go!
Waited for a moment!
Kakashi! We are your worse incubus!
It prepares to you to die!
Here my special pozione that it will make you to always cry… in order!
I asked myself when you would be escapes outside.
Ce you have made it, finally.
But before.... Sasuke, Sakura, Naruto…
Which thing held fairies in these strange ones?
Ehm… but. mma.. veram.>.
We must find one at all costs excuse!
You have fallen in trap!
You were chasing Kakashi-sensei, was clear.>.!
Which thing!?
You want to say that you knew our plan from the beginning!?
Sure!  An elaborated  plan is right in order to catch to you! And it has worked!
Then you knew it!
Merda! Dealt to us like children!
I do not know nothing of this history.>.
You are going well, Sakura!
I have not understood what well is happening.>.
however…
You excuse to us! You excuse to us!
It is not a problem.
E' the end!
He is  exactly  that  that is happened 3 years ago!
We are legacies still with to one rope.
And it is making of new the same gestures!
E' still of buonumore!
It has purpose, you who you are?
It is more not remembered not even than we!
Ehi, Kakashi-sensei!
Eh?
Which thing hides your mask?
Which thing? You want to see  that  that there is behind my mask?
S ì.
You had to say it before to me.
Ce you would have shown it?
Sure. I do not have problems.
That there is? That there is?
In this case…
The cod egg mouth…
One stupid what…
A mysterious ace?
Under my mask…
Under its mask…
There is an other mask.
Aaah! he is not possibilee!!
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
You listen to me! You listen to me!
They are born and grown in the old Village of Konoha, my name is Uzumaki Naruto!
A Ninja maldestro!
But not of all!
Which thing storys?
With a po R-di.fortuna, we could meet great Wasabi head!
And I  will obtain  its respect immediately!
Next episode
Critical moment - One new mission
The sense of the duty towards the men