Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking NFS}
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the fire!BANG!
Uh-UhmÉ
Return to house in the fog early riser.
My mother and my father have been killed.
Because of my weaknessÉ
É the entire clan has been swept via.
They have been killed one by one.
Merda!
Training finished early riserÉ!
An other hard training, not as soon as waits for me eaten.
Grandfather.
(Konohamaru).
Hey, Konohamaru!
Naruto-onii-chan!!
(it is a friendly way in order to call it brother)
Ah, the lessons of the academy still are not recommenced?
N..NoÉ not still.
The classrooms of the school are collapsedÉ
É therefore all we are giving one hand to repair them.
Ah.
Naruto-onii-chan, and you?
You are training yourself?
, enough.
What is?
What watches?
Oh, nothing of thatÉ
Well, ahÉ
Now what is?
Also you, than hide to me?
Nothing, trulyÉ
They are not at all sad.
Eh?
It is not the moment rattristar.
How many are all working hardly
in order to reconstruct this village.
KonohamaruÉ
E' the moment to engage itself until in bottom for the village.
Therefore also you it works hard and
it trains to you hardlyÉ
É otherwise  I will become  Hokage before you.
Huh?Stupido.
I  will be sure what it will become Hokage.
Also why you must before graduate yourself to the Academy!
Ah, sureÉ
What?
Oh, I have found it.
Here, you hold.
A Ramen gratis
from Ichiraku?
Indeed?
Of it I have an other anchor, therefore this is for you.
Thank you (thanks),
Naruto-onii-chan!!
Hey, Konohamaru-chan!
Buongiorno.
Now I go.
We will work hard today!
Yeah!
Today we must fix the blackboard.
Yeah, I have carried the varnish.
ViaÉ not as soon as ended to eat
the ramen from IchirakuÉ
É my training will continue!
From that partÉ
Oh!Ma that one is....
E' a beautiful one po' that they are died.
A lot probably has happened before the examination from chunin.
ThenÉ
É finally I have understoodÉ
É that you are damned Orochimaru!
After to have assassinated Kazekage-samaÉ
É Orochimaru or Kabuto has taken
sembianze of Kazekage-sama.
We have been imprudent.
That you are damned, Sarutobi!
He is not cos “  simple.
After all your adversary was a Hokage,
considered from all more strongly of the 5 great villages.
But he has gone better of the previewed one.
You have killed two of the five KageÉ
EnoughÉ
Enough with these words that play very of comfortÉ
É or I will kill  to you!
Naturally it was not in my intentions.
Although we are not resolutions to destroy the villageÉ
É the other objective of this planÉ
Uchiha Sasuke.
Now it has on the neck yours I seal.
I have sacrificed both the arms and all my techniquesÉ
If only pits be in a position to making my Uchiha Itachi,
we would not have met all these problems.
But it is a dream that will not be able to never come true.>.
É now it is even more powerful than me.
Here whyÉ
I have left that organization.
E' KakashiÉ
What will be happening?
Breakfast! Breakfast!
It waits for to me, mine ramen!
Sai already which is the place?
.
Then it will be all easier.
We go.
Eccola that arrives!
Well, wellÉ just what I tried!
The village of Konoha is fantastic.
Just of great level!
Still it occupies your time with similar cretinate?
Beh, this is not other that one collection of information.
Mrs. Komura and Koharu-senseiÉ
What wants from me the Council?
What we want from you?
You know very well, not is need that you says.
What is those makes cos “  scaredÉ
I have known that the truce with the enemies of the Sand is stipulated.
The Village of the Sand has given the guilt
of all how much to Orochimaru.
Moreover, they have declared their complete yield to Konoha.
But they are not here in order to speak about this.
Konoha did not have other choice, to accept the excuses for being able
to maintain the reputation of more powerful village.
ButÉ
The power and it want to fight of Konoha are reduced to the bone.
In a situation like this, the first priority is
to still avoid that they happen events gets worse.
We do not know if and when the enemy villages
they will try to attack us of new.
Therefore we have decided to create a emergency council
composed from the best ones ninja of the villageÉ
É in order to decide the line to hold until to when the village
it will not have repurchased its power.
But before thisÉ
We have need of a powerful and charismatic leader.
We have very many enemies who are in ambush.
Orochimaru is only one of the many.
I do not understand the need of having to tell
all these things just to me.
Beh, hour I must recommence the collection of informationÉ
What does not seem to have understood oneÉ
We have immediate need of a Fifth Hokage.
Yesterday, to the reunion with the Daymos of the village of the Fire,
we have decided that you JirayaÉ
É the six prechosen one!!
Me dispiace, but they are not just the person adapted.
At this point it is all deciding. Who others if not a Sannin, one of the three best ones shinobi than always, would be adapted?
If you want a Sannin, there is n' is an other beyond me!
Forgotten Tsunade.
Although it is true that it could be the just personÉ
É we do not have the minimal idea of where it can be.
I  will go to try it! Cos “  not will be more some problem, just?
ButÉ
Rather than to try to convince to act controvoglia, I think to me more intelligent to choose Tsunade for the role of Hokage.
That of thoughts?
It goes well.
We will be believed on. But I would want to place side by side, in order to find Tsunade to you, three units of Anbu search more quickly.
You do not preoccupy yourselves. Not  scapper˜  via.
Not there is need that someone me controls.
One single whatÉ
There is a boy that I would want to carry with me in the travel.
I have found an egg a lot interesting.
Strange, nevertheless I was sureÉ
Dispiace but if it does not find to me the good meal I cannot give the ramen to you.
It waits for.
They are sure to have of still oneÉ
AhÉ had been the last one the one which I have given to Konohamaru?
Welcomes!
NotÉ mine ramen!
Hey, you two.
Seemed one beautiful brace together.
Idiot. We are here in order to only buy of the Dango (balls of rice) for Anko.
Instead you that what you are making here?
Beh, I have bought of the Sonae Mono, and have an appointment hereÉ
(Sonae Mono = votivo food for the tombe of the defunct ones)
É with Sasuke.
Eh.. E' rare to see to you to wait for someoneÉ
That food is for the tomba of Obito?
Obito?
Beh, something of the sort.
KakashiÉ
Strange E' that you have arrived before me.
Once every a lot.
It does not appeal to the Natto to me (fagioli of soia fermented)
and all the other cakies.
Ah, indeed?
Uffa! It is not possible, is too much strange!
Ehi voi!Non me you seem inhabitants of the village!
What you have come to make here?
We do not look at ourselves from much Asuma-saint, Kurenai-saint time.
Inasmuch as you know our names mean that six one shinobi original of Konoha, me mistake?
YouÉ you sixÉ
Without doubtÉ
Uchiha
Itachi
Itachi, is of yours knowing?
ThereforeÉ
I  will have to introduce alsoÉ
Hoshigaki KisameÉ
You remember yourselves of this name in futureÉ
Not there will be some futureÉ
Been in order to take one tide of legnateÉ
Itachi-saintÉ
It seems that you are not a lot very seen in this village.
I know to you wellÉ
Hoshigaki Kisame, ninja of the secret village of the FogÉ
É searched for homicide from the village of the WaterÉ
É suspected to have participated to the revolt in that county.
You two are criminal of S Class in the black book of you search to you.
Itachi.
After to have caused that massacreÉ
How it dares to replace foot in this village?
A six impudent one.
Asuma-Saint, Kurenai-Saint
Fairies feint not to have to me met.
I do not have some intention to kill to youÉ
How I can be trusted a person who has killed its relatives?
To go around itself in under the secretly mentite village empty is an attitude that I find a lot losco.
Which are your intentions?
These persons are many annoyingÉ not tasks?
To how much she seems we cannot calmly go itself some from the villageÉ
But she goes to us flat. Your special attack creates much bustleÉ
At this point it is decided.
This isÉ
Genjutsu (style of illusory combat)
It is holding to me to attends with the single tip of the sword.
How much force will really possess?
My sword, Samehada (Rough Skin)É
É it is made in order to tranciare, in order not to cut.
Kurenai, six in delay.
This isÉ
É the end!
A Genjutsu of this level does not work on me.
This isÉ
Genjutsu Gaeschi
(reflected Genjutsu)
Kurenai!
Me it does not seem that you have the time to watch to you around!
Me dispiace for Kurenai-saint youÉ
ButÉ
But it ends here!
For you twoÉ
What?
Suiton
(Water Release)
Suikodan not jutsu
(Squalo di Acqua)
My same technique?
Then in order which reason devil you have caught up to us?
Beh, before I had asked you two to follow themÉ
But I was being boredÉ
Kage bushin?
Hatake.
Kakashi.
You have kicked up a row all this!
BehÉ
É I did not want to gratis lose the good meal during the training of the mattino.
É cos “  I had hidden it within to the Coprifronte.
Well, it is all I lie in wait for.
It eats well and it works hard.
What?
You will go to still train to you after this eaten, is not true?
Sure, hardly.
OkÉ hereÉ
Uh?
E' offered from the house. It trains a lot to you!
Thanks, getlteman!
Ah, welcome!
They have come here since they have said to meÉ
É that it is just true that only eats ramen.
EroSennin!
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete
Uchiha Itachi
A man who has become head of one Anbu unit to 13 yearsÉ
É and the entire Uchiha clan has destroyed alone.
I do not know why you are reappeared just now butÉ
É we cannot leave to return without to say nothing you.
Dimmi your true intentions.
Next episode:
Sharingan against Sharingan