http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
According to examination for the selection
of the Chunin it has hour beginning!!
We try some monellaccio!
Those three just?
Evvai!
We go!
Well, first of all we try they.
Six of agreement, Hinata?
It calm To You, Lee.
We are only to the beginning.
I know.
But
I cannot be calm when I know
that of the enemies many forts wait for to us.
I imagine that
you know qual' is our objective!
It seems that they have begun.
It was urlo that one?
I am myself innervosendo.
Not to worry to you, Sakura-chan!
I must make pip  ....
Idiot!
What tasks to make in front of one Miss.!?
It goes to make behind a bush!
To eat or to be eaten!
Naruto becomes food for snakes!
How much I have made some!
I have said to you that
it is not behaved to us cos   in front of
Sasuke-kun, not was need
to hit it a lot violentemente!
Which devil takes to you?
Where is found the true Naruto!?
But what devil you say cos   to the unexpected one?
Dov' is ended the wound that
it has made the esaminatrice you in face?
Moreover your bag
of the shuriken it is on the left.
Naruto the right door.
The six worse one than Naruto in the transformations.
That misfortune!
Cos   you have to me uncovered?
Who of you has the coil?
Then I must use the force!
Katon: Housenka not Jutsu
!fuoco!esecuzione:
(technical mystic of the fire flowers)
Sasukeeee!
Diamine the coglione!
Well!
S ! Six distracted to you!
I seal explosive!
That fortune!
If you move I kill you!
Now they give the coil to me!
Sasuke-kun!
Bastard
You will not go far away!
Always six in Naruto delay!
I must use the chakra in order to hit it!
Bastard
What?
Sasuke-kun!
Not distrarti Sakura!
They could it are to us of others!
If it lowers the guard it risks the life!
That misfortune!
I have mistaken to attack them
alone in order to pick them of surprise.
Scappato E'.
If we had ourselves to be separated, not reliable to you
of nobody, neanche of one of we
The enemy could use the Henge like little ago.
What we must make?
We will use one order word.
Word of order?
Ascoltate.
If the word will not correspond
you will have considers it like an enemy
and fatevi not to trick from the appearances.
You listen to me carefully,
repeating   only once.
The melodia of the ninja, "Ninki".
When ce we ask it we answer cos
"the shinobi it is found to its comfort
in the confusion of the enemy."
It must hide and remain in Hush.
The shinobi it must know the opportune time
of when the enemy is tired and disattento."
This is all.
Okey!
You can repeat it of new?
I had said, only once.
You do not succeed memorizzar it?
Six stupid?
I memorizzato it to the moment.
Naturally memorizzato all!
I thought you asked to repeat it
an other time in the case that....
Terr   I it parchment.
It waits for, Sasuke
What?
Other enemies!?
You gone boys to amuse to you laggi.
I instead me occuper   of they.
Sakura
Sasuke-kun!
You are behind!
Before the coded phrase.
The melodia of the ninja, "Ninki"!
"the shinobi it is found to its comfort
in the confusion of the enemy."
It must hide and remain in Hush.
The shinobi it must know the opportune time
of when the enemy is tired and disattento."
Good.
Hey, boys goes all good?
Naruto, a moment!
The coded phrase.
Oky
"the shinobi it is found to its comfort
in the confusion of the enemy.".
It must hide and remain in Hush.
The shinobi it must know the opportune time
of when the enemy is tired and disattento."
What takes to you?
Stavolta is one that succeeds
also to schivare my attacks!
But what you are saying, Sasuke-kun!?
Naruto has said the word
of order correctly!
This is the point.
Naruto would not never succeed
_ to memorizzare one phrase cos   long.
According to you what would have answered Naruto?
"You excuse to me I have forgotten It!"
In more the movements with which
my attack has schivato.
they are evidently different
from those of Naruto.
It reveals your true aspect, impostore!
Not you six fact to trick.
But if you knew that she would have forgotten it
why you have not used one short phrase?
I knew that someone was listening
the conversation from underground.
For this I have chosen that word of order.
Capisco
No fatigue or disattenzione, eh?
Six more wide awake than how much you thought.
It makes me to rabbrividire!
And then dov' it is Naruto?
U ugh devil
They are rolled end here, and
What?
Where they are ended Sakura-chan
and that bastard of Sasuke?
C what
Enormous E'!
I have not never seen a snake cos   large!
I haul!
They are in trap
Been trying the parchment
of the "earth". Just?
you boys instead have that one of the sky
Hour has beginning
the battle to the last blood
for the coil.
Illusory Genjutsu!?(arte)
Not
it was only the projection
of its fury omicida.
Incredible!
I have seen the dead women in face simply
watching it in the eyes.
Who devil is!
S Sakura
Us it does not remain other that
to scappare far away!
Otherwise
we will come all....
it kills to you!!
Sputa me outside!
Sputa me!
Damned!
It is put badly.
I must think next to something!
Oh, my ball of rice for breakfast!
It has melted
If it has melted the rice cos   in a hurry, then....
Not!
You pull to me you pull to me fuoriii!
More not succeeded to move to you?
It wants to kill to us!
you move you move you move muoviti!
You move! You move!
You move!
Still a small effort
Please you move!
What creeds to make
What you mean to make with that one?
I can move
Not preoccuparti.
To end to you   to the moment.
It will be fast and painless one dead women.
I only hoped that you would have to me
fact to amuse more.
Much evil.
I am truly in order to die here?
Iruka-Sensei
Hokage Grandfather
Konohamaru
Kakashi-Sensei
Sakura-chan.
Sasuke
I have made many sciocchezze with he.
We hate always an other
but we have worked with against
Zabuza in order to save Kakashi-Sensei.
During the training with the chakra in the forest
we were we are obstinate to you and competiti to you
in going up on the trees.
Sure!
I have not still arranged the things with he!
Still!!
If not me sputa outside
obbligher ?  to make it you!
Capisco.
Sasuke-kun
It has been hurt alone
You move! You move! You move!
YOU MOVE!
MUOVITII!
in order to cancel the fear with the pain.
As I thought, whichever is not one preda.
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!!
I am the ninja that it will become Hokage!
I cannot be transformed in cacca of snake!!
Sasuke-kun, goes all good?
Not to make noise, otherwise will find to us!
But like
How we can scappare?
I have not never seen
Sasuke-kun cos   in the panic.
Sasuke-kun, the snake!
I was cos   mental patient, than I have not perceived the snake!
Stammi far away!
You cannot lower
the guard neanche a moment.
A preda she would have to scappare
with all its forces
in front of the predator.
Scusami, Sasuke!
Naruto!
The order word
I have scordata it.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
nee kikoe masu ka?