http://naruteamplus.alterista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
You will ruin the reputation of our village.
What tasks that we have come
to make the village of Konoha?
It listens To Me, Gaara!
They have provoked to us!
Hush
or I kill to you.
He pardons, will not succeed more to us.
Scusami is guilt mine.
You pardon to us.
Then the head is he.
Not me piacciono its eyes.
It has hit konkuro with a pebble
and with great facility.
E' in leg.
Andiamo.
We have not come in order to amuse to us.
I know.
Waited for!
What is?
From the coprifronte one would say that you are
ninja of the village of the sand.
The continent of the fire and
of the wind they are allies to you
but a treaty prohibits to the ninja of the two
countries the free passage without permission.
Therefore qual' it is your scope?
To second of the cases lasceremo not to go to you.
The solution is nearer
next to you of how much you think.
Not sapete then null?
This is my permission.
As you have said, we are of the genin
of the village of the sand
and we have come here in order to make
the examination of selection of the Chunin.
Examination of selection of the Chunin?
Ep. 21: Identification!
The powerful enemies who are arrive to you!
Cos' is the examination of selection of the Chunin?
You do not know just nothing.
Head!
Pu   to have been promoted from Genin
to single Chunin if it exceeds this examination.
Truly!
I to this examination even propose anch'!
Hei you!
Qual' is
your name?
Mine?
Not. That neighbor to you with the giara.
Gaara of the Desert.
Also you me incuriosisci.
How it calls to you?
Uchiha Sasuke.
Ehi! Ehi!
You do not want to know my name?
It does not interest to me.
The thing begins is made interesting.
Konohamaru, I seem cos   weak person?
Regarding Sasuke, s .
Sasuke! You will not succeed to strike to me!
But that you want?
What of tasks?
They are not a large one that
but the Moor of Konoha and that one with the giara
they are from holding of eye.
Now that we are ready for
to begin the selection of the Chunin
who delegation new the Genin
make a step ahead.
Kakashi, Kurenai and Asuma.
You say what to me?
Between your boys there is someone that you would want
to candidare to the examination of selection of the Chunin?
Not there is need that ve says it
but a genin that it has completed
at least eight missions
pu   to candidarsi if yours
opinion is favorable.
Even if more a genin is indicated that
of it it has completed the double quantity.
To that it serves to ask it?
Discounted E' that for they it is too much soon.
We begin from Kakashi.
I, Kakashi Hatake, candid
Uchiha Sasuke
Uzumaki Naruto
and Haruno Sakura
group 7
from guided me, to the examination
of selection of the Chunin.
I, Kurenai Yuhi, candid
Hyuuga Hinata
Inuzuka Kiba
and Aburame Shiro
that is
all group 8 from guided me.
I, Asuma Sarutobi, candid
Yamanaka Ino
Nara Shikamaru
Akimichi Chouji
that is
all group 10 from guided me.
All how many candidates!
They will want years before to us that
the rookie to the examination arrive.
Incredible E'.
Waited for! Ve I pray some.
Iruka Speaks.
Hokage-sama, I would want to express my opinion!
I would not want oppormi to the taken decision
but the majority of the nine boys candidates
they have been my students to the academy.
Sure they are full students of talent,
but it is too much soon for fargli supporting the examination.
They have need more experience
before candidarsi to the examination!
I have become Chunin when
I had six years less than Naruto.
Naruto is various from you!
You have intention to make to die them?
Those three are always complained during
the missions without to comprise of the importance.
E' well that they suffer
and it would be also amusing
to see to be dying them.
As you can
Clearly it was one struck
Iruka-sensei.
I comprise your perplexities and I know also that
us   that I am for dirvi you it will give on the nerves.
Kakashi, you end it.
Not intromettetevi!
Why they are not more your students
bens
mine subordinates to you.
He plants it a po' to you.
But the examination for chunin pu   revealing itself
Iruka
I understand what you want to say.
Hokage-sama.
We will make these rookie genin
one special preliminary examination.
A preliminary examination?
Ehi! Ehi!
Because it always must be
and rigorously in delay?
Just! just!
It does not hold account of the feelings of a child whom it has made late
and it has not been able to wash hats!
Also I was in I delay therefore
the teeth are not washed me by it the face of
Here because
it is always cos   dirty.
Goodness knows as they make to being
cos   it lives to us from the first one mattino.
Ehil, buongiorno boys!
Sapete today I have lost the straight one via
Bugiardo!
You listen to me.
I have candidate to you to the examination of selection of Chunin.
Here the registration question.
To the examination of Chunin?
However you are not obligates to participate to you.
You will be same to choose if to make the examination less or.
SIII!
I adore to you, Kakashi-sensei!
Ehy you stop it!
It leaves me!
Only who of you wants
to participate to companies the sheet
and the deliveries to classroom 301 of the academy
within hours 16:00 tomorrow.
E' all.
The esama of Chunin! The examination of chunin!
- Uzumaki Naruto. Candid this person
to the examination of selection of Chunin to my name.
The jounin. Hatake Kakashi. -
The examination of Chunin
Us it must be strong lots of people.
Like that type
and like he.
Well!
Not inferior me dimostrer  ? to nobody!
If to win , arriver   to the title it
of Hokage much more veocemente.
Orami is Naruto the most indicated to the title it of Hokage.
Old we drovemmo to withdraw to us.
Potr   to even fight against of he.
I not
I do not succeed to be behind Sasuke-kun
and not even to Naruto
I cannot go to the examination of Chunin.
Naruto-chan! we play entirety!?
Of agreement, today I do not have no mission
cos   I can play with you.
Yeah!!!
Head!
Konohamaru-chan!
What you would want to make Moegi!
Hey, removes to you from Moegi!
Bastard
Konohamaru, we must chase it!
Ok!
Waited for!
The examination of Chunin
Ehy!
Sasuke-kun!
What happens?
You want to come to make one walk?
Pu   not to be!
Indeed!
They succeed to follow me to this speed?
You keep yourself strong, Moegi!
Dov' has gone Naruto?
Creed that we have lost them.
It leaves me!!!
If within secretly during the examination of Chunin
the village of Konoha pu
easy to be stormed.
Six fast state.
Hey, old you grassone!
What you want to make with Moegi?
What I want to make?
You want to know it?
Not to move to you!
If you move, this morir child.
Why it is making this?
I try the "parchment of I seal"
of the first Hokage.
If me the ports, lascer   to go the child.
"the parchment of I seal"?
Uhm
Sasuke-kun
because all this cos   to the unexpected one?
Sakura.
It withdraws to you from the examination of Chunin.
For you it is too much soon.
D indeed?
The examination of Chunin will be full of people much fort.
If something goes badly, could die.
Sasuke-kun, six preoccupied for me?
Sure one.
Thanks for this rappresentazione.
Vattene, if you do not want to die.
Not to deal to me cos !
It does not make me to anger!
Sasuke-kun!
Not to take me the light one!
Sasuke-kun
Sasuke-kun!
What you are waiting for?
Portami the "parchment of I seal"!
and
if you refused to me?
It does not import you of that one
that the pu   to happen?
M' the understood one does not interest what
to that heap of straw!
What? When it has happened!
I have already recovered Moegi without problems.
Head, very made!
He seems that six improved a lot!
Cursed bastard
Chip ax the defeat from man!
Prendetelo!
Naruto!
Six arrived late ones, Konohamaru.
Konohamaru-chan, I was scared!
Ahi, ahi.
Head, you have captured it?
, it is right here.
D where?
E' kawarimi not jutsu!
Merda! When it has been replaced with this cliff!
Naruto
If you do not want to make the same end,
it withdraws to you from the examination of Chunin.
Sasuke-kun, not to die!
You mistakes of large if creeds
that it decides to withdraw to me.
Me they are shrewed of your technique
illusory from the principle.
What?
The true Sasuke-kun
it would not have never invited me
to make one walk.
Above all it would not say to me
those stupid things.
These illusions from principianti
they do not work with me.
"Principiante"?
Moreover
me of they are already shrewed who also you six
an illusion and that it originates it them is not here.
This we will see it!!!
Approval!?
After all six one subordinate of Kakashi.
For , in the examination of Chunin he will be all real.
You will be able to face it?
You are provoking to me.
I accept your challenge anytime!
The examination of Chunin is
The examination of Chunin is!
The fact is that they are not sure
Stupid Vattene.
Who ce has made it?
Even if the nine have had to face
this preliminary examination,
all have exceeded it.
It seems that its abilities are improved,
just as you had said.
For   the true examination of Chunin
it will not be cos   easy.
You have felt?
For before the time after 5 years
there will be of the esordienti to the examination.
But it goes
They will be l   only for the pride
of their masters Jonin.
Not. One says that three of they are
those of the group of the famous Kakashi.
Interesting.
In any case
I would not want to be in their cloth.
Sakura-chan! Six in delay.
Me dispiace
Buongiorno, Sasuke-kun.
Hello!
Sakura today is a po' strange.
Insufficient as you are you would want
to participate to the examination of Chunin?
Ve I advice against it, children.
You are only of the mocciosi.
I pray, fateci to pass to you.
Che infami!
What you have said?
You open the orecchie!
We make for gentility.
The examination of selection of Chunin
it is much difficult one.
We have seen many candidates
to remain invalids
or to abandon the trade of ninja
because of the examination.
To be Chunin involves to command a group.
The failure of a mission means
the dead women of the own subordinates.
Of the children as you they are not any in degree.
You will not get lost nothing not to participate
to a examination that however you will fail.
The speech spins.
For
I pass however.
And it plants to take to us in turn
with this illusion.
I must go to the third plan.
But what is saying that one?
Of it I do not have idea
OH!
You of six shrewed one!
What you say Sakura to me?
You you of will be shrewed first of all.
What?
Your acquaintance on the genjutsu is more
developed to the inside of our group.
Sasuke-kun
Thanks.
Sure, me of I was already shrewed!
Here we are to according to plan.
!
You have been good.
But to that you servants
to have understood it!
That speed!
E' a lot different from the person
that it was made to beat little ago.
It has adorned my soccer!
Che Chakra has in the arms!
Hey, you have not maintained the promise.
Six state you to say that we did not have make us
to notice in order to avoid of being held of eye.
, for
Eccolo!
It is
They are talks nonsense to you
the signs of the blows that have taken.
They had to be feints.
My name is Rock Lee.
You call you Sakura, true?
Eh?
You put yourself with to me!
You protegger   to cost of living!
By no means
Eh?
...... you do not appeal to to me
Hey, you.
Introduce to you.
Maledizione, still!?
Always Sasuke!!!
Of usual it is introduced to us for first
when the name is asked someone.
You a six esordiente, not?
How many years you have?
They are not obliged to answer to you.
What?
That pretty.
They are too much only
To me nobody notices to me
Sasuke-kun, Naruto, we go!
Soon!
Those must be
the boys of Kakashi and Guy.
For hour they have passed the test
of the delivery of the registration question.
Already!
He seems that there will be from amusing itself
with the candidates of this year.
Already, like examiners.
Well, well.
He seems that to the esama of Chunin
it is full of interesting people.
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Showy short hats, eyelash and folte!
Oh, you six
what it is in love of Sakura-chan little it makes!
The next episode
Energy 120%! One new and hard challenge!
Avr   an important role also this time!
!
DVD 1  "20       !