Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking NFS
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh!  Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the fire!BANG!
Sasuke-kun.
My arms!
It is felt badly, Orochimaru-sama?
It drinks its medicine, quickly!
Neanche I make in time to return and I already must clean up the room?
Please it takes the medicine.
I do not have need of one stupid sedativo.
Miscelato Ho the ingredients personally.
The pain would have lenirvi.
My arms burn…
I could not never have imagined much suffering.
Sarutobi.
Or better, the Third Hokage…
Its last painful maledizione has inflicted you.
We do not lose time in useless to chiacchiere. Six successful one to find that person?
She seems that that person finds itself to Tanzaku-gai.
Tanzaku-gai…
Optimal.
However, that person is also always one of the leggendari Sannin.
Sannin: Ninja Leggendari
It will not be much easy one…
A miraculous cure is not much easy one to find.
It watches.
E' the same one. E' this the crucial point?
They are sure that you were one of that came sgridato for the concentration lack.
I do not understand what there enters now.
It watches this sheet of paper.
I have seen.
Well. Now it of new watches.
What I must see?
We see, would not have to be much difficult one to explain…
When you have observed the paper piece white woman, six successful one to perceive all the sheet?
Probably.
Now instead what focuses your look?
Sure on the sign in the center.
When a person observes something of white man…
She does not succeed to focus the look, cos ì  its eyes watch everywhere.
But if you put a sign in means, that person will concentrate itself in that point.
Called E' focalization in a point.
When you succeed to concentrate to you, your mind becomes stable…
Only then you can rilasciare the enormous one to be able inner.
When you have made that hole in the caucciù ball…
… you have had spasmodically to accumulate all the your Chakra in the right hand.
! !
If pits concentrated you would have made little hard work to you…
But it is difficult to concentrate itself without some type of sign.
This is how much. It listens To Me, Naruto.
When you have intention of rilasciare the Chakra from the palm of your right hand…
It tries to concentrate to you carefully on that point.
Concentration…
It goes well!  I will make!
Episode #88
The coprifronte
&
The symbol of Konoha
Concentration!
I do not succeed to us.
I must make to explode it.
Concentration!
Excuses, I can make them a question me?
Eternal damnation!
Concentration…
Nothing to make.
Eternal damnation…
What I must make in order to concentrate to me?
You are cursed, Sarutobi!
Later. I return in city in order to collect other information.
What? Six as soon as arrived!
I do not have time to lose.
Hey Hey!
It waits for! You do not have time in order to play to ball with your student?
Ugly stronzo!
Strike!
Okay, I have taken it.
We look at ourselves after.
We forget ourselves about Ero-Sennin. I must work hard mine on behalf.
Naruto.
You must succeed to carry out this part of the training alone.
You have the potentialities in order to become like the Fourth Hokage.
You can make it us.
I have not never seen it.
It goes well…
Excuses the disturbance.
I have seen it…
And  sò  also where he can  find  it.
I can offer them from drink.
Not there is need.
Lately I have gained one hazard fortune playing…
Spennato Ho that woman!
Oh! Just as we expected from the Losing Leggendaria!
Succeeded E' to still lose?
Che schiappa!
Inasmuch as it was losing ugly…
It has preferred to change air.
Where it has gone?
Ecco Tanzaku-gai…
One of the leggendari Sannin…
Tsunade-sama is found here.
Finally  I will be able  to recover my arms…
We are resolutions to find it… Now the difficult part of the plan comes.
Not to worry to you.
Tanzaku-gai
Seven… Seven… Seven…
Seven!
Seven… Seven…
Seven… Seven… Seven…
Seven… Setteeeeeee…
Jackpot!
Felt congratulations!
Emplacement 44 has turned out that one winning!
Please continued to play!
E' cos ì  rare to see to you to win…
Tsunade-sama.
Are escapes three 7?
Mrs.... Been going to the large one!
Other that to the large one!
I would only want to have a po' of its fortune!
Oh, of new!
Yatta! You have succeeded of new!
I am gaining truly a lot…
I have a bad prefeeling.
I know some things Tsunade-sama care.
After all also I am a doctor like she.
Nowadays it is normal school that is at least a member of the medical square in every mission…
But she has been she it before to which this brilliant idea has come and it has proposed it to the council.
Considered E' one miliare stone of our history.
What you would happen in battle if not there were a doctor to cure the other members of the team?
The answer is obvious.
The survivors of the war of Amato…
… they brought back important considerations a lot.
Thanks above all to the innumerevoli victims fallen on the field.
When a person loses something, only then account of its importance becomes.
She was then that the medical specialist of the leggendari Sannin partor ì  this idea…
Because of the victims.
He does not work…
Still… I must concentrate itself more.
Concentration… Concentration…
Concentration…
It concentrates to you on a point.
Strike!
Hey, as I can be concentrated… With that face from stupid pervertito in my head !
Well, well…
It seems that from some part there is a girl who is thinking to me.
Tsunade-sama, aspects please!
What happens? Tsunade-sama never is not capitato that you have gained cos ì  many moneies…
But not seemed for nothing content.
This city…
There is something that does not go.
Sbrigati. Ce n' we go.
What? But this is one city for tourists.
We would have at least to see the castle!
It goes well. A visit and then ce n' we go.
Waited for… Tsunade-sama!
Orochimaru-sama.
We try to end this mission quickly…
Also to cost of having to use the force.
I must succeed to us…
Ahi!
Ahia!
I do not succeed more in rilasciare the Chakra with this pain…
It must have arrived to its limit.
Just little…
I must be rested for a po '.
Returned here!
The lesson is still not finished.
Race of idiots!
But it is possible…
Possible E' that you never do not succeed to concentrate to you?
You will not never succeed to become at this rate of the good ones ninja.
We cannot at all always remain seated on the benches…
Just, Akamaru?
I have hunger…
Sensei… Sbrigati with this lecture…
Children!
We will make one integrating lesson in order to improve your concentration!
What is?
What you see…
E' an ancient tradition of the ninja of Konoha…
Servants in order to learn to concentrate itself.
You must concentrate all your energy on that leaf…
Therefore pasted your Chakra.
E' a method much ancient one…
But it is the better way in order to increase your abilities to concentration.
Only who succeeds to concentrate itself will be able well to become Bravo ninja.
This is also the origin of the symbol of Konoha on the coprifronte.
Konoha: Leaf
To me it seems a bale…
You have invented this history in order to try to motivate to us?
History is not one! True E' all!
A Ninja will not never become the best one only why it succeeds to concentrate itself.
Bravo ninja second me, must be only much fort.
, you have reason.
That stupid history…
We look at ourselves, Sensei!
Hey! Waited for!
I do not have time to lose!
That loss of time!
Waited for! Ungrateful stupiden!
E' the same thing.
If you had only given straight more to the words than Iruka-sensei.
They are just an idiot.
I will not improve  here sure being some to me to piagnucolare.
Ok! I will succeed  to us. Of they are sure!
Concentration. Concentration…
Concentration!
Wow!
The castle of Tanzaku is truly impressive!
I understand why one of beautifulst is considered of our nation.
You stop it with chiacchiere.
Now we go ourselves some from here.
Tsunade-sama, why we do not give one look more give near. The entrance is free.
Tsunade-sama?
What is… this feeling?
Now!
That boy…
He has accumulated cos ì  much Chakra in its hand to burn itself…
He succeeds to astonish every day more to me!
Burst E'…
Perfect! You have completed the second phase of the training.
We begin endured with the third phase…
You must still wait for a po '.
Come E' the moment to meet Tsunade.
That one is…
Orochimaru!
I have found to you.
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete
You say that I must train me for the third phase while we walk?
Diamine continuous to gives more and more difficult orders to me!
Cretino! If not us muoviamo quickly, we risk not to find more Tsunade.
Where we are going?
E' from some part in city, we will try it watching from the high.
We will salt on the castle.
Castle?
We would have to be in a position to finding it, from lassù.
But where we go?
It is found… But…
But that it happens?
Next Episode
The maledizione