Subbed by Shinji 89
Cheked by [ Fabry ]
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
NARUTO
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not fukinukeru
Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda YEAH!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite kanashimi mo
hoho tsutatte namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Baby
Shikamaru has always believed in me!
Chouji is the much strongest one
of me, Neji, and anyone other here
We begin, grassone!
You feel who speaks!
Bubun Baika not jutsu!
[ Technical of the partial expansion ]
Arm!
Bubun Baika not jutsu!
Leg!
Arm!
Not to underrate me, scarafaggio!
You take this!
What?
Chou Baika not jutsu!
[ Technical of the gigantismo ]
Episode #114
Goodbye, friend mine!
Ce I will make  it, Shikamaru....
What ?
I would not have never thought about having to enter in the second one
phase against an adversary like he.
Rising palm!
[ Blow of the mounting palm ]
What ?
It has been transformed ?
To this point you do not have more hopes.
Hour not there are enemies whom they hold. The second phase
it succeeds to duplicate my force.
It makes badly cos   that I do not succeed to move to me.
I did not think that the effect collateral of the tonic
to the curry it was cos   devastating.
When a bond to null like you,
It meets persons like we,
it would be better if it continued to play to make the ninja.
Who wants to play to the ninja
he seizes my finger
I, I!
Waited for!
Pebble, paper, scissors!
You wait for to me
Hei! You must hide!
Ouch.
It finds to you!
You surrender pacifically!
Finally they are successful to take to you.
To me it does not appeal to Chouji.
Every group that has it in square always loses.
Excuse
In order to maintain this state I have need a lot chakra.
I will eat  the chakra that it remains you.
Good appetite.
Bah! It is not succeeded to suck not even a little chakra.
And to think that I still have hunger!
I have said to you that I still have hunger!
That disappointment, is only remained one patatina.
Still they are starved.
I had reason to say that only six one pawn
sacrificabile.
Leak, neglected wretch ciccione!
You cannot play to the ninja with we.
Why?
Why the square of which you would make part would have the insured defeat.
You six obtuse one.
But  without of he we are uneven.
Also the shogi it is beautiful why everyone has the same number
of pawns.
[ Shogi: game of chess ]
If a pawn is useless, a lot is worth not having it.
Just, just!
We play with little persons, than problem there is?
We begin.
If to you he is well cos ,  not there are problems.
Perfect, he is decided!
We will win!
Where you will hide ?
..  They say that in the Akimichi clan they are all
obtuse fat people and.
I have understood.>.
But  Chouji, not is no kind boy like you.
A day you will sure make of the friends that they will appreciate
this your gift.
They you will be able yourself to be trusted and have to consider them precious
of more every other thing.
And you will become a reliable friend.
I will succeed  to having bonds friends ?
But  you are calm.
After that I will have  victim of a murder  to you,  I will make  the same one with the rest of
feccia without heart that has left you here
It has promised.
After you must absolutely catch up to us
Chouji.
It has promised that it will strike the adversary....
and that it will catch up to us.
Sure.
If s' it engages it is one that it knows to make to us.
In this case,
it will be well to add these.
Also I.
Boys listened
We must resume Sasuke before that Chouji catches up to us!
He waits for!
Evvai!
Jiroubo is in delay.
E' large an eager bastard.
It will be sure sucking theirs chakra until the bone.
how much I would want someone to arrange.>.
You can resume it to you.
If they are not much far from p otr recovering  them here.
You  I will end  hour.
Hour me remains only the red tonic to the chili pepper.
But  if you took it
I would end sure in order to die.
Not to die, Chouji.
We have been with from that day.
it has six here!
You six that one before
What has happened to the game of the ninja ?
It had stew to me therefore are scappato via.
This is my special place.
Your special place ?
It appeals to sdraiarmi them to me and to watch clouds.
Six come here to watch clouds ?
I can be based ?
This is an optimal place, from can here see the sky.
Also you
You make the lazy one and watches clouds with me.
Ok! I have of the snack with me. We eat them together.
Thanks.
To watch the sky eating patatine.
Fantastic E'.
I am Shikamaru, of the Nara clan.
You as he calls to you?
Chouji! Chouji Akimachi of the Akimachi clan.
Chouji, eh ?
It would appeal to to me that from hour in then we worked together.
Also to me.
From that moment, we have been always together.
Chouji.
Shikamaru,  I will not be able  to catch up to you.
This is the end.
But
this
I will strike  it  to cost of my same life!
By now it is too much late for whichever thing!
Crushing palm!
[ stritolante Blow ]
What ?
But!
Rock Slam!
[ cliff Fist ]
Useless E'.
I am 100 times more strongly than before.
One says that the hatred gushed from the food deprivation is terrifying.
This blow
.. it was why you have eaten me the last patatina!
Incredible!
It possesses cos   a lot chakra to change its physical structure.
However this other blow
it is in order to have to me taken in turn giving me of the ciccione and the pawn
sacrificabile!
But
still more unforgivable
Pessimo a head renders weak person the group.
The subordinates if they pass it just badly
when they have one stupid like head
But rasserenate to you why I will kill  to you  still before
that you try suffering.
You would have to hate your stupid leader.
e' who speaks badly about my better friend.
More unforgivable than one that steals the last mouthful to me of the plate
more exquisite of the world
or of that ciccione calls me....
With all the chakra that I have in the left hand....
They are in danger!
this fist encloses my life!
It waits for, not to be frettoloso!
I have won
As me it has won.
All
But  Chouji, does not exist boy kinder than you.
A day you will sure make of the friends that they will appreciate
this your gift.
They you will be able yourself to be trusted and have to consider them precious
than more every other thing.
then you will become a reliable companion.
(sbrigati to come)
(all we are waiting for to you)
He must have been Naruto.
Kiba
Shikamaru
Ino-Shika-Chou!
I will not allow  you  to eat the last patatina to you!
They have been with he in order much time.
It is that one with which I agree better.
Father,
I
What happens ?
Null
Boku Tamani Boku Tamani
Hito Yume ni afureru not kakeraga
Yama not yonimieru
kamisama nihotoke samani
Hito Tsutae naiteru not karekaga
Yama not yonimieru
Nandero Dan dan dan sura
Borushoino placed ninarandara
Shake shake shake sagaso janainowa
bye bye bye not let' s of
Yama not yonimieru
Cosa?Cosa!
Kage bunshin not Jutsu!
What!
You take this! Gatsuuga!
Byakugan!
That boy dangerous spider.
Even if Naruto, Kiba, Neji and I am working together
he does not go well for nothing.
If we will be cos   discs of a valve, Sasuke will be unattainable!
What we can make?
If we want to continue the pursuit there is alone
one what to make
Next episodio:Il your adversary is mine!