Subbed by # [ Fabry ]
Cheked by Shinji 89
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not fukinukeru
Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda YEAH!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite kanashimi mo
hoho tsutatte namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Baby
They to are near!
Strange…
…   not trap is not even one
Shikamaru…
What tasks that it means?
That they to are underrating
They believe that…
…  he will be only that energumeno to try them.
…  Nobody puts of the traps
against the own companions
As they to give!
As they to give to underrate us!
Not to there is doubt…
they have to us completely underrates you.
But
…  this will return to our favor.
Sure.
We will pick them of surprise.
Episode #115
Your adversary is the!
More Jiroubou is putting of the two.
Not, already it has arrived.
Why you have put us cos  ì   to lot?
Excused.
It has taken more Time to me of the previewed one to suck the chakra
of those wretch.
Ciccione you see to wake up you!
It tries not to slow down to us.
And door the barrel!
That one is your job!
Understood, cretino !
It goes well.
What is Jirobo?
Today six rather calm one.
What you mean ?
That the cannot they give the barrel to you!
Why you not six Jiroubou!
Hour touches me!
Sakon, Tayuya, you go ahead!
Jiroubou resumes in continuation…
…  the way to speak about Tayuya.
The understand…
Ninpou: Kumo Shibari
[  catching Art magica!Ragnatela! ]
Ugly bastard!
Ninpou: Kumo Soukai
[  Art magica!Nido of the spider! ]
Naruto!
Kiba, Akamaru.. touches you!
Suspended hour and to half air
and   it cannot   it moves!
Gatsuuga
[  Zanne armor-piercing  ]
You will not escape to me!
This is my territory…
It watches the feet to you
You. >.!
These Creeds indeed that pack-saddles to stop to us!
We proceed…
Tzk!Cosa is arranging that ciccione?
Accidents!
We have been imprudent to leave that job
to more the weak person than we 4.
The have taken to you
Neji!
C-Cosa. >.?
It has caught me Naruto, Kiba and Neji…
The plan has not been enough.
Will the veteran   to you in to cocoon.
Eternal damnation!
Accidents!
Of that devil is made this thread?
I give not succeed to cut it!
My threads to are cos  ì   resistant…
that it does not pull to you from two elephants fall apart themselves!
The Kage Bunshin?Interessante…
The threads me to are attacando to the body!
Probably. >.
..  it creates this propietà. >.
…  adhesive mischiando the chakra
with loads its particular secretion.
Moreover, the chakra it flows continually to the inside ei you spin,
cosicchè they maintain their resistance
although they to are not connects you to its hands.
Irreale The level of its techniques is  cos   ì high to seem.
You to are calm. >.
Must use the mines…
Chakra. >.
Ninpou: Kumo Kenkin
[  golden Art magica!Ragnatela! ]
The color of the thread is various!
What means to make?
Stà hardening itself!
The want to amuse   to Pò   inasmuch as the six first one.
We play to "fortunes teller qual' is the true body  "…
Which cabbage you to are saying?
Laggiù The first one will be… that in bottom!
Naruto!
Eheh… Was one copy
Well, to here the next one!
That fortunate child.
Tore   Hour   two to the Time
Cos  ì   the probabilities to are reduced to 50%.
This child is indeed fortunate!
But stavolta, it is by force one of the two
Tsk! Neither it is remained one!
Beh, for being to game, has been interesting…
…  but now the game is ended!
You die!
One is made!
What?
The have understood. >.
It has only attacked to me with its copies. >.
it is remained hidden the to entire Time in wait. >.
as it… is successful to preview
all these movements in advance payment
Beautiful movement.
But. >.
hour six lacking in resources… You die!
What?
Naruto!
Thanks in order to have earned Time.
Neji!
As devil. you have made!
One substance based on the chakra…
…  it becomes useless in front of the technique of the "Juken  "…
…  that it destroys emitting chakra.
It seems that…
The am the only one to being able to contrast this technique
Gone!
Next to he the to us   will think.
What happens?
Hey, Akamaru
It seems that this is stronger
of the before ciccione.
And also of much.
You had said that ce we would not have made it
if we had not been decided to fight separately.
Just ?
, it is true…
Moreover, if we lost Time to here…
…  we would not catch up more Sasuke.
Chouji still is not returned
We have like here why…
…  our mission is to bring back Sasuke behind
But it is not only this…
In how much ninja, we to are following and proteggendo
the ideals of Konoha
Remembered the words of Iruka, during
funeral of the Third Hokage?
Iruka-sensei
Why the persons risk
their screw for the others?
When someone dies. vanishes…
…  its past and its present,
…  cos  ì   like its future.
To bag of persons dies in war and the missions
cos  ì   to the unexpected one. >.
…   and cos  ì   easy…
…  these Hayate is one of. >.
Every person who dies door behind the own dreams…
but all how many have something that joins them
Parents… siblings… friends and affections
The persons who you think precious.
All help and believe the uni in the others…
They to are the relationships with the persons who you know sin from when six been born.
The thread that joined they to you
he has become and more and more often resistant
with passing of the Time.
Logical therefore E'…
…  that to person who holds this thread
she behaves myself in such to way…
…  inasmuch as it is precious.
Listened…
Sasuke is going from Orochimaru
We cannot allow that someone of our village goes to us
Nobody
And…
Naruto. >.
You possess better eyes of mines.
Sasuke hour
it is wrapped from the dusk
Andate!Presto!
The will catch up   to you after!
Ok.
We go.
You catch up to us with to Choji!
Neji
we look at more late.
The will not make   them to escape.
Byakugan!
Attention!
This boy if the quarry well…
Neji
The knew
Not still!
You will not go via cos  ì   easy.
You will have to pass on my corpse
Useless E' all.
It goes well. >.
It seems that you to are more strongly of the group
Tsk!
It has like to me wants to amuse to me.
E' to waste if in to game it is not advanced flat.
The will amuse myself   makes you outside in three minuteren.
Taken.
The six indeed skillful in padroneggiare chakra
Insidiosa Moreover you have one seen
Forms one blade with the chakra
to the extremity of the finger
cos  ì   you succeed to cut the burlap
in its point that contains little chakra.
Orochimaru-sama me of it has spoken
Your art would be the I know-called Juken, true ?
But   hour that your annoying hands to are immobilized…
…  you will not break more not thread.
When the trick in to game is discovered. >.
…  of blow it is not more amusing.
Last E' only to tiny
but they to are already the stew of you.
You die
Kumo Nenkin!
[  golden Ragnatela! ]
What?
But as devil has made?
The will reveal   you to secret. >.
Grant the provilegio to know it to you.
The am able to make to flow the chakra from the holes
of chakra of all the body.
Moreover
they to are that the call the game over!
Juukenhou
[  Juga Style  ]
Hakke Rokujyuu Hanshyou!
[ 64   Closings  ]
Boku Tamani Boku Tamani
Hito Yume ni afureru not kakeraga
Yama not yonimieru
kamisama nihotoke samani
Hito Tsutae naiteru not karekaga
Yama not yonimieru
Nandero Dan dan dan sura
Borushoino placed ninarandara
Shake shake shake sagaso janainowa
bye bye bye not let' s of
Yama not yonimieru
Naruto: next episode
Mercoled  ì   5   January hours 7:00 PM
The secrets of the Byakugan!
To believe in if same. >.
He will be fundamental for Neji
Naruto
Continuous Naruto the next year!
The furious battle of strongest
The ninja-genius in the Dattebayo special
You cannot get lost it!