Subtitles By: BakaSan
He's totally late.
Ah... Where's Sasuke?
Dosu who's supposed to be my opponent isn't here either.
Hey, you two there...
Stop being anxious. Stand tall and show
your faces to the audience well.
In this final round, you guys are the main event.
Has Sasuke been found yet?
Teams made up of a few Anbu each
have been looking for him, but not yet...
Perhaps, he's already in Orochimaru's hands.
If that's the case, we won't be able to find him anymore...
I see.
Oh... it's you, Mr. Kazekage.
You must be tired from the long trip to here.
No. It is good that this stage is in Konoha.
Even though you're still young, it would be hard journey for
you, Hokage-sama, if you needed to go to another location.
Isn't it better for you to decide the next Fifth soon?
Don't treat me like an old man. I plan
to stay for at least another five years.
Well... We should start it soon.
Ladies and Gentleman. Thank you for coming
to Konoha-gakure (hidden Leaf) Chunin Exam.
From now, the final round for the eight
who passed the prelims will start.
Please stay until the end.
If it's for eight, then I see one missing.
Before the matches begin, I have something I need to say.
Look at this.
There was a little change in tournament blocks.
Confirm whose your opponent once again.
I had one more match then everybody else before...
I guess Dosu forfeit.
I thought I'd finish you here.
That gives me the possibility to go against
Sasuke since I'm the odd one out in the first round.
What are you anyway!
Hey... Excuse me!
What is it?
Sasuke isn't here yet... so what'll you do about him?
Did he really escape from the hospital room then?
I wonder if something happened to him.
If he doesn't come here by the time his match starts, then...
he loses without a fight.
It's strange. From his character, he should
be here even if he has to drag his body.
Where're you going, Gaara?
I'm going to verify my existence.
Once more!
What's up? You can still move, can't you?
Sasuke, come on!
I told him repeatedly not to do something fishy, but...
I wonder if he killed the kid, Uchiha Sasuke, too...
Listen, you guys.
There are geographical differences, but the rule
is that there's no rules like in the prelims.
The match lasts until one of you die or admit defeat.
But if I judge the match is over, I'll stop it then.
I won't allow you to argue against me.
Understand?
Well, the first match is Uzumaki Naruto and Hyuga Neji.
Other than those two, go back to the waiting room.
Byakugan VS Kagebunshin! I'm gonna win no matter what!!
Hey, Hinata. Those seats are open.
This'll be an impressive match.
I can understand that you're worried about Sasuke-kun.
But I think you should give
Naruto a little cheer, shouldn't you?
Yeah, you're right.
But, there's no possibility for
Naruto to win because his opponent is Neji.
That isn't true!
Can you be certain?
Anyway, who'd imagine that kid survived until now...
This will be the end for Naruto
who survived with just his luck.
His opponent is too strong. He won't win
against the Hyuga clan no matter how hard he tries.
Well, I thought the same at first. But
you'll be surprised if you underestimate him.
What's wrong, Akamaru?
What did you say?
Where?
There!
Why is an Anbu at a place like this?
Is something going on here?
You seem like you want to say something.
I told you before, too...
A loser is a loser after all. You can never change!
I promise...
I'm gonna win no matter what!
Those are eyes that show he believes in himself completely.
There's no overconfidence.
It's more worthwhile fighting against you.
When you face the true reality, those
eyes will show disappointment.
I'm looking forward to seeing those eyes.
Stop talking so much...
Let's begin already!
Well, let the first match...
Begin!
You should watch it carefully, Hanabi. There's no other
person who has inherited the Hyuga's blood-limit so much.
It's needless to say your big sister is less than him.
More than my sister?
Perhaps, more than you.
He's not somebody you can beat with a fart this time.
That guy also has that thing.
A close battle is taboo.
Does he understand that, Naruto?
Idiot! What is he doing by attacking from the front?!
No! Naruto!
The guy can see Tenketsu (chakra holes)!
It's called Tenketsu...
It is said that by pressing exactly on those body points,
you can control the chakra flow of the opponent...
and stop it or increase it as you wish.
Not good.
I missed it?
That means, if I get too close to him, he'll push
those points and I won't be able to use any Jutsu.
I have no other choice than to fight from a distance.
Now you understand it, don't
you? You don't have a chance to win.
I was just testing your ability.
The real battle starts from now!
Kagebunshin-no-jutsu!
You used your brain, Naruto! With Kagebunshin...
Interesting kid.
Kagebunshin is a jutsu at Jonin level.
I didn't know he can use that jutsu.
The outcome isn't so obvious anymore.
Kagebunshin?
I see... Because his chakra is
equally distributed among all the clones,
I can't easily tell the real body even with my Byakugan.
But after all, there is only one real body.
Don't bluff.
Come at me if you want to come.
It's useless in front of the Neji's defense.
He's not at all offensive.
Don't underestimate me!
He's coming.
Got him!
Foolish.
Shit. I'll have him next time.
Here!
Does he have eyes on his back?
You'll become Hokage, eh?
I guess it won't be possible with this.
I can tell most things with these eyes...
Talent is decided when the person is born. In other
words, everything is decided when one is born.
Why?
Why do you always jump to a conclusion like that?
Then, you say anybody can become Hokage
just because of his hard work?
Only a handful Shinobi can be chosen to become Hokage.
See the reality well.
Those who become Hokage are born with such a fate.
It's not they become one because they tried
to be. It is decided by their fate.
Each person is different. We need to
live in the flow that you can't go against.
The only one fate that everybody equally has is...
death.
Those eyes... He's still holds a grudge against
the Souke (main family) as I expected.
So?
So what?
I'm not good at giving up.
Kagebunshin no jutsu!
What's going on anyway? I, the one
who gives a blow, is blown away!
But I promised Hinata.
I can't lose here!
Next episode Zero blind spots! Another Absolute Defense
Good news! The Year 2004 Naruto Calendar
will be given to 30 randomly chosen people!
Write down the required info on the post card,
and mail it to the address shown on the screen!