http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
If you do not possess the Sky,
it earns acquaintance and you be prepared.
If you do not possess the Earth,
you run for the fields and finds the force.
If you open the Sky and the Earth
the dangerous way becomes sure.
With this principle you will become
" " ()
Which thing means?
Sure one refers to the coils.
Task that
it wants to say to open them.
Well.
Then we open them.
But that cos' it is?
Hito Jin
E' the formula
of the Kuchiyose not Jutsu!
* Technique of the evocation
Naruto! Sakura!
It throws them to you via!
But you
Hello.
How much time.
-  The SECOND OLD E' TEST! -
The alignment of the 9 esordienti.
What happens?
E' be hard
true?
Iruka-Sensei, why six appeared
with the Kuchiyose not Jutsu?
We chunin must receive the candidates
.... to the end of the second test
and for case he is capitato to me
it makes you from messenger.
Messenger?
uhm....
Just in time.
All and three
you have exceeded the second test.
Congratulations!
It would appeal to to offer you to me of the ramen
for this happening, but
Evviva!
Ehi Naruto!
It listens until the end
Ramen! Ramen! Dattebayo!
They are a large one!
They are the best one!
I want the ramen!
It has some of energies.
Hush!
Accidents
You do not succeed in rilassarti a moment.
Six not changed at all.
I have understood!
!?
If we had opened the coils during the test
Iruka-sensei
what you would have made?
Sasuke
intelligent as usual.
As you have intuito
the rules of this examination
they put to the test your abilities
to execute the missions honestly.
If during the examination
you would have opened the coils
smashing the rule
What would be happened?
Those candidates would be
remained incoscenti until
to the end of the test.
These were the orders.
Fortune that you have not opened it.
Kabuto-saint
thanks thousands.
For a hair!
Me excuses, sensei.
What means the written one on the wall?
It seems type a indovinello
but we do not succeed to understand it.
Which devil you of frega?
A lot we are promoted!
Not
my task is also
to explain of the meant one to you.
!?
Indeed?
Sure that is true!
You read here.
E' the maxim of the chunin
written from Hokage-sama.
The maxim?
S !
The "sky" represents the mind of the man
while the "earth" represents the body.
Without the "sky" the wisdom is not obtained.
Fundamental E'.
As an example:
If the point weak person of Naruto is the mind
it will have to take of conscience
and to improve that aspect.
But
that beautiful example!
Also it is written
that without the "earth" not
it runs for the fields.
If the point weak person of Sakura is the physical resistance
then it will have to be trained with tenacity
every day.
Having it is the "sky" that the "earth "
whichever pericosa mission becomes just.
That is
the missions will not be more a danger.
Then
what is in place of the lacking word?
It represents the Chunin.
The word "man" who found itself
within parchments.>.
This test verified
necessary the basic abilities
in order to become a Chunin.
And you have exceeded it.
The chunin he is a squad leader
and as such he must guide the square.
He possesses acquaintance, force and inner sagezza.
All this
it is necessary in order to carry out the own tasks.
I would want that you faced
the next obstacle
holding to mind this instruction.
This is
all the one which I had from dirvi.
Received!
But
in the third and last test
not exaggerated.
Especially you naruto
six the one which more
Iruka-sensei
From when I have received the coprifronte of Konoha
they are not more the dispettoso student of the academy!
Not there is reason of preoccuparsi.
Moreover this....
it is the maturity symbol
that you have given to me.
Perhaps always they are stirred violently
but they are not more a child.
Why
now they are a ninja!
I have understood.
Scusami, Naruto.
I
they are what it knows
better their force.
Inasmuch as riusciranno to us I would not want to be
I to assist them to the withdrawal.
If you hold us cos   a lot
to the square ve I leave it
but you are sure of wanting to you
to assume an ungrateful task cos  ?
Ringrazio to you.
But it remembers to you
that they are of the group of Kakashi.
I waited for me great things
from genin from he candidates.
Stanne outside!
They are not more your students.
Bens
my subordinates.
What he knows better their force
Kakashi-saint
six sure you.
He still burns the Juin Jutsu?
(Cursed Brand)
I can make something?
Not.
Thanks but hour go very better.
To propostito, Orochimaru is one of the three
leggendari ninja of Konoha, just?
E' a ninja traitor of class ' present S' in the BingoBook
and neanche the Ambu could face it.
(BingoBook: Black List)
Also I have felt to say that it was dead.
Why
it is intentional to return to the village?
It was from that I tried a type like he.
That boy will make road with
the blood of the Uchiha clan.
Probably
For Sasuke I imagine.
Anko-sama.
Ventuno boys has
exceeded the second test.
Like from regulations
the preliminary matters will be carried out
for the third test.
The second test has been concluded.
While
we continue this examination
and we observe with attention
the movements of Orochimaru.
Well.
First of all
it compliments in order to have old the test!
Of the 78 participants
they are still remained 21 persons.
I had announced that I would have halved the number
in truth I expected only a pair of squares.
I have hunger!
E' still remained all this people?
That balls
Also Sasuke-kun and its square is passes to you.
Obvious.
We have faticato a casino in order to save them.
If they were not it passes to you only we would have lost time.
Your group if it it is cavando.
Perhaps they will have only had fortune.
But finch there is my group
they will not be able to continue.
Inasmuch as in the next test
they count only the abilities characterizes them.
The giovinezza e' po' sweet and a po' bitter
and to times it does not pardon, my Kakashi beloved.
uhm? You have said something?
Oh my god ~~~~~~! !
Six Bravo eternal Kakashi my avails again.
With this your way to make
"trendy" they always give to me on the nerves.
Ohh!
That one is the eternal one avails again of Gai-Sensei.
From the aesthetic point of view
Gai-sensei remains defeated.
Between all the masters
Gai-sensei remains the best one!
Only E' that risplende!
But sure!
You watch Gai-sensei To Me!
Anch' I  will shine  like you.
I do not want more to see
one person to me beloved to cry.
And she is for this
that  I will not be
never more
struck, Gai-sensei.
All the more remarkable elements are remained.
Uchiha Sasuke-kun.
You  I will make  to pay for
my arm
Uchiha Sasuke
You can bet to us.
Only 7 squares on 26
she begins them are remained.
As I thought does not have not even a scratch.
Gaara.
Akamaru is behaved in strange way.
The three of the sand
And cos   six passed also you,
Naruto-kun.
Little evil.
But like
are remained all the esordienti of Konoha?
Ehy Ehy
There is also the old Hokage, Iruka-sensei
and also the sopracciglione!
it seems that there are
large pieces of Konoha.
I have an ugly prefeeling.
Of they are remained several
and nearly all debuttanti.
Here why they insisted to candidarli.
Now
Hokage-sama will illustrate to you
in what the third test consists.
Therefore you open the orecchie well.
I pray.
Hokage-sama.
S .
The Third Test is in order to begin.
But before the explanation
I want to clear one what
R-with regard to the true scope of this examination.
The true scope?
Sapete why the examination is carried out
with to the countries it allies to you?
For rinsaldare the friendship and in order to raise
the general level of the ninja.
Why this examination
in practical
In practical
E' the simulation of war between countries allies to you.
What means?
If we return behind in the history
the countries ally to you that you know hour
adjacent countries were alone
in continuous war for the power.
In order to avoid to waste the forces
and to destroy an other
it came established a battle place
that it gave origin
to this examination of selection of the Chunin!
But like?
We do not participate in order to become chunin?
Sure.
This examination serves in order to select the ninja
in a position to becoming Chunin.
But it is also true that the ninja
that they carry on the shoulders
the dignity of the country
they must fight to cost
of the own life.
The dignity of the country?
And above all the Daimyo and the ninja
commanders of every country
they will assist to your combat.
When he comes cleared the difference of being able
between several the countries
the strong countries obtain
numerous demands for job
and to the contrary the countries weak people
they suffer from one lessening of the demands.
To that point the adjacent countries
with the stronger countries they are felt threatens to you
why they comprise the development of the power
military of the other states....
in degree therefore to exercise
political pressures on they.
And then!
Why there is need to fight
to cost of living?
The power of a country
it is the power of its village.
The power of a village
it is the power of the ninja that they dwell to you.
This examination
servants in order to demonstrate the force of every country.
Only if....
she fights herself to cost
of the life the examination has sense.
Also your predecessori have
fought in this examination
for the same reason.
But then why it is spoken
a lot of friendship between the countries?
For this to the beginning I have said to you
not to misinterpret of the true one meant.
In the world of the ninja for friendship one agrees
to improve itself to vicissitude fighting to risk
of the own life.
This will be a mortal crash them that you will face
in name of your dreams and the honor of the village.
Beautiful speech.
Not me of frega nothing.
Sbrigati to speak us about the details
of this Examination
where we risk our life.
It would appeal to to me to illustrate to you in the detail
the third test, but
it is a task that
Eccomi, Hokage-sama.
I, Gekkou Hayate, in how much
designated arbitrator
.... I  will be to occupy some to me.
You proceed.
Sono lieto to make your acquaintance.
There is something that I will make  to make  you....
before beginning the third test.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
What?
The preliminary encounter now ?
But if we are as soon as it arrives you to the tower.
Also Sasuke-kun does not seem well to be.
You cannot go ahead cos ,  Sasuke-kun!
Please it withdraws to you !
Not six in the conditions for fighting.
However it goes  I will say  to the Sensei of that sign.
-  NEXT EPISODE  -
-  the CANDIDATES MUST HALVE THEMSELVES  -
E' a battle without warning !
I have fear, Sasuke-kun