Subtitles By: BakaSan
What's wrong?
You come at me and could only do that?
You couldn't even lay your finger on me.
You make me laugh!
"Explosive"
I don't know how far I can go, but...
I'll do whatever I can do!
Explosion!
This is the Naruto Ninpo Book!!
Kagebunshin no Jutsu
I'm coming!
From now, the secret Taijutsu technique,
Uzumaki Naruto
Bunshin Taiatari
(Clone directly dashing against you)
Now!
O.K.!
Kagebunshin no jutsu
One more!
Take this, the Hidden Konoha secret Taijutsu
technique I learned from Kakashi sensei.
Senen Goroshi
(1000 years of pain)
It's just an enema...
Kaboom.
That was a great blow.
Did he do it?
After all that effort, you only got one blow.
Shut up.
Who think he'd attack the root of the
tail where the defense is most weak...
Though I didn't get any injuries, it's
impossible to absorb all the impact.
Did I underestimate him too much?
Hey, Naruto.
You've got to save Sakura with all you've got.
And after you rescue her carry
her away from here immediately.
I know you can do it.
Sasuke, you...
Even with my current condition, I
can stop him only for a little while.
If I'm finished here then I was just only at this level.
I lost everything once before.
Never again...
I don't want to see my precious comrades die in front of me.
Precious comrades.
I won't never let my comrades die.
I get it...
That's right.
Because he was like me... because he's lived
feeling the sadness and loneliness like I did.
I thought he is strong because he's living in
such loneliness and kept fighting for himself.
But the real strength isn't something like that.
You cannot gain real strength
from fighting only for yourself.
Do you have somebody precious to you?
When a person wants to protect
something or somebody precious to him...
he can be truly strong.
You will become strong.
What amount of chakra is he creating!?
Is this Naruto?
I'll definitely...
protect them till the end!
Taju Kage Bunshin no Jutsu
(extra multiple shadow clone)
He does that well.
Sorry for keeping you waiting for long time!
This is the beginning of Uzumaki (swirl) Naruto Ninpo Books!
What is the number of clones?
What is this?
Wow! This is amazing!
You're somewhat promising.
You... this is...
Sasuke, you take a good rest.
Leave everything to me, Uzumaki Naruto.
This is...
Alright, everybody! Let's go!
*that* Naruto?
Jump!
Naruto Ninpo cho (book)
Shiho Happo Shuriken no Maki
(Chapter - Shuriken Everywhere)
My body still isn't recovered. I have to defend with Sand.
Here it comes!
Uzumaki
Naruto Nisen Rendan
(2000 continuous attacks)
...chapter
This guy...
This time will be 4000 continuous attacks using both legs!
Here it comes!
What the heck is he all of the sudden?!
No way... against Gaara in that form...
From where did he get this much power?
I...
...against this...
It's impossible that I lose to a guy like this!
What is that?
It's finally out...
The final form.
This is the monster inside of him.
I never imagined that I would show this form to you guys!
Shit... my body...
Theres not much chakra left anymore because of the Bunshin I did...
Shit...
Inu Tori Saru Hitsuji
(Dog, Hen, Monkey, Sheep)
This is the end.
Sabaku Sou...
Kuchiyose no jutsu!
I'm surprised he did Kuchiyose in that situation.
I'll protect Sakura-chan.
You keep me entertained till no end.
Naruto... you.. what on the earth...
Finally you see the result of my training!
Good.  I can do it.
What're you doing?
You again? What do you want?
It's Shukaku of Sand, if I remember correctly...
Gama Oyabin, fight with me!
I don't think so...
Why should I go to all the trouble against that guy?
It's so stupid.
Why? You told me you'll make me your subordinate!
Isn't Oyabun the one help out the Kobun
(subordinate) when he's in trouble?
That's the Moral code, isn't it?
I sure did say I'll make you my subordinate, but..
I still haven't exchanged Sakazuki (Sake cup) with you.
What? I'm not twenty years old yet! I can't drink Sake!
Don't say that and listen to what he says, Dad.
Dad?
Why are you here in a place like this Gamakichi?
I came out to play because I was bored...
What? What? You guys are father and son?
...but that guy tried to bully me.
What did you say?
Then I was saved by this guy.
He fought with that monster. This guy is an interesting guy.
I see.
Kid, I accept you as my subordinate.
Plus, I'll show you what Jingi (moral code) is about.
I'll make you pay for what you did.
You, worthless kid!
Hold on tight!
Take this!
Incredible!
What a guy. It's too heavy and I can only swing the dagger.
If I don't finish quickly, the landscape will change.
Hey, Hey, oyabin!
Sakura-chan is somewhere over there. So, don't go there.
Lure him out this way, please.
That's his woman, dad.
I can't rescue Sakura-chan without beating this guy up.
Interesting. Interesting, Uzumaki Naruto.
Damn it. Gaara's planning to do
that. I have to get out of here.
That is...
Is that the medium, eh?
This is my regard to you keeping me entertained until now.
I'll let you see the real power of the Sand incarnation.
That dark circles of his eyes...
That medium shows signs of insomnia
because of being possessed with Shukaku.
What? Insomnia?
A person who's possessed with Monster Tanuki (raccoon dog)
Shukaku is unable to have good sleep, not even one night.
Because of fear.
Once you fall asleep, Shukaku will eat
your own character little by little,
and eventually you'll not be yourself.
Since it's not possible to sleep well normally, a
medium tends to have his character getting more unstable.
Therefore, while the medium is awake, the
power of Shukaku is suppressed normally.
But,
when the medium goes into sleep...
Tanuki Neiri no Jutsu
(fake sleep no jutsu)
He did it.
What's gonna happen, Oyabin?
Once Tanuki Neiri no Jutsu is
started, Shukaku's gonna come out.
Yahoo! I'm finally be able to come out!
That's Shukaku?
He's unexpectedly funky, isn't he?
Suddenly, I find a guy I want to kill!
We're gonna jump.
What?
Fuuton Renku Dan
(Wind element Continuous Airwave Cannon)
Suiton Teppo Dama
(Water element Bullet)
This is as if it's a storm.
What kind of battle are they doing...
Oyabin, that way isn't good!
Be quiet. I know that.
Renku Dan!
Teppo Dama!
Sorry!
It's bad, Oyabin. There's one left!
Yahoo! I did it! I killed him! Killed him!
That hurts!
You throw a ball with a lot of chakra in it!
Even I can't take any more those.
Then, what should we do?
As a start, rough up the medium kid to wake him up.
Then the jutsu will end.
How're we gonna wake him up?
Just give one blow to that kid.
Teppo Dama!
You won't hit me.
Now.
Oyabin! I can't punch him if you don't hold him firmly!
I'm a Toad... I don't have neither
fangs nor nails to stop his movement.
Then! What should we do?
Transform into a thing that have
those with Henge-no-jutsu. (Transform)
But, I'm not good at Henge.
What?
So, you become my will and do the hand seal.
It's a Combination Henge.
Yes, sir!
One with fangs and nails, you got it?
Let me see...
Let's go!
Oh no! Wait! Hold on a sec!
Fangs and nails... fangs and nails... fangs and nails....
Henge!
Henge no Jutsu!
That is...!
I don't know about your past.
Even my past doesn't matter.
I have something I want to protect. That's all.
Hey, no-eyebrows. Me and you, the
similar ones, let's finish this now.
I'll finish with the next one.
This is truly true,
this is the end!
Next Episode
Go over the limit!
~ Light and Shadow ~