http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
Sasuke-kun
it is true that Naruto is one
confusionario and is not strong, but
at least it is not a codardo!
Just!
Sasuke-kun!
Stupid brother
if you want to kill to me
you must hate to me.
You must survive from wretch!
Not!
and to continue to scappare
and to grab hold of you to the life.
Not!
Not!!
The Sharingan revives!
Katon Ryuuka not Jutsu!
Just as I expected from the Uchiha clan.
It seems that its blood is ribollendo.
I want to take it with calm
and to amuse a po' to me with you.
I must survive in order to kill my brother.
This is that one in which creed.
I was the only one to being scared.
Naruto! Sakura!
If I do not succeed to risk my life here
as I can think to succeed to defeat it?
I see its movements!
I see to you!
Far from negligible.
It anticipates my movements
it aimed at the vital points
me it is behind.
E' already the sunset.
I must find it to the svelta.
With the night
avr   little possibility against than he.
But
why in a moment like this!
Qual' is its objective?
However not ago no difference.
If six come in this village
today it will be the yield of the accounts.
I have taken to you!
Kawarimi?
Sasuke-kun!
Too much easy!
You are disonorando the name of the Uchiha.
To kill to you   with calm.
Like when torture a bug.
Sharingan Windmill, Triple Blade!
(turning it of the Sharingan, atacco to triple blade!)
Katon:Goukakyuu not Jutsu!
Fuoco!esecuzione! :tecnica of the destructive fire spheres!
!
Sasuke-kun!
Ce you have made it!
You are well?
A moment rests to you.
Kanashibari?
In spite of the age it uses the Sharingan very well.
There is indeed the blood of
Uchiha within of you.
Just as I thought. I want to you.
You are indeed siblings.
In your eyes there is cos   a lot
to be able to exceed Itachi.
Who devil six you!?
My name is Orochimaru.
If you want to meet me of new
you survive and exceeds this examination
Ah, the coil!
striking the ninja of the sound to my service.
About that devil speaks!?
We do not want more see again to you!
Not creed that will go cos .
Sasuke-kun!
Cos' you have made Sasuke-kun?
I have made a goodbye gift.
Sasuke-kun to the fine ones will try to me....
made thirsty of power.
Indeed they are amused me with you.
Sasuke-kun!
You hold hard, Sasuke-kun!
Hey!
Sasuke-kun!
Sasuke-kun! Hey!
Sasuke-kun....
Naruto, Sasuke-kun Is.....!
Sasuke-kun is....!
Naruto!
I
I what must make?
I perceive its presence.
Near E'!
From how much time we do not look at ourselves.
In the this most dangerous moment six
person searched between those of S level.
I must stop to you to cost of living!
I have learned all on you.
I was one of your soldiers
therefore, it is a task that is up to me, just?
Orochimaru?
Impossible one.
Senai Jashuu.
You will not succeed to escape to me!
Orochimaru, I am in order to take in
loan your left hand.
That position of the hand is
.
We moriremo here together.
Ninpo: Souja Sousai not
Indeed you are thinking to kill to you?
That one is one copy.
A six jonin special of this village
you would not have to use all those
forbidden techniques that I have taught to you.
I have already said you that it is useless.
Why six returned?
Although it is from that we do not look at ourselves
six a lot bearing away.
Six returned in order to assassinate Hokage-sama?
Not, not.
I do not have men for that one still enough.
I thought to recruit of someone
in this village.
I have already donated to a boy
I seal equal yours, you know?
There is a boy who I want.
Egoist, like always.
That morir boy.
Vero!
The possibilities to sopravivvere are 1 on 10
but as you it could make it us.
It must appeal to this boy indeed to you!
Six gelosa?
Ce you still have it with me why
I have taken advantage of to you and abandoned?
With the exception of you,
it seems skillful indeed.
Of other part he has inherited
the blood of the Uchiha clan.
And it is also much beautiful one.
Perfect for being my successor.
If that sopravviver boy
we will see some of the beautiful ones.
I recommend myself, not to suspend the examination.
There are also three members of mine villagio.
I want just to enjoy it.
Know that if someone will intralcer to me
it will be the end of the village of Konoha.
We have lost average day
to try food and water.
Many squares now are resting.
E' the moment to attack.
We begin the recognition of the area
and it is that we will find or less
of the other squares
we will return here.
You have understood?
Okay.
Roger!
Of agreement.
We go!
The breath is returning normal
but it has always the high fever.
I must protect them!
I must sbrigarmi make relationship the Hokage.
Eternal damnation in a moment like this.
This is
Kanashibari not jutsu.
(technical of vincolamento of the body.)
Then dov' it was here.
For being Anbu you are indeed discs of a valve boys.
Hey, not to say cos .
It is felt well? Hey!
But this is!
The brand is reappeared!
This is not
Orochimaru?
What? Where?
Eternal damnation.
We will better make to carry it from the Hokage.
Not, to the tower.
But what you say!?
The martial law must be restored
from the moment that is reappeared Orochimaru.
The examination now does not have more importance!
This already I know it
later you  spiegher ? all.
Capacities also the Hokage.
We have finds them to you.
Coma has ordered Orochimaru will attack to the dawn.
Our objective is Uchiha Sasuke.
But if the others intralceranno to us
we can kill them true?
Sure!
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
nee kikoe masu ka?