Subbed by Shinji 89
Who you are ?
I have not had one good day.
If you decide to go ahead,
you know that  I will not have  cares!
Bastard
you cannot speak to us cos ì.
You come here.
I will use  your ribs like one xilofono.
Do-Re-Mi-Fa-Sol-La-Si-Do
E' mine!
It has blocked the legs to me with a thread?
It makes to feel me well like sounds.
I give!
What !
King!
From where he has attacked to me ?
Your boneses have a low intonazione.
You must emit of the higher sounds
understood ?
Hour is the time of me-ago-sol
Eccoti the last blow
Concatenato attack of the lion!
I invite of the sound.
Here ready!
Itadakimasu!
Sakura-chan, eats fastly!
it eats fastly!
Spaghetti to the pig is made very well in this place!
Yeah,
not to worry you this it is my special treatment.
Just getlteman ?
From to a your fiancèe special treatment, Naruto?
Six truly intelligent one.
Fida..nz… What you are saying?
I have one today important argument with Sakura-chan.
She is not still my girl…
Sakura-chan?
Excuse, Naruto.
I was thinking.
He seems truly good.
Well, We eat!
While it eats,
it speaks me about Sasuke.
Sasuke has said not to say to you it to me.
E' all guilt of Orochimaru.
Enough!
Kakashi-sensei has said that I do not have preoccuparmi,
and I want credergli.
But when he has fought against Gaara, he has happened of new.
Sasuke had the same look all and the two times.
This is why I…
Orochimaru, eh ?
I have see again time little makes.
Where ?
When we were trying Tsunade.
You die!
Merda!
Ero-sennin and Granny…
It had in face two of they…
and he was rather strong
E' without dangerous doubt.
Cos ì  I suppose.
Not to worry to you!
Sasuke
it will not never accept I invite of the sort from a ceffo.
E' end too much Bravo for needing Orochimaru!
I guarantee!
!
Why our Orochimaru getlteman wants one similar
invalidity?
To this point it was better Kimimaro.
However until you will be in a poor village
like this, you will remain ninja like many and yours
force will not grow.
Why? My series of attacks was enough
consisting!
Nevertheless it seems unharmed!
To play to make the ninja with yours amichetti…
it will carry to you marcire.
You come with we!
Orochimaru will give the force to you!
It would be useless if we strained to you to come.
You must decide to you.
Orochimaru-sama has given a difficult task to us.
What tasks to make?
You want to come?
or not?
You decide yourself.
When one invalidity makes me to lose time,
it comes to me wants to kill it.
And then it tries to us!
You… possess you seal?
Not to believe of being the only one pupillo of our getlteman.
You would do good not to use too much those I seal.
or better.>.
inasmuch as not six in a position to controlling it.
if it uses it to along…
… it will erode your body gradually.
You still seem to be in the first phase.
the erosion speed is low.>.
but once arrived to the term of the process…
you will end with losing your identity.
In order always.
In exchange of the power of I seal,
it is come catches to you from orochimaru-sama.
For we not there is more freedom.
In order to obtain something… it must sacrifice qualcos' other
Which is your obbiettivo?
You want to pass your life leccarti to the wounds
with your companions in this village
And to forget you about Uchiha Itachi?
Not to scordare your obbiettivo.
For you this village is equivalent to a pair of throttles
it would be enough to cut the ties to you that they withhold to you here.
If lascerai this village
you will acquire an enormous one to be able.
Not to scordare your obbiettivo!
It returns of new!
Sakura-chan!
All good goes.
Cosa?Cosa?
to go alone is not dangerous?
Luminous E' cos  ì, not will be problems.
Sakura-chan?
Naruto, thanks.
Hour I would want alone to be.
Oh?
Not to worry to you!
What you make from these you leave to deep night?
In order to leave the village it must take this road
Vai to house to sleep.
Why ?
Why you do not say nothing to me?
Why you are always zitto and not never null me storys?
Why not ce neither need.
Stò  asking  to you not immischiarti.
Not to be to think me.
I am from always an annoyance for you Sasuke-kun.
You memories ?
The day that we are…
It becomes to you genin and have composed our trio.>.
just in this place I and you are remained alone for
before the time, and you six angry one with me.
It has not never had parents.
If I involved to me like he, I would come sgridata from mine!
This is the reason for which he cos ì  it is indisciplinato.
Solitudine…
The solitudine is a pain, than it does not have null to that to see with
before the time, and you six angry one with me.
But what takes to you?
Six insopportabile.
I not memory.
Normal E'.
Last E' cos ì  much time.
But  that day has been, beginning for we two.
beyond that for Naruto and master Kakashi.
We have carried out several missions in four.
They were hard and they have been many difficult moments…
But.>.
I must say…
that I was happy!
I know of your clan.
but  with the single one vendetta
you will not render nobody happy.
of you same… of me…
I knew…
I am various from you.
Our roads are not intercrossed.
We have gone ahead in four and effectively.>.
.. I have tried more times to convince that this to me
it was the just road.
,, But to the end my heart has chosen the vendetta.
I live for this reason.
I cannot become like you or Naruto.
You have decided to go of new towards the solitudine!
That time you have taught to how much the solitudine to me is painful.
And hour I succeed to understand it end too much well!
I have one family and of the friends…
But…
if you lost to you.>.
For me,
he would be like remaining single.
From this moment, everyone of we…
… new road will begin to cover one.
I…
I AM IN LOVE OF YOU! I LOVE TO YOU TO DIE!
If you will decide to be with me,
I swear to you that you of it you will not repent.
We will be always allegros and I you  will render  happy sure!
I will make  whichever thing for you!
I pray to you enough
I will even help  you  in yours vendetta!
I promise to you that in some way I will succeed  to us!
For which it remains here… with me…
And if this is not possible,
portami with you…
You just six,
insopportabile.
Not to go!
If you go via, also to stop to you  I will put myself  urlare!
Sakura…
Thanks.
Sasuke-kun.>.
There were aspettando..nobile Sasuke.
That it takes to you without warning ?
It had been decided that you would have become ours
advanced once abandoned the village.
You pardon the impoliteness to us you bring until hour.
These particular do not interest to me…
We go.
It is begun!
Boku tamani, Boku Tamani
Yume ni hito Afureru not kakeraga
Yama not yonimieru
Kamisama nihotoke samani
Hito Tsutae naiteru nokakeraga
yama not yonimieru
Dan dan dan sura nan deru
Borushoino poseninarandara
shake shake shake, sagaso janainowa
Bye bye bye not let' s of
yama not yonimieru
Next Naruto week: special to the 19:00
In the room we go.>.
We do not see, but us rannicchiamo.>.
Chuunin Shikamaru.>.