Subbed by Gandelr
Chekked by Kyubi
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
It seems that my movements are return to you normal.
Blood…
Tsunade-sama!
Ehi, ehi! What is happening?
Why Kabuto-saint and the Old Tsunade…
Its watches well coprifronte.
It is  a servitore of Orochimaru.
Episode #94
You take this!
The fury of the Rasengan
Therefore Orochimaru is he!
Occupied of the quattrocchi, Shizune.
And I  will take care myself  of Orochimaru.
But before, I want that Tsunade makes something affinchè recovers my forces.
Creed that the effect of the poison will still last in order much time.
Nothing  cannot be made.
Like! Indeed!
I do not have much choice…
I must fight in this state?
Tsunade, you resume yourself and cures to you.
Well, and I that I make? What I make?
You remain here with this small pig and Tsunade.
Ehh, I want to fight!
Also I want…
You are zitto!
Also those quattrocchi has said it.
You do not have the same level.
In as far as he, it is a Sannin, like me.   He has been he to kill the Third party.
Eye for eye!
They are the solo to being able to fight against of he.
And the quattrocchi, it has the level of Kakashi.
Much good… In this case…
Kage Bunsh…
Firm!
Not to use the Kage Bunshin.  It is  useless.
How?
It would not work against of he.
You would consume your Chakra uselessly.
Now I must take care of these two…
Well, we begin!
Kuchiyose not Jutsu
[ Invocazione ]
Yo!
Che cos' is this?
From dov' it is sbucato?
We do not look at ourselves from a lot!
Jiraiya-sama, because of the poison, you cannot use yours correctly chakra.
Your stupidity is too much, is not true Jiraiya?
You have not never had talent, six pathetic one.
It seems that Tsunade you has played ugly a shooting.
That technique needs of sacrifices.
Apparently, it did not want.
Probably she has given a poison to it that limits its power.
To sacrifice Jiraiya, eh?
Creed that Tsunade wanted to make it, but…
Merda, has uncovered my handicap.
It is always cos ì,  jokes.
Eternal damnation, is made fun of of Ero-Sennin. This makes me to ribbollire the blood!
Kuchiyose not Jutsu!
The Child with the Kyuubi demon of the examination of Chuunin…
I would have had to kill it when of it I had the opportunity.
In place of sealing its power and to leave it to go via.
But only that can remove those I seal…
they are the Sannin and the Third Hokage.
Then it has been Jiraiya-sama to remove I seal to Naruto-kun?
It would seem of s ì.  If this child succeeds in to extract the power of the Kyuubi Demon.
This is…
It does not seem.
In any case it is truly a Ninja, even if it is not equipped of no talent.
Cos' is this?
It seems that it is not still ready…
It is  that cos' it is this!?
Good Afternoon.
Ehi Yamatatsu! Which you make thing here us?
Ah, Gamakichi-niichan.
It is  my first invocazione. I can help you?
Imbecille! You will be one dull for he! You would better make to hide!
Eh! I can have one dull?
"Wai! Wai! "
[ an expression of Giapponense joy ]
We go!
It leaves Jiraiya Me.
Occupied of the others.
A Sannin…
it is from that I wanted to face Jiraiya-sama!
Naruto!
They are I your adversary!
"Doton Yomi not muma "
[ Swamps of the other world ]
Merda, I cannot face it with this pathetic attempt.
The poison makes always effect.
At least the snakes cannot move.
Ninpo Doku Gasu!
[ poisoned Gas ]
I do not have to breathe!
Ahi, my ankles!
You  lascerò  not to eat an other time to me!
We go!
Ninpo Marin Jijizo!
[ Thorns of the altromondo ]
Merda!
Still with your disgustose techniques.
Also you, your thorns have caused many troubles to me.
It abandons to you.
That sin. Medical Siccome we were all and two of the Ninja, I respected to you.
Detention! Not to move to you!
You control yourselves, Tsunade-Saint.
If continued cos ì,  you will make to suffer Orochimaru-sama.
Ahi… My body… is cos ì  heavy…
In past, you were the hero of the village.
You carry to you nearby wherever this child. Rinunciando to the village not six more that hero, is not cos ì?
What I see, is someone fort as well as how much you…
This child…
He is not worth nothing.
He is  for that I do not have intentional the boy of the Uchiha.
He is not amusing to teach someone that already is perfect.
Above all because he is like you were.
Here because you cannot leave it single.
Compared to the child who has inherited the Sharingan,
this child does not have no future…
Since Naruto-kun does not possess the Sharingan.
Best the Ninja is those that have the greater abilities.
The word "Ninja" designates those who is able to use the "Ninjutsu."
It is not all the one which ago a Ninja.
You have not understood!
To be Ninja.... is qualche.cosa that a Shinobi becomes.
Cos ì  creeds?
I will say  one  to you what.
The more important thing for one Shinobi…
It is not the number of jutsu that it knows.
The thing more important is…
Not to abandon.... Extreme determination!
Infame! I have not ended with you!
Of the determination in order not to never abbondonare …
This child of is full!
I ignore of that technical he be a matter himself.But with this speed, he could not hit to me.
Not there is way… I cannot hit it if one moves.
Ouch!
In any case, I have still enough chakra.
It would seem that after the attack of the snake, the left leg is fractured you.
It was only a leg, you could still move.
Now not more.
Why I have broken the nerves of your skillful leg.
Which thing I can make?
For this technique I have need of all and the two hands! If I lose the use of a hand, is ended.
I make fear you, is not cos ì?  You have wants to escape?
Naruto-kun.
To the Chuunin examination, you have said:
For who you take to me!  I will not escape!
"For who you take to me?  I will not escape. "
Even if six become Genin, and even if for case you would become Hokage, is well.
In I do not have fear of you. You could dirmi the same thing?
They are not like you. I  will receive  the title it of Hokage!
Why to become Hokage, is my dream!
A not more six child.
You would have to stop to fight.
It watches in face the truth. If you want to escape, makes it.
Ehi, cos' is this look?
You are in order to die. And if morirai your dreams svaniranno in the null one.
You want to perhaps die! Nawaki, six solo a Genin.
On the battlefield, it is well to escape.
I will not never escape !
The children believe that all it is easy.
This is because they allow it to say of the stupidities and having of the unattainable dreams…
It is  for that they never do not abandon.
Jiraiya, six state you to insegnargli the Rasengan?
Insegnargli one technical that will not be able to comprise? The just six its Master?
You would not have to encourage it.
He is  for that this child says that he dreams to become Hokage and other fesserie…
If he continues to run after this stupid dream…
Morirai!
They give 3 days and I will dominate  this  technique to me!
In this case we make a bet.
Merda!
I  will respect  the given word.
This is my Ninja creed!
A bet?
I give one week to you.
If it succeeds in to dominate this technique,  I will admit  that you can become Hokage.
And I will give  this  necklace to you.
If it remains here firm, the much worse one for you.
How?
Why?
Ehi, Old Tsunade!
Still?
As I have promised to the age of our bet,  I will earn  this necklace!
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu
Because a Kage Bunshin!
Hour enough! You do not have need of proteggermi, Naruto!
Stopped!
I had said to you that if continues to you with this attitude you would be died!
And if you die.... Your dreams will die with you!
Not firm! It moves to you from its road! You escape!
It is not preoccupied.
I…
Not  morirò  before becoming Hokage!
tsk.. You will not go from no part!
Vai!
The same technique that it has used before.
Not, this is…
I understand…
In order to concentrate the chakra in its hand, it has used a Kage Bunshin.
If I can compress my Chakra…
I can make my movement!
Impossible!
RASENGAN
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
The next week, Naruto begins to the 19h!
Special Naruto Commemoration! The 3 Sannin are faced! During a special episode of an hour!
You cannot lack!