Subbed by Kyubi
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://www.narutofansub.altervista.org
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh!
just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
kewashi shura not michi not naka
hito not chizu wo hirogete doko he yuku?
gokusaishoku not karasu ga sore wo ubai totte yaburi suteta
saa kokoro not mikiwamero shikato mihiraite me ima wo
"yeah!"
ushinau mono nante naisa iza mairou
we to are fighting dreamers takami wo mezashite
fighting dreamers narifuri kamawazu
fighting dreamers shinjiru ga mama ni
oils oils oils oh! just go my way!
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire
right to here, right now! "bang!"
buppanase like to dangan raina
right to here, right now! "burn!"
buttagittekuze get the to fire "bang!"
Soon we will be to Konoha. They are already all?
S ì!
Obasa brother, me seems that someone lacks.
What? And who?
Idate. Morino Idate Lacks.
Eternal damnation, that rompiscato them!
Which thing we must make? We must wait for it?
We have not chosen.
Who six?
You are the Wasabi of the village of the Tea, is not cos ì?
Hey, you who six!?
You would make starvene calm better.
You do not have no possibility against a Ninja.
You do not preoccupy yourselves. I will not kill  to you.>.
I hope that you have learned the lesson. Council to leave you to lose the Race of Todori.
Cursed…
We must carry this to Konoha at all costs.
Perfect! Still missions and missions! Evviva!
But. Kakashi-sensei not is?
It must be in delay, as usual.
Not, Kakashi will not come.
Oh! The old Tsunade!
Not to call to me cos ì!
Euh.... Hokage-sama…
Why you say that Kakashi-sensei will not come?
Like sapete,
Kakashi and the other Juunin is is left in order to complete other missions.
Therefore I will only assign  this mission you three.
It is  of B category.
You are extremely prudent.
Extremely.... Prudent?
Sure, to second of the circumstances, mission of level could also become one To.
Then? Who we must protect?
Who knows it!
That what you want to say with "who knows it "
To the Country of the Tea, there is the Race of Todori, that he has every place four years.
We were waiting for the messengers who had to participate to the race, but.>.
before that these persons arrived here,
they have been attacked from their adversaries, of the impostori.
Impostori?
Euh.... I have not understood much good.
Well, in order to make it short, you o to the Country of the Tea and speeches to Jirochou head.
Jirochou head?
Ah! It would not have to be the head of the last time?
He is  exact.
If you do not have questions, gone!
And fairies in way to catch up the Country of the Tea before this evening! Gone!
S ì.
S ì!
We have understood!
I entrust all you.
Episode #102
The crucial moment - New Mission
The sense of the duty towards the men. To help the Country of the Tea!
Ehi Sakura-chan, you do not have hunger?
Beh, a po '.
Then it is decided!
Since we are next to a restaurant, we make one pause!
Ehi Naruto…
Six here?
I have made  that  that you had asked to me.
After avergli broken boneses, the head of the Wasabi will not leave.
These persons will still participate to the race?
Exactly.
In more, there are of the voices that assert that they have engaged of the Ninja.
I have understood.
The next time, will be during the race.
The next time,
I will not show  no mercy.
Welcome.
Ah, Mrs.! Of the oshikuro!
[ Zuppa of red fagioli ]
I  will take  of the Dango.
[ Sweet ]
And you, Sasuke-kun?
Tonkoro ten.
[ Tagliatelle flavored with honey or vinegar ]
Well, I pray you to attend a po '.
Of the Ninja di Konoha…
I will make  of my best!
Naruto. Not to try to make alone all.
Of agreement.
E' one beautiful day, and you ve been some seated to the shadow.
This why the Ninja is sensitive.
About that what speaks?
Sure Konoha is too much pacific.
It must be popolato from persons like you, small mascalzoni.
Which thing you have said!?
Oh! Beautiful girl is also one.
That beautiful surprise!
Euh…
Sono Morino Idate.
And you, Miss.?
Eternal damnation! Not to approach to you Sakura-chan!
Sakura, eh?
That beautiful name!
The destiny has intentional that we met there.
And if we went to speak about our future?
Eh?
To speak about our future?
I want to say. not to be more Ninja, and becomes my woman.
Ehi! How it dares to speak in that way!? Stopped, imbecille!
However, I was joking.>.
Ehi you, parasite!
You depreciation! All you Ninja!
If continued to go towards the Country of the Tea, lascerò  not to continue  to you!
Then if you want to make botte, I please to you endured!
It waits for Naruto!
Who if of frega.>.
We do not have time to lose in order to amuse to us.
You are zitto Sasuke!
I will not never excuse  the persons who despise the Ninja!
I will make sure  that it comprises  that  that it arrives to it.... Eh?
It is  disappeared.
Impossible! I have not felt it.
Dov' is scappato?
Here  that  that you have ordered.
Merda.
Thanks thousands.
Two you count?
Which thing is?
The boy who is as soon as left he has said that you would have paid also for he.
Which thing!? Cursed!
E' already far away. It runs very quickly.
Inasmuch as it has fregato to us, I cannot here be to make nothing!
I must chase it!
Mrs., thanks for the meal.
I leave the money here.
Thanks.
All the travellers today have haste!
That impressive speed!
Probably it has followed a special training.
Who is?
Anyone is, will take it!
Che Ninja idiot!
They will not never take to me!
Merda! Calm, I must remain calm.
You do not have nothing of special.
You must be without moneies in order to have to us left also your account to pay.
Excused!
I did not want!
I have lost my pocketbook and I did not know that what to make. You were here and…
We must believe to its history, is sad.
You had to say it before to us.
Which thing is this?
Not to touch it!
This belongs to me!
Which thing.>.?
When   I count until 1…
Ready…
Left!
A smoke-producing one?
You come! Tried to take to me!
Scappato E' still!
That bastard!
It does not want to let go
It is not possible!
That speed!
E' impossible to catch up it…
Ce we will not never make to take it it.
Merda.... The next time, lascerò  not to scappare  to you easy cos  ì!
You have done good to come here.
I introduce myself! I introduce myself!
Been born and grown to Konoha, in the Country of the Fire,
I adore to eat of the Ramen from Ichiraku and my name is Uzumaki Naruto!
And the persons call to me…
The Ninja maldestro…
The Ninja maldestro. Eh!? it is not veroo!
I know to YOU well.
Jirochou head has the happy air, like always.
Ehi Naruto!
It leaves to be. A boy must be full of energy.
Now that there are introduces to you, we speak seriously.
Godaime Hokage has said that you will reveal us the details of our mission.
First of all,
You have felt to speak about the Race of Todori?
To.... To-I give.... Of that what?
You put yourselves comfortable.
The origin of this history…
laughed them to time it makes, and it begins with one legend.>.
A man, General Todori, made a rituale in order to guard the storms under its control.
He was decided to organize an event where its rituali were kept, every four years.
In principle, podistica contest was only one,
And all it was carried out pacifically.
But recently, the race has taken one different direction.
In the way of Tekarou, from the old times,
There were two groups, the Wasabi clan and the Wagarashi clan.
Unfortunately, these two clan never have not been in peace,
and they began to strike itself along the distance
Not only they, but also the countrymen were imply to you, and there were many wounded.
For being sure that all good went,
The getlteman have caught up an agreement.
Beginning from hour, we will not fight more, but we will make one challenge.
Therefore that this challenge is…
It is  the event that has every place four years: The Race of Todori.
Four years ago, the Wagarashi clan has cheated,
I have felt that they want to rifare it also this year.
This is the reason for which we have decided to call to you, and I have sent of the messengers to Konoha.
They have been attacks to you on the road.
Ve I pray some.
You help us.
We cannot lose the race against the Wagarashi clan.
Left that me of it I occupy!
And who we would have to escort?
Oh, accepted the mission?
You have called to me, Head?
Which thing, you know?
That  will facilitate the presentations.
It is not exactly that one.
Sai, Jirochou head is intelligent.
In truth, never it would not have been inchinato in front of you.
Even if it has been inchinato in front of me,
I do not have wants to escort a bastard like you.
Not even I!
I do not know that six kind fantino, but I would not head at your horse.
Which fantino!?
It watches that I.>.
a day,  I will receive  the title it of Hokage, and I  will be  the shining and intelligent Ninja, the great Uzumaki Naruto!
A Hokage is not nothing!
Your small head is not for nothing fantastic!
Idiot! Jirochou head is one brilliant person!
The Hokage risks their life and they are taken care of the village! They are of the Ninja fantastic!
Jirochou head is ready to giving its life in order protect the village.
He is  a large one
Grande
Great person!
A Hokage is fantastic
Fantastic
FANTASTIC!
But. it is only a giocattolo.... E' all cos ì  beloved here.
Me dispiace.  He is  too much beloved?
N-No, not a lot.
To say the truth, I do not want truly to sell them cos ì  beloveds…
But from when the Wagarashi clan has…
Ve I pray some, you have mercy of me.
With who creeds to speak?
You will not want to be rebelled to the Wagarashi Clan!?
Not not not!
But I have need to earn from the money.
We for you will guard!
Ehi!
S ì!
You stop yourselves.
A lot in order to begin, I will take  to you  to soccer in the culo!
Who.... you Who six?
You go yourselves some before that me innervosisca.
Getlteman, escaped! These men are of the Wagarashi Clan…
All good goes.
Bastard!
Ce we will go some from here. in order today.
But not to put to you in means to the feet, child more. You will do good to understand endured it!
The next one we will make pieces!
Via…
Getlteman…
Thanks thousands.
Much good!
We have the certainty that the square of Jirochou Head will win!
Sasuke-kun.
S ì.
Head!
You would not have had to call this Ninja di Konoha.
Not being contrariato, Idate.
They are not contrariato.
They are objective…
Idate, creed in you more than in anyone other.
The rest depends on you.
And if I had confidence in they?
Idate, you go to run for the village?
You I pray some.
Head…
S ì!
Even if the life will cost me.
I did not think that a lot important was a event!
But that race kind is?
Since you do not know it, I will explain  to you  as the race will be carried out.
The departure point is the Tegarashi port.
Once that the race has left we direct to Modoroki.
It is  Modoroki?
Exact.
We will use one boat in order to go to Modoroki. E' the faster means.
Beginning from here, the road  can  vary,
And it will be run until the end.
Here the rules.
Low Scorciatoie, blows, sabotaggi.. are all means allowed.
Then, to call of the Ninja does not go against the rules.
I ask myself as they are the Ninja employs to you from the adversaries.
They must hide and they must make attention.
Not to lower your guard, Naruto.
S ì!
You must watch to me from far away.
Not me continuations.
Which thing!?
I have said that I do not want to be disturbed!
You…
Well, well, we work entirety…
Who would want to work with he!?
Strange way would be said that these two are resembled, but in one…
Listened to all, the Race of Todori will begin soon.
The runner of the Wasabi, Morino Idate.
Morino.... Idate?
The runner of the Wagarashi: Hiyokuya Fukusuke.
To your places…
Start!
Much good we go!
Which thing!?
It escapes?
Where gone, Idate-saint?
Bastard Ehi! It waits for!
Which thing devil makes?
I have said to you to wait for!
The Believe your promised. It' s too hard to give me courage…
Allways, the feel it. The precious Time with you…
tachidomatta kata ni
asu he mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
machi not akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
futari tsutsumu kedo
sorezore ni chigau
kagayaki ga aruto
warau kimi ga
ichiban mabushiku mieruyo
yume wa ryuusei not you ni
ame agari not niji not you ni
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
mayoi tsuzukeru koto ga
hitotsu not kotae ni naruyo
gomakashitari shinaito chikao yo
Allways the feel it, the precious Time seeing you…
Next to that what thinks? This imbecille!
E' a lot, much fast one! It leaves the coast more quickly!
Merda! The adversary is already on the sea!
Cabbage! If the distance that divides them is too much large, it will not be able to recover!
That stupid! We must increase our speed, Sakura-chan!
We must make all the possible one in order to recover what we have lost!
The trap of the deep sea!
Naruto goes to bottom!?
Next episode