http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
We pass to the next encounter.
The new recruits seem
to know the fact they.
Evvai! evvai! evvai!
Thanks for the wait!
Arrived E' my turn!
That fortune!
Contr˜  of he will be one walk, Akamaru.
Now mostramiÉ
É improved how much six.
Ce I will make  it.
Akamaru to the attack!
Defeated who sara'?
Seventh encounter.
Uzumaki Naruto
Vs
Inuzuka Kiba
I was tired to wait for.
E' the moment to show my techniques!
You are zitto!
Against of you I have the Victoria insured.
Just Akamaru?
You are dreamming!
You will not never strike to me!
What!
Then it leaves the cucciolo outsideÉ
É that otherwise intralcerˆ to us.
Idiot! Akamaru fights with me.
But it is valid?
Sure, animals and bugs are thought crews.
You would have to know it.
It makes nothing!
E' the just advantage of which you have need.
You make the hard one, eh?
WellÉ
Akamaru, waits for to me here.
I manage alone.
Naruto! You do not have to lose with that braggart!
There are finally.
Naruto, eh?
Me dispiace, but it  cannot  strike Kiba.
É Kakashi.
Naruto-kunÉ
É I would want to make the tifo for youÉ
É but they are in the group of Kiba-kunÉ
É and Kiba could be angered,  butÉ
Naruto-kunÉ
Kiba-kun has been fortunate.
I do not know how much is improved
after to have become geninÉ
Today ripassiamo the Henge Not JutsuÉ
É you will transform yourselves in Hokage-Sama.
It was not a granche 'É
Henge!! (Transformation)
What happensÉ
É I was making a beautiful one sonnellino.
That one was only one joke.
I have made on purpose.
Not to take to me in turn, Naruto.
This is your third year of academy!
CabbageÉ
É but who is that one?
We have been fortunate to have changed class.
It has made one joke earning
the attention of all.
Circles of being amusing, eh?
It tries again to us, fool!
Henge!
And this would beÉ
Six in academy from three yearsÉ
É and you do not know to use the Henge decent?
Not to say cos “É
É why a day  I will be  Hokage!
Six stupid or what?
Tu Hokage?
I will strike  to you  with a single blow.
Ah is?
Then anch' I  will make  the same one.
I have said not to make the hard one to you!
WellÉ
É you can begin.
Gijyuu Ninpou, Shikyaku not Jutsu!
(WILD MAGICAL ART:
Technique of four legs)
Via!
The fastest E'!
Examiner, will not wake up itself for a beautiful one po '.
As I thought.
It was impossible that Naruto struck Kiba.
Naruto-Kun, than figuraccia.
Approval?
I did not make it cos “  insufficient.
Naruto-kun!
É
I will exceed  in ability all the HokageÉ
É cos “  all the inhabitants of the village
they will recognize my value!
I had not never believed, to its wordsÉ
Cos “  this is a Jonin?
A true one ninja.
I must scappare.
OtherwiseÉ
É IÉ
É I  will come  sure killed!
You are wellÉ
É fifone?
It becomes more strongly than me.
Damned!!!
Why… perchè you have made it?
The idiot and codardo that I have of foreheadÉ
É  he cannot  beÉ
É the Sasuke that I know!
Not to take to us in turn!
What!
But  I mistook myself.
HeyÉ
You are wellÉ
É fifone?
I not me rimangio the words.
This is my creed ninja!
NarutoÉ
É dillo to all!
You makeÉ
You make badlyÉ
É to underrate me!
It has acquired emergency.
Naruto-kun.>.
Force, Naruto!
Stupid!
You stop it to make the arrogant one!
I will strike  to you  easy!
I wanted to only see your abilities.
Test pure to use the cur or
what you want!
You of it you will repent!
We go Akamaru!
Smoke-producing bombs?
It pecks this to you!
I must exit from the smokeÉ
É or it will strike to me.
I do not succeed to see nothing.
Six falled to us.
What?
Eternal damnation cos “  is not looked at null.
Evvai! Ce you have made it!
Beautiful job, AkamaÉ
AkamaruÉ why?
Why?
Six falled to us.
Transformed youÉ!
Damned OuchÉÉ
v..via!
You have the sapore of a dog!
Akamaru, dov' and '?
E' here!
Akamaru!
Eternal damnation!
Incredible E' Naruto!
It is fighting at par with Kiba.
Indeed, it seems quite more fort.
Incredible E' that Naruto
it has used the Henge not JutsuÉ
É with the Kage Bunshin Not Jutsu.
It has had an optimal tempismo
in I use of the techniques.
E' better than how much you thought.
Truly interesting this NarutoÉ
É it is making to drive crazy the adversary.
Naruto-kunÉ!
Optimal movement, Naruto!
I admit that six improvedÉ
É but you do not have hopes.
Now  I will make  seriously.
Ah s “?
Then anch' I!
E' still improved more during this examination.
That beautiful surprise!
That one is indeed Naruto,
the worse one of the academy?
It does not seem the Naruto that we know.
Already.
As it has made Kakashi
in order to make to improve it a lot?
butÉ
É the force of Kiba and Akamaru
he is sure advanced.
Naruto
You are in order to give back my Akamaru to me!
WhatÉ
You have given what to it?
Why its hair is red.
Ecco perche' calls Akamaru
(red Aka =)
One pill?
KibaÉ
É you will end cos “  the encounter?
To the attack, Akamaru!
GIJYUU NINPOU
(wild magical Art)
Jyuujin Bunshin!
(wild Multiplication)
It has a terrifying expression.
This is dopping!
But it is valid?
É the pills have considered one instrument
From always the reason!
WhatÉ
É it has eaten?
* gunryo gandayo
Tonic from war
gunryo gandayo?
E' a secret medicine that allows
to the guerriero to fight for
three days and three nights without having to sleep.
Proteico and highly easy digeribile E'.
At the same time it has an effect
stimulating and reassuring.
The chakra of Kiba and Akamaru
temporary it is doubled
Hour  I will close  the encounter.
Via!
Technique ofÉ
É Gatsuuga!
Naruto!
Naruto is in danger.
The chakra of Kiba it encircles its bodyÉ
É ideal for he that it fights like one beast.
Those pillsÉ
É they are ideal for he.
Naruto-kunÉ
Cabbage!
Nothing to make.
Even if I concentrate all the chakra in the feet,
I only succeed in schivare its attacks.
At this rate it will have the better one.
Uncovered E'.
You take this!!
You they are much advanced one.
I mustÉ
É to become the next HokageÉ
É I cannot lose here.
You? Hokage?
But if six more weak person than me?
I  will becomeÉ
É Hokage for you!!
Within of you you know very well
that you will not never become Hokage.
Therefore  you stop it to repeat it.
Like six cruel one, Kiba-kun.
Naruto-kunÉ
É she is not cos “  weak person.
A dayÉ
É I will receive  the title it of Hokage!
You will see!
With the exception of me, Naruto always has
believed in the own forces.
I have always admired for thisÉ
É inasmuch as I understand how much is difficultÉ
É its training.
But  nobody has never tried to understand itÉ
É and to see the true Naruto-kun.
E' he that child.
E' be the only one to being bocciato.
It was a bond to null.
It would have been a disasterÉ
É if it had become ninja.
Why it is alone.>.
Zitta! Sai that it is forbidden to speak of.
No test to recognize the true Naruto-kun
Bushin not jutsu!
But  nowÉ
É all are watching it.
It raises To You, Naruto!
All will recognize its value.
If you want to compete with me for the title it of HokageÉ
É I will have  to defeat to you.
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII