You must use of the techniques using the head…
… otherwise he will be your adversary to use of you.
And then scemotto…
… it makes me the favor not falling
in obvious traps cos  ?.
The ninja they must anticipate the adversary!
I know anch' ' ste things!
Instead he is because you do not know to them that you I say.
Understood?
The movements are mistake to you for via of your impulsività.
Arrived E' my opportunity.
Finally it is uncovered!
Just six…
Waaah! You have centered!
Sasuke, wretch! You have exaggerated!
Maledizione! Of new the technique of the substitution!
From my attack it will have understood my position!
It has made feint to lower the guard!
They have fallen in its trap like a cretino!
Sasuke… where six!
Already it will not have been put
outside combat from the sensei!
Not! It will not never happen to Sasuke!
For a hair it is not shrewed of me!
Sakura, behind of you.
Eh!
"the ninja they must know to anticipate the adversary"?
That anger! I swear that not cadr ò  never more in one its trap!
Like not dettooo!
Bocciati? The decision of Kakashi!
Eh? Eh!
Cos' has happened!
Dov' is…
… the Sensei?
What has happened?
But that…
I do not understand!
Sakura…
Sasuke-kun?
Know. Sakura… To. Aiu.. Helps Me…
Perhaps I have exaggerated a pochino.
But it had to hold account if he were real or less.
That urlo…it was of Sakura.
According to foundation of the combats of a ninja,
it is that one of the Genjutsu.(Illusory Limbs)
The Sakura small is falled easy.
Genjutsu, eh? One risen of ipnotismo.
It does not astonish to me that with she it has worked.
For ò…
I am various from they.
Pits in you I would wait for to say it after to have taken a door-bell.
Sasuke-kun.
E' useless to try of the direct attacks!
One trap!
What!
But you it watches.!
That bastard! It does not leave me…
… the time not to read "the Paradise of the Pomiciata".
Uh? But that…
Hour memory! Sasuke-kun was in end of life and I…
Sasuke-kun! Not to die! Not to leave me!
Where seiii!
It watches that one looks at hung a tree…
There is from eating on that stone!
The ninja they must anticipate the adversary…
All adding I must say that various six from the others two.
Horse!
Tiger!
Katon Goukakyuu not Jutsu
(Technical of the Supreme Fire Ball)
What!
That one is one technical that a Genin
it would not have to succeed to use…
In theory it must not have the chakra sufficient!
Not there is!
Dov' is escaped!
Of side!
Up!
They are here under.
Thing.?
Doton Shinjuuzanshu not Jutsu!
(Element Earth: Decapitation kills)
The third foundation of the combats
of a Ninja it is the Ninjutsu. (magical limbs)
How you are? You cannot move, true?
I must admit that…
… you six fact to be worth.
Even if…
… one says that to caval that better it pulls,
toccan it gets worse to them scudiciate.
Eternal damnation!
Also without to me it are earned honestly it
taking a door-bell, I can eat the same one!
Good appetite!
Ehi!
I was alone joking.
Too much late!
Merda, is too much difference between of we.
Sakura.
It has cut the testaaa!
But that it takes to it?
Sasuke-kun?
But then six alive one!
Mollami!
It lacks little to noon.
I go.
Sasuke-kun, you still have intention
to take those door-bells!
Little ago I have grazes them to you,
the next time to take them ò.
Eh!
Indeed.?
Fantastic E' Sasuke-kun.
Maledizione! I not to never succeed ò
to take one of those door-bells.
Risk of having to separate to me from Sasuke-kun!
For ò, you know, by now not is more time
Even if this time ce we have not made it,
the next one you will see that it will go better.
Only I…
… I can kill that man.
Eh?
But who?
It speaks about the Sensei!
That time…
… cried.
Pianse..?
But…
… about that it speaks?
I am a vendicatore.
I must become more strongly than he.
I cannot be stopped now.
I want to kill…
… who I know.
Eternal damnation. We have wasted time speaking.
Sasuke-kun…
You feel you feel like brontolano your bellies.
I wanted dirvi that, considered this practice…
… nobody of you will have to return to the Academy of the ninja.
How? But I am alone svenuta…
Went well the same one?
The love always wins!
And you go!
YAH!!!
Then…
… it wants to say that we three…
Exact one. I want that you three…
… you stop of being of the ninja!
In… incredible…
It has not promoted neanche one student?
Iruka…
It will not be cos ì  if those three will have to become of the ninja effective.
The decision of Kakashi always has been corrected.
To stop of being ninja! What you would want to say!
I admit! True E'…
We are not resolutions to take the door-bell!
But because we would have quite
to stop of being ninja!
Why you are all of the inadatti plump children
to this profession.
Sasuke!
E' for that I say that you are of the pivelli.
Not to tread on Sasuke-kun!!!
But that idea you are made of the trade of ninja?
According to you because you have been uniforms
in groups for this practice?
What you would want to say?
In practical…
… you have not understood null
of the solution of this examination.
The solution!
Exact one. The solution that marks the outcome of the examination.
We thought that he was…
Stupiden…
You are stupid or what?
Understood because you are not in a group?
What enters there…
… that three persons are in group!
E'…
… THE SQUARE JOB.
It says to cooperate between of we?
Just cos ì.
But by now it is late although hour of it you have conscience.
You would even have taken the door-bells
if you had attacked to me in three.
But you have mistaken.
It waits for a moment…
Like it is made to head at the square job,
when ce two of door-bells are alone!
Even if we had tried to take the door-bells
with all our forces, one would be remained outside!
Other that square job!
There would be puttinges to litigate!
Sure!
The attempt of this examination is just that one makes you to litigate.
What!
In this way, we select those more capacities to the square job…
… that it does not give importance to the personal gain.
This was the objective…
For ò  you have made tutt' other.
Sakura…
You instead thinking next to Naruto that you had in front of you…
… you had in mind single Sasuke although you did not know neanche where it was.
Naruto!
You six rashly launch to the attack alone.
While you, Sasuke, have made the same game hermit
because convinced that the others two were only a weight.
A mission is executed with the entire group!
True E' that to a ninja serves…
… ability characterizes them advanced…
… but the square job assumes greater importance.
The individualismo that corrupts the square job
it puts in danger the companions, ending with killing them.
As an example…
Sakura! You kill Naruto or morirà Sasuke!
And it goes to end cos ì…
Oh! That fright…
… that you must take one impossible choice after that has taken to you
a hostage. And this door to the dead women of someone.
The rischiosi missions are job!
Watched here…
… all these names affected this slab…
… they belong to the ninja that in this
village comes calls heroes to you.
It appeals to to me! It appeals to to me!
Hour that I know it, I want to record my name…
… on that stone!
A hero! A hero! S ì, diventer ò  a hero!
For ò… whichever are not heroes.
Ah not! And that type of heroes is?
Then! Which heroes are?
Those who is said K.I.A.
K.I.A.?
Heroes Died in Mission.
This is one lapide.
Also the name of my better friend is recorded here over.
Hour…
… to give ?  a last possibility to you.
For ò  in the afternoon the fight for
the door-bells will be still more hard!
This challenge will eat only who chip ax.
But…
… dates not to eat to Naruto.
E' the penance in order to have tried to eat
alone going against the rules.
If the dates to eat…
… I disqualify to you from the examination.
Here the rules I them make…
Clearly?
Me excuses…
It listens, Iruka.
It does not import the result, not to take it to you with Kakashi.
S ì.
I am very well even if I do not eat!
I am very well!
…
Prendi.
Ehi..! Sasuke-kun!…
The Sensei has said to us…
Not to worry, I do not feel more to you its presence.
In the afternoon we will go to take the door-bells in three.
To empty stomach me it would be only of weight.
Sasuke-kun…
(Sakura-chan…)
Thanks…
You do not have ringraziar, eats how much you want to me.
for ò, uhm…
I was… they are to diet
Just like Sasuke-kun.
Cos ì  you do not have yourself to be worried.
For ò…
Vedi…
Sbrigati, we do not know when it will return.
Making ò  only for this time…
Only for this time.
Understood?
Understood!
VOIII!!!
You have smashed the rule!
You are ready for the punishment?
Your last words?
P… for ò…
AH?
For ò…
For ò…! For ò…!
You have said!
Here because…
… we three are one square, just?
S ì!
We three are one square!
! ! !
E' cos ì!
You would be one square, eh?
Promoted!
EH?
Promossi.
Promoted!
Because!!
You three are first.
All the children who have preceded to you did not make other
that to obey blind to all us ò  that I said they.
"a ninja he must know to anticipate the movements of the adversary"
In the world of the ninja, who does not respect
the rules come considered feccia.
For ò…
… who does not hold from account the own companions
… he is feccia of peggior the species.
The Sensei…
The Sensei Is…
The Sensei is a myth!
Your practice ends here.
You are all promoted!
From tomorrow Group 7 it will begin the true missions!
S ì, getlteman!
Ce I have made it!
They are a ninja! A ninja! A ninja!!!
We go to house!
Fantastic!
Ehi! I knew that I made this fine!
SLEGATEMIII!
Diamine!
We are making missions borings alone…
And I that I thought to make something of large.
For ò  the only one that we will accept it will be protect this old one.
It jokes on me, laughing to me in face
and saying that I have the face from idiot.
It must decide.
Old Ehi listens to me carefully!
Now I transform myself…
Ehi! You are listening to me! Eternal damnation!
In the next one understood it: Important Mission!
Towards the Country of the Waves!
You will not lack to see to me in action!