Subtitles By: BakaSan
Hyuga Hinata vs Hyuga Neji
Give up now. It's not your destiny to be a ninja.
Don't decide what the other person
is, dumbass! Beat this guy up, Hinata!
Hinata! Say something back to him! He's getting ME agitated!
Naruto-kun... Thank you!
Her eyes changed...
So, you won't forfeit... then I'm not
responsible for what'll happen to you!
I don't want to run away!
Byakugan!
Brother Neji... Let's fight!
HERE!
In front of the person she admires!
She's only at this level, just as I thought...
The power of the Souke(the main family).
What's going on?! Hinata's attack was perfectly landed, too!
Not yet!
What a guy!
It can't be...
Oh... He's indeed at the level to be called
the most genius in the Hyuga clan's history.
No, it can't be...
You were.. from the beginning...
That's right. My eyes are able to see Tenketsu(chakura points).
What is he talking about?
There are 361 points on the Keirakukei(chakura highway).
They're just about size of a needle point.
They're called chakura points.
Theoretically, if you hit these points
exactly, you can stop the opponent's chakura flow,
or increase the flow.
You can control it as you wish.
I'll tell you one more thing, since
I'm already explaining to you.
I'd have to say that even my
Sharingan can't see the chakura points.
Even though he can use his eyes to see in, I can't
believe he can spot their exact position during a battle.
Hinata-sama..
This is the difference that can't be changed.
The difference between losers and elites..
This is the reality that can't be changed.
At the time you said you don't want to run, your fate was set.
Now you're despairing.
This is the final warning.
Forfeit this battle!
I...
...don't...
...bend...
...my
words.
I won't run away!
This is also my Nindo(way of Ninja).
I didn't know Hinata was this amazing...
She is just like you.
Right... now I think of it, she's been always watching you.
Come on!
She's at her limit. If she takes any more of those attacks..
Neji's attacks to her chakura points have
stopped Hinata's chakura flow completely.
In other words, she can't do Juken attacks
that thrust chakura into opponent's body.
This battle is over.
But well.. I never imagined there was a guy like this. I have
to say that even Sasuke in my team won't be a good match for him.
I'd have to say that Neji will win this. It's
impossible for that girl's level to beat him.
What eyes... Hinata won't be killed, will she?
It's like.. his strength seems
to be unfair. Too strong.. Really
Hinata! Go for it!
Again, I can see her strength come back to her eyes
I've always been watching,
for so many years, I've been watching you
I wonder why...
Next, Uzumaki Naruto!
Dammit.. tiring
It's all your fault
Not mine...
Let's do it..
Naruto-kun... do your best.
Transform!
I don't know why, but...
My Name is Uzumaki Naruto! I won't lose to you all! Got it?
"I won't lose to you all"? Man...
How stupid. He makes everybody here his enemy in one second.
Looking at Naruto...
Stand Up! Naruto!
If you fight over the Hokage’s name, you'll be a looser!
I feel courage grow in me.
I start to feel like even I can
do it If I put my efforts into it.
I can start believing that even I am worth to something.
Hinata...
Who always falls into a habit of giving up, but you
started to try changing yourself along the way...
Hey Hinata. Let's go home now!
I know the most, that you've been training so hard.
but you always fail in missions. You were weak at
the time it counted the most, and easily depressed.
But... Today's Hinata is different.
I've never seen her eyes like that before.
Naruto-kun. Until now, I could only watch...
but now, I finally.. finally I...
You're a blockhead. Your attacks weren't
giving me any damages from the beginning.
It's over.
Hinata, that's enough. You may have lost
this battle, but you are different now.
You did great.
I want to change myself... that's why I voluntarily...
That was the Neji's final blow that attacked the heart.
I feel sorry, but she won't be able to stand up anymore.
I decide that this battle can't be no longer fought.
Don’t stop it!
I said, Don't stop it!
Hey, what're you saying Naruto! Stupid.
It's her limit. She's unconscious now...
Why do you stand up again?
If you overwork yourself, you're really going to die.
In front of the person whom I
admire...who finally starts to look at me.
Why?
I can't show him me like this...
Not yet!
Don't bluff. You can barely stand
up. I can see that with my eyes.
You were burdened the fate to be Hyuga clan's heir.
You've been blaming yourself for being weak.
But a person cannot change. It’s your fate.
There’s no need to struggle anymore. Give it up.
That's not true, Brother Neji.
Because I can see it.
Even more than I do, you're struggling.
What?
In the fate of Souke(the main family) and Bunke(the
branch of mainfamily), it's you who have been struggling.
Neji-kun. This match is already ended.
...not good.
Neji, stop it already. You promised me that
you won't get carried away about Souke things.
Why do other Jounins always come to
stop me? The Souke get special attention?
Hinata. Are you alright? Hey!
I ..
Was I ..
Was I able to change myself a little bit?
Hey, looser...
I'll warn you about two things.
If you are a real ninja, stop the
meaningless cheers for the others.
and one more... a looser is always looser. It'll never change!
You wanna try?
You..
I can understand your feeling very well.
But the battle should be fought in a match.
A looser will beat an elite with his efforts.
It's going to be fun in the real final exams.
It may be I who will fight against him.
There's no hard feelings, if you are the one to fight him.
Alright.
Wasn't that good? Guy sensei!
Lee! What a guy you are! Nice!
Not good. Her heartbeat is getting weaker.
Was he intending to kill her?
If you have time to stare at me, you'd
better use that time to look at her.
Medical Team! What're you doing! Quick!
Sorry!
Move her onto the strecher. Now..
She won't last 10 min. We need to move
her to the emergency room. Hurry up!
That's also my Nindo(way of Ninja).
I promise you that ...
I will win!
Perfect defense using sand?
No one ever has injured him before.
He's very strong and has no faults.
Those thick-eyebrow won't ...
He's not being pushed! He's way faster than
before. Is this the result of that training?
Next episode: Crash Gaara! It's Youth! It's Power! Explode!
But that training, I get a little envy.