Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking NFS
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh!  Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the fire!BANG!
Well, Gai…
I entrust Sasuke to your cures.
Jiraya-sama.
Please found Tsunade-sama and riportatela behind with you…
We will find…
And we will bring back it to the village!
Naruto-kun…
Me piacciono the brave boys like you.
I have a gift for you.
Lee has become stronger with this.
Eh? What? What ?
This !
Excellent E' in the perspiration and dispersing the sweat…
…  it is studied in order to facilitate the movements and designed with a look wonderful!
It wears in order to train to you and you will become account of the difference immediately!
You will not more succeed to less make some.
To the end, you will want to always have I lean it like Lee.
Just as I make!
Instead carrying behind one "similar what to you", it would be better that you had with you one mirror…
Idiot!
How me he will be…?
You stop it. Watches well gives it behind…
E' truly orrendo…
Well, we have arrived.
What?
This is  the casino  more beloved of the country…
Then true that it has been trying Naruto.
"Kidnapped Naruto "
These are the orders that we have received from the Akatsuki.
What happens?
You feel, Ero-Sennin…
Why those types were trying to me?
Ero-Sennin, you know it, you are not true?
What they are trying in truth not six you…
But what you have within of you.
Then it is this which they want?
It is not perhaps the monster that has attacked Konoha?
Here why they are all only scare to you also to name it…
Why… those tizi are trying it?
It is narrated that the Kyiubi joins periodically in the history of the humanity…
Kyiubi: Demon Vixen to Nine Tails
E' a Youma that destroys every thing you meet in its way.
Youma: leggendari demons equip you of immense being able
Because of this, in passed people considered the Kyiubi one catastrophe.
You ask to me why those persons are trying it…
Honestly, I do not have the minimal idea of what they have in mind to make.
But…
Until that the Kyiubi will remain sealed within of you…
They will try to get hold of for being able to control it.
Dispiace to say it to me, but they will not surrender a lot easy.
E' your destiny…
But I you  proteggerò, not to worry to you…
Then I must become stronger, quickly!
Perfect!
Sbrighiamoci to find Tsunade…
We carry it from Sasuke, and then we will be able to finally begin my training!
Finally that one is returned always…
Episode #86
To the search of the acquaintance
I will succeed  to become stronger!
Qu..Questo is  the casino  with the higher mail…
Six too much frightening one.
Giocatrice
of hazard
I go.
Please… you wait for to me!
That there is?
The that beautifulst woman about which she speaks to me to you…
E' this Tsunade?
Oh? Six just wide awake one.
Then, that you want to know?
Therefore, Ero-Sennin, also it is one of the three Sannin like you, is not true?
Sannin: ninja leggendari
, why?
How many years it has?
My age.
One old…
This is…
You could please change to all these moneies in chips?
Eh.. wants to make it truly…
Who is this woman?
You do not know it?
It has a nickname.
A nickname?
Then, than person kind it is this Tsunade?
Hmm? It interests to you?
We see…
In order to say it in short, I would define it unpleasant.
Moreover it is fixed with the gambling…
For this it is known in all the countries.
Then we will be able to find it easy! Inasmuch as it is much famous one…
Sure famous E'…
The leggendaria…
Motoshimi, which is its nickname?
The leggendaria?
They are all laughing!
The leggendaria…
Losing!
But even if it is the "Losing Leggendaria "…
It will not be much easy one to find it.
Why?
It dislikes to age…
Sure now she will have changed its aspect with one of its special techniques.
Even if it is a cinquantenne, are sure that she will have the aspect of one ventenne.
Moreover, they have said to me that lately it changes often its aspect…
Adolescent…
Trentenne…
Forty-years old, in order to escape to its creditors.
That history! Truly absurd.
Tsunade has always loved the gambling than more every other thing.
But never he has not been skillful in the games neither fortunate.
They have affibbiato that nickname inasmuch as it has always lost against anyone.
Always scappata E' after to have accumulated credits of game.
How many memories…
Hey, is not the moment for the memories!
How we make to find it?
Not  the sò…
We can only continue to try it, are very many places to control.
Ehhh !
If this is your strategy could put very many time, not creeds?
We will not waste time,  but.
I will dedicate myself  to you during the dead times of the travel!
To me?
The only system in order to render more fort you…
Training!
Optimal!
Not not not…
You do not have need of that one… we go…
I do not have intention of having to my flank someone with that ridicule coveralls.
Hey hey, Ero-Sennin! Sbrighiamoci! We begin the training!
Not to be much impaziente.
We must before think to collect information on Tsunade… It is not still the moment to train itself.
To collect information?
In this city.
It waits for!
Fantastic!
E' before the time that I come in a place like this.
E' important also to amuse itself, we will remain here for the night and we will begin the training tomorrow.
The festivity will last still some day…
Until then we will remain in this city.
I will follow  your training here.
Yatta!
Oh! You have many moneies in the portamonete, six much rich one!
I have many moneies why I have put from part little little the moneies of the missions…
We look at ourselves!
It waits for Naruto!
I  of yours will have cure portamonete.
Eh, what you are making?
This would have to be enough to you today in order.
What!? Only 300 Ryo!
Not to say cos ì!  You would have to know that 3 sins exist that a shinobi would have to avoid to commit.
3  sins forbidden to the Shinobi?
About what you are speaking?
What? You do not know it?
They are the 3 things that every Shinobi would have to avoid along its way.
It remembers you to avoid the Sake…
The women…
And the moneies.
Well, they are things that they do not try to me at all…
I do not have still twenty years therefore I cannot drink, and…
Still I do not succeed to understand what have a lot interesting the women…
Moreover I do not have intention of sperperare what I have put from part with much hard work.
Idiot!
Not to underrate the power of the money!
You will not be able more to make some less!
The attraction for the money is one terrible what!
The Tsunade that we are trying risks continuously to ruin its life for guilt of the moneies.
Ero-Sennin attracted you instead always six from the women.
Now  I will begin  to ask in turn information.
You instead take my bag.
If you had to lose to you, you can evoke a "rospo seeker": he will lead you from me thanks to its olfatto one.
E' still a child although its aspect.
Well.
Per.primo.cosa  I will fill up  my stomach.
Getlteman! I can have of the Takoyaki!
Takoyaki: polpette of pastella of polpo (literally piovra to the slab)
Eccolo!
Potatoes to the butter!
Perfect!
I would want one banana to the chocolate.
Eccola.
I would want also a Anzuame!
Anzuame: a type of cake makes with fruit sand bank and liquid sugar
You hold!
I would want a Okonomiyaki!
Okonomiyaki: frittati some cooked together to of the meat or the fish
Eccolo! Careful that scotta!
Getlteman, I can have one Yakisoba with of the sauce?
Yakisoba: spaghetti Japanese to the slab
It arrives! I see that you have bought a lot roba to eat…
You you will not eat at all all alone?
Eh? I do not see what is badly.
Here.
I have eaten a po' too much.
I ask what are making the others…
Kakashi-Sensei…
Sasuke…
Sakura-Chan…
I will train myself  more hardly possible, and to my return they will find very more fort to me.
You wait for to me.
But before then, I must smaltire the stuffed oneself one.
Last one (last)!
! Perfect!
The training with the shuriken has carried its yields!
Uhh…
Ragazzino..sei one schiappa!
Eternal damnation… now you will see.
It waits for.
The shinobi they cannot use the Ninjutsu.
Here.
E' dangerous to go in turn wearing one mask.
Book of the Budgets
from 1237
Jiraya
_________________________
The book of the budgets of Ero-Sennin…
1… 10… 100…
There are one tide of zero!
Inasmuch as it possesses cos ì  many moneies why not me it has some leaves you a little more…
Spilorcio!
Me they remain little spiccioli… I will spend  them  all in the next store.
The only system in order to render you more fort… the training!
Getlteman! I can have two Ikayaki!
Ikayaki: fish to the grill
Me of it make one more large, for an adult.
Hey child! Me it seems a likeable type! Smallest you the gift!
You hold.
Thanks getlteman! Fantastic E'!
Kind Oh that! Well! I will give   the more large fish to you metà.prezzo!
Oh, thank you!
Eternal damnation, where will be ended?
The voice of Ero-Sennin?
Which beautiful girls, eh?
Oh, Naruto !
You have already ended to amuse you to the festivity?
Why you do not repeat "the 3 Forbidden Sins of the Shinobi" once again !?
Six successful one to smash them all in once single! Idiot!
Oh… It waits for according to Naruto…
I cannot wait for!
Six successful one to spend all the moneies that I had saved with much hard work!
You take this! And this! And still this!
Stopped.
I will reimburse  to you!
You have emptied mine rospo portamonete!
Hey! What been arranging here within?
You have spotted the signed coat of my brother!
You must repay it to it! Give 100' 000 ryo immediately to us!
That coat costs 100' 000 ryo!?
Not thoughts that 100' 000 ryo are po' too many for a dress ridicule like that one?
You are trying to provoke to me?
You would better make to stop it immediately.
My brother is a Chuunin of the Village of the Stone, known and respected like the ninja of the shadow!
Ah! Known? Indeed?
It seems that you have not still understood!
Naruto…
This is an optimal opportunity in order to show the technique to you that you must learn.
It watches carefully.
You take this!
Fantastic!
I have tried to make slowly… But you two are just of the schiappe.
You are… the leggendario.>.
Dispiace… I have destroyed your stall to me.
You take these like compensation.
Thanks.
Old… already that there are  I will take  to all your water balloons, of agreement?
It does not interest to me.
It has not been only a blow with the palm of the hand.
What was that technique then?
Naruto.
You come with me, this is your training.
!
Finally the training begins!
You take this, is a water balloon.
Eh? What I must make us?
You have observed the technique carefully that I have used before?
Which type of technique I have used according to you?
It was like if the enemy roteasse violentemente…
It was not watching in the just place… But task that can have understood…
, one species of spin.
The water within to the balloon is roteando without movements of the hand?
During the training on the trees, six concentrated and you have maintained the chakra to you.
In the training on the water, six successful one to free one constant amount of chakra.
You have carried out these two sin' hour, just?
Now, with the training of the water balloons, you will learn to create a flow of chakra.
In short, one spin.
A flow of chakra?
, when you succeed to learn the bases, I will explain you   the other particular well in detail.
For first, you make like if you walked on the trees, the aim to maintain the chakra in your hand.
Then it uses the training with the water, in order to free one constant amount of chakra…
With this training, you will succeed to push and to make to roteare the chakra in the water of the balloon.
I have understood!
Until to that the balloon does not explode… I must make circular the water possible, more fastly true?
You are becoming more and more perspicacityes!
Well! Today we will train ourselves until to the sunset!
Getlteman!
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete
I will succeed  to make to explode this balloon does not import like!
Oh! That indomito spirit!
I waited for many optimal ones turns out to me to you from you.
The roteante water!
Well, when it succeeds to make to explode the balloon?
Next episode:
It goes well!!!  I will make  to explode this balloon!
The will force!!
You break off the water balloon!
Why I do not succeed to make to explode it?