Subbed by # [ Fabry ]
Chekked by Shinji 89
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not
fukinukeru Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda Yeah!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite
kanashimi mo hoho tsutatte
namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa
tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Episode #123
Here the green beast of Konoha!
Merda.
It does not import how many times me attacks.>.
you will obtain always the same result!
Far from negligible.
Not only six wide awake one,
but you have also the balls.
And not only. I have also good heart…
To hit one defenseless woman
she goes against mine princ ì devout.
But, you me do not seem of all the defenseless one.>.
Therefore in this case…!
Not to excite to you in order to only have melted the illusion.
Head of I haul!
Still I do not succeed in bloccarla.
Merda.>.
I   will not be defeated!
Still a po '..
That cabbage of chakra is this!
Although its state
it still succeeds to overwhelm to me.
But if I let to go it is the end.
To how much it seems  I will have  to use this
technique in order to place aim to the crash.
You hold hard, Akamaru!
Eternal damnation! But that it is happening?
Eternal damnation!
Of it one lacks only.
This type. he is maledettamente strong!
They are not successful to dargli a single blow,
neanche with all those cloni!
E' nearly hour…
The first step towards the realization
of the ambitions of Orochimaru-sama.
Sasuke.
Sasuke!
Which you make cabbage us with these types?
You give We return behind.
Sasuke?
But…
We go via.
Ok!
We are arrives both to you in top!
I want to fight also against of you.
Hey. Andiamo via.
They are all preoccupied for you.
Here why…
Sasuke!
Sasuke-kun…
You I pray filler Sasuke-kun behind!
You feel to me, maledizione?
It waits for, Sasuke!
Useless E'.
You die.
Who six?
The rinato student.>.
The green beast of konoha!
Rock Lee!
S-Sopracciglione!
Sopracciglione… but your body?
Not preoccuparti, Naruto-kun.
You follow Sasuke!
But… you…
For favor. it leaves it me.
This boy is strong.
Sopracciglione you are careful.
USA the own boneses in order to attack!
The own ones…
… boneses?
This type. E' truly strongly.
What you are making?
Sbrigati to go!
Naruto-kun…
I have made a promise to Sakura-chan
with it puts down it from figo, not?
I will bring back  Sasuke for all once!
I promise with all the heart!
I will defeat  this person.
You I promise!
Tasks that I you allow?
You die!
Not to ignore to me.
Sopracciglione…
You do not have time in order to watch to you elsewhere!
Aspect one your reaction!
But…
supposing that Sasuke
it was in that barrel.>.
To send a composed team they only give
genin it has been rather imprudent.
We jounin have even reduced ourselves cos ì
after to have fought with they…
We would have to send one
squarda special of support.
I cannot make it!
To continuation of the attack of Orochimaru
Konoha has lost part of its power.
You are to the current of the situation.
We have sended the chuunin and jounin
to resolve the problems to the inside
and to the outside of our country.
If also the sharingan it fell
in the hands of Orochimaru…
Our priority hour is to avoid
the war with the other nations.
But. the issue of Orochimaru…
matter is not one that
it can  ignore so much to along.
If riusciranno to recover
forces will return newly.
I know.
They are not one unprovided.
Already I have considered, and I have already
supplied to make something.
Down here!
What happens, Gai?
A six disaster.
E' succeeded something during the mission?
Not As soon as ended the mission they are
returned here more in a hurry that I have been able.
But, still more important. Lee!
Lee!
As its operation has gone!
E' be happening!
It will be able to begin the training tomorrow.
But calm for a po will have to be taken it '.
terrible N-N-news, Fifth hokage!
Rock Lee is scomparso!
Nooooo!
I will end  to you  with the next movement.
Merda!
It must be escaped while
medicavo Genma and Raidou.
Lee…
That stupid.
What has follows them?
Rather confused E' also…
It has exchanged mine sakè for its
medicines and have carried it with if.
Sake!
N-Non goes well!
What happens, Gai?
Here the truth.>.
… when Lee drinks also
only a goccio of sake…
He becomes terrible!
Terrible?
Konoha From The Senpuu!
E' much skillful one…
It has not hit it not even a soccer.
Six agile, rather true one?
Your movements are much precise.
Six much spigoloso.>.
just like your name.
[  Kimimaro refers to name of Lee
written in Katakana alphabet: E' more
spigoloso of the other Japanese alphabets  ]
Ended E'.
It waits for, I pray to you!
It pardons to me,
I must take my medicine.
Dispiace, but I must take it to me.
Only a moment…
It is not never piaciuto to take medicines to me.
Succeeded E' when I carried Lee to the restaurant
in order to celebrate the income in academy.
It has exchanged mine sake for water…
Of it it has drunk only a goccetto,
and it has been transformed in something of orribile!
Something of orribile?
Like the quiet ones after the storm…
When then I returned…
the restaurant…
completely it was destroyed!
The medicines have always a strange taste.
What will have drunk?
The destroyed restaurant?
What you want to say?
The truth …
Tsunade-sama…
Lee.>.
… traforma in a drunk outside control!
And you who devil six?
But who cabbage !
Uhmp, bastard…
Therefore, it comes to it natural…
… to use the technique of the Fist of the Drunk.
Sasuke!
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
bokura kara shaberi kaketure
meiwaku ni omou kara
sonna fuan wo kakaetie
yuuki wo dashite mitayo
umaku shaerinai bokuno
bukiyou na hanashi
kimi wa mimi wo sorasazuni
chanto kiite kuretayo
soredaked bokuwa ukarete shimaunosa
dakedo kimi wa boku nante
nantomo omottenai yone
setsunai yo
dakedo
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
hajimete kimi to shabereta
Six fallen in my trap!
Qual' was my plan?
This is called
to hide the secret plan of one shinobi.
Gai-sensei, ce I have made it of new!
But. That it happens! It turns to me all…
I feel that  I will not lose!
Next episode:
The outbreak of the wild beast.
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Enjoy:p