Subtitles By: BakaSan
Where the fuck is this?!
I was saved.
Incredible!
It seems a little too huge.
That's right...
Is this...
a frog, right?
Let's see...
No Tail!
This is...
not something like this...
or something like that.
It is a true
real frog!
Jump! Fly! Dive! Gama Oyabun Appears!!
This time I see...
he was able to pull Kyubi's chakura with his own will.
But,
I can't say it's stable.
He used too much chakra.
And of them all, he summoned him...
I did it!
You little punk!
You punk!
On whose head do you think you are sitting on?!
This is the head of Gamabunta-sama...
aka Gama Oyabun! This fool!
Be quiet!
What's up with him?
He's so powerful.
It's been a long time and I want to enjoy the air of the...
outside world, but a wierd kid is making noise on my head.
Hey, Jiraiya!
Where's Jiraiya?!
What the fuck do you want from me?!
This is not good.
Even I can't deal with Gamabunta.
Jiraiya! Hurry up and show yourself, asshole!
It's gonna be a big hassle if Gama finds me.
I'd better get away from here quickly.
Hey, you punk.
Y..yes!
Where's Jiraiya?
Jiraiya? Who?
The perverted middle aged man who call himself Gama Sennin!
Where's Jiraiya?!
Scary...
If you obey what I say without arguing...
I might think of making you my subordinate.
Answer me already!
Yes sir!
Ero Sennin is on top of this cliff, Gama
Oyabin! (oyabin = oyabun + naruto's own twist)
At the top eh?
Ah... May I ask you one question, please?
What?
What do you want from the Ero Sennin?
That's what I wanna ask him, that Ero Oyaji! (perverted oldman)
What's he thinking summoning me at place like this!
Ah... but...
What?
It's me who summoned Gama Oyabin...
I thought I needed a little help because I fell off the cliff.
Yeeeessss!
You punk, I was wondering when you were going to start talking.
It's impossible for a little kid like you to summon me.
It's true! It's really true that I summoned you!
This fucking frog!
Just because I've been modest to you,
you're saying whatever you feel like!
Because I summoned you, I'm your master! Got it?!
What? Who do you think you're talking to, huh?!
A kid who can't drink a cup with sake...
is telling Gamabunta-sama that you're his master??
You! Shut the fuck up!
I guess they came up on the surface.
Wow... Huge...
Hey kid!
By yielding one hundred steps, no ten thousand steps to you,
and even if you really did summon me,
I won't accept you, who easily
fell off from my back, as my master.
Anyway... it's been a long time
since coming to the outside world...
If Jiraiya doesn't have anything to do with
me, I guess I'm gonna hang around a while.
Hey, Wait!
Go home and sleep.
It looks like you won't even be fit for my subordinate.
Shit!
What're you doing, punk?!
If you accept that I summoned you by me
not falling off from your back, then...
I won't get off from here for a whole day even you make me.
What?
And, I'll make you accept that I'm your master!
This punk!
You grow vain just because I've been nice to ya.
Get Off!
Stick with chakra.
I don't have enough chakra!
Listen carefully, you, Gama Oyabin!
My name is Uzumaki Naruto.
Remember me as a future Hokage!
Who cares!!!
This is getting very interesting.
Sorry Naruto, but I am going back to my "work".
Gathering material!
Let's eat!
Those guys going to Korean BBQ again.
A reward for training seriously, eh?
I thought we were told not to lose sight of Gaara.
Don't worry. Even he ...
won't do anything funny in full daylight.
By the way, that Shikamaru is the one who match
up with you at first round, if I remember right.
Don't you need to plan something for the battle?
I won't lose to a guy at that level... Besides...
Unfortunately...
If we took this exam a year earlier,
we could've been Chunin easily.
Don't say that.
What did you just say?
The Sand village will send three
of you to take this Chunin exam.
But it's not for making you pass the chunin exam.
It's to crush Konoha village by
taking advantage of the Chunin exam.
Why?
Don't we have an alliance treaty between Konoha and Sand?
The alliance treaty is the problem.
What do you mean?
I don't think you gennins know much, but...
Upon concluding the treaty, that
idiot Daiymo of Kaze country...
forcibly pushed forward a military reduction
plan on us, the hidden Sand village.
He asked Konoha to do requests, which
should've been brought to us. In addition,
he cut the budget for the village and
the number of shinobi's in a large scale.
When a head is stupid, the ones
who suffer is us, the arms and legs.
Our village had no other choice but bring up the quality
of each shinobi to keep the same level of military power.
That's why a shinobi like you were created, Gaara.
Now, the Kaze country is in a very
dangerous situation for its security
But that Daimyo and his aids don't understand it.
Kazekage sama, who fear the declining
of militar power of Hidden Sand,
decided to crash Konoha in cooperate with Hidden Sound
At the same time of recovering the dignitiy of Sand,
it's to let the stupid daimyo learn the
importance of security control of this country.
If we wait any longer, the Sand will completly
lose the military power to go against Konoha.
There's no other time than now.
This mission is all depnds on your work, Gaara.
yes.
Once the plan is carried out,
it's going to be a war with Konoha.
It's gonna be a war again?
Breaking the aliance treaty, which was
created with so much sacrifices, and ...
again so many people will die.
Hey, Temari
Everything is Kazekage sama's will.
Kazegage sama's...
After all, Shinobi are just a tool for a quarrel.
It turned out that the alliance treaty
was just to threat our existance.
This is super A rank mission. Do it with care.
Yes sir.
A day seem to be very long when doing nothing.
thats true...
Man, this is a tenacious kid.
Oh man... Naruto seems to be struggling.
He should've used up almost all
of his chakra to summon Gamabunta.
Look! Look! It's beautiful. It's a rainbow!  Wonderful!
Yes, yes. It's wonderful.
Kaze
Thank you, Baki.
As planned, all three safely moved
foward to the final exams, Kazekage sama.
There's no problems about the agreement with Sound, right?
Yes.
This is the action plan of the Sound.
You have anything else?
No.
What is it? Tell me.
Yes.
I would like you to have forces close
to the border pretending to be maneuvers.
Only four of us are...
Konoha isn't stupid.
Their Anbu's are moving around.
If we do such thing, our plan will be clearly leaked out.
But with the current war potential...
That's why I chose Gaara and the others to go.
The recovery of the Hidden Sound village's
dignity is decided by your teams work.
Now, go.
Yes.
Just a little bit longer...
If I don't fall off from here until the sun completely sets,
I'm your master!
Who cares! You started to say that. Not me.
I will never fall off!
Naruto should've already exceeded his limit a long time ago.
It's not a surprise if he fall off soon.
It's ok to ignore what the kid says, but it
irritates me a little bit to be underestimated.
I guess I'm gonna settle this already.
Kid, what was your name?
Naruto! Uzumaki Naruto!
Uzumaki Naruto, eh?
Naruto, don't hold a gridge against me even if you die!
Gamabunta is getting a bit stubborn now.
This isn't good.
No! The place where the young girl's have fun...!
Just a bit longer... I won't fall off!
What?
Naruto channeled more chakra from that condition.
I'm gonna fall!
See, Gama Oyabin! I'm still on your back!
I won!
Damnit! He'll die if he falls like that!
What a shame! It was just a little bit longer.
I didn't think he would stick to Gamabunta this long.
Jiraiya... it's not neccesary...
I know that this boy summoned me with his own power.
Anyways, this is the first one to
sit on my head since the Fourth.
Indeed, he must be emtpy.
I can share my energy, but it's best to take him there.
What?
The deserted hospital room.
An uninvited visitor.
The vision of childhood days.
A daydream that keeps coming back.
When the forbidden door is opened...
He appears.
Next episode. Steal up Evil hand! Hospital room Targeted
Who's the next victim?