Subbed by Shinji 89
Chekked by [ Fabry ]
http://narutofansub.altervista.org
Hikarabita Kotoba or tsunaide
sovedemo boku not shinpuvu na
omoi or tsutaetai dake na not fukinukeru
Kusunda ano hi not kaze wa
kinou not haikyo ni uchisustete
kimi to warau ima or ikiru noda YEAH!
sovedemo kono dekigoto wa
kimi not kurushimeru darov
dakara koso sayonara nanda
kono mama dwaries mo nokorazu ni
anata to wakachi an dake
yagate bokura wa
sove ga endured from to kigatsuite kanashimi mo
hoho tsutatte namida or kawa ni naru dake
yureru omo wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte
take an not yo
Baby
Muoviamoci.
They are near!
The adversaries are still two.
while we are in three.
We are three against two.
If ce we play it well,
this could be the last crash.
We go allora!Forza!
Ce we will make it!
Not! We are four against two!
Sure, sure…
Scusami… four against two.
This time we will close in a hurry
the game with our technical new!
Ah ?
Then I could execute a Kage Bunshin
of dimensions never seen before!
Then that we can be calm.
But  per.primo.cosa my plan is respected.
You have understood?
Remembered that we must find them before the sunset.
, I know it!
We increase the step!
The sun is tramontando.
Jiroubou and Kidoumaru are not returning.
Task that is making more hard work of the previewed one.
Who if of frega.
We must before think
to our Orochimaru-sama getlteman
In average day we have covered
only a third party of the route.
They have all of seals cursed.
The other time you have picked to us of surprise,
but it will not be repeated.
There are too many interferences.
Eternal damnation.
We do not know not even if we will make in time.
Eternal damnation, we have not still caught up them!
Not, it goes well.
We must only continue to hold the same one
distance between of we, and to continue to follow them.
What you are saying ?
It means that we must avoid whichever
crash before that the sun rises.
you stop it to lose time in sciocchezze!
How you make rilassarti a lot ?
It has reason!
We are trying to attack them, would not be
better to make taking advantage of it the dusk?
The dusk will be an advantage for we
when we must attack.
In that moment,
to take Sasuke and to scappare to the sure one
it will be nearly impossible.
If we will not succeed to take endured it,
they will increase the defense of the barrel.
This means that we will succeed
to act in the shadow.
From that moment they will not waste more energies.
If we had had the byakugan it would have been an other history.
Hey, hey six forgotten to you about Akamaru and my olfatto one ?
I have already put R-on account your abilities,
but they are stronger than we.
If  I will not be able  to use my technique,
it will be totally useless.
If I used the Kagemane in order to stop them,
and one cloud bloccasse the moonlight
the effects would vanish.
There are too many risks.
But cos ì -
I will make!
Naruto!
You the six head!
I will follow  your orders, Shikamaru.
, it makes it please.
Episode #118
The rescue!
We must arrive in time to the barrel!
Hey Tayuya,
ce we will make it in time ?
We must carry Sasuke-sama within tomorrow.
In order tomorrow, eh ?
I am not saying that he will be simple,
but task that we will succeed ourselves.
, ce we will make it.
Orochimaru-sama.
Sasuke....
Sasuke still has not arrived ?
Not there is more time.
By now it is to the limit.
Orochimaru-sama,
if it is a body that you want some we have very many to disposition.
and in the case…
Not, I want only Sasuke.
How many tasks that it has waited for ?
But we are in one emergency situation!
The technique of maledizione of the 3 Hokage is more strongly of the previewed one!
Its maledizione is too much strong!
You take this!
Fuuin Jutsu!
Shiki fuujin!
What happens?
You take this!
My arms…
if you do not decide to be reincarnated now,
risked to lose all!
You want this !
To lose all !
I have prepared of the optimal ones chosen.
Trusted you me please!
After  I will take care myself  also of the recovery of Sasuke.
I will use  Kimimaro.
That you are cursed… Sandaime!
Release!
You listen to me well!
You fight some finchè will not remain only one.
Sopravviverà who will be able to exit of cell.
As I thought,
they have not been called not even this time.
Kabuto-sensei.
I…
You it thinks next to your body.
You have already carried out your role.
That one by now is one square of four elements, and you of six outside.
I am… still…
Your successor already has been found.
Moreover… its force equals yours seals of the earth,
inasmuch as it it has been donated I seal of the sky.
I asked who for you two is strongest.
What takes to you!
You do not have to be churned…
Kabuto-sensei…
How much me remains living?
Better E' if it does not speak more.
The persons are born for one reason....
.... in the life they have a task important to acquit.
Here why I have understood.
The meant one of the life…
is to find one scope....
it is the only freedom that of i
they have granted to the men.
I understand  that  that you want to say.
Effectively our getlteman
Orochimaru-sama is suffering,
it crosses a condition that has not never experimented.
But  I will be  frank…
what you could make reduced like six ?
You have already lost your value like container.
Hour is a new container....
that one is heading towards the village.
Bè, even if is already too much late.
You had said that you would have let out me!
I ask that the promise comes maintained!
What you are waiting for ?
You move to open that door!
Still ?
You  I will make  endured -
It does not go well....
… it will divorerà to me!
I will let out  you  from here.
Moreover  esaudirò  also an other desire.
I ask you to free my clan
that you had captured for your experiments.
It will be made.
Not preoccuparti. This your strong will
it will continue to survive within of me.
All it will not go lost.
Then I take your body.
For some year it will have a body
in which the resurrezione will not work.
But  there will be an other occasion.
Effectively…
… I am not worth null like container
for the technique of the resurrezione.
Having lost all…
… it was difficult to find the scope to me of my life.
Hour  but  they are successful finally
to understand which it is.
Even if  I will not make  from container,
I  will be to carry that new one here.
Also to cost of living....
E' my thanks for
my getlteman, Orochimaru-sama.
E' the last thing that  can  make a useless being like me.
It waits for a moment!
We are already in proximity?
Not, it still wants much to us.
Rather…
What has arranged those cretini of Jiroubou and Kidoumaru !
We have caught up to you!
And it goes well!
I will kill  to you  in four and quattr' eight!
Cos ì  to the unexpected one ?
You take this!
Kareken!
The chakra on its hand ?
Kage bunshin, eh ?
Rasengan!
My hand!
I have stopped to you before that you can make
whichever thing. Useless E' all!
Kiba, hour!
Tsuuga!
It was only a clone!
These smidollati small have joined for a direct onslaught.
They aim for a long time at this!
Not to think to go some to you via cos ì  easy!
Merda…
I feel myself in trap!
The Kagemane jutsu is not successful.
Small piece of merda…
It is coming!
Tayuya, what you are making l ì  impalata ?
Not!
What you are making!
I cannot avoid it!
You take!
Perfect!
Kiba! Shikamaru!
Shikamaru! We must move!
Bastards!
Smidollato small, what you have dared to make ?
As I have said before, they
they have a heap of possibility.
They have distracted themselves too much.
Gone E' all good!
, all the second plans
The first one of the two passages
previewed it is completed.
I do not want to take you boys, gone via!
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
bokura kara shaberi kaketure meiwaku ni omou kara
sonna fuan wo dashite kakaetie yuuki wo mitayo
umaku shaerinai bokuno bukiyou na hanashi
kimi wa mimi wo sorasazuni chanto kiite kuretayo
soredaked bokuwa ukarete shimaunosa
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yone
setsunai yo dakedo
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de
hajimete kimi to shabereta
kimi wa waratte kureta
boku not kono kotoba de!
hajimete kimi to shabereta
Eternal damnation, we have walked too much, and has arrived a boy…
I have a prefeeling… is not a normal boy.
Cosè this brivido along the back ?
Now we are of the same number… 2vs2
But… this is…
Me dispiace naruto.
This boy is outside from your capacity.
Next episode:
Errore!Un a new enemy!