Sasuke's movement has stopped..
But there's still a little ways to go.
We finally caught up to him..
Sasuke..
Alright!
This smell..
What is it?
Did something happen to Sasuke-kun?
I didn't notice until now, but..
You and I use the same shampoo!
That floral green scent..
..there's no mistaking it!
Hey you!
But I have shinier hair.
Don't bring up a ridiculous thing like that now!
I use the same as a dog..
- Sorry, sorry.
Same as a dog..
..same as a dog..
..same as a dog?
- Sakura-chan?
Same as a dog..
Sakura-chan..
wait!
Hey! Don't go ahead of me!
The mistake of Hokage
The real face under the mask
Shit!
Uchiha.. Sasuke
I won't let you escape.
Of all people, this guy shows up while Gaara's in this condition.
This is the worst case scenario.
Alright then.
Kankuro, take Gaara and go ahead!
I'll take care of him.
But Temari..
against him, one opponent isn't enough.
Don't worry. This mission is important to the Sand.
Gaara is your first priority.
Plus, this guy is kind of my type.
Go, Kankuro!
I won't let you!
You won't get away.
Take this!
My opponent is Uchiha.
This is not good..
I don't have much chakra left.
Also, if he uses the Sharingan that will put me at a big disadvantage.
So, I need to get him to use up a lot of his chakra.
Should I quickly finish this with Chidori?
Or..
should I use..
Just as I expected..
He's trying to save chakra for Gaara.
Ninpou - Kamaitachi!
Here it comes!
Quit playing around!
Ninpou - Fu Sajin!
Damn it.. I gotta do something about that fan.
I wonder how long he'll last with that style of fighting.
There's no choice.
Finally, he's ready to fight.
Fire element - Hosenka no Jutsu!
That's what I expected.
I'll pinpoint that target.
Fire element - Goukakyu no Jutsu!
Did I get her?
Kamaitachi!
You fell for it.
Now!
I have you!
Alright!
What? Kawarimi!?
Oh no!
Sorry..
..but I don't have time to play around with you.
Damn it..
No matter what, Gaara needs to be..
What is that..
What's going on..
Who is that young one?
Who the hell are you!?
Is it that much of a shock that you can't figure it out?
It's me.. I'm Orochimaru.
Impossible..
You can't have already acheived the completion of that kinjutsu..
It's been more than 10 years since I left the village..
You terrifying inhuman creature, you..
That one, he's finally done it..
One of the reasons I didn't choose you to be the Yondaime..
..was because of your twisted ideology..
It looks like you've finally found me..
How unfortunate..
Orochimaru..
What is the meaning of this?
I laid so many booby traps..
enough that I thought I'd be safe..
So I was really surprised.. But now I see.
Recently, a bunch of ninjas from the genin to chuunin and even some of the ANBU have gone missing..
and there have been reports of your strange behavior as well..
Orochimaru-sama.. How could you of all shinobi do such a thing?!
Shall I kill you as well?
Orochimaru..
So it was you, after all..
Speak!
What were you doing here?
Oh, my goodness..
If the cat's out of the bag then..
I've been working on developing a jutsu.
Orochimaru-sama.. you'd kill your own village's shinobi for that?!
It's as I thought, kinjutsu..
What on earth did you hope to achieve?
Everything there is.
Everything, you say?
I want to obtain all the jutsus and gain a true understanding of everything in this world..
The first person to mix blue and yellow..
..named the new color that was created green.
I only want to do the same thing..
If blue is the chakra then yellow is the seal, and green is the jutsu..
Just as there is no end to the variety of colors, there are so many thousands..
tens of thousands of jutsu in the world as well..
But.. in order to obtain every possible jutsu and truth, it would require an eternity, you see..
Only the one who understands everything after spending such time on this can be fittingly called the "ultimate being".
For me, the lifespan of the body is too short, too fragile..
Even if you were to be called Hokage, when you die everything ends there so..
Orochimaru..
This jutsu you're experimenting on here, it can't be..
Yes, it's what you think..
The "Spell of Immortality".
This immortality jutsu is a spell where you anchor your spirit to this world forever..
In other words, it's a reincarnation spell where you find a new body, enter it with your spirit and gain possession of it..
The reason why I disguised myself as my old self until now was..
because I thought I'd let you feel nostalgic about the past..
To grow old.. how destitute it can be..
When I look at you I can feel it deeply.
You will die here..
and I will obtain an even younger, more beautiful, stronger body..
The Leaf really entertain me to no end..
I see..
Uchiha Sasuke.
Yes.. that's it exactly..
It's Sasuke-kun
A reincarnation jutsu that steals the body of another and makes the spirit immortal..
What number face.. body.. is that one!?
I believe it's the second one..
I intend to possess Sasuke-kun after he grows up a bit more to my tastes..
But to have you die, cursing your fate and regretting your entire life..
I suppose this face would be best..
You hideous monster!
Hokage-sama!
You mustn't let your guard down now, sensei..
You were always too compassionate.
What's the matter with you?
This just ain't like you..
Sorry..
His eyes..
Malice and ambition have always been hidden within his eyes.
I have always been aware that he had these qualities.
I knew about it but acted as if I couldn't see it..
A genius bursting with tremendous abilities..
..in a time that was still chaos because he was, without a doubt..
..a talent you'd find only every few decades.
He was the one to carry on my will and strength.. I wanted to think it would be so.
And it was this weakness of mine that..
..allowed that event and the current situation.
Are you going to kill me?
Ninpou - Kuchiyose!
I wonder if you can actually do it..
Sarutobi-sensei!
Kill him, Sarutobi!
This is your only chance!
Sarutobi.. you..
But I couldn't kill him..
I'll kill you now and correct my past mistake!
Let's go!
It's already too late!
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
Why is he using the Kage-bunshin?
Why would he distribute the little chakra that remains in him like that?
You've really grown old..
To think you'd shorten your own lifespan out of impatience..
It.. it can't be that you..
Mi..
..I..
..Hitsuji..
..U..
..Inu..
..Ne..
..Tori..
..Uma..
..Mi!
The order of the seals..
Sarutobi's going to use that jutsu!
This must be the death that Yondaime spoke of.
Only those who form a contract with this jutsu can see it..
It's already too late, no matter what you do.
I have won.
Konoha will be demolished!
The Leaf Village is my home!
The Hokage is one who continues to act as the main pillar of the house, protecting it!
He's the one who carries the will of the Leaf, entrusted with it..
..it won't be that easy for you!
Genjutsu - Kokuangyo no Jutsu!
What absurd nonsense..
You're just, for a short while, one of the leaders in the history of the organization called Konoha..
Even the remains of the rock portrait will eventually fade and crumble.
To me, the Leaf Village isn't just an organization..
Every year, there are a lot of shinobi born and raised in Konoha.
They live.. fight.. to protect the village..
Even if we are not related by blood, those of the village like these are..
to me, my most precious..
most important..
..family!
Well then, I'll break you in half, the main pillar, that is..
and that will destroy the house, Konoha.
Even if you were to kill me, the beam won't break!
I'm the man who inherited the will of the Leaf,
the will of the Shodaime-sama and Nidaime-sama.
I am the Sandaime Hokage!
No matter how much you target the Leaf Village..
there will be a new Hokage who will inherit my will and become the pillar to protect the house of Konoha!
Isn't that right Yondaime?
Orochimaru!
I'll show you a special jutsu from now that even you don't know about!
Take this!
Fuuin Jutsu - Shiki Fuujin!
#Yomp@Rizon
yomp1.cjb.net
#Anime-XP@Rizon
Ani-XP.com
Many ninja are born in the village of Konoha every year as they grow, fight, and die while protecting their home.
Even if the people in the village are not blood related..
..they are all important family to me.
My family will no longer allow you to have your way!
Next -
Forbidden Master Technique! Shiki Fuujin