Arrived E'! E' arrived to the end!
We are to golden the Time!!!
From Naruto today it will be transmitted
every mercoled   to the 7:27 PM.
To that they have followed every Naruto week
and to that they watch it for before the time, Good Vision.
- Head Head -
Much good.
We begin with the new acronym
of opening "Haruka Kanata".
YOU WANT TO LISTEN TO ME, CAPOOO!
What you want, Konohamaru?
You do not see that they are occupied?
They are only the 7 PM.
What?
Still 27 minuteren lack.
One supposes that hour they would have
to transmit "to Prince of Tennis".
What what what what we can make?
What we can make?
I have already made the introduction!
I do not want to be put in the troubles.
M' it does not interest!
We see to leave with Naruto!
Hey, Sakura, Sasuke.
Naruto has begun alone the show.
You are ready?
Not! Not still.
I have not still ended to arrange to me.
Dov' is the tape of the show?
Still it has not arrived.
It goes well, you will have to dance
or whichever other thing in order to entertain the public
while I go
to take the tape.
You of the Show take care while they are outside.
EH!
Account on you.
E' one mission.
One mission, eh?
It goes well.
Much good, we make it!
HEY, NARUTOOO!
All this has happened for your eagerness!
Why you act like if you dispiacesse!
Ahi Ahi Ahi
We go! We go!
http://naruteamplus.altervista.org
NaruTeaM
IT INTRODUCES
fumikomuze akuseru
kake hiki wa naisa sou dayo
youru wo nukeru
nejikomu it knows saigo ni
sashihiki zero know sou dayo
hibi wo kezuru
kokoro wo under
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
todokuyo kitto
tsutau yo maxim knows aa
iki isoide shiboritotte
motsureru ashi
dakedo mae yori
zutto sou tokue
ubaitotte tsukandatte
kimi ja nai nara imi was naniosa
dakara haruka kanata
C that place is this?
- Prohibited area -
Qu   is where the Second Examination will have place.
E' the training area n44
better known like
"la forest of the dead women".
"the forest of the dead women"?
EH?
It wants is made to pass for one cliff?
And it would want to make of one in the grass?
Hey! Konohamaru!
What six come to make?
I would have had to wait for it to me
from R-he who I want to exceed!
Six state Bravo to find to me.
Hey!
We have used too much powder.
The one who that the "fascination" of an adult possesses
and it is ninja the female of the better group, Moegi!
C$r-he who loves to make divisions
Udon!
Brilliant ninja the number one of the village
Konohamaru!
We three are
the Konohamaru Patrol!
What would want you three?
I am nearly in order to begin According to Examination
for the selection of the Chunin.
I do not have time in order to put to me to play with you.
We have not come here to play!
We have come for the history.
,!
History?
The periodical of our school has to us
asked to make one exclusive history
on the examination of selection of the Chunin.
Cos   we have come makes you of the questions.
Please, it collaborates.
Please.
For
Eh, you!
That fairies!
Konohamaru would want an exclusive right
for the periodical of its school.
Oh
s , I forgot that Hokage-sama
me it had mentioned some.
Very well! We will make one pause of ten minuteren!
If they will come to you made questions
collaborated and you answer with tranquillity.
But
Naruto, we begin with you.
It goes well.
You parler   of all my dowries!
You must observe! The relation before
to enter in the Forest of the Dead women!
The scholastic periodical of Konoha!
Understood it of Rin.
- Presentation of the Personages -
It introduces to you alone please.
Ok.
I call Uzumaki Naruto.
They are a ninja of the Secret Village of Konoha.
Mine hobby it is to make jokes.
I go matto for the ramen
and they are Genin from little time
but I have a great dream.
I want to become Hokage
and I want to be strongest
of all the other Hokage
and to make that the inhabitants of the village
they recognize my value.
To the Ninja Academy they called to me useless,
imbecille and things of this type but
I succeeded to being promoted to the examination
and to become member of the group
n7 of master Kakashi.
I have made difficult missions every day.
Qual' is the distance from the objective?
Five meters.
I am ready.
Also Sasuke and Sakura-chan are in group 7
but what ago all they are I
cos   I do not have myself to be worried for they.
I have taken!
Not to say cos , introduces also they!
I know, I know it.
E' sure the objective.
It goes well!
This child is Uchiha Sasuke, a vain one.
E' the only survivor of the famous Uchiha clan.
But he is simply a child
useless as you can see.
OH!
Here it is when I have taken its sembianze.
But all good goes finch sees
my sublime techniques ninja.
This is the child who is itself in love of me,
Haruno Sakura-chan.
They say that hatred makes part of the love
cos   it does not succeed to express
its true feelings
but this its timid side appeals to a lot to me.
It will be true?
S ! S ! E' the truth.
Who has said that she appeals to Naruto to me!
Bastard!
Therefore lie was one.
Me dispiace
However it is
we work in groups from three
and we have made missions
much dangerous like this.
Ehy, you!
Ah?
Mrs....
I have ended to remove all the erbacce.
What is?
These
they are not erbacce.
Ah?
It was the garden that I was cultivating!
!!!
That someone me aids!
Cadooo!
Idiot
- Zone with traps -
- not to enter -
Hey, not to go from that part.
Hey, we go!
That idiot
This happens why
it has taken a dog too much large.
And these would be dangerous missions?
It only seems that you you make under, Naruto.
Some times me are made under
Rifalla.
Transformation!
Here it is when I have defeated the old Hokage.
I cannot make an article with this!
Then it makes an example me.
Ok!
My name is Konohamaru.
They are the grandson of the head village, the Hokage.
My grandfather is the more important person
of the secret village of Konoha
the third Hokage.
To carry the name of Hokage means
to be ninja the number one of the village.
In particular the quarter is the hero who defense
the village from this monstrous vixen.
It waits for, it waits for, it waits for!
It only speaks about the others!
I was in order to say other!
Moreover, it speaks too much about same you.
Obviously, they are the protagonist!
M' it does not import of the others!
Naruto from when six given a degree to to you
six forgotten to you about me, true?
For   at least you could introduce to me!?
It goes well, goes well!
This is the first person of the village
that me apprezz , Iruka-sensei.
E' a person much good one and offers to me
often of the ramen of Ichiraku.
They are good only why
I invite to you to eat the ramen?
Not, uhm, bond
Not freghi nobody!!!
The next one, Naruto!
Oh.
Ok, creed that parler
of when Sasuke if it made it under.
This we have already felt it!
Be more serious!
That Naruto will be telling
a bag of frottole.
To who you want that amounts!
Here it is the unsurpassable Kakashi.
There is nobody?
Here it is the precious Sakura.
Naruto is managing
in order to continue the show.
How it goes?
Ce you will make it?
Creed that I can make it before us
of the term of the publicity.
Moreover, it informs the viewers
that they will have a special gift.
Kakashi-sensei.
Kakashi-sensei, receives to me?
Cos' has happened?
It has said that it would have arrived
before the aim of the publicity!
Of it I do not have idea
Sakura, continues you.
What? I?
You make of your best, Sakura-chan.
You make what us l ?
Good
it does not remain that to make it.
Understood it of Hyou - Ninjutsu -
Hour the unsurpassable Sakura-chan
the Ninjutsu will explain us.
Blank, they are the beautiful girl ninja,
Haruno Sakura.
Beautiful one
Then? Creates you some problem?
Not, not.
Transformation!
First, we observe the ninjutsu of Naruto.
Sexy not Jutsu.
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu.
Transformation!
Transformation! Transformation! Transformation!
Ebisu-sama! Ebisu-sama! Ebisu-sama!
Harem not Jutsu.
I have called Harem not Jutsu.
We tell also of when
E' guilt its that is in delay.
The Fall of Cancellino.
We speak about R-he who has been graduated
like the best one to the academy, Sasuke-kun.
It will not serve to you to null the taijutsu.
Sasuke-kun was the best one in class
and lott   nearly to parimerito against Kakashi.
Six wonderful Sasuke-kun.
- What? -
Your presentation of Sasuke
it is duration end too much.
Taci, Naruto! They give one to you calmed!
Horse!
Tiger!
Katon Goukakyuu not Jutsu!
(What!)
A Genin would not have to be
in a position to executing this technique.
It must not have sufficient Chakra.
Fuuma Shuriken
the shadow of the wind!
The shuriken they do not work with me.
You the mostrer .
Which thing? That one is
the Sharingan!!!
Cos   this would be the Sharingan.
If it possesses the same specialty
innata of Kakashi-sensei
it will be able to preview the techniques
of that sopraciglione!
That it is ninjutsu or genjutsu
it also remains always magic.
To discover   its secret!
As you can see knows to use
many powerful techniques
like the Katon Goukakyuu not Jutsu
the Shadow of the Wind
and the Sharingan, but
its best one moved is
its cutting look.
If girl with these eyes watches one
she innamora of he.
Sasuke-kun, watches from this part!
Six
insopportabile!
But cold its atteggiamanto
it renders tutt' other that fascinating.
Hour we arrive to ours
teaching Hatake Kakashi-sensei.
Also known like the Ninja Kakashi Copy.
Pu   to emulate and to anticipate the techniques
of the enemy thanks to its Sharingan.
Vocifera that it has copied more than 1000 techniques.
But it arrives always late to the appointments
and when one is bored it begins to read one strange
called book "the Paradise of the Pomiciata"
moreover it seems bored all the time.
The leggendario secret blow
of the Secret Village of Konoha!
Pain Millenarian!!!
Its main mystery is the face
that it comes hidden from one mask.
I ask myself that type of face has!?
Ninpou Kuchiyose Doton Tsuiga not Jutsu!
If I cannot follow with the eyes or the hearing to you,
then I must use the fiuto.
E' which succeeds when
you cover the eyes in the fog.
This is one technical of evocation
used for the inseguimenti.
Moreover, why it possesses
the Sharingan in the left eye
when they only have it
the members of the Uchiha clan?
Mysterious E' and we do not know a lot on he.
Glielo domander   the next time.
Lightning Edge!
What!
I succeed to see to eye
knot the Chakra in its hand.
You six too much dangerous one.
Technique of the Aquatic Prison.
It attacks!
Advanced Technique
Ice mirrors.
And hour we observe the techniques of others ninja.
They are many and I do not have the time in order to explain them.
Understood it of Tou - You avail again -
Sasuke-kun, hour that six mine
occupied of this part.
Sure!
They are adapted for this.
I knew sin from the beginning.
You stop it of wanting to be always the best one.
Six too much vain one, Sasuke.
Not intrometterti.
You remove yourself of means, idiot.
Taci!
It does not appeal to to me that you attract all the attention!
But seem
that the enemies do not have
some interest for you!
Cos' you have said!
It watches here!
Hey!
You.
Qual' is your name?
Gaara of the Desert.
Also I am interested yours.
How he calls to you?
Uchiha Sasuke.
Hey, you.
Identify to you.
Maledizione! An other time!!!
They speak alone with Sasuke
One supposes that present us
before asking the name to others!
You, from the sguado oblique
it waits for a moment!
Eh?
I propose you one challenge.
Lotter   I against the sopraciglione.
I do not want to fight with you.
Uchiha.
E' with he that I want to fight!!!
- Sasuke, Sasuke, merda, you have to me broken!
True E'
nobody considers you like protagonist, Head.
You mistakes!
They are not cos   intelligent in order to become of account.
It has made you outside with facility.
It is not true!
Konoha Wind Strike!
Approval?
You six fact outside alone.
Also you, Sakura-chan
The pupils who have come for
the examination of selection of Chunin
many forts are all.
Nara Shikamaru.
Akimichi Chouji.
Yamanaka Ino.
Hyuuga Hinata.
Inuzuka Kiba and Akamaru.
Aburame Shino.
But we will be able to strike them easy.
It is worth the pain knowing it.
Eh!
Obvious E' that it they are.
Not distrarti that after
you lose against one of they.
Sure that not.
S ! We have exceeded the First Examination
of Selection of Chunin
and we head to the place
where it will be kept According to Examination.
It does not import which difficulties we will meet
we not scapperemo.
We hope to pass this examination
and to be able to become of the Chunin.
Why we
Why we have a large one
square job whom it joins to us.
Well!
We go!
Thanks in order to have answered to the questions.
Thanks.
Head, you make of your best!
Of agreement!
It also counts to us!
Goodbye!
- Be serious!
You make of your best!
Blank, boys.
Me dispiace of to have arrived late
but in the way I have met
one beautiful girl
and cos   we have danced.
Bugiardo!
You do not say cos .
You would have to praise to me why
I have carried you the cassette.
Good job!
kakashi-sensei!
Hour we will be able to see the next episode!
You must see it all!
Already, for   before there is the publicity.
Optimal chosen.
Moreover
for the First Examination
you all
You are promoted!
You have exceeded the test.
The First Examination of selection of Chunin is finished.
I augur you good fortune.
Evvai!
It augurs to us!
! !
Yeah! Yeah!
That amusing child.
Someone is passed leaving the sheet in.bianco.
Uzumaki Naruto.
It appeals to this boy to me.
The second examination has beginning!
All enemies!
E' indeed a place buio.
You will make yourselves endured idea of
why this place is called
"La Forest of the Dead women"
You will make yourselves endured idea of
why this place is called
"La Forest of the Dead women".
Even if it threatens to us cos ,
not to believe makes fear us!
They are not for nothing scared!
Indeed?
It seems that you have many energies!
Those as you they are first to die
and they make it schizzando blood
red that appeals to a lot to me.
I give back the kunai to you.
Thanks!
For
not to come me to the shoulders
with that bad air.
Less than you do not want to die young.
E' that
I am touched myself when I see of the blood.
Moreover, I was churned why you have cut to me
my beloveds hats.
Naruto-kun
Me dispiace.
This esaminatrice is sick!
Dangerous E'.
And also this other.
Why it has the long language cos  ??
It seems that this time ce is some
several from the ardent character.
Interesting!
Six you that one with the more ardent character.
Well, before beginning the second one
test you consegner   this.
- Sheet of Consent -
E' a Sheet of Consent.
Those that they want to make
the examination must sign.
Why?
Of hour in ahead scapperanno to us also of the dead men.
For which I must receive yours
consent to participate to this test
of sar ? otherwise  responsible I.
Beginning to explain to you as the second test works.
Saying simply, draft
of a test of extreme survival.
A survival test!?
That laborious examination.
We begin from the map
of the practice field.
The practice field n44 is encircled
from 44 doors of income sluices to key.
There are a river and a forest
with to the center one tower.
The tower tos be distant approximately 10 km from the incomes.
To the inside of the delimited territory,
you will have to start the survival program.
The program consists
in one fight without rules
in order to get hold of this coil.
Coil?
.
The coil of the Sky and the coil of the Earth.
You will fight for these two coils.
In total 26 squares have exceeded the first examination.
The half of these squares will have the coil of the Sky.
The other half will have the coil of the Earth.
Therefore every square will have one of these coils.
You will not have to make other that to fight for these.
Therefore
what must make in order to esere promoted?
To carry the coil of the Sky and the Earth
to the tower with to the own companions.
Therefore
the thirteen squares whom they will lose
their coil will come bocciate.
For   you must make all this in a lasso of time.
The second test will last 120 hours
that is five days.
Five days!
And as we make with the food!
Ve the procurerete alone.
The forest is a treasure of the nature.
Full E' of food.
However it is
there are also many animals that eat
bugs, velenose plants e men.
Oh not
Idiot! E' for that
it is called "of survival".
Moreover, you know that it is impossible that
exactly 13 squares come promoted
inasmuch as with passing
of the days the engagement increases
and the time for the recovery is shortened.
It seems enough hard.
In more we will be encircles to you from enemies
and we will not be able to sleep with tranquillity.
To part those who will lose
in the fight for the coil
someone senza' morir other
demolished from the severit of the examination.
Me excuses!
We can be withdrawn to half?
The withdrawal during the examination is not allowed.
You will have to be in the forest
for all and the five days.
As I thought
Sai that it wants
Inasmuch as there are, I speak to you
of the bocciatura conditions.
Per.primo.cosa
they will come bocciate the squares who not
riusciranno to carry the two coils until the tower.
According to point.
The squares who will lose a member or those
with a disabled member to continue.
Moreover, you know
that you do not have to watch the content
of the coils before arriving to the tower.
What succeeds if we watch them?
E' one surprised that you will discover same.
Once Chunin, is obtained
missions with forbidden witnesses.
Cos   we will verify your reliability.
This is the rules.
You consegner   the coil in exchange
of the consent sheets
dopodich to establish   the number
of the departure door and you will begin.
A last council.
Tried not to die!
I have understood.
Cos   is not known which of the two
coils have ciascuna square
of it who of the three holds it.
E' as Ibiki has said.
In this examination fight to cost of
life in order to collect the information.
They are all enemies.
We are all cos   decided
that we could commit suicide
an other, if necessary.
It seems that they have understood
the meant one of the consent sheet.
Oh, six you!
My girl with the wide forehead and dazzling.
I thought that you of it pits returned to house!?
I did not hope to see to you here!
Oh, six you, my spiacente Ino.
Sai com' is must be five days
in mission with Sasuke-kun.
For no reason I would return to house.
- Ugly!
- Forehead!
- Ugly! Ugly!
- Forehead! Forehead!
- Ugly! Ugly! Ugly!
- Forehead! Forehead! Forehead!
Sakura, you will not succeed to exceed this test!
For your good you would have to return some to you to house!
The same one is worth for you!
Hey, why these two hate a lot?
M' they do not interest their problems.
Why
it gives cos ? much  time to us
if we must only put one company?
Eh?
Hey, Hinata!
That you make us here?
Naruto-kun
Ummm
That strange girl.
Six hurt.
Um here
- we look at ourselves.
Naruto-kun
E' hour to exchange the sheets for the coil!
How many sopravviveranno groups?
If you have received the coil continuations
the person person in charge and gone to your income.
We will begin between thirty minuteren!
Yeak!
The survival is our specialty.
Hinata, pulls outside a little grinta.
Ok
We must risk our life for this.
Sai that it wants, but we must make it.
We will go behind Naruto.
It makes to see me that snacks I have of potatoes, pastella
These two
Very well!
I do not want to lose!
We will defeat all those that are approached!
, that one cursed!!!
E' arriavto finally the moment
in order to complete our mission.
The other squares not me piacciono
but the thing that f me more fear
it is to be five days with Gaara.
Before we head for the esordienti.
It seems that from now it can also be killed,
cos   it will be easier.
Guy-sensei!
To make   of my best!
Superer   also this!
According to Examination of Selection of the Chunin
it has beginning!
Those boys tried!
Those boys!
Force!
It is begun!
Ok, we go to try
that one about which we spoke before.
Hinata, can try it you?
Byakugan!
We do not have much haste, Lee!
We have as soon as begun.
I know!
But
I cannot be calm when I know
that of the enemies many forts wait for to us.
Incoreggibile Tonto
I imagine that
you know qual' is our objective!
What you are making, Chouji?
Me rest.
Tired and they are starved.
But that you are saying!
We have only begun five f minuteren!
Not there is solution
when they are starved.
But insomma!
Instead carrying all to you those snacks
it was better that you took one or two kunai in more!
Cabbage!
Ino, you hide!
Merda!
We must go ahead cos   for five days?
First, all will have like goal the tower.
Therefore it would be better to place
of the traps in the vicinities.
You feel?
It seems that we have company.
Where they are?
They are just of the children.
they have been made to find easy cos  ?.
It seems that they are shrewed
of our presence
but they do not know where we find ourselves.
What happens to you?
It seems badly star.
Cos' is that thing!?
The sanguisughe of Konoha they are attracted from
perspiration and from the corporea temperature
and they assault the prede to groups
If the blood for five minuteren sucks you, six ended.
Optimal idea to put of the traps in
possible via of escape of those bestiacce.
M maledizione
Less one.
It seems that they have begun!
It was urlo that one?
I am myself innervosendo.
Not to worry to you, Sakura-chan!
I must make pip
Idiot!
What tasks to make in front of one Miss.!?
Vai here behind!
How much I have made some!
I have said to you that
it is not behaved to us cos
in front of
Sasuke-kun, not was need
to hit it a lot violentemente!
Why you have made it
Which devil takes to you?
Why me the questions?
E' my way to make!
Sasuke-kun!
Well!
Sasuke-kun, please, you stop it!
It watches well!
Eh?
Liberalo!
Where is found the true Naruto?
Eh!
I do not know of what you you are speaking!
Which aim has made the scar in face?
I have asked to you, than fine it has made
the wound that has made the esaminatrice you?
Moreover, the bag of the shuriken
it is to your left leg.
Naruto the right door.
The six worse one than Naruto in the transformations.
Imbroglione!
That misfortune
I suppose not to have other
chosen hour that you have to me uncovered!
Who of you has the coil?
If me you will give spontaneously
you risparmier   the life.
Capisco.
Then I must use the force!
nee kikoe masu ka?
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
janai to nai chau kara
mawari or mimawasa naku I fear
mou iin from yo
kono you not naka ni wa minna ga
iru kara
naki taku natte
nige taku natte
shiawase or wasure teu shimatta ra
mine utae
hikari ga to umare
yami ga to umare ta
futatsu wa hitotsu
HARUMONIA kanji you
TEREPASHII
nee kikoe masu ka?
It waits for a moment
this is a giant snake?
What? Real E'? It waits for! It makes me to breathe!
They have been swallowed!!!
The next time:
To eat or to be eaten!
Naruto becomes food.