http://naruteamplus.alterista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
E' before the time that you see to die a friend?
This is the destiny of the ninja.
You will pay!
To kill to you !
The Past White man, The Feelings Secrets.
That instinct omicida!
Completely various E' from before!
It arrives!
What!
It has deflected with its chakra!
Then
You take this!
And then
Oh not!
Impossible!
This Chakra!
I seal of Naruto is broken!
Not!
To how much it seems
I seal still maintains
its effectiveness.
But the demon is in order to fuoriuscire
from I seal.
Good
I seal completely is not broken.
There is still time!
You feel to me, Zabuza?
Enough to play!
It is not even in your style
but that you would say some to begin
mean it
and to put aim to this history?
Interesting!
But what tasks of being able to make in these conditions?
From the Kakashi, it makes to see me!
I do not succeed to reject its force!
Zabuza-saint one
I do not succeed
to defeat this boy.
Zabuza-saint one.
I am!
You six
the boy of that morning!
Why six stopped to you?
Although I have killed a your beloved friend
you do not succeed to kill to me?
Eternal damnation!
Cos' has happened to your force?
It will not be enough in order to kill to me.
Was not one important person for you?
You have someone of important?
I want protect the person
that me she is beloved
to help it to realize its dreams
this is my dream.
There are persons who make the error
to save their enemy
why movements from the mercy.
But it is an error.
You have idea
of the suffering
that one involves living life
it deprives of dreams and someone
what has need of you?
What you would want to say?
Zabuza-saint it does not have need
of ninja weak people.
You have removed me the only reason of life.
Why?
Why you make all this for he?
E' a criminal to the money of other criminals!
Possible that it is the only one
important person of your life!
Much time makes
I loved of the persons.
Were
my parents.
I am been born in a village
snowy of the country of fogs.
My parents worked hard
in order to only pull ahead
but in spite of everything they were satisfied.
I was happy.
Mine was indeed admirable parents.
But
when I was much small
succeeded something.
Something?
Which thing?
This blood.
Blood?
Then?
Cos' has happened?
My father murdered my mother
and then prov   to kill me.
Eh?
In the country there were numerous wars
and those that had innate abilities
they began to being hates to you.
Innate abilities?
Transmitted special abilities
to the prole from the parents.
Because of these abilities
these clans came used
as you arm in battle.
Result: the clans came feared and accused
to carry misfortune and war to the country.
After the conflicts
these clans had
to hide their abilities.
For that discoveries came
it attended them the dead women.
That boy of sure has suffered a lot.
The persons with particular abilities
often they are feared.
My mother was one of these.
She hid my father
hoping in one pacific life
at least for a p  indeed, in order always.
Mother, watches!
You see? You see? It is not fantastic?
Why also you!?
Why!?
Why also this child!?
Me dispiace!
Me dispiace a lot!
But
my father scopr   our secret.
When me risvegliai
my father was!
That time
I thought about same me....
Not.
the more painful thing.
And it was unavoidable that you thought it.
More painful what?
S . Intuii with exactitude
that my existence was useless.
Equal E' to me!
You have said to me of wanting to become
the better one ninja of your village
in order it makes you to accept from all.
If someone appeared that
you chip ax with all the heart
she would not become the person
more important for you?
Zabuza-saint we took to me with himself although it knew
of my innate specialties.
These abilities that all hated
they were accepted and wished from he.
Morirai here, like an abandoned dog,
without freedom of dreams.
You have my same eyes.
Boy
you want to be accepted from someone?
Riusciresti
to only dedicate to you to me?
From today your blood belongs to me.
You follow to me!
I was much happy one!
Haku, purtoppo
stanotte account to abandon the county.
But a day torner   sure
in order to take of the possession.
For this I do not have need
of consolation or encouragement.
That one of which I have need truly is
I know.
You do not preoccupy yourselves.
I am one your arm, Zabusa-saint.
You hold me to your flank
and you use as wished to me.
Six Bravo boy.
Zabuza-saint me dispiace.
They have not been able of
to be the arm that you wanted.
Naruto-kun
I pray to you
you kill to me!
Ninpou summoning!
Earth element, Tracking fang not jitsu!
Any thing you make you are useless.
You cannot understand where I find myself.
But
I know exactly where he finds Kakashi to you.
Six caught in mine jitsu.
Cos' is this noise?
What?
What happens?
If eyes and orecchie do not work,
enough to use the nose.
This is one evocation that
it only uses for the inseguimenti.
You has worked because six obstinate one
to hold the eyes sluices.
E' for that they are left me to hit.
And hour your crews are sature
of the odore of my blood.
These are my beloveds dogs ninja.
Their olfatto one exceeds that one
of whichever other segugio.
Six state caught in mine jutsu.
The fog is diradando.
In your future I notice
the dead women!
They are I stew of yours hauled!
Not to be foolish!
You do not have hopes.
Your dead women are sure.
Zabuza
not you of six shrewed anchor?
Your ambitions were too much large.
You have failed the attempt to assassinate
the Mizukage and the coup d'tat.
You have abandoned county and six
become a ninja without rules.
In little time your reputation has arrived
to the village of the leaf.
You had need of money for yours vendetta
and for scappare from ninja the pursuers.
Probably the reason is this for
which six joined to you to Gatoo.
Zabuza
six convinced that I am survival
only thanks to the Sharingan?
Hour you mostrer   one my technique
and not one copy.
Lightning Edge!
What!?
In the hand such amount of chakra has one
that it is even succeeded to see it.
You six too much dangerous one.
Tazuna, the man that you wanted to kill
it is the courage of this country
the bridge that it is constructing is the hope.
With your ambition you want to sacrifice
too many persons.
This is not from a ninja.
Not me of frega nothing.
I have always fought for my dream
and always making !
You I repeat.
Hmm!?
Rassegnati!
In your future there is the dead women.
I pray to you you kill to me.
Why it continues to hesitate?
E' ridicule!
Instrument? Arm?
And you think one to it precious person?
For you this is enough!?
Mistaken E' this?
Eh?
What of is mistaken?
Umm
well.
Zabuza-saint it has of the plans on me.
It has need of me.
They are not successful to carry to
term my mission.
Hour does not have more need than me.
For this you I am asking.
Now
Sbrigati!
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear