Naruto Fan Subber
Presents
Naruteam checking NFS
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
Not hito not michi Kewashi shura naka not
Chizu wo hirogete doko and yuku
Goku you know shoku not karasu ga sore wo
ubai totte yabu rivers suteta
Saa kokono not mehiraite to me
shikato ima wo mikiwamero (Yeah!)
Nante Ushinau mono naisa
Iza mairou !
We to are Fighting Dreamers
Mezashite Takami wo
Fighting Dreamers
Narifuri kamawazu
Shinjirugamama ni
Oils 0li Oils Oh! Just go my way!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the to fire!
Right to here Right now (Bang!)
Buppanase like to dangan raina
Right to here Right now (Burn!)
It throws gittekuze get the fire!BANG!
Hey, hey É
Hey, heyÉ Ero-Sennin.
(Pervertito Hermit)
Which kind of technique you will teach this time to me?
The other time you have taught to me to walk on the waterÉ
This time to walk on the fire?
Or quiteÉ
É to fly like a bird?
Ah-ahh! Sbrigati to teach something of new, Ero-Sennin to me!
Ero-Sennin hereÉ Ero-SenninÉ
Task that you do not know how much I you are famous!
Huh? Famous you, Ero-Sennin?
Diamine, listens well !
Gama-Sennin is only one pseudonymÉ
Hour I will reveal  you  my true identity.
They are known all over the world.
I am one of the three SanninÉ
The wizard of the ranocchie from the white-haired one chioma!
The man who places aim to I plant of the children, Jiraya-sama.
Uh Uh! They are just I!
Episode #83
Ooh, Noooo !
Jiraiya and the women! The misfortune of Naruto!
Atafuku Village. It says that they are 10 Km from here.
Otafuku village is written !
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Ero-Sennin !
Me you must call Jiraiya, diamine!
If it is true that famous Ero-SenninÉ
É it has decided to take to me like travel companionÉ
É it means that within of me there is an enormous one upgrades them! I knew!
Hey, hey, hey, dimmi. Why you have to me chosen?
The Fourth Hokage has been my student, time makes.
In some way, you and the Quarter resembled a lot.
Therefore, this is the single reason!
I.... am similar the Fourth Hokage?
What happens?
If it is true that I and the Quarter resemble themselvesÉ
É it means that we have also the same talent, just?
I knew!  I will become  Hokage sure!
Huge!!
Yatta!
They are landed on one cacca of dog.
The single thing that you have in common you and the QuarterÉ
É they are the blond hats and your cocciutaggine.
What you go saying? Vecchiaccio of Ero-Sennin.
Of new!?
Sakura, you come here.
It goes well!
You could carry this Ohagi to house of Ino-chan?
(Ohagi: typical cake of rice)
To house of Ino?
These?
.
You see to make soon and not to make to lose them time.
We are all occupied with the repairs.
I know well.
Soon.
Idea! Of it  I will carry  some to Sasuke-kun later!
They will appeal to cakies?
I have some also for NarutoÉ even if task will not eat them.
Hey, Kakashi-Sensei, I want to learn also the Chidori.
(Technical of the Thousand hawks)
To learn also you? It is not cos “  easy, you know it well.
What? They are not of agreement? Insegnamelo and enough.
Sasuke-kun, thanks.
Six you that you have saved to me from the Sand, it is not true?
Not.
Per.primo.cosa, begins to concentrate the Chakra in your hand.
It goes well!
What it has saved to youÉ
E' be Naruto.
But from i, you stop it, Sasuke-kun. Six too much modest one.
I know that Naruto is a lot improvedÉ
But that boy of the SandÉ
E' the pure truth.
That boyÉ
He has put its life to risk also to save to you.
He has shown for before turns its true force.
E' be Naruto É
É  to save to me?
Chidori!
Ch-Ch-Chidori !
Well! Of po rter˜  also to Naruto!
IÉ
They are not successful to make nothing.
NotÉ
I do not want more to seeÉ
É my more beloveds friends to die in front of my eyesÉ
É an other timeÉ
I do not want more É
At all costsÉ
É  the protegger˜!
Taijuu Kage Bunshin not Jutsu
(Technical of the Cloni d' Ombra Multiple)
Kuchiyose not Jutsu !
(Technical of Evocation)
Naruto is becoming more and more strongÉ
In comparison to heÉ
IÉ
E' an adversary to which you could hold headÉ
É I instead would not succeed to us.
E' too much strongly.
Sure.
If we attack it, we could remain murdered both.
Or moriremmo together to he.
Even if we had other men with weÉ
É the result would not change.
After all it is one of the three leggendari SanninÉ
He would be a hard adversaryÉ
É also for a member of the Clan Uchiha di KonohaÉ
É and for one of the seven Shinobi-Katana of the Fog.
.
ButÉ
Also the more powerful men have they point weak person.
You stop it, before that they fall to you in head.
Hey, hey! Ero-Sennin !
Which kind of student has been the Quarter?
Task not to exaggerate saying that it is
become strong thanks to my instructions.
Inasmuch as six my student also you,
Naruto, six much lucky person.
Not me creeds?
A good ones teaching grows good students.
Normal E' not creeds?
ThenÉ ThenÉ
Ero-Sennin, who has been makes you to grow?
To me?
What it has taught to me all is the Third party.
The Third party?
.
The Third party was still enough young then.
The Third party?
Young person?
, and also I was young.
Young person? Haaaaaaa.
They are remained embedded.
You see! You I had said.
Inasmuch asÉ
É six state trained from KakashiÉ
É you would have it are practiced with the door-bells, true?
, in fact. I have made!
They are the only one that it is remained legacy to that log, eternal damnation.
Ah? Also you?
What?
Also?
What means "Also "?
It leaves to lose, it raises to you and you replace them to place.
It goes well, butÉ I do not succeed to free to me.
There are only 2 door-bells, this means thatÉ
One of we will remain without lunch.
Always six perspicacityes, Orochimaru.
Perfect! We begin!
In order to obtain them you will have to pass on my body!
Jiraiya, seems that it has gained the bet of new.
The always six losing usual.
Taci! Tsunade, six one flat child like one table!
Which thing you have said? Pervertito dirt!
Oh, oh, smettetela!
Tsunade and Orochimaru, gone to house.
It goes well.
Diamine, always you!
As you would call it a ninja that she falls
always in the more banal traps?
, butÉ
You would have to learn from Orochimaru.
Sarutobi-Sensei. You always sayÉ
Orochimaru "here", Orochimaru ""É
When I make the guardone, they are best in applying
the camouflage techniques.
Idiot, to that they would serve these techniques of camouflage?
Nobody has never pecked me! E' the truth!
If what you say it is trueÉ
Next time v err˜  with you.
Sarutobi-Sensei, six pervertito.
What? What?
What is of cos “  amusing, Ero-Sennin?
I have as soon as understood that a good ones teaching has a lot
to learn also from a its student. Understood?
I do not succeed to understandÉ
We go! You have replaced all to place?
, I have ended!
From as the things goÉ
É it seems that still they have not found Naruto.
Just for this É
It does not find the thing bizzarra?
Given the ability with which they are it infiltrates to you in this villageÉ
É they must have already captured Naruto, you do not believe?
Itachi would have to know the face of Naruto.
Kakashi !
Why Kakashi is sleeping?
With all the Jounin to watch by it?
What is happening?
What has happened?
NotÉ
Nothing of chŽÉ
Calm.
True E' that "that" Itachi is returned to the village?
And thatÉ Naruto is trying?
Idiot!
Eternal damnation! Naruto?
E' returned to the village.
And Naruto is trying!
What means all this?
Sasuke-kun!
Where It is Naruto?
As soon as they have arrivedÉ
I have carried to Naruto some ohagi.
If the hands put it lean, Naruto is died!
I will not allow  that it happens.
Old! Naruto must here have come before.
Sai for caseÉ where has gone?
Oh, Naruto?
It makes to think meÉ
E' come with Jiraya-saint towards noon.
And they have taken of the ramen.
Then they had to go from some part.
Where?
It seems me to have understood that they went to the village
of Shikuba or something of similar.
Therefore it has left with Jiraiya-saint.
Jiraiya?
One of the 3 leggendari ninja Sannin, Jiraya.
Even if he seems only large old from hats white men.
LargeÉ Hats White men É
Diamine. You could at least buy one cup of
ramen, after all these questions!
Dolcetti!
Sure thatÉ is a just strange village.
Naruto !
Today we will stop ourselves here!
Ehh? They are still in a position to walking.
They are I the master, therefore I decide!
I want to only learn technical new.
Here why I have to you chosen like student.
Naruto!!
These are the keys of the room. It knows them on.
It concentrates to you on the ChakraÉ trains to you and then you go to sleep. OK?
What?
You are saying to me that it is hour that me it goes some to bed and you lasci alone.
It is not right, Ero-Sennin!
If they are directed to the Shikuba village, lacks little.
Every time that I find myself with Ero-Sennin, always goes to end cos “.
They have arrived.
Dolcetti!
I must control in every store.
Health!
It will have intention of supervisionare my training truly?
That one here?
Ohh. Not mistake a blow.
For case they lodge a blond child here of
my height with the face from stupidÉ
É and large old from hats white men?
This hotel is only for women.
I am trying someone....
A blond child of my height with the face from stupidÉ
É  and large old from hats white menÉ
This is one residence only for old.
MmmÉ This lecca-lecca ago to pizzicare the language.
Hey! Why been sleeping all?
For case they lodge a blond child here of
my height with the face from stupidÉ
É and large old from hats white men?
Hats white men?
They are found here?
Hmmm.. I am trying to remember if someone has arrived of the sort.
Strong E'É you resist it?
Health!
OhÉ A blond child and old with hats white men.
They are found here?
In which room?
We seeÉ
According to plan, aim of the corridor. Room 1.
Already it has been made to unload and it is returned?
Arrival.
. . Now I open.
Naruto!
They are not theyÉ
Gaman not renzoku dattaro
Naite Kokoro de itandaro
Jibun de kimeta is yume dake wa
Yuzurenaindaro
Wakiyaku dakedo
Kage not hito dakedo
Yume to mimu au toki
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
Manaka ni isasete
Shoujiki ni isasete
Imamade nando mo
Nantoka akiramezu ni
Kita Tachi agatte janaika
Imamade nando mo
Bokura
nando mo
Shinjite
Mild Yume
nando mo
Imamade nando mo
Mitekita Baka wa janaika
nando mo
Not tattekita Hito kage ni janaika
Sou shuya ku dayo
Jibun not yume kurai
Wagamama de isasete
The same Sharingan di Sasuke.
The same clan of Sasuke, Uchiha.
Will be thisÉ the enemy juror of SasukeÉ that one about which he always speaks?
Next Episode:
Tipsy the Chidori.
The roar of Sasuke.