http://naruteamplus.alterista.org/
NaruTeaM introduces:
Like on!
NARUTO
owareru youni - isoi de iru
kawai ta mune ga - kari tateru it does not know
to give not tame de naku
to give not mono de naku
hours tachi not ima ga
itami hodoki
kokoro hodoki
kage or hodoki
iki or tsunete - hashiri nukero - yami or saite
kana shimu koto mo
yume or miru koto mo
owari wa shinai
On the way!!!
Wanna ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
Zabuza is dispersed in the snow
Gatoo
Why six here?
And then
what are all those men?
It has been a small change in the plans.
Me dispiace, Zabuza, but morirai here!
What?
If you had contacted a ninja official
beloved would have cost me.
For this I have assumed a ninja fuggitivo like you.
If you ended killed I would save
problems and money.
You just make me to laugh, and you make yourself to call
il Demon of the Village of the Fog?
According to me six solo a poor one demonietto.
How many are?
Indeed infinity.
Kakashi, me dispiace
but our crash finishes here.
From the moment that I do not have more a reason
in order to kill Tazuna
I do not have neanche more reason
in order to fight against of you.
Sure one. They are of agreement.
Dimenticavo.
I have an account in suspended with this moccioso
The arm has tightened me until breaking off it to me.
This is died here.
Bastard!!!
That I haul you are making!
Detention!
Not to be much impulsive one!
D   something also you!
He was a your friend, not!
Taci moccioso.
Haku by now is died.
You want dirmi that t' it does not import null
if its body comes treaded on!
You two have been always entirety!
As Gatoo has used me
I used of Haku.
You I have already said
we ninja are only of the instruments.
To me he interested its force alone,
not its personality.
I do not have resentments.
You say seriously?
Naruto Plants It.
We do not have more to fight against than he.
And then
Hush!
It is my adversary!
He
He you.
It wanted to you truly well!
You have someone of important?
Infinitely well!
A person becomes truly strongly only when
she wishes protect something of important.
Indeed not tests nothing for he!
Me it is difficult to adopt the mentality of the ninja.
Truly
Not tests truly null for he!?
I want to esaudire its desires
and in name its
I could become pitiless!
Becoming forts like you
forgiveness indeed all the feelings?
It has
It has sacrificed its life for you!
Of this person I want to esaudire desires.
This is my dream.
Living without to see realizes the own dreams to you
I was happy.
and to die like one instrument
would be
too much
too much painful!
Marmocchio
Not to say nothing more
Haku
It not only fought suffering for me
its heart suffered also for you.
I knew.
It was too much good.
They are content to have fought
against of you my last battle.
piccoletto
to the end you had reason.
Also the ninja they are human beings.
Probably pu   not to become itself
one instrument without feelings.
You have gained.
Marmocchio, gives a kunai to me.
Hour enough, uccideteli all!
Stupid, creeds of being able to win against
All
A demon!
If you hold us cos   a lot to catch up your companion
You catch up it alone!
Me dispiace
But I do not mean to go
in the same place of Haku.
That you say!
Tasks perhaps of sopravivere?
NOT! Task
to carry to you with me to hell!
Not you tratter   badly.
Also the small Devil
of the Village of the Fog
pu   to become a true demon
once caught up hell!
It waits for it with anxiety.
Laggi you will be able to verify
if they are only
"the amiable devil" that you say!
Haku
it is hour of dirci goodbye, Haku.
Thanks of all
and it pardons to me.
Not to distogliere the look.
E' the end of a man who
it has lived with all if same.
!
They are died
Sasuke-kun
Sakura
I
I!
Sakura
Weights a lot
Sasuke-kun
Sasuke-kun!
Sakura you make me badly
They are happy for you, Sakura.
Not, not to move to you!
Dov' Is Naruto?
And that it has succeeded the masked boy?
Naruto is well.
And the masked boy......
he is died.
Died!
Naruto has killed!
I do not know what has happened esattamete
but it is died trying protect Zabuza.
Confidavo in you!
Schivato Hai all the mortal attacks them!
From the beginning it has not been never tried to kill to me.
Naruto!
Sakura-chan
Sasuke-kun is well! Alive E'!
Eh?
Haku fought suffering not
only for me but also for you.
It was too much good.
Hour I understand its words
I understand, therefore also Sasuke is well.
They are content.
Hey, Hey, Hey!
Been you rilassando too much.
Cursed ninja!
You have killed our source of gain!
Us it does not remain that to attack the city
and to steal to all the roba of value.
To not it wanted us.
Kakashi-sensei
You do not have no technique
for being able to strike them all together?
Not, I have used too much Chakra.
We go!
You still approach yourselves of a step the island
and been sure that all its citizens
spediranno you to hell!
Inari!
The heroes always arrive at the last moment.
Inari
Boys!
Well then them aiuter   also I.
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
With the Chakra that me remains I would have
to succeed to make a bluff.
Kage Bunshin not Jutsu!
Kakashi version!
We begin?
Scappiamooo!!!
Evviva!!!
It seems is all ending!?
!
Kakashi, you would make a favor me?
Sure one.
I want
to see its face.
Of agreement.
It is snowing
Snow in this season?
Haku
You are crying?
Thanks, Kakashi.
Always we have been together
therefore I want to be to yours
flank until the last one
and if possible
I would want to be with you
also after
the dead women.
Born E'
in a country where often it snowed.
For this
he was a candid child like the snow.
Zabuza you will be joined
also in the afterlife.
Kakashi-sensei, I was thinking
The life of a ninja
are just like said those two?
A ninja reason does not have to try one to exist
but to exist like instrument to the service of the country.
This is worth also to Konoha.
To become a ninja consists in this?
It is not
that
me enthusiasms a lot!
And you what of tasks?
Neanche to me
E' for that the ninja unconsciously they live
suffering for this aspect of their life.
Like Zabuza
and that child.
Well!
I have decided!
Diventer   ninja to way mine!
I want to follow my way.
And to make so that it does not have to repent me null!!
Thanks to you we have completed the bridge.
But we are dispiaciuti for your departure.
Good fortune.
Thanks of all.
Mass   Tazuna!
We will come to still find to you.
You promise?
Ah?
Inari
Six sad, true one?
You can cry, if you want.
Piangi.
Not to cry !
If you want you cry, Naruto!
E' that
We go!
That stubborn
That boy has changed the feelings of Inari
and Inari has changed the feelings of the citizens.
The courage of that boy has made us
from bridge in order to catch up the hope.
Already the bridge
We must give a name to this bridge.
True E'.
I have the perfect name for this bridge.
And which?
"the Great Naruto Bridge", than you say some?
E' a beautiful name.
Well!
We return in a hurry, than cos   I make myself
to offer a ramen from master Iruka for
to celebrate the completion of the mission.
Then I must tell
my heroic enterprise also to Konohamaru.
Then I
Hey, Sasuke-kun!
When we return to the village we exit together?
Not, thanks.
Oh, not!
Hey, hey!
If you want I with you exit!
Hush!
Zitto, Naruto!
What?
Six sure one that this name goes you well?
, I choose this name
in the hope that never does not come pulled down
and that it becomes a famous bridge cos  ?
..da to make to rieccheggiare its name
all over the world.
Before Cultivate your hunger you idealize.
Motivated your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain
never coming down.
Break into the contents
never falling down
My knee is still shaking
like the was twelve
Sneaking out of the classroom
by the back door
To man railed at twice me though
but didn' t the beloveds
Waiting is wasting for people like me
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fears
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
' hate Causes you will yourself in the end
Don' t try to live I know wise
Don' t cry ' causes you' king I know right.
Don' t dry with fakes or fear
Hey, why we of the 7 group
We are making simple missions alone?
I want to face the ninja strong
of the other countries like Zabuza and Haku.
You do not have a mission where it can make beautiful
figure and that it is also moving?
I must cover my "way of the ninja",
you know my heart, you know
The next time, begins following understood it:
The Examination from Chuunin.